[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello this is Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we talk about the most advanced
healing information out there we're
talking about leafy greens you know you
think about leafy greens and maybe it's
not a big deal like why would he do a
radio show about leavea your greens I'll
tell you why cuz it means everything no
matter what diet you're on so if you
just say if you're listening right now
doesn't matter if you're on the best
paleo diet the best high protein animal
diet the best vegetarian diet the best
vegan diet the best plant-based diet the
best whatever diet the best keto diet
whatever you think you're an expert at
or you're an expert on if you're not
getting enough leafy greens it falls
flat it becomes a problem it's a
disaster for the future if that sounds
like fear and Chaos you know don't get
me wrong it's not it's reality it's
truth and truth matters when 10 years
down the road and you're you don't know
what's going on and you got symptoms and
conditions and you're sick and you don't
know why you're mineral deficient and
all these problems and you're seeing
doctor after doctor after doctor and you
didn't have all your leafy greens the
right ones at the right time in your
life all these years think about it have
you been eating leafy green since you
were a child lots of leafy greens no you
haven't this is an important show so
hang on there fasten your seat bels get
ready for this one because um this means
a lot I I I feel like it means a lot
because what happens is I see it over
and over again you're not getting enough
leafy greens you're not getting enough
celery juice you're not getting any
celery juice how about that I mean do
does everybody have years of celery
juice behind them in their in their
whole being of their whole nature of who
they are and their existence their
physical nature all these years no they
don't they don't have that some people
think juicing is just it's just not a
good thing that you don't have to juice
that back a long time ago no one had
juicers so why should we use them now
back in the caveman time nobody was
juicing so why do we need them now
because we're in a different world right
now toxins pollutants liver
troublemakers poisons that saturate the
liver all kinds of different viruses
bacteria everything we're up against now
we need every Edge we can get and guess
what everybody's digestive tract is
basically annihilated by these things
okay B bad bacteria by the millions and
billions inside their intestinal tract
and sometimes really bad versions of
bacteria bad strep aactas causing sibo
ecoli different groups of ecoli
different varieties of SEI all kinds of
Staff all kinds of fungus sitting inside
our intestinal tract
thriving and taking up space making it
harder to absorb what we need to absorb
our nutrients juicing is one of those
lifesaving elements life-saving elements
I juice every morning and I take my
Omega Juicer that's the best juicer
there is there hands down the best
juicer there is out there there's no
question about it I know all the juicers
the masticating ones all the different
ones the ones with the gears all that I
know all the juicers and a mega juicer
is incredible it's the one I use I run
my celery through there every single
morning I make sure there's leafy greens
in my diet you know people say well what
do you eat Anthony what do you eat
what's your whole thing I'll tell you
what I do eat I'll tell you something
that's in my diet and it's no secret
okay it's leafy greens it's drinking
celery juice absolutely but here's the
key no matter what you do in your diet
whatever you believe in I'm going to
tell you right now also I want to back
up a little bit we also need the potency
and the quantity of the juice that's
critical we can't get that just from
eating so we do need to eat our leafy
greens because we get we get lots of
minerals lots of nutrients from that too
but we also still have to juice we have
to juice our celery we have to juice
other things too not just celery and so
we do have to keep this in mind you know
I like the juice just straight celery
and then I like to eat my leafy greens
and I'm going to talk about it all too
and we're up against so much so many
pollutant so many toxins so much stress
so much adrenaline when you get stressed
out okay your adrenals Purge and flood
they Purge and flood that's what happens
that adrenaline is toxic abrasive it's
poisonous it's like a battery acid it's
corrosive it gets in the intestinal
lining that that adrenaline gets into
the intestinal lining and it burns the
lining scor pures it making it a
campground for bad bacteria it kills
good bacteria our own adrenaline from
when we're under stress destroys our
good bacteria in our guts our good
microorganisms in our guts and as all
our good microorganisms and our good
bacteria start to disappear over time
from all that adrenaline scorching it
and all the pollutants and poisons we
end up eating all these foods that feed
bad bacteria so we're still eating some
eggs cuz we think eggs are healthy we
think eggs are in a healthy diet now we
we think that they're healthy right
meanwhile they're not they feed viruses
bacteria pathogens microorganisms and
when they when all your good bacteria is
disappearing from stress okay and
adrenaline scorching the Linings of the
intestinal tract and colon and all the
way up to dadum and everywhere when that
happens we start eating we're eating bad
food too we think we're getting a
moderation diet good moderation diet
we're eating a good healthy raw cheese
maybe we're eating some eggs we think
we're doing good for ourselves a little
grass-fed butter these things feed
bacteria they feed viruses but this may
not hit us all at once it takes a few
years for this to kind of happen and
roll in and kind of Roll Along and then
we start getting our first symptoms we
start getting our first issues we start
getting the bloating you know gas
gastritis we start getting different
things happening cramps and all kinds of
stuff and bad breath and all these
different things and our proteins rot in
our gut and the fats that we're eating
because we're all on high fat diets turn
ran it and Cake the Linings we got the
bad bacteria proliferating and thriving
off of all this the good bacteria is
diminishing and diminishing and
probiotics doesn't cut it a probiotic
won't do it won't take care of it and
that's why if we're not doing that
celery juice we're not doing that herb
and if we're not doing that powerful
herb the celery juice and we're not
getting our leafy greens in when we need
to like a spinach soup which I'm going
to talk about in a little while and
other things we're not replenishing
we're not killing off the bad bacteria
as well see everybody thinks probiotic
Prebiotic probiotic they're thinking all
that kind of thing right but probiotic
doesn't kill bad bacteria if you're
loaded with bad bacteria that's already
been thriving you could take all the
probiotics you want that doesn't stop
bad bacteria a probiotic isn't a killer
of streptococus it's not a killer of
coli is the very things that create sibo
um sinusitis the very all mucus and
discharge loose you know loose bowels
when you're not supposed to have loose
bowels mucus in the stool gas cramps
bloating ulcers I'm just naming a few
diverticulosis diverticulitis I'm just
naming a few things
appendicitis you know eoli and strep and
strep in our system creates all this
rosacea it's another one too all that
can just from all this down in there and
you think a probiotic is the fixer of
that you know when I see a commercial on
television or something when I'm I was
at a friend's office and I was waiting
because I was I was going to go out to
lunch with them and you know I'm waiting
and and I'm in their office and there's
a TV on in the office and it's sitting
there and I see a commercial of a
probiotic like it's this big answer and
then it's funny I saw a commercial after
of fish oil fish oil the very thing that
actually feeds feeds all viruses is fish
oil cuz the Mercury to trace the trace
essence of mercury left in every single
fish oil capsule there ever was and it
feed feeds all that bacteria and all
that that viral stuff it's amazing the
world we live in where the information
is so still backwards not helpful I I
almost think sometimes it's just meant
to be that way just to keep people down
and keep women down keep women kind down
you know I just really believe so I
believe that the systems actually set up
to hurt people but the professionals
don't really know that I mean they
they're they're just they're all they're
trying to help people I get that but the
bottom line is is that probiotic you're
taking cannot kill off the bad bacteria
that's already been growing over time
for a long time and you need to do
something bigger and better than that
and leafy greens come into play if
they're not enough leafy greens in your
diet I promise you we're going to have
problems later I I look I'd rather be
straight out I've always been straight
out with you guys always have I love
hearing sometimes out there and YouTube
land and other places and all that and
lectures and stuff when people say that
they're straight out with them and then
you're listening to the information
you're like okay sure sure meanwhile
it's just nothing but propaganda to the
usual stuff to the usual songs everybody
singing listen I'm being straight out
that's why I've always delivered the
information to the core the reality of
it if I wasn't I'd be all about
probiotics 247 and trying to sell you
one probably too hey here's my probiotic
you guys here's my my new probiotic from
Anthony William look instead what am I
doing you got to buy leafy greens and
Anthony William gets no pennies off of
that not one cent not $1 okay you know
what I mean I want you juicing celery
juice Anthony William gets nothing off
of that the point is is I want you guys
to have it straight and know what's
going on so let's go let's go into leafy
greens have a living microorganisms on
them think about that how can that be
possible you go to your go to your
Farmers Market Market in the summertime
in the fall in the spring you get any
leafy greens whatsoever or any leafy
green herbs cilantro parsley you get any
of these herbs there's microorganisms
riddled on there you don't want to wash
them thoroughly you just want to rinse
them off and get any dirt off or
anything and that's fine kale out of the
garden there's microorganisms on there
they're called elevated biotics
undiscovered still by research and
science I brought elevated bi biotics I
brought that to the world through spirit
and spirit's information I put it in
book one medical medium book one okay
that's the one with the chest x-ray on
the cover so if you go to Amazon or you
go and look for it you'll see the
medical medium book one and and that has
a chest x-ray on it's like a blue cover
you'll see that right there secrets
behind chronic illness and how to
finally heal so here's the deal is
elevated biotics is only on these fresh
fruits and leav leafy greens you can get
from farmers markets pick off a tree
pick out of your garden or growing
Sprouts if you grow Sprouts in your
kitchen you grow some different Sprouts
in your kitchen you can brow grow
broccoli Sprouts fenig Greek Sprouts you
can grow different kind of um Sprouts
that are really helpful red clover
sprouts and when you're doing that the
microorganisms they will just appear on
these leaves naturally in the wild even
on your kitchen counter on a sprout they
will they will prosper on there these
are the very microorganisms that create
the B12 inside your body so when you're
doing leafy greens you're getting your
own B12 restored by your own body using
microorganisms that come from these
leafy greens called elevated biotics
that end up in your Elum of your
intestinal tract creating abundance of
B12 so you can heal and lose methylation
issues and actually heal and Rise Above
methylation problems which are liver
issues um vitamins can being converted
issues all these different issues that
happen in fact the MTHFR gene mutation
you won't even get that to ring up at a
doctor's office through their testing
that's basically just an elevation of
inflammation test anyway but it won't
even ring up if you're getting enough of
these elevated biotics through leafy
greens into your body that end up in
your elium producing B12 and gets you
out of trouble this is a lot of
information it's a lot of information
but it's here for you so that you can
heal and move forward so here's the deal
we're growing all this bad bacteria in
our guts bad microorganisms in our guts
we're growing it all it's prospering we
got the strep we got the eoli we got all
the different varieties of bad bacteria
so many so it's not even cataloged or
calculated by any science or or research
or any kind of any kind of institution
none of them have their fingers on all
the different bad bacteria that's inside
of us but it grows it prospers and it
and it develops and as it develops we
need something to knock it out something
to sweep it out something to eliminate
it out leafy greens not only have like
your own that you grow in your garden or
you grow at the or you get at the Farm's
Market not only do they have these
microorganisms called elevated biotics
to it to actually repopulate your
intestinal tract unlike any probiotic
can ever or any kind of soil born
microorganism can ever not only are
these elevated bi biotics that powerful
and can
repopulate but the leafy
green can sweep it sweeps the walls of
the intestinal tract lining gently
caressing the walls a lot of people
think greens are hard and difficult to
digest but they're easy to digest
they're super easy they're very leafy
greens are actually predigested
practically they're easy to digest
that's not the problem it's just that
the fiber content touches gently
massages and touches the intestinal
track so it touches the dadum and small
intestinal tract and colon and people
who are inflamed automatically from
colonies of eoli and colonies of strepto
coctus because they have all these
colonies of bad bacteria they're
elevated with inflammation they also
have the shingles virus they also have
the epscene bar clinging to the walls of
their int inal tracts and Linings and
when you have all that and bad fungus
not candida that's a good fungus bad
fungus when they have bad fungus all
clinging to the walls of the intestinal
tract the nerves on the intestinal tract
Linings get hyp sensitive so that if
you're not eating something really soft
like a piece of gooey bread that sits in
the middle of your digestive tract or
you're not eating some eggs that turns
into straight goo in the middle of your
digestive tract or having something like
a piece of ham that just sits there in
the middle of your intestinal tract if
you're not eating like simple things
like that or something soft and smooth
you know soft and smooth something that
feels like it's not abrasive and it
becomes gooey inside of you or something
like chicken just plain chicken which
doesn't rub on the sides of the
intestinal tract Linings and colon it
collects there over time the chicken fat
gets rancid and it collects on there and
I'm not saying that because I'm
anti-animal products or Pro Pro vegan or
Pro an animal or Pro whatever that's not
what it is I'm just saying it like it is
what would when these things like eggs
and all this gets gooey you don't feel
it you don't feel it move through you
don't feel it move through and because
you don't feel it move through what
happens is you think you're digesting it
and you think you're digesting it fine
you see how it works you eat some
lettuce and you're just like I can't
digest lettuce it's cuz you're feeling
it you're already inflamed now this
isn't everybody but there's a lot of
people that have this elevated
inflammation in their intestinal tracts
and Linings and all that but see the
leafy greens go in and they clean up
those rancid fats and proteins that are
rotting and also feeding bacteria in the
intestinal walls and I'm going to go
into that a little deeper in a minute so
what I'm trying to tell you is the
sensitive nerves in your intestinal
tract and colon those sensitive nerves
are because we're inflamed by viruses
like the shingles sitting in there
causing mild colitis and the Celiac
which is caused by bacteria and viruses
and all these different conditions of
the intestinal tract the bowels getting
inflamed pockets in the bowels pockets
in the colon that expand so expansions
in the small intestinal tract where it's
going normal and then boo it Puffs out
like it's herniated you know we have all
that in all of our guts and then
shrinking in intestinal tract where
there's narrowing people have narrowing
so when something's kind of squeezing
through if it's not gooey and soft and
squeezing through like eggs being gooey
after you chew it and turns into just a
mucus ball as you swallow it and you
know goes down you know if that's going
through those little narrowings then you
don't really feel it so bad even though
it's still feeding the problem and
feeding the very bacteria that creates
intestinal tract wall narrowings so all
of that but when you start eating a
little leafy green and you're one of
these sensitive Critters and you start
eating some leafy green say oh I don't
not digesting good because your nerves
are feeling it you know you're feeling
it because you feel something it's
touching the walls of everything what
it's doing it's sweeping it's cleaning
it's doing the cleanup it's touching
rancid fats rotting proteins that have
been there for years that are feeding
all the bad bacteria it's touching all
this stuff see so it's cleaning up the
system that's a whole another thing the
leafy greens do but what else do they do
they leave trace minerals behind that
feed good bacteria they're prebiotics
celery juice in herb is a pre biotic it
feeds all of the good bacteria that's
what it does the good thing about celery
juice I talk about my celery juice book
medical medium celery juice you got to
pick up that book you won't be
disappointed I promise what what's in
there and I can't explain it all here
it's impossible it's too big of a book
but what's in there is that celery
juices sodium cluster salts they hit the
bad bacteria they hit it the sodium
cluster salt hits the bad bacteria sucks
the life out of it pulls it apart cleans
out that bad bacteria the poison inside
of it the carcass of the bacteria ends
up being now fuel for good bacteria your
good bacteria devours the bad bacteria
because the sodium cluster salted celery
juice allowed that to happen it actually
allowed that to happen is what it did so
then when that good bacteria is feeding
off of the Dead bad bacteria it's
getting refueled
and then that's how we're we're
prospering even more and more there's so
many good things about why you want to
do the celery juices the herb the leafy
greens all of it celery juice is not a
leafy green it's got leafy greens on
celery okay so the stocks you buy the
whole bit there's leafy greens on there
so it is partly a leafy green okay but
it is an herb but I like the leafy green
herbs the cilantro The Parsley the
celery I like these in your life These
Are Powerful in the leaf leafy green
herb family that I want you to be on and
celery juice and leafy greens go hand
inand together to recover illness to
stay healthy so we have to remember that
you can't just if you want to just do
leafy greens it's great bringing leafy
greens in your diet now want to talk
about quantities and all that as we go
along so I hope you guys all hang in
there for this because we got so much to
talk about but you have to have the
celery juice too these are some of the
tickets I can't tell you how many people
that are plant-based fail in their
plant-based diet fail in their
recoveries because they don't have any
celery juice in there or not enough or
they only tried it once or no no leafy
greens in there too it happens all the
time all the people that leave the
plant-based movement all of them that's
that ended up going to a doctor a
functional medicine doctor that believed
in Pro protein protein protein and
they're not getting enough protein and
it was the it was the vegan diet that
hurt them you know they hear that and
they just they wa back and forth or they
just they start heading to animal
protein Kingdom again and they start
heading there they're always they're
always at that point where they they
lose out because they never did enough
leafy greens they never knew about the
28 day cleanse in book one medical
medium book one they never knew about uh
the 369 in Liver Rescue and that's the
thing and I'm even talking about the
plant-based movement where it was all
high carb and low fat that plant-based
movement there's a plant-based movement
where it was lowfat um high carb they
never did enough leafy greens they did a
handful of romae lettuce that was the
big thing it's some Ro Roma lettuce once
in a while they they eat a lot of fruit
a lot of starches but they didn't do
celery juice and they didn't do leafy
greens and that's how it works and I
can't tell you how many people in the
Paleo movement the non- plant-based
movement where it's paleo or keto animal
protein or high animal protein or some
kind of Mediterranean or animal protein
whatever it is where they get sick they
get sick but it's never blamed on their
diet it's never blamed on their diet
ever I mean it's always blamed on the
plant-based person all you do is have to
cough once and that's it it's your diet
that's what happens that's what
everybody says you can't escape that you
have to walk on water as a plant-based
person you can't H you can't even have
flatulence as a plant-based person you
can't have bad breath as a plant-based
person cuz it's your diet causing it you
can't have anything wrong but when your
animal protein is some kind no matter
what it is it's never blamed on diet no
way it's just hey look that you're
getting enough protein that's all that
matters okay let's go look at some there
something else that is it's probably
your genetics or your body's attacking
itself or something El or it's your
metabolism or something that's what be
thrown at that person or you're not
exercising enough or you're not maybe
you're eating too much maybe you had too
much fruit one day five years ago here's
the point
okay I never said ever just to eat fruit
I never ever ever told anyone in my life
to just meaning
someone someone that didn't have a
particular problem not like I remember a
long long time ago there was this child
that could not eat anything and the mom
took this child everywhere didn't matter
what this child would do or couldn't eat
anything there wouldn't be best doctors
in the world she flew her she flew her
son around the world to the best clinics
best conventional clinics there were on
the planet all around the globe us
abroad everywhere and the child couldn't
e
anything and then okay spirit said
bananas is going to be the key and the
child ate bananas and ate bananas only
and recovered and it saved the child's
life now the child's actually just
filled with muscle strong and adult now
and living life has children has a
family and it's because of those bananas
and I've seen that too with Papaya but
see these are different circumstances
these are very trying difficult times of
food poisoning very very very trying
different difficult times and even then
the leafy greens had to come in later
they still had to come in in order to
sustain that so there's like people who
have gone through heck and back with
food poisoning critical food po
poisoning issues you know I've seen more
than one case of a child that could only
eat banana too it's just there's been
more than one cases over the last three
years I talked to doctors where a doctor
said you know what it's unbelievable
it's it had a child that was it could
not eat anything would didn't matter
what it was it' be debilitating cramping
except for except for banana and I even
I even saw that when I was talking to a
doctor we had a big conversation about
it one time and so I've seen a doctor go
through that too where it saved a
child's life but the leafy greens have
to come later same thing with you know
people when they get severe food
poisoning papaya is the only thing you
can give them when I had food poisoning
as a child when I had severe food
poisoning as a
child um the only thing that worked for
me spirit said was pears was pears okay
so I got these right pears off my my
great-grandfather's tree and I had an
abundance of them for like two or three
straight weeks and I lived off of these
pears until I can bring in some leafy
greens and bring in some celery juice
the point is is that that's the only
times I've ever ever ever recommended or
seen wear fruit on its own for a certain
purpose and there are these certain rare
situations but other than that everybody
have ever talked to recommended a diet
or or some kind of food regime or some
kind of food you know food s uh system
some kind of recovery system leafy
greens were in there celery juice was in
there other things were in there besides
fruit and so but fruit is really it's an
important key to our health and we can't
lose that but the bottom line is when
you're plant-based whether you're
plant-based in in in the mindset of say
low carb lowfat plant-based you have to
have those leafy greens or the celery
juice and you have to have them long
enough long enough it can't be for one
month in your life out of 5 years of
being plant-based it's just it's just
that you're going to miss out same thing
with paleo same same with keto same with
any kind of other diet animal protein if
you're not doing the leafy greens in the
celery juice you're going to end up
having problems you're going to have
problems because it's the missing link
and I've been saying this since day one
day one going back decades now decades
it's the missing link it's that critical
and you have to take it that
seriously it's not just the mineral
salts that you have to have which are
critical for our life the trace mineral
salts it's a phytochemical compounds
it's the
alkaloids it's all of it that's in these
leafy greens it's the
antioxidants it's the trace mineral
nutrients it's all of that it's a
micronutrients it's even more than that
it's an energy in the leafy green
there's an energy within the leafy green
for the human body there's a symbiotic
relationship that they need each other
it's so critical if we want to go in
that direction I know I don't go in that
direction all the time or I talk about
that but it's that important and there's
vegan diets and plant-based diets that
actually are they're not about the
lowfat ones they're all about the keto
vegan keto plant-based it's all about
heavy fats all the time the nut Butters
the nuts and everything else and the
oils and the coconut oil and everything
like that where's the leafy greens
where's all the leafy greens and that's
why that crowd tends to go away from
vegan eventually once they start getting
sick or they're losing some weight and
they're getting a little bit better in
different ways because they cut out glut
and they cut out dairy products they cut
out animal proteins and they end up
getting sick too because we all have
things in us and troublemakers and heavy
metals and it's not coming out and leafy
greens helps get those out get the bad
bacteria out get the viruses out a
little bit get the toxic heavy metals
out get the poisons out of the liver so
you don't get sick so no matter where
you go on what diet front you want to be
on without the leafy greens and the
celery juice you're lost it's amazing
and you know it's not like this
information's out there spirit's the
only one putting this information out
there that's it it's coming from Spirit
it's coming from up there and and that's
where I get the information if you
haven't if you don't know anything about
the medical medium but the point is is
that that's where it has to come from
because no one else has ever talked
about it it's it's unbelievable we're
still stuck in that whole protein World
high fat world and and we're all still
stuck in that not eating enough leafy
greens and and all of that so it's
important leafy greens hold precious and
vital mineral salts partially composed
of a group of co-actors associated with
sodium and in the case of celery juice
it's a sodium cluster salt which is
entirely different than what's in a
leafy green but in the spinach there's
this partially comp there's this group
of co-actors associated with sodium that
group of co-actors is powerful too such
as Trace bioavailable iodine chromium
sulfur magnesium calcium potassium
silica manganese and malinam you know
all of that critical for
neurotransmitter and neuros support
neuron support the foundation the
building blocks the electrolytes all of
that see the electrolytes they come from
the celery juice especially the celery
juice nothing beats that but the but the
leafy greens also hold these different
constituents these different things of
electrolytes these different Power
sources electrolytes the different
groups of electrolytes too so we can get
some of those from there these leafy
greens are high in enzymes enzymatic
power celery juice has like in the
celery juice book the medical medium
celery juice book you'll read about the
enzymes and celery juice which is
unmatched but still the leafy greens you
need those enzymes too vitamin A vitamin
B folic acid alkaloids healing alkaloids
plant compounds that fight disease are
in Leafy grains and if you're only
eating a handful once a while in a mixed
green salad at a restaurant it's not
going to be enough micronutrients for
restoring the endocrine system the power
these leafy greens have providing
micronutrients to restore the endocrine
system these unique groups of nutrients
working together to feed all organ
systems all the organ systems that's the
power I'm talking about from leafy
greens so guess what let's just throw
all that away who cares
let's just make sure you get plenty of
eggs let's just make sure you get you
know some turkey let's just make sure
you get plenty of nuts and N Butters if
you're vegan let's just make sure you
get plenty of avocado and some oils and
maybe get some fish oil too take some
fish oil capsules take some whe protein
powder you know I'm kidding right I
don't want you on any of that really and
make sure make sure you're getting you
know let's just say let's make sure
let's let's focus on oatmeal I mean
there's nothing wrong with oatmeal but
the point is is that's what I'm saying
is without these leafy greens everything
else will fall flat it will fall flat it
won't be enough not in this world not
with what's going on in this world not
the viruses and bacteria and everything
else we're up against in this world not
with all the chronic illness and the
suffering and the anxiety and the
depression and the memory loss and the
brain fog that we're dealing in this
world and the headaches and the
migraines and the Tinkles and numbness
and vertigo and aches and pains and
ringing in the ears and body aches body
burning all that different stuff body
burning that's the body feeling like
it's on fire the skin rashes lupus
related rashes ecus ricis all related
rashes all the different problems
everybody has it's not going to be
enough it's going to fall flat without
the leafy greens and celery juice that's
it I look you know I mean I'm just kind
I just got to tell
you you know I got to keep on going I
got to keep on going that's what I have
to do wake up in the morning and say
let's what can I do for everybody bu
what can I do how can I help you greens
are the most bioavailability for for the
protein aspect too and I don't even care
about that I don't care about protein
protein protein because there's protein
in everything protein's not the problem
if we if we were like if we weren't sick
in this world and the whole world wasn't
getting sick I mean then you then look I
mean if protein was the answer the whole
world's getting sick what does it make
any sense think about it so there's
plenty of protein in Greens there's
plenty of protein in all foods it's not
even the problem but if you're worried
about if you're one of those protein
people then don't have any fear there's
protein and greens that's the thing and
the thing is with the greens the protein
and greens no other protein touches it
it's the best protein there is even
though it's actually the mineral salts
not the protein in the leafy greens the
body needs to build muscle with the
proteins are still good in in leafy
greens building muscle all hinges upon a
carbohydrate and mineral salts building
muscle all hinges upon a
carbohydrate and mineral
salts that's how it works I want to talk
about bulking for a minute bulking with
people who are weightlifting bulking
with people who are actually pushing
weights they're trying to get big
they're trying to get muscles all that
stuff I want to talk about that a little
bit what people find when they don't
have enough carbohydrates in their diet
what they find is a they can't bulk up
those M muscles as big as they want to
get them they can't get the muscles to
where they need to be they can't build
them like they want to so they end up
adding carbohydrates to their proteins
which is fat so they put fat and
carbohydrates together and they end up
building more muscle because they
brought carbohydrates in but they kept
the fats and because they kept the fats
they kept fat on their body so they bulk
up they end up with a layer of fat plus
more muscle and then they're in the
realm of how do we cut back how do we
cut back to somehow get the fat off of
us and try to keep the muscle it's a
game that doesn't work out that good
because now you're trying to cut back
now you're going it's a yo-yo you're
going back and forth on a yo-yo and
you're like trying to cut back on food
and cut back on carbs again but you
don't get rid of the protein and the fat
so you end up you end up getting stuck
where you get stuck with this little
excess weight on you and you're trying
to get rid of it but then you start
losing your muscle once you get rid of
carbohydrates again because
carbohydrates is the one thing that
builds muscle it's that and mineral
salts it's
carbohydrates and that's the whole point
but if these people just did carbs and
greens leafy greens lots of carbs
healthy carbs I'm talking about healthy
carbs like fruits and leafy greens and
celery juice if they did these things
all together you'd be able to build
bigger muscle and not get the fat layer
that's the whole thing and not get the
fat layer why do you think someone has
to use a carbohydrate to bulk up in
order to get more muscle why do you
think they need to bring that in because
when they're on just their lean meats
and their vegetables they can't get the
muscle they just can't get the muscle
they want so they have to bring in all
these carbs and it's called bulking and
you end up with a layer of fat on the
body and that layer of fat shows hey
what that layer of fat is it's from all
the protein and all the and all the
dense fat plus the carbohydrate combined
you can't put put those together leafy
greens contain Omega-3s naturally so
they're already in there if someone's
worried about Omega-3s and all the
omega-3 fatty acids they contain them
leafy greens have them butter leaf
lettuce red leaf lettuce they all have
it greens hold some of that that's
something right there that's
automatically in there so it's something
you know about barley grass juice powder
is a critical leafy green critical one I
like the vimergy barley grass juice
powder it's viz and Victor I EMS and
Mary E rgy they have the best spirina
they have the best barley grass juice
powder hands down I've ever come across
yet it's a mama poop company I love
those guys because they care about
people and when I use it I know it's
good and I know it's good and so that's
the kind of leafy green I really like a
barley grass juice powder I make sure
that's in there I do the heavy metal
detox smoothie every morning I put the
vimergy barley grass juice powder in
there I put the vimergy spirina in there
I get the Frozen wild blueberries I put
the that day I even use the viie uh wild
blueberry powder I mix it up I mix it up
in some coconut water I put it in a
smoothie but the point is that's what
you need I throw some cilantro in there
which is my other leafy green I like
getting my leafy greens from like the
fresh cilantro I like DOL it's a sea
Leaf it's a leafy vegetable so I like
DOL which is a which is a leafy
vegetable it's what I love but my leafy
greens is MASH which is MH Water Crest I
love that one Swiss Shard lettuce red
leaf lettuce um green leaf lettuce
spinach kale I love all those those are
my leafy greens that I use all the time
darker leafy greens plus lighter leafy
greens I love them all so that's what I
do and then I love that DLS in my
smoothie for the heavy metal detox
smoothie which is a sea Leaf a sea
vegetable I love that one and so I put
the cilantro in there which is a leafy
green I put the vimergy barley grass
cheese powder I'm getting my leafy
greens I wish you guys could because
it's that important the trace minerals
how alizing it is it's all
incredible and then you know it's so
what matters is if you're into like even
if you're into exercising and you're not
just trying to recover from a chronic
illness and build some muscle you're
just you feel fine and you want to build
muscle you don't have to combine all
that fat with all those bad carbs to try
to bulk up because that's what people do
now you want the healthy
carbohydrates you want the fruits you
want the mangoes you want the papayas
you want all that in there you want the
oranges you want the apples you want the
pears you want all that healthy fruit
you want the the blueberries the wild
blueberries and then you want to combine
that with leafy greens and celery juice
make sure that's in your program whether
you're plant-based or your paleo or your
animal protein and you're adding in the
animal protein into your diet or if
you're plant-based and you're adding in
something else into your diet would it
could be beans I see plant-based people
on beans whatever it is that's what you
want to do and that with your workout is
how you start building some mustard
muscles you know and unless you you know
unless you've been through chronic
illness been through Hellen Mac you got
fatigue you got nerve pain and you're
trying to get rid of the viruses through
the medical medium information to clean
those viruses out and you're trying to
start to work out again for the first
time in a long time then you take it
easy and I'm going to do a whole show on
that again about how all that works you
can recover your muscles recover your
bodies as you're healing from chronic
illness so I'll do a whole show on that
too and I'm also going to do a show on
just in general muscle building
bodybuilding in the future because it's
never been my focus my focus is about
saving lives offering life-saving
information that's ahead of Science of
research and chronic illness getting
people recovered from the deaths of
Despair that's always been my focus it's
not about building a few muscles it's
always been about recovering people so
they can get to a point where they can
work out and and because they can't
because they're suffering and they're
sick they got the lupus and the Ms and
they got the hives breaking out the
fatigue the anxiety severe depression
body aches and pains their face hurt
nerves teeth hurt they can't talk they
can barely walk so the people have
helped out recovering my whole life for
decades so I never I never worried about
the bodybuilding aspect of it because
it's about saving lives not about
getting somebody to look better for the
beach that's never been my issue it's
never been my goal to worry about that
but I do help professional athletes I do
help them to get better on their game
all of that over the years absolutely
and to build more muscle and get more
agile more flexibility and all of that
of course but the goal has always been
people suffering struggling getting out
of the depths of despair of the chronic
illness finally getting answers for the
first time ahead of science and research
so they could rise above it helping out
their family members all of that and
that's what the books are about and
that's what these shows are about leafy
greens are a part of that so let's move
on to the next part of leafy greens this
is so great the 28 day cleanse in
medical medium book one the 28 day
cleanse I love that one powerful I've
seen it bring lives back long before
that book was published and the spinach
soup in the 28 day cleanse and this is
for anybody who's animal protein non-
animal protein because it's a 28 day
cleanse to get them back on track I've
seen people live on this 28 day cleanse
for years in their life recovering
themselves getting themselves in in the
in and where they want to be the
Perfection to their health the way they
want but the bottom line is um spinach
soup is a big part of it all that
spinach soup you take a whole bunch of
spinach in there I'm not talking about a
little handful of spinach I'm talking
about like two three cups of spinach
half a container half a big container I
put one full container in there and you
keep on blending it up in your in your
mixer keep on blending it up I throw it
in the food processor and I do it I like
it in the blender the mixer I really
like it in the blender for this one 2
and 1/2 cups of chopped um chopped
spinach love it I put that in there it's
incredible I throw a couple of large
tomatoes in there mixing I you could put
cherry tomatoes in there I like the
large tomatoes an heirloom tomato I like
to put in there too two heirloom
tomatoes like to put a good handful of
cilantro in there too and one stock of
celery or half a stock of celery believe
it or not just put that in there like a
little half clove of garlic if you're a
you know a garlic person I love garlic
it's it's a miracle medicine too I love
it so I put like a half a clove in there
sometimes it's too strong for other
people people hate garlic it's all that
and then I squeeze some fresh oranges in
there tan tangin just a couple of
tangerines or a couple oranges I squeeze
in there I make sure they're not the
real bitey ones they they're sweet
they're easy you know they're easy on
easy on The Taste Buds and you different
oranges different times different
citruses add at different times
sometimes you get an orange it's really
bitey it's got a little little bit of an
acidy flavor and it's too spritely but
there's a lot of oranges they're sweet
they're juicy they're delicious they
can't be afraid of them because they're
amazing for the body I squeeze that in
there I blend it up and you got the
spinach soup you blend it up real nice
fill it in Nice in a good size Bowl you
sit there and you have that as your meal
that is an incredible way to get a large
amount of spinach leafy greens in you to
get you better now if you're someone
that's in fear of the whole hey oxyc
acid oxalates oxyc acid spinach stay
away from it you're completely wrong the
fresh spinach there's nothing of that
concern going on there at all it it's
far from it it's when you cook spinach
it's the opposite it see somebody
flipped that a while back with
misinformation years ago I don't know
who did it or how they did it or how
they accomplished it I don't know if it
was on purpose by accident by default
whatever but they flipped it they said
cooking Your Spinach you know to get rid
of the oxyc acid that's the only way you
should eat that's that's the opposite
You Hinder the spinach you hurt the
spinach you make the oxyc acid actually
you destabilize it you know when it's
when it's that but when it's in raw
spinach it's in a form that's completely
harmless it's not a it's not an issue
with oxyc acid at all when it's raw and
its raw state is the way to Eat Your
Spinach it brings back vitality and
health so many people h i mean I've
worked on over 200,000 people with
individually over the last 35 years
recovering their health I can't tell you
what that spinach soup has done to save
lives in the past from people who were
in their teens to to um people that
young adults to people who are older to
Elders to people in their 90s I can't
tell you what that spittage soup has
done and so you want to bring that in
it's a great easy way to do this and
it's really a great healing power it
really has it's incredible so you know
let's keep on going let's talk about
this a little bit um no matter what diet
you subscribe to it's not going to hold
it's not going to hold without adequate
leafy
greens a person needs at least Le two
and 1/2 cups of chopped greens daily
that's the
minimum most need more than that and all
of that along with your celery juice you
guys all of that along with your celery
juice it's that important now if you
can't do that every day it's okay it's
okay can you do it twice a week look
baby step we can totally baby step this
because you're still going to get a lot
of good out of it can you do it once a
week for me once a week for your family
can you do it once a week for the person
who cares about you the most I mean I
care about you but you have somebody in
your life that you know you see every
day and they care about you you want to
do it for them okay do it for me if you
can but if you you want to do it for
them you want to do it for the people
that love you and your family you want
to your closest friends you want to do
it for them because when you're doing
that you're going to be healthier
stronger less ailments less problems
less issues with your health and it's
going to give them a better life and
then they may start doing it look pick
up the medical medium lifechanging Foods
book medical medium life-changing Foods
I talk about leafy greens I have a
section of leafy greens in there and I
talk about the conditions leafy greens
help I talk about the symptoms leafy
greens help they help with depression
they help with Lyme disease infertility
they help with ADD anxiety they help
with all kinds of different endocrine
disorders adrenal fatigue
insomnia they help with all kinds of
stuff lymphodema skin disorders acne
they help with PMS hormone imbalances
dry skin scaly skin calcifications low
platelet count abdominal cramping
arhythmia heart palpitations balance
issues blisters on the body which are
viral body aches brain fog cavities yes
cavities in the teeth chest tightness
which is neurological which is your
Vagas nerve dizziness even air wax build
up leafy greens help jaw pain and even
knee pain that's just some of the things
in lifechanging Foods I just I just read
that right out of life-changing foods
that part right there so you know leafy
greens are that important look what they
can do for you look how important it is
they can give you alkalinity but they
can help rebuild your hydrochloric acid
now celery juice helps rebuild your
hydrochloric acid like no other but the
leafy greens also add to it too and help
rebuild it that's another thing too they
help you digest they strengthen your
digestion they bring you enzymes they
ease your pancreas they can prevent
pancreatitis pancreatic cancer
pancreatic tumors pancreatic problems
they can prevent diabetes type 1 type 2
diabetes for the future you see why the
leafy greens are important they can
balance blood sugar work with the
hormones these are just some of the
things the leafy greens can do it's that
powerful so the bottom line is if you
got a guru that you go to and you got a
book you love out there and if you're
not getting enough leafy greens in the
diet and celery juice that book's
falling short and the guru is falling
short not because the guru is not a good
person it's not that at all I'm sure you
know that Guru is a great person I'm
sure that coach is a great person I'm
sure that trainer is a great person I'm
sure that trainer seems like they got it
all down in the gym and they got some
muscles they know all kinds of stuff
about protein and what shakes to use and
they and they know about you know
different things and all that and and
all of it I'm sure they're really good
too with what they do absolutely I'm
sure your best functional medicine
doctor is good what he does I'm sure
that book or pamphlet you picked up or
something you found online or that
website on online but if it doesn't have
the celery juice it doesn't have the
celery juice in the right amount so make
sure you get the medical medium celery
juice book so you know the right amounts
of celery juice to use if you don't have
the right amount of celery juice and the
right amount of leafy greens and the
different varieties of leafy greens in
your diet on a daily basis no matter
what you're doing you're missing the
most important aspect of your health and
your life your well-being and your
recovery think about that so whatever
you subscribe to whatever that might be
whatever that is it's not going to be
true it's not going to be true to who
you are your physical needs your body
your organs what your soul needs if the
leafy greens and the seler juice aren't
there bottom line that's it and if
you're into the whole like ancestry
thing where it's the Paleo and the old
old cavemen and all that if you're into
that whole thing where where all that
that that fake science gets developed
just like fake science in all the
movements and everything from veganism
to pism to all that where everybody's
just throwing science at each other and
hoping something sticks on the wall
because they're hoping and they're just
all digging for things whatever you
believe in that you fell
into okay just know that the world has
changed the world has changed 10 years
ago you guys the world has changed 15
years ago we're more polluted now we're
more hindered Now by pathogens that it
basically mutated Epstein bar was
nothing like it was when I was do when I
was doing this back 20 years ago helping
people 20 25 years ago the varieties of
Epstein bar that were out there now
compared to the ones that are being
passed around now that people are
Contracting nothing like it was we're up
against toxic heavy metals like never
before in history we're inundated with
toxic heavy metals we're desperate to
get the heavy metal detox smoothie for
medical medium we're we're desperate to
get that out of the body those Metals
out of the body we're desperate to get
those leafy greens and the barley grass
juice powder in us every day we're
desperate to get the celery juice in us
every day to pull the stuff out so if we
think about hey back in the old days
back thousands of years ago you know uh
men just picked a few berries and they
hunted down some game and they ate a few
mushrooms and that's what they needed
you that that that does not apply
it doesn't it doesn't apply at all we
have so many different disorders that
have developed that never existed ever
in history before ever so many different
diagnoses somebody can get so many
non-diagnosis they can get with so much
confusion with so many different
problems and symptoms mystery chronic
illness has turned into something unlike
ever before in our history today and
that's why we need the juices that's why
juicing is critical if you're one of
those that believes you know you have to
have the fiber yeah who's who's taking
your fiber away I'm telling you to eat
leafy greens I'm telling you eat fruits
and vegetables and leafy greens who's
taking your fiber away because that's
the only place we get fiber so pretty
much the only place we get real fiber
but the celery juice and juicing is
critical because our bodies aren't even
able to handle food so good they're so
worn down internally our guts are such a
mess we need the revitalization of the
juices to revitalize to strengthen this
so we can actually even handle fiber
that's the whole point so we can even
handle fiber to the degree that we need
to handle it that's how important it is
you can juice your leafy greens too I
like doing two juices I like big big
celery juice in the morning is what I
like to do the end of the day I like to
do a whole another juice where I add
celery and then I add a few more things
of course it stops the celery juice from
working the celery itself but I add the
leafy greens cucumbers I like the
cucumber and leafy green juice that's
what I like at the end of the day maybe
a couple of stocks of celery in there
it's not going to do what the celeries
just did in the morning cuz by itself it
has to be by itself to do the power it
really has but I like separating like
doing two
juices but the point is it's juicing is
important so you need to know that
that's why I used my mega juicer and I
just put it all through there and that's
it it's the best one that ever that's
ever been made out there but the bottom
line is you guys have to make sure
you're getting your leafy greens look I
know this show is probably tough on a
lot of a lot of people because you're
hearing me say
look no matter what you're subscribing
to out there if you don't get enough
leafy greens and the juices and the
celery juice applied into it it's not
going to be its best and I get it if I
heard that if I was living my life and
listening to the best doctor out there
or the best book I read or whatever it
is that's out there on stuff and I'm
doing it and and all of a sudden I'm
hearing this right now I'd probably be
irritated too but just kick back sit
back and realize I'm working for you I'm
working for you you can just throw away
you can throw what I'm doing away you
can throw what I me working for you away
you can push it aside you can forget
about it may maybe it's wasted energy on
my side then cuz you maybe you don't
like that and you're just like I don't
care if he's working for me who cares
but I'm working for you no matter what
I'm there whether you like it or not I'm
working for you okay I wake up in the
morning I want you to get better and I'm
hoping you hear this message I'm hoping
you hear this message there's no
infomercials on this on this radio show
there's no infomercials trying to sell
you 20,000
products that's the bottom line okay
never received a penny from any of the
products I've ever even recommended the
point is is that I'm here to tell you to
do leafy greens and I don't got this
thing where I've I've all of a sudden
bought out every leafy Green Farm in in
the world so you guys are going to run
and get your leafy greens and and make
me a big big you know Big Rich Man has
nothing to do with anything I'm telling
you to juice celery go to your store and
buy it I'm telling you to pick up your
leafy greens and recover your health
that's what's critical I love you guys
and I stand by you and um believe in you
and I know how hard you work and I wish
I wish I had time to you know I got to
tell you that more how much I really am
blown away at which what what you do
every day and what you're doing out
there you're fighting for truth and not
just truth in your health and the hard
work you're doing but you're even
spreading this information and the
answers around and I really do
appreciate it I love you Spirit loves
you for it and I want you to take care
and till the next show all right bye