how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about natural
flavors natural flavoring sounds good
doesn't it all natural can't be bad the
thing is there's something kind of
sinister we don't know about natural
flavor flavoring it's everywhere it's in
everything did you know that it appeared
after something really bad disappeared H
wonder how they did that bait and switch
get ready fasten your seat belts because
we're going on a natural flavor
ride let see oh so sorry sorry ma'am
yeah okay God what am I looking for
again cereal cereal cereal that's on the
list all right oh here they
are
ingredients whole
oats natural flavors why is everything
have natural flavors I don't understand
this sorry no I'm yeah that's my that's
my Carriage right over there yeah thank
you um I can't find anything without
natural flavors I don't understand what
what is going on here my doctor's not
telling me about natural flavors
nobody's telling me about natural
flavors but I see it all right let me
just check my coconut water really quick
natural flavors my coconut water what is
this let me check my other package chips
that I got the healthy ones I love so
much natural
flavors what is going on I don't get it
I've been shouting about natural flavors
for years ever since they did the
switcheroo the great bait and switch the
Old
bamboozle what happened was there was
something in everybody's ingredient list
in everything they ate it was called M
SG mono sodium glutamate you know funny
thing thing is is it was everywhere it
was in every single Frozen TV dinner it
was in every single Frozen dish it was
in all the restaurant Foods everywhere
it was in fast foods takeout but it was
in snack foods as well sauces dips
dressings it was in everything it was in
all canned food anything canned canned
beans canned fruit it was in canned
vegetables canned peas canned green
beans anything canned at all canned
tomato sauce it was in everything Jarred
Jarred pickles Jarred olives jellies
jams peanut butter almond butter and
even ice cream any kind of ice cream or
any kind of dairy products like milk
yeah milk cheese butter and then candy
bars chocolate bars any kind of candy
really MS G was in almost everything but
here's the interesting part it was
listed in the ingredient list you look
at the back of a jar of pickles and
you'll see
MSG you look at the back of a pack of
cookies and you'll see MSG it was always
in the list it was written there the
amount of MSG was never disclosed there
wasn't like well 500 Mig of MSG 750 Mig
of MSG
10,000 mg of MSG the reason why it
wasn't disclosed because in different
packages different foods it would be
like over the top generous amounts
placed into everybody's food they were
eating and why because it made it taste
good not only taste good it made you
want to go back for more it was highly
addictive and when those neurons in your
brain
received that
MSG it made you remember the package you
ate it from like wow those chips are so
good I'm going back I'm going to get
another bag next time in the store
getting another bag of those chips I'm
going to grab three bags of those chips
and I'm going to eat one in the car on
the way home it was the Wild West a food
company can put 10,000 milligrams per
serving of MSG in their food another
company
might only put 200 mg another company
30,000 mg and the MSG industry chemical
companies that actually created it were
booming the food chemical industry was
taking off and MSG was the pilot light
and at the very same time MSG was really
taking off and the food chemical
industry was really taking advantage of
putting it in every single food for
everybody something else was happening
artificial flavors artificial flavoring
was big food chemical companies were not
only creating MSG synthetically but they
were creating artificial flavors
synthetically and artificial flavors
were in everything people didn't care it
was almost in every single food this was
pretty much the Golden Age of food this
is when people really didn't look at the
ingredient list nobody cared what was in
it it would be like canned the peas
that's all who cares it's just a can of
peas doesn't matter what's in there um
TV dinner doesn't matter what's in there
just TV dinner steak fries a little
dessert to TV dinner who cares what's in
there right macaroni and cheese doesn't
matter what's in there this was the
Golden Age It's when no one cared about
the ingredient list and the food
corporations knew this and they were
running with it and the food chemist
manufacturers ran with this they knew
this too nobody cared what was in the
food now we're moving into the 70s and
there were people that were
sensitive they realized they would get a
headache feel sick not feel good after
eating a meal this had nothing to do
with the health movement had nothing to
do with health and wellness or the
movement of healing this was just
regular people that were feeling kind of
headachy and sick and decided to look at
the back of the package these were
mainstream people these weren't that
group of people that went off the grid
decided to live by the land you know
grow their own food make their own
butter back to the Landers got their own
beans and rice going in bulk and lived
in nature it wasn't that crowd and it
wasn't the crowd that was doing aerobics
exercising a little bit worried about
Wellness to some degree that that group
of people either it was mainstream all
the way and they decided to look at the
back of the package because they weren't
feeling good conventional minded
everyday people that started to read the
back of the packages cuz they weren't
feeling good saw the MSG and made the
connection now at this point in time the
food chemistry manufacturing world was
in high gear with the MSG production
there was already a booming business
with it so thousands upon thousands of
pounds were leaving the factories and
heading to the food manufacturing
facilities MSG was booming crazy thing
is people were getting aware and it was
booming and then that collided together
the awareness and the booming both
collided the heads of the MSG
manufacturing world were sitting in
their boardroom and they were saying oh
crap we got a problem now they come a
long way from from where it originated
MSG commercial production started in
1909 after a Japanese Professor who was
a chemist figured out how to isolate
glutamate from seaweed broth commercial
production was about souping large Vats
of broth and then dehydrating the broth
so the white powder can be singled out
and then bagged up sold to restaurants
around the world but that was the
original old innocent way of doing it
that's not what we have today and it
wasn't what we had in the' 60s 7s and
80s either the old way was too expensive
cumbersome it was crude and it wasn't
even that toxic compared to where it
went later food chemical companies
didn't exist 100 years ago food
companies existed but not food chemical
corporations that manipulated food and
when these food chemical manufacturing
companies got wind of how addictive MSG
was they had to recreate the process in
an inexpensive way but potent and much
stronger than the original manufacturing
of MSG in 1909 in the 20th century there
was a conditioning with how we taste it
and flavored food Salt was always there
it was always on the table fine Pepper
too but this is beyond just salt and
pepper the flavor games began the food
chemical companies knew this this was
about ating to another flavoring and
another taste this was MSG other food
chemicals too in the artificial
flavorings people got used to
stimulation from eating cheesy crunchy
things that came out of a bag chips with
the most intense flavoring after you
finish up a bag you look at your
fingertips and they're all red and
orange looking with a powder on there
those intense flavors from the chemical
corporations they stimulate the neurons
that run the senses older Generations
that were raised on just plain old food
ended up learning how to eat all these
high sensory intense Flav and then
people now are raised on instead of old
plain food they're raised on these
intense flavors now the younger
Generations are highly addicted highly
addicted to all these chemical Food
flavors well I know what you're thinking
though you're not one of them right
because you're eating all the healthier
snacks and the healthier flavored foods
and all the good different treats that
seem like there's nothing bad in them
right so you're not one of the people
that are reaching their hands in those
real orangey red cheesy crunchy things
in the bag you're someone who is maybe
picking healthier options like in the
restaurants you're picking healthy
options on the menus and then when
you're in the store at the health market
health food store you're picking
healthier packaged foods that doesn't
look like it has anything bad in it or
maybe it's organic and not GMO and
you're like no that's not me I'm not
doing the real junky stuff the real fake
garbage but youve been fold in a way
that I'm going to fill you in on in a
little bit it's also why when someone
goes and eats cleaner and cleaner and
they're avoiding any of the packaged
Foods or restaurant Foods it gets really
boring really quick the reason you can
get bored really quick is because you're
coming off the ride you're coming off
the addiction you're going through
withdrawal you're coming off of the food
chemical ride it also leads to this
problem when someone actually stays away
from the food chemicals or they try to
clean up maybe do a cleanse a really
healthy one like a plain steamed potato
or some bananas it gets really old fast
and then you feel like you're
restricted it's hard to eat without all
that brain excitement that addiction the
food chemicals hitting all the neurons
it's like when you see somebody out
there and they get sick they get all
these symptoms and they have to dial it
back learn how to heal and maybe they'll
find some really good information maybe
they'll pick up a medical medium book
and they'll learn how to Mono eat for a
while and they'll do it and their
symptoms go away and they start healing
they get better because they've been
holding back all these toxic foods
they've been allowing their body to heal
they've been not feeding their pathogens
from all the different foods that are
bad for them and they're staying away
from all the bad flavorings and all of
the tricks that are inside food that
food chemical Industries create and then
they dropped their guard they got better
enough better enough to experience other
things again or experience the old
things in their old life when they were
sick so they go out to a restaurant they
order a vegan pizza maybe something that
has all that flavor and their mind is
blown their brain is just totally like
overloaded from those senses that
intense flavors back it hits every
single neuron it's excitement it's a
high and a happiness comes over and
takes over and then you hear friends and
family saying why can't you eat in
moderation why are you so restrictive
and you almost forget that you had a
restrict to heal to do the right things
to recover but now since you're better
it's like why am I eating that way why
should I just have a plain potato why
can't I just eat what I want in balance
in moderation
now you're on the addictive train again
the food train and then you go for
another vegan pizza and then you go for
another treat and then you go with a
chocolate bar and then you go with
something else a coconut ice cream and
then you go with something else and it
doesn't stop and now you're back on the
restaurant tour you're eating scrambled
eggs you're eating all these other
dishes you're eating salads with all
this flavoring in it and it's so easy to
poo poo what you did to get to this
place of Health where you got strong
enough all the stuff you did to get to
the place where you can go on the
restaurant tour now but you're smarter
now at the same time you're choosing
decent meals you're eating healthier
overall you're being mindful because
you're not doing what you did years ago
before you got sick which was standard
everything standard American diet eat
whatever now you're like educated about
food so you're like oh I could balance
that out I can moderate that I could
have this and you got the high and The
Addictive feelings you think you
outsmarted everybody you know best you
outsmarted the original diet many many
years ago you used to eat before you got
sick and then you outsmarted the diet
you brought into your life to get you
better and move you forward and now
you're outsmarting as you move forward
everybody else thinking you got this
whole thing down you outsmart at the
processed food world you outsmart at the
chemical food industry you outsmart at
everybody cuz now you know your body or
so so you think but you've been fold or
maybe you're somebody that did a keto
diet you got off the train the flavor
train off the standard American diet you
want to lose some weight you want to get
your life in a better place you want to
eat healthier you stay it off of all the
packaged Foods you don't go to
restaurants so much anymore because you
don't want to be tempted you're doing
the lean proteins you're staying away
from snacks you're watching your carbs
you're eating more vegetables you're
losing a little weight you're dropping a
few pounds you're feeling a little bit
better got a little bit more energy
you've been restricting restricting away
from all that flavor all those dressings
all those different dishes all those
combinations and then you're watching
your friends eat what they want through
eating pizza left and right ice cream
chips and dip macaroni and cheese
buffalo chicken wings flavored coffee
drinks drinks with alcohol in them take
out every day restaurant Sandwiches and
you remember that things taste so much
better in restaurants and all your
friends they're getting those highs
they're excited they're excited about
food they're watching you with your diet
and they're reminding you every second
how you're missing out then you start
feeling down about yourself you start
thinking what am I doing why am I
restricting how come I can't eat like
everybody else but what's really
happening is you broke your addiction
for a little while you're not living off
all that flavor you went through
withdrawal long enough to know what it's
like you lost a few pounds you started
feeling a little bit better you didn't
didn't cheat so much and maybe you
didn't cheat at all for a while what's
really happening though is you broke
ownership you were owned well that's the
thing the flavor companies they own all
of us that's the whole game the flavor
industry wants to own everybody the
chemical flavor industry knows you're
going to lose you're going to lose the
battle no way you're going to be able to
hang in there that long they know they
got you they know they got everybody
they know that eventually you're going
to be peer pressured by somebody family
friends people you know loved ones
anybody co-workers and they know the day
is going to come and the food chemical
Industries think tanks you know the
group of people that know you better
than you know you sometimes those think
tanks no you're going to fall into that
whole thing of hey I'm craving it maybe
my body needs it this time and those
think tanks know you're going to fall
prey to that old trick I just needed a
little s salt I was craving a little
salt that's why I went with that bag of
chips that's why I went with that fast
food restaurant french fries but if
that's the case why can't you just try a
steamed potato plain with a Sprinkle of
a little salt on there no it doesn't do
the trick and how come homemade french
fries made at home baked in the oven or
in an air fryer just don't taste like
the same thing when you go through the
fast food restaurant and you get some
french fries there there because it's
not just salt not even homemade french
fries fried in oil will satisfy you like
a french fry somewhere in a restaurant
so you end up coming off the Bland train
and you end up cheating and then you're
like wow that's what I remember but it's
even more exciting than ever before the
stimulation is crazy this was amazing
food your adrenaline's pumping you're
laughing with friends you can't believe
how awesome the food is is and now
you're like why can't I do this another
time why am I restricting so much now
you're back in it with everybody else
you're on a train again but the think
tanks know that that's the whole point
chemical food industry knows this is
going to happen and they love it they
know you're going to join the losing
team now don't get confused with herbs
and spices that's not what we're talking
about here we're not saying hey you
can't shake a little tomb brick on your
meal or you got a little Cayenne or
oregano we're not talking about clean
herbs and
spices oh my God I can't wait for my
meal to come yeah oh here's the
waiter thank you thank you yeah can I
have an next extra Fork
right oh my
God oh my God it's so good yeah so what
were we talking about yeah
I can't shove it in fast enough right
now can I try your
appetizer I'll order one for myself
don't
worry this is so good I've been off my
diet right now for like what 2 days now
and it's like I'm happy again I'm happy
like what was I doing what was I
thinking isn't there such thing as
moderation and balance
yeah yeah I was talking to this coach
and the coach said that I can just eat
what I want and still be happy but I'm
trying to remember didn't I start eating
really clean because and started eating
really like fresh and no junk and
garbage and no processed foods because I
wasn't feeling good right and I had
weight while I lost a few pounds yeah
and now I feel like I can just start
fresh oh my God this is so good I could
do this like every day right now I know
some people think they've escaped it all
because they've figured out intermittent
fasting for a while in their life and
they're not a part of all this flavored
game but it's actually the opposite
they're doing the flavored chemical
coffee drinks all day long and then at
the end of the day they're eating
anything their heart desires cuz they
starve thems all day long and how do you
get vanilla flavored coffee when there's
no real vanilla in there and then when
you eat you eat anything you want and
they take pride in the fact that they
can eat what they want and do eat what
they want but that really means they
really haven't escaped the whole that
the food chemical companies have on them
and then there's the athletes out there
that work really hard with their
athletic work and after they're done
they award themselves with their
favorite food like donuts or bagels or
something cheesy usually something from
their favorite restaurant and what's
incredible is that these athletes
they're in good shape they look amazing
they're working hard everybody aspires
to be like them but at the same time
they're trap too and the chemical
industry the food chemical industry
knows this and when you talk to an
athlete they'll tell you it's about
balance and moderation and that's why
they do it too they love their favorite
foods they feel like they earned it they
ran 20 miles they burned off all those
calories why not eat our favorite Donuts
now but the funny thing is the food
chemical industry created the term
balance and moderation they created it
with the the pharmaceutical companies so
that people go you know what I can have
a little bit more of that toxic crap the
industry pushed and promoted the balance
of moderation narrative so that you
would buy more chips and cookies and
donuts and package food and drinks and
restaurant food and any other foods from
other food companies that they've sold
their chemical additives to so let's go
back to the Collision where the food
chemical industry realized ocean it and
people in the mainstream realized
something's bad in these products the
moment enough people realized MSG was
doing something to them the moment they
realized it was on the label and the
moment they realized it was actually
toxic in causing a problem the MSG
realizations the MSG realization from
the food chemical industry too where
they're like oh my God they're figuring
it out they're finding out what do we do
the food chemical industry said to
itself if we don't keep this stuff tasty
addictive we're going to lose a lot of
sales and the effect was going to happen
from the highest part of the food chain
down to the lowest part of the food
chain the chemical manufacturing
facilities which is the highest part of
the food chain that were producing all
of that MSG plus artificial flavoring
and other kind of food chemicals too
they were going to take a big hit
because they were the ones that were
selling all of that product all of that
MSG to the other food corporations the
food corporations that sell all the soft
drinks and the drinks and the package
foods and the bagged and packaged snacks
and the next line on the food chain was
the food chains meaning the restaurant
business restaurant chains fast food
they purchased all that MSG and all the
other food chemicals too and were
putting in it in all their chain
restaurant Delights and tasty dishes but
it didn't stop there and then all the
other food businesses food companies
that bottled and canned things they
purchased the MSG and other food
chemicals to put in all their different
things you find on the Shelf all the
bottled stuff all the Jarred pickles
Jarred olives Jarred artichokes all the
different jellies and jams mayos
mustards ketchups dressings and then the
next stop on the food chain Candy World
chocolate bars candy bars all of those
packed with MSG and then the next part
of the food chain dropping down to the
mom and pop stores mom and pop
restaurants where it's condiments in
bulk soy sauces vinegars tomato sauces
peanut oil canola oil olive oil MSU was
added to those bulk oils this was the
wholesale market and this is the
wholesale Market that was fed to the mom
and pop stores and restaurants all laced
with MSG the entire food chain business
was infested with MSG and contaminated
with food chemicals from the highest
Echelon and beneath then the word got
out MSG was toxic it was bad and then it
disappeared like a ghost ship in the
night the letters
MSG disappeared off of all the labels
all the labels in the food World changed
but the recipe stayed the same emergency
action was taken by the food chemical
industry which was illegal because the
word MSG monosodium glutamate was
removed off of all the labels of every
single food in the industry but yet MSG
was still in the food all the same and
then people got wise though they still
weren't feeling good and so individuals
looked into the products and were
looking and searching for MSG it was
still there this was during a time when
food Chemical Testing was approachable
the Layman can get food tested for
Basics and actually see results a small
window in time before the food chemical
industry to control over almost
everything when when the food chemical
industry joined forces with big Pharma
and determined what we allowed to truly
see in our food and drugs and for the
short moment of time in our history
added MSG was no longer there it was
removed it wasn't in the food anymore it
disappeared but then it reappeared under
different names different tags different
ingredient words private deals were made
behind the scenes with these
organizations private deals
grandfathered in that you're never
allowed to know the MSG found its way
back into the food under code names
yeast artificial flavors fermented
products fermented foods soy products
Protein Isolate and so many more but
there's a big one really scary one it's
natural flavoring natural flavors why is
it scary one reason
it's so deceiving it's really a trick
out it's natural all natural natural is
great natural's good natural can be in
any organic food it can be in any
product that's healthy for you and all
the people that wanted food transparency
like they wanted transparency of what
they're eating what they're feeding
their children they think they're
getting that transparency natural
flavors what could go wrong think about
all the people in the health world World
Health and Wellness World they care
about what they're putting in their body
they look at everything they read
everything moms buy juice boxes juice
boxes say apple juice and then natural
flavors underneath it almost every
single health food out there has natural
flavors in it one way or another
including supplements any kind of
supplementation you'll see natural
flavors in there now here's where it
gets really confusing you'll see organic
natural flavors
still the same thing we're going to talk
about that in a minute organic flavoring
organic vanilla flavor vanilla flavoring
vanilla flavors Berry flavor organic
Berry flavor any kind of natural
flavoring but it doesn't stop there it
might say fruit flavoring or it might
say caramel flavoring or it might say
something else but it never stops
there's so many different versions and
different types of flavors and then the
individual fruit names or vegetable
names it'll be like Blackberry flavoring
raspberry flavoring and then you think
it's just a raspberry that was put in
there but it's not just because you hear
the word natural flavors and then you
read the package and you're like well it
doesn't say natural flavors on here it
says poisonberry or Blackberry flavoring
or fruit flavoring I'm off the hook
everything's okay it's not natural
flavors but you're not off the hook it's
not okay it's all the same but at the
same time it's so different so let's
talk about that what I mean by that is
every time you see a flavoring of any
kind in a product there could be 200
different ingredients within that
flavoring 400 ingredients 1,000
ingredients 100 ingredients it could be
anything and that's the whole point it's
like the fragrance world it's a secret
you don't get to choose or know what is
inside the product it's like perfume
perfume fragrance cologne you'll never
know a thousand ingredients many of them
toxic sitting inside of it and you don't
know about it natural flavors is like
the perfume perfume fragrance world of
food and you thought you're getting
transparency full transparency of your
health food you're in the store you're
in an organic market you're in a Foods
Market you see some healthy snacks some
healthy drinks and little do you know
you got MSG in your or drink in your
snack it's in the natural flavor along
with many other chemicals you don't know
about that are in the natural flavorings
now why would natural flavors or natural
flavoring of any kind have MSG in it if
you look into MSG you'll see out there
that it has to be listed in an
ingredient list on a food product so if
you want to choose to use MSG to flavor
your food it has to be listed in the
ingredient list but what people don't
realize is there's a workaround for
example if you're a food company and you
want to produce a tasty food product and
you want to buy and purchase isolated
mono sodium glutamate to make it taste
good you can you can purchase it and
then you can add it to your ingredient
list but you have to have the
transparency you have to say mono sodium
glutamate in your food product
ingredient list but if you're a
health-minded person and you see it in
the ingredient list mono sodium
glutamate you may not choose to purchase
that product so the workaround comes
like this the food company can purchase
natural flavors natural flavors can go
into the food snack or food product you
don't have to list monosodium glutamate
it's in the natural flavors food
chemists that work for the food chemical
industry create the natural flavors they
add the MSG into the natural flavors
along with a whole bunch of other
chemicals then they sell those natural
flavorings to food manufacturer ing
companies if you have a package of
snacks that you like and they're a
healthy package of snacks and GMO free
the whole bit gluten-free and you see
natural flavors in there and you call
the company and say what's in your
natural
flavors hello super erer duper healthy
Sac Delights Incorporated how can I help
you yeah um anyway I got your package
right here and I just have a question it
says natural
flavoring yeah and it say natural
flavoring and I'm just want to clear
this up for a second cuz I'm thinking
what is that like what's in the natural
flavoring our snack foods are non- GMO
they're grain-free they're gluten-free
and the best there is out there so
what's your question again
sir the the natural flavorings is it
possible something else is in the
natural flavorings because what is
natural flavorings do you know
M hm I think I really don't I can't
answer that right now I can get back to
you though what's your phone number the
thing is no one will ever know no one's
supposed to know it's not meant for
anybody to know that's the whole point
it's a way for the industry to sneak in
anything they want to sneak in now we're
highlighting MSG but there's a whole
bunch of other chemicals getting snuck
into those natural flavors but there's
good reason to highlight MSG because
it's really that bad now there's a lot
of gaslighting going on about MSG out
there you'll hear about it it's not so
bad for us after all there's really no
harmful effects there's no evidence or
data there's no proof clinics are even
saying well there's really no proof that
MSG has harmed anyone so you can
actually have it in moderation why not
no one's really getting hurt by it now
here's the big one they hang their hat
on right here they'll say mono sodium
glutamate is naturally occurring in all
your Foods Dairy meat fruits vegetables
and this is where they're totally wrong
if you have an organic non-GMO cherry
tomato in your hand they will say that
there's naturally occurring MSG inside
that tomato this is not true to begin
with your cherry tomato is organic it's
non GMO you have to remember that what
you'll find in that tomato is naturally
occurring glutamic acid in traces not
the mono sodium glutamate additive
that's used in the industry the thing
that's added to the food that's isolated
and synthesized highly concentrated and
GMO if a supplement product or food
product says non GMO but has natural
flavors in the ingredient list and those
natural flavors are comprised with a lot
of different chemicals and additives
that are derived from GMO sources is the
product now truly non- GMO or because
the natural flavors has GMO chemicals in
there it's truly not a non-GMO product
but in defense of supplement product
companies and food product companies
they just don't know no one's telling
those people who own and run those
companies that natural flavoring is GMO
or natural flavoring has a lot of MSG in
it or natural flavors and natural
flavoring has 100 200 300 500 different
chemicals in it if you see a drink or a
packaged food that has say 10
ingredients in it and it's wholesome and
the ingredients look clean and good but
you see an additional ingredient called
natural flavorings or natural flavors or
just plain flavors or raspberry flavor
vanilla flavor or any kind of flavor
flavoring then in true reality you're
not dealing with 10 ingredients you're
dealing with at least an 11th which is
MSG but here's the crazy part you're
really dealing with 100 more or maybe
200 more or even more than that could
even be a thousand no one would ever
know so really instead of 10 ingredients
on that package there should be a list a
mile long on that package names you
can't even believe and that's the
workaround and that's how everybody's
being played as the years go on anything
could be put into those natural
flavorings and natural flavors and then
put into your food no one would ever
know the MSG of today is different than
the MSG years ago decades ago and the
MSG decades ago was different than the
MSG originally discovered back in 1908
the MSG now is produced and created out
of GMO sugar beads GMO corn GMO molasses
making MSG GMO and then that MSG is
added to a natural flavor mix whether
it's or organic natural flavors or
natural flavorings or vanilla natural
flavor it's added to that now it's a GMO
product then those natural flavors get
put into a package of organic food
organic food label says n GMO but now it
is GMO and here's an interesting thing
MSG isn't just MSG anymore by itself
sure they derive it from GMO sources
like the GMO corn GMO sugar beets and
other GMO products but they also add
different chemicals to it now so it's
not just MSG by itself it's MSG with
other chemicals added to it and it's
random you won't know what kind of MSG
you even get some MSG is just plain old
just sugar beads that are actually GMO
gmoe corn it's dry from it and you just
get the MSG mixed into those natural
flavors and some MSG will have that plus
chemicals but it's all random and it's
all bad and then when you think it's bad
enough there's different forms of MSG
there's a cloned version where it's all
synthetic what this means is the
original was made off of GMO sugar beets
or GMO molasses GMO corn but chemical
companies found cheaper ways of doing it
cloning it cloning the building blocks
of GMO corn GMO sugar beat versions of
MSG creating an identical synthetic
compound and calling it MSG and then
that sold to food companies and put into
the natural flavors and then those
natural flavors get put into your ice
creams your drinks your snacks your
cereals your supplements and then little
juice boxes that your kids drink it was
the ultimate baat and switch it was an
invasion natural flavors became an
invasion into our food supply without
your consent nobody ever asked you hey
everybody do you want this crap in your
food sad thing is you're not even going
to taste the real flavor of what the
food was because they added all their
chemical natural flavors in so if it was
apple juice you're not going to taste
the apple juice to the natural way it
would be you're going to taste their
concoction they added into the apple
juice the thing is there's all these
people out there that pride in how they
eat they pride in what they avoid too
like they avoid fast foods or processed
foods they think they escaped the
conventional machine but they didn't the
conventional evil machine still has
their hands in your Pure Food so let's
head back to the MSG why is it bad well
conventional world says right now like
don't worry about it clinics even say
hey it's not really causing a problem
with anybody something not to be alarmed
about there isn't enough studies we
don't really see anything we haven't
seen anybody really get hurt by it so
maybe you don't have to worry about it
but how would they know science of
research doesn't know why anybody sick
still to this day they don't have the
technology to know why at the same time
chronic illness is exploding out there
especially neurological conditions and
disorders I'm not saying that all the
chronic illness of today is because of
MSG but I am saying they figured out
years ago decades ago that the MSG was
bothering people giving them migraines
making them dizzy giving them
neurological symptoms and then they
backtracked they papered it all up
doesn't exist it's not happening they
rewrote history like they do all too
often so let's go back a little ways
when people first started complaining
about problems that they identified with
MSG first of all your doctor could not
identify why the MSG was causing a
symptom or a problem they didn't have
the technology to diagnose it and they
still don't today which is why they can
rewrite history right now and tell you
well we don't know what the effects are
and we don't think think there is any
problems MSG really isn't an issue like
we maybe thought before but let's talk
about the truth to begin with MSG isn't
the cause of somebody having OCD bipolar
depression anxiety but it can help
worsen it and MSG is not the cause of
severe migraines or the cause of other
symptoms and conditions that are severe
but it can worsen the symptoms here's
why MSG could be a problem it can build
up inside the brain over time deposits
of MSG can build up around neurons
dampening electrical impulses neurons in
neurotransmitter activity so if anybody
has a problem like toxic heavy metals in
their brain or lowgrade viral infections
or high-grade viral infections chronic
illness autoimmune there already is a
compromise going on between the
pathogens the metals and toxins
somebody's dealing with or brain
inflammation that somebody is dealing
with MSG can be the straw that breaks
the Campbell's back all these problems
are happening MSG deposits are building
we have more issues now with the brain
this way if somebody's already sensitive
from metals and pathogens and other
issues then they're going to be
sensitive to the MSG if someone doesn't
have any big health problems they don't
have any symptoms or conditions yet and
they go through life ingesting a lot of
MSG along the way it keeps building up
over time and eventually the MSG
deposits that build up on the neurons
become a weakness I talk in great detail
about this in the brains saver
books H my favorite snack bars let me
see this what flavors do they
have ooh strawberry and
almond o raspberry and macadamia nut let
me read the
back what's this natural flavors thing
oh that's right right I remember that
stuff's bad putting this
back the word natural isn't safe space
anymore it never was the lines are
blurred always have been there is
treachery in the stores natural can mean
anything at this point in the world not
even good old non GMO is sketched in
stone nor
secure what we see with our own eyes
isn't all that's cracked up to being
known and what we can't see with our
eyes is in a leag of its own words can
have different meanings when it comes
down to our health there's a lot of bad
still out there in our way when it comes
to healing and who knows it's still so
confusing and sad when you think about
the tricks in games played on the ones
by the bad who take care of their health
the most but they've been had and as we
walk down the food aisles filling our
baskets with wholesome options and have
no idea why corruption somehow found its
way into the door of the natural and
even organic food stores how strange it
all really is that the back of the
bottle or package has a mysterious word
puzzle that most everyone
ignores sometimes it's even on the lid
it's time we become aware about the
flavors that make the food tastes less
Bland and so bizarre so many pride in
themselves when it comes to taking care
of their health and they think about
everything that enters their mouth
because they're all told health is
wealth at the same time something is
hidden and completely stealth
interfering with your self-care and your
self-help when it comes to these small
little words hiding deep within the
labels we seem to trust the ones that
control our taste buds and tell us
[Music]
Fables