how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about
pharmaceuticals we're talking about
medications drugs are you on a
pharmaceutical have you been taking a
drug or a pharmaceutical prescribed by
your doctor maybe you're not on any
pharmaceutical and you're proud of that
maybe
you're proud because you're clear and
free from all Pharmaceuticals but what
you don't know is you still have
Pharmaceuticals running through your
veins and inside your organs
Pharmaceuticals and drugs that have been
there for a very long time including
drugs and pharmaceuticals that you're
exposed to every day and don't even
realize it get ready for this episode
it's going to blow your mind and make
you rethink your everyday
life
jeez this pole is
packed God I should have got here
earlier this is insane there's a LIF
guard here who
oh just got splashed in the
face God you know I used to really like
this hotel but this place is insane
right now it's like everybody took a
vacation all at the same time or
something I think I just got a water
Drop In My Mouth from the
pool all right I'm I'm going to get in
just what's that floating
there what is that why is the Lifeguard
like starting to round everybody
up he's he's shutting down the pool he
everybody's got to get out all
right all right we're all we're getting
out what what is that in the pool
even if you're not taking a
pharmaceutical even if you're not taking
a drug that's prescribed by your doctor
you're still taking them you're taking
them in different forms pools and water
parks great way to absorb
Pharmaceuticals have you ever been into
a public pool or maybe a private pool
that many people have swam through the
course of the years have you ever been
to water park all of these places have
Pharmaceuticals inside the water I know
what you're thinking you're thinking
they chlorinate the pole it's
disinfected so there's nothing to worry
about they shock it with chlorine for
parasites bacteria and
algae
chlorine doesn't remove any of the
pharmaceutical
residues so how do Pharmaceuticals get
into the water in the pool or the water
park how does it get out of somebody's
body and into the water when someone
takes antibiotics anti-depressants
anti-inflammatories sleeping pills
biologics
immunosupressants prescription
amphetamines opioids statins blood
pressure medications hormone medications
thyroid medication
steroids the pill pharmaceutical alcohol
recreational drugs of any kind it comes
out through the skin it's sticking to
their skin in their sweat it's coming
out of their bodies it's in their
armpits it's in their breath it's in
their spit it's in their urine it's
everywhere so when someone's swimming in
the pool there's pharmaceutical runoff
that's Pharmaceuticals running off of
their skin coming out of their armpits
coming off their genitals coming out of
their mouth when they get water in their
mouth and even when they pee in the pool
they don't have to urinate in the pole
they can have a little few drops of
urine in their shorts and they get into
the pole or feces that hasn't been wiped
good it gets in the pole water and when
someone's taking Pharmaceuticals and
they're prescribed drugs and medications
or on recreational drugs it's inside
their intestinal tract so when they have
flatulence gas it's inside the
gas so when one person farts in the pole
that gas is filtered through the water
so as the gas bubbles come out of their
anus it's now circulating through the
water and it rises to the top and then
the gas appears people think that's
funny a lot of times and there's a lot
of jokes around it but either way that
gas was filtered through the water the
water acted as a filter grabbing onto
everything in there including residues
of
pharmaceuticals and then there's
pharmaceutical creams a lot of people
are on ointments prescribed by their
doctors ointments and creams acne creams
dermatitis creams steroids for
ecori creams for all kinds of different
ringworm creams and ointments for the
shingles creams and ointments for herpes
simplex one Simplex 2 creams for rashes
creams for hormones and cream and
ointments for poison ivy and poison oak
and then there's creams and sprays and
ointments for feet problems foot fungus
athletes foot toenail fungus and
fingernail fungus and there's ointments
and creams for warts warts on the feet
warts on the hands and there's so many
more creams and ointments from
pharmaceutical companies prescribed for
patients and over the counter at the
drugstore and of course we can't forget
Kim therapy drugs that are topical but
you might be thinking maybe none of this
matters you weren't swimming on the day
they were swimming plus all that
chlorine that shock to the water all
that fungicide to the water takes care
of it it's fresh and new the minute they
do it and then the filtration pull
filters that must get everything nope it
doesn't doesn't get anything the filter
doesn't filter any of the
Pharmaceuticals the pharmaceutical
runoff stays in the pole for the
lifetime of the water that's staying in
the pole a hotel pole could potentially
have thousands and thousands of people
inside that pole throughout the years
and a hotel may not drain the water out
of that pole for a decade or more the
pharmaceutical soup inside the pole
concentrates and concentrates and never
dissipates but don't worry don't worry
the pool guy will come in test the water
make sure everything's okay throw some
chlorine in there clean up a little bit
and everything should be great but the
pole guy isn't testing for
pharmaceuticals there could be hundreds
and hundreds of different
Pharmaceuticals in the pool water for
years many Pharmaceuticals that were
even taken off the market because they
were dangerous or cause
problems and then what about the big
concern that so many people have and so
many doctors have and health authorities
have which is
mixing Pharmaceuticals pharmaceutical
cocktails you can't take this drug with
this drug can't take these two drugs and
then take this drug you can't take these
three drugs and bring this one in boom
they all go bad you can't take this drug
and that drug at the same time if you
take this drug with this drug you could
have a bad reaction could even be death
meanwhile the pole is filled with a ton
of different kinds of
drugs all right so they open the pole
back up yeah get your towel okay yep
lifeguard says it's all clear
okay it's actually warm in here pretty
good
okay I just swallowed a whole gulp of
water
did you ever swallow a gulp of water in
a public pool did you ever swallow a
gulp of water in a private pool either
way it's easy to swallow a gulp of water
in a pole or get water in your mouth or
get water in your eyes nevertheless in
your ears and once you swallow that gulp
of water all that pharmaceutical residue
Finds Its way inside the body gets into
the liver gets into the organs the
tissue gets to your brain and and all
the pharmaceutical creams they actually
enter into your body really easy too
Through Your Skin other Pharmaceuticals
enter your body through your skin too
all of it could get through your skin
does it even have to be in your ears
eyes or mouth and then what about
someone who's swimming that's on
recreational drugs weed ecstasy Molly
meth you don't think a meth head swims
what about cocaine heroin crack or just
anybody who's addicted icted to opioids
one way or another through prescription
Pharmaceuticals CU they were in a lot of
pain or someone who's a drug addict who
just has a connection and takes them
anyway either way it ends up in the pole
and it stays there and stays there and
then concentrates over time and then
more people come in and bring in more
Pharmaceuticals and what about the water
supply where did the water come from
originally that entered the pole and
then water filtration systems they don't
grab on to pharmaceutical residue how do
Pharmaceuticals get into the water
supply people are eliminating the
Pharmaceuticals out of their body when
they go to the bathroom and it ends up
back into the water system so that when
we're filling our poles with water we're
filling our poles with water that has
pharmaceutical residue in it already and
our water supplies in general have
contamination in them this also means
that Med medication leased water can end
up anywhere it could become part of our
food through reservoirs irrigation
Public Water Supplies wellwater near
septic tanks and fish swimming in lakes
rivers and oceans all absorbing
pharmaceutical residue and maybe you're
thinking you haven't swam in a pole for
a very very long time like years but
guess what when you did swim in that
pool a long time ago that pharmaceutical
resident do got into your body and
stayed there unless you're doing
something actively trying to remove it
or get it out or cleanse it or if you're
brushing your teeth with the water or
cooking with tap water or eating at at
restaurants or getting coffee at
restaurants drinking tea in restaurants
you're getting that pharmaceutical
treated water and restaurant water
normally contains pharmaceutical run off
this isn't about fear this isn't about
not being able to live your life that's
not not it it's being aware of what's
happening out there so you can do
something about it so you can be
proactive
empowered because it's Death By A
Thousand Cuts it chips away at us over
time and then when we get sick how do we
get better fast how do we look out for
the pitfalls the
potholes and how do we get rid of the
pharmaceutical exposure even if we're
taking Pharmaceuticals prescribed by our
doctors we still want to cleanse out the
old stuff the residue
our bodies are up against a lot we
already have a difficult time naturally
detoxing anything here on planet Earth
our bodies have a difficult time enough
getting rid of natural bodily toxins
we're not designed to get rid of all
these different chemicals and metals and
man-made Industrial Waste not to mention
things that were exposed to every day
fragrances colognes perfumes cleaning
products and then there's pesticides
herbicides fungicides we get it on us
all the time just buying brand new
clothes our body gets exposed to so many
different chemicals from that alone our
bodies are not indestructible they're
not meant to receive all these different
toxins and poisons and get
bombarded and at the same time our
bodies are resilient and they're strong
but they have a breaking point we take
our bodies for granted here on planet
Earth and then when our body starts to
fail like we get symptoms and conditions
we're not feeling good we listen to
people telling us it's our fault our
body's fault then we end up hating our
bodies we start blaming our bodies
thinking that they're faulty they're not
working good how come we can't get out
of the sickness or the symptom your body
can't just tell you hey mister we got
exposed something got into us when we
were swimming all these Pharmaceuticals
entered us our bodies can't say hey did
you know that tap water that was used in
the coffee at the fancy coffee shop was
toxic and it got something into us and
our bodies can't say Hey listen all that
tap water we're using for the shower and
the bathroom and for your coffee and for
your food is all saturated with
Pharmaceuticals and getting in us and I
just need a little help getting it out
of us our bodies need assistance they
need help they want to heal they're
fighting for us it's important to be
aware of all the different things that
our body is up against this isn't about
never swimming again or drinking
something from a restaurant it's just
about becoming empowered because all of
these different toxins like
pharmaceutical runoff from other people
going into your own body sits in us and
sits in us and it builds up over time
and it becomes something that gets in
the way down the road find out more
information on how to get rid of certain
toxins such as pharmaceutical exposure
in the brain saver books if you're on a
medication you know you're on a
medication if you're on a drug you know
if you're on a drug your doctor
prescribed it if you're doing drugs
recreationally you know you're doing
drugs you're on them
there's a knowing they were administered
or you're partaking in choosing to use
them and that's okay because you know
that's what you're doing any residue
from those drugs and pharmaceuticals is
in your liver it's in your body it's in
your bloodstream it's in your brain for
years to come but what about the drugs
and pharmaceuticals you're unaware of
what about the ones we collect
throughout our life in the ways we've
talked about what about the ones that
enter us without our permission without
our intentions without our own free will
we didn't have a choice they just
entered us they invaded us and our body
cries for help along the way we develop
symptoms and conditions from so many
different things that our body is
exposed to but this is just one of those
very things our body ends up
battling but we can turn it all around
we can give our bodies what they need we
can assist we can be our body's greatest
advocate original published medical
medium information gets stolen and
poached by podcast doctors social media
doctors influencers and medical clinics
medical medium information has never yet
been proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not manmade it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion