The Following episode is part of a
series dedicated to exposing an
organized hateful group that has been on
a Relentless pursuit to destroy the
medical medium community and that has
been attacking bullying harassing and
preying upon the chronically ill joining
me in the series is a guest named Amber
bakaro she's an alternative medicine
practitioner who became a whistleblower
after she witnessed this hateful group
in action when they tried to recruit her
to join them last year Amber caught the
main members of this group on legally
recorded calls describing their
premeditated multi-step plan to create a
quote postm medal medium era by feeding
false stories and claims about me and
about medical medium information to
Major media outlets in hopes that it
would lead to securing themselves a deal
for an anti-ed medium documentary on
Netflix that would bring Fame and other
benefits to them now known infamously
instead for their malicious plot that
was caught on recording and exposed we
refer to this hateful group as the
plotters their entire smear campaign is
spearheaded by one woman who comes from
an extremely wealthy family didn't get
what she wanted from me years ago and is
now seeking re Revenge she's made it her
mission to gather a bunch of plotters
with ulterior motives and AES to grind
including competitors in the health
industry to try to frame medical medium
and take down the community what this
organized hateful group has done is
unprecedented it's one of the biggest
scandals that's ever happened in the
health industry as you'll see it's also
one of the biggest instances of
capturing corruption within the
mainstream media so prepare yourself for
lots of details and nuances as we are
going to be thoroughly untangling the
massive Web of Lies they have spun and
we're going to be releasing a lot of
disturbing new information new
recordings and mind-blowing evidence of
just how far they are going to lie to
try to get what they want some of the
evidence we're presenting in these
episodes in includes original written
content such as text messages social
media posts that have been produced by
the plots and will be reenacted for
greater ease in following along those
who are listening along to the podcast
can find video versions of these
episodes on the medical medium YouTube
and Rumble channels that will be
displaying screenshots photos videos and
more some of you may be unaware that
this has even been happening but many of
you have been tremendously injured and
harmed by what they have done the record
needs to be set straight and they need
to be called out for what they've done
and are still doing the medical medium
Community does not deserve to be
attacked like this and we are going to
set the record straight as many times as
we need to
[Music]
all along Ashley Foster has had ulterior
motives all along Ashley Foster has been
wrong all along Ashley Foster has been
lying Ashley's original story about
Stephanie included the claim that
Anthony never told Stephanie to see a
doctor we've proven that wrong with
evidence even before we released the
evidence Ashley was publicly corrected
on this claim Years Ago by the husband
of one of Stephanie's friends friends
this husband was actually around for
what happened with Stephanie while
Ashley was not after being publicly
corrected Ashley pivoted and moved
forward with a new manufactured story
line the new Stephanie story became well
okay he told her to go to the doctor I
guess but it wasn't until the end after
it was too late we've proven that wrong
with evidence Ashley claimed that
Stephanie discovered her breast lump
while she was staying nights with Ashley
in
2016 we've proven that wrong with
evidence Stephanie did not develop the
breast lump until a whole year later in
2017 Ashley then claimed that Anthony in
2016 had told Stephanie that her breast
lump would never become cancerous we've
proven that very wrong with evidence
that is not possible because the breast
lump that was discovered in 2017 did not
exist in 2016 Ashley's story was
artificial
Ashley also claimed that Anthony told
Stephanie that she had hurt her back in
yoga but that Stephanie told Ashley that
she didn't remember hurting it in yoga
we've proven that wrong with evidence
Ashley said that Anthony's message to
Stephanie was to just lie still on the
floor we've proven that wrong with
evidence Ashley claimed that Stephanie
had done everything Anthony ever told
her to do we've proven that wrong with
evidence that's seven major falsities
that Ash was proven wrong on last year
seven major falsities that were designed
to tarnish Anthony's reputation and to
scare people away from applying medical
medium information to heal seven major
falsities that harmed many people's real
lives seven major falsities that Ashley
needs to be held accountable for among
all of the other falsities and lies that
have been produced by her since this is
the false story that Ashley took the
Vanity Fair when the journalist Dan
Adler reached out to me regarding the
hit piece she had him working on I was
sent a list of hundreds of questions the
questions that were asked line up and
coordinate exactly with Ashley's
original false Stephanie story from
2020 we are going to be reading off
those questions in an upcoming episode
Vanity Fair manipulated material and got
so many things wrong in the story they
published and that is going to be
thoroughly exposed in this series but
there 's a reason why even Vanity Fair
would not publish these falsities from
Ashley that Ashley wanted them to the
plots have since expressed dismay with
Vanity Fair by stating that the article
only quote skim the surface the article
is a lie it just isn't as big of a lie
as they wanted it to
be we held back on a lot last time
around with these podcast to give Ashley
an opportunity to do the right thing and
at the very least just stop lying and
spreading
misinformation not only has Ashley not
taken any accountability for the major
falsity she's been proven wrong on but
rather she has since continued on with
her deranged plot she's pivoted she's
created new false narratives and she's
manufactured and spread an unimaginable
number of New Lies I suspect that
another motive of Ashley's now is to try
to cover her tracks because we exposed
in a large scale that her original story
about Stephanie was fabricated and that
she was lying from the very beginning we
have also only just begun to publicize
the evidence of the true corruption that
took place in the process of Ashley and
the other plotters pushing their false
storyline onto Vanity Fair having to
hammer it into the head of the
journalist and having to threaten him to
get him to publish it yes you heard that
right if you're new to the series it's
all on recorded calls and there's a lot
more that's coming Ashley probably feels
like she has to keep going and trying to
come up with more lies and stories and
trying to drum up fake controversy to
keep up the facade so that she doesn't
look like the liar that she is but being
dishonest and manipulative can only ever
get you so far we are going to be
exposing all of it it's all coming out
now Ashley's pattern is that when she
gets proven wrong she pivots to other
topics and she deflects it's a tactic
meant to distract everyone who's
listening to her by throwing more
seemingly inflammatory false information
about Anthony at them to divert their
attention away from the fact that their
leader Ashley was proven wrong and is
lying so I implore anyone who's left out
there still taking Ashley seriously in
any way to ask themselves this if Ashley
is so principled about honesty and the
truth as she so claims then why hasn't
she addressed any one of these seven
major things that she spread online that
she brought to the media and that she
got so blatantly and provably wrong I
will let you sit with
that one of Ashley's true obsessions is
repeatedly declaring how perfectly
honest and morally Superior she is at
the same time as she incessantly calls
Anthony a liar sometimes multiple times
per day it seems like Ashley thinks if
she just repeats the words and accuses
him enough times that people will submit
and believe her regardless of how much
the substance of her arguments either
makes no sense at all or is just
verifiably wrong that is the definition
of true brainwashing and
indoctrination after our podcast came
out that exposed her and the other
individuals involved with this plot
using their own words on recording
Ashley really ramped up this behavior
for example on April 20th of 2023 Ashley
changed her Instagram bio to
read in case anyone comes looking for
information about mm/ Amber
frauds and
Liars of course she now attacks and
targets me as well because I am the one
who exposed her and her friends using
their own words on recordings around the
same time Ashley posted the following
comment and then deleted it along with
the post that was attached to it shortly
after
period I will die on this hill if
someone literally pointed a gun at me
and ask me to say something other than
the truth I am telling I would not do it
if I don't have my Integrity I have
nothing when asked by a commenter do you
seriously believe your own
Ashley
replied I believe fully in the truth of
what I'm saying
yes and on May 5th of 2023 Ashley posted
this
when Anthony started spewing more of his
dark lies on his wacky and idiotic
podcast because of the impending Vanity
Fair article I realized just how
confused and lost people would
be Ashley has yet to produce a single
piece of legitimate evidence that
Anthony or I have lied about a single
thing she's only just continued to spin
ridiculous false stories get things
wrong spread ridiculous rumors and other
plotters who might think that they've
got something with posts on social media
they are very wrong and that will all be
exposed in due time meanwhile Ashley and
her hateful group continue to ignore the
fact that Ashley was proven wrong on
these seven major falsities and more
with evidence after the podcast came out
last year Ashley went on a whole Rampage
about lying as she tried to deflect
attention away from that in that Rampage
Ashley used a well-known true story
about the experiences of a family that
saved the lives of an estimated 800 Jews
and other refugees during the Holocaust
Ashley used the story to try to make a
ludicrous point about lying and in the
process of doing so Ashley ironically
got no less than 18 facts wrong she
expressed extremely offensive viewpoints
regarding the Holocaust she disgraced
the names of honorary women who risked
their lives to save others during World
War II and Ashley provided a perfect
example that every everyone can verify
of just How Deeply she manipulates
butchers and twists the story she tells
to serve her own agenda we are going to
read off what Ashley posted and then I'm
going to unpack all of the 18 things
that she got wrong one by one almost
every single sentence of Ashley's entire
series is wrong in some way the story of
the ten booom family was recounted in a
book called The Hiding Place written by
Corey tboom I read it cover to cover my
myself and anyone out there can use this
book to independently fact check
Ashley's false information for
themselves I encourage you to do so for
context here's some background on the
ten booom family from the official
website of the museum dedicated to
preserving its historical Legacy it says
during the second world war the tboom
home became a refuge a hiding place for
fugitives and those hunted by the Nazis
by protecting these people Casper and
his daughters Betsy and Corey risked
their lives this non-violent resistance
against the Nazi oppressors was the ten
boom's way of living out their Christian
faith during 1943 and into 1944 there
were usually five to six people
illegally living in the tboom home some
of whom were Jews and other members of
the Dutch underground additional
refugees would stay with the ten Booms
for a few hours or a few days until
another safe house could be located for
them through these activities the ten
booom family and their many friends and
co-workers of the B group saved the
lives of an estimated 800 Jews and other
refugees in July of last year Ashley
posted the following
series okay question do you believe that
sometimes lying to them is in people's
best
interest I am a lying is never the right
choice person no matter what I want to
share the story that convicted me of
this Betsy 10 boom was personally
convicted about honesty she and her
family including Corey T boom hid juice
in their house throughout World War II
and were eventually arrested Betsy died
in vve Brook concentration
camp okay already we have falsity number
one it was Betsy's sister nollie and
nollie's daughter cocky who were
convicted about honesty and struggled
with the concept of telling lies in
order to save Jewish life not Betsy
Betsy was clear in her stance that under
the circumstances of the Nazi regime it
was the right thing to do to lie when
necessary for the purposes of saving
innocent lives Ashley also got the name
of the Concentration Camp wrong it's
Raven's Brook not Rave Brook she
continues her sister Corey recounted a
story of Betsy's
honesty falsity number two again it was
not Betsy who was convicted about
honesty it was nollie and nollie's
daughter cocky and we've got falsity
number three here what Ashley is
referring to is not a singular story as
we go through the next several posts
you'll see that Ashley incorrectly
conflated multiple stories of separate
instances once when German soldiers came
to search the house there was not time
for the Jews staying with them at that
time to fully hide so they hid onto the
kitchen
table we've got falsity number four the
incident involving the kitchen table in
fact occurred when there was a ria a ria
was a hostile raid during which the
Germans would come to forcibly enlist
young males in Holland to work in
Munitions factories the tboom family had
the young men in in their household hide
in a cellar with a trapo underneath the
kitchen table we've got falsity number
five the target of this raid was not
Jews to be placed in concentration camps
it was Dutch boys like Corey's nephews
that the Nazis wanted to enlist to work
in
factories and falsity number six during
the Razia Cory's nephews did not hide
underneath the table because they didn't
have enough time to quote fully hide
there was actually a Cellar underneath
the kitchen table that had been
specifically designed for hiding from
Nazi soldiers and other threats The
Cellar under the table is exactly where
the boys intended to
go a German soldier asked Betsy directly
are there any Jews hiding in this
house falsity number seven this is not
the question that was asked in fact the
German Soldier asked where are your
brothers do you have brothers how old
are they where are they now again in
this incident the soldiers were looking
for Dutch boys not Jews and falsity
number eight it was not Betsy who the
soldiers questioned it was cocky Betsy's
niece she said yes they are under the
kitchen
table falsity number nine this is not
what happened cocky not Betsy at first
tried to avoid the question next when
pressured cocky tells the soldiers that
two of her brothers were under the table
but then cocky burst out laughing which
tricked them the Nazis thought that she
was joking they got upset and they left
the soldiers did not capture any of the
boys her sister Corey was horrified and
crushed the couple was arrested and
taken away to a concentration camp Betsy
held fast to her
conviction this post unbelievably has
four falsities in one falsity number 10
this is where Ashley began conflating
different incidents there was a
different event separate from the
kitchen table story in which one
individual woman not a couple was taken
away to the old Jewish theater in
Amsterdam the theater was a holding
place from which Jews could be
transported to concentration camps it
was not a concentration camp
itself falsity number 11 even in this
other incident that occurred at a
completely different time than the
kitchen table Story the Jewish woman who
was captured Analise was never taken to
a concentration camp falsity number 12
Corey was not horrified nor crushed by
the kitchen table incident the kitchen
table incident in fact made Corey start
to question the logic of nollie and her
daughter cocky who nearly gave her
brothers up to the Nazis Corey was
horrified and crushed by the theater
incident that resulted in Analise being
captured by by the Nazis which happened
later
on falsity number 13 it was not Betsy
who held fast to her conviction it was
nollie and it was in a completely
different
incident less than a week later the
Concentration Camp those Jews were taken
to was liberated by Allied Forces and
everyone there was transported to
Freedom including the couple that had
been in hiding
and this one post from Ashley shockingly
has five falsities in it falsity number
14 the kitchen table incident was
further than a week apart from this
event Ashley conflated different
incidents and got the timeline wrong
falsity number 15 in the other story
involving Analise it was not a
concentration camp that got liberated an
aisee was being held in the old Jewish
theater and the theater was broken into
falsity number 16 the book does not
specify that the theater was broken into
by Allied Forces falsity number 17 not
everyone in the theater was transported
to Freedom only 40 Jews were rescued and
it was not a concentration camp that
they were coming
from and falsity number 18 Analise was
part of those 40 rescued Jews but she
was not part of a couple like Ashley
said it is not our job to control the
outcome of our action ctions it is not
our job to decide how and when the truth
should be known we either believe in the
immutable importance of it or we don't
period here Ashley concludes her
mutilated version of this story by
asserting her ridiculous Viewpoint that
anyone who lied to the Nazis to protect
and save the lives of Jews during the
Holocaust was morally wrong following
her as
logic Ashley is saying that she believes
everyone should have been honest with
the Nazi soldiers even if it led to more
Jews being Mass
murdered Ashley declares that one should
not be concerned with the consequences
of their actions even in the context of
the holocost and even if their actions
Ena
genocide truly
unbelievable people who lie are liars if
you're willing to lie about one thing
you might be willing to lie about
everything One Lie calls into question
the entirety of someone's
character what about 2 three 4 100
lies I mean how much more ironic could
this possibly be Ashley Foster told 18
falsities 18 falsities in a story she
tried to use to make an absurd point
about lying this series was all about
Ashley's Doctrine on always being honest
which Ashley claims she aderes to
perfectly and she's literally violating
that in the very story she used to try
to make that
point and then here Ashley even went as
far as to use derogatory terms to refer
to what the tboom family heroically did
to protect and save the lives of 800
innocent people from being murdered if
the members of the tboom family did not
lie to the Nazi oppressors who were
committing atrocities those 800 Jews
would have died and Ashley has the
audacity to call into question the
entirety of the ten booom family's
character who cares if people are being
tortured abused and murdered it's not
your job to worry at all about the
consequences of your actions what's
important according to Ashley is that
you try to prove your own superiority
like she's trying to do with this warped
story that she
invented this is not about promoting
lying it's about having sanity Ashley
could have used anything any other story
or anecdote or something else to express
herself and make the claim that she
doesn't believe in lying but to use this
story in this way let alone distorting
it with 18 falsities in the process to
say that when faced with Nazis asking
about Jews hiding in your home during
the Holocaust knowing that they are
going to be taken to a concentration
camp Ashley saying that she would give
up the Jews it's a window into how
Ashley thinks this is what we're dealing
with who in their right mind thinks like
this Ashley's entire false story about
Stephanie was built on her original
claim I never told Stephanie to see a
doctor and not once did Ashley ever
reach out to me or call me up and say
hey what's up did you tell Stephanie to
see a doctor but because she lied she
had a save face and stay with the LIE
and that takes a certain kind of person
a person who doesn't want to admit a
huge mistake a person who doesn't want
to come clean and keeps going making
more huge false claims lies and mistakes
if anyone wants a window into Ashley's
mind it's this Holocaust story tell
dozens and dozens of lies and falsities
and then say how one should never tell a
lie so much so that it's best to just
call out the Jews hiding underneath the
table to the Nazis you have the daughter
of a billionaire family that lies and
tells falsities and she's using this
false story about the Holocaust to try
to give you permission to not care about
the consequences of your actions this is
the entitlement of Ashley who doesn't
care about who gets harmed by a false
story she just wants her documentary she
doesn't care who's in the way
when Ashley's business proposals got
turned down by Anthony and her big
career dreams didn't work out the way
that she wanted them to Ashley set out
on this mission to tear Anthony down to
constantly take stabs at him to try to
blast him in the media to attack him to
put him and the entire medical medium
Community down to be little and demean
them to try to make them feel small and
there is no low that she will not stoop
to in her
Pursuit what makes Ashley serious on
lying even more of an absolute farce is
the fact that Ashley Gravely missed the
mark on what the actual ten booom story
portrays about lying which is very
different from the story that Ashley
seems to have made up in her head Betsy
and Cory ten booom took on the role of
protecting and saving Jews they are the
heroes of the story their sister nollie
and nollie's daughter cocky are the ones
who were struggling with the concept of
lying not Betsy whom Ashley confused
them with throughout the story nollie's
family pointed out nollie's illogic
nollie was still doing lies with her
actions even if she wouldn't tell lies
from her lips with words and nalo taught
her daughter to think in the same
illogical
way for example to nollie as well as
cocky it was okay to partake in creating
the hiding place in the cellar under the
kitchen table for her sons to deceive
and hide from German soldiers in but
when the soldiers asked cocky a question
she felt that she must tell the truth
from her lips even though it nearly
harmed her own brothers and then cocky
also burst out laughing during this
incident which made it seem like she was
joking about the boys being under the
table and that was not truthful it was
an inconsistency that was directly
addressed in the book itself such as in
the following excerpt written by Corey
tboom it says it was a strange dinner
party that evening veering as it did
from heartfelt Thanksgiving to the
nearest thing to a bitter argument our
close-nit family has ever had nollie
stuck by cocky insisting she would have
answer the same way God honors truth
telling with Perfect protection Peter
and Bob from the Viewpoint of the trapo
weren't so sure and neither was I I
could spot the illogic and it isn't
logical to say the truth and do a lie
what about analise's false papers and
that maid's uniform on Katrine
nonetheless Ashley goes on to end her
depraved series with the following
quote choose your Leaders with wisdom
and
forethought to be led by a liar is to
ask to be told lies Octavia E
Butler 18 falsities later and on top of
the repulsive spin she put on a
holocaust story Ashley also disrespected
the names of true heroes but ET and Cory
tboom were incredible honorable
leaders by demonizing the decisions
these women made under entirely evil
circumstances in order to save hundreds
of people's lives Ashley utterly
disgraces the ten booom Legacy and all
of those who fought the absolutely
reprehensible acts of the Nazi regime
including the 6 million Jews who
perished during the
Holocaust and then of course what
Ashley's inferring with all of this is
that I'm a liar and that she's not she's
saying that she's such an honest person
she wouldn't even lie to protect a Jew
during the Holocaust while she's telling
a story herself with 18 falsities in
it this is Ashley's pattern she accuses
people of what she's actually doing
Ashley lies Ashley tells false stories
Ashley's version of The Hiding Place
story had 18 falsities in it in Ashley's
March 6th 2020 Instagram post about
Stephanie there were more than 15
falsities in the comment section of
Ashley's March 6th 2020 Instagram post
about Stephanie Ashley told more than 15
additional
falsities in Ashley's March 7th 2020
blog post about Stephanie there were
more than 20
falsities in the comment section of
Ashley's February 11th 2020 Instagram
post about Stephanie Ashley told more
than 10 falsities
in just these few instances alone Ashley
told a total of 78 verifiable lies and
falsities for someone who supposedly
feels so strongly about the truth that
she believes it's not even right to lie
to save a Jew's life during the
Holocaust for someone who claimed that
they are a lying is never the right
choice person no matter what that's a
lot of
falsities I am a lying is never the
right choice person no matter
what a lying is never the right choice
person no matter what H but wait a
second in addition to the immeasurable
number of falsities and flat out lies
Ashley has continued to spew in the last
year like saying that her family doesn't
have a private jet or vacation homes
when they do and that she's never made
money off of Instagram when she has
Ashley also has a document Ed record of
instructing other people to lie and be
dishonest for her in fact I am one of
those people in my calls with the
plotters last year after they had
explained their plan to smear Anthony
and try to create a postmed medium era
Ashley said this to
me
so I'm just grateful that you that
you're on that on that you're exploring
that now and and I hope that you'll
honor Robbie and Taylor's confidence
by by um by not sharing
with oh anything with Anthony until it's
the right time it's a little bit of a
it's a little bit of a d Dynamite like a
loaded situation right
now and Taylor said this to me as
well yeah I want to make sure you would
tell
Anthony can we hear that again I want to
make sure you would tell
Anthony I wanted to make sure you
wouldn't tell Anthony the plotters and
Ashley specifically wanted me to keep
everything they told me a secret from
Anthony if Anthony had reached out and
asked me what was going on Ashley's
expectation was that I was supposed to
lie to him Ashley apparently believes
it's never the right choice to lie not
under any circumstance no matter what
but not even to save people's lives
during the
Holocaust except when Ashley wanted me
to lie for the benefit of her and her
friends that was somehow
okay on July 16th of 2018 a friend
texted Ashley and said by the way a pure
encapsulations order I placed went
missing and they are calling me but just
in case they accidentally call your
number that's why haha and Ashley
replied okay just tell them I plac the
order for you because I'm not supposed
to let people use my account
LOL so here Ashley is letting a friend
use her supplement purchasing account
and she's acknowledging that she's not
supposed to this is what Corey and Betsy
tboom from The Hiding Place story that
Ashley referenced would call doing a lie
then Ashley's also instructing her
friend in this text to lie about who
placed her supplement order as her
actions make very clear Ashley said she
is a lying is never the right choice
type of person only because that suited
her Narrative of the moment as that is
obviously not something Ashley actually
believes in or lives
by again we're not arguing for or
against the morality of lying here I'm
simply pointing out the absolutely
unhinged contradictions in Ashley's own
thinking writing speech and
behavior since the beginning of Ashley's
mission to smear Anthony Ashley has
attempted to shield and cover for her
falsities by saying that she's just
sharing her truth she's also tried to
infer credibility based on her purported
direct experience with Stephanie for a
short period of time in the comment
section of a post Ashley made on
February 11th of 20120 she said
this the reason I chose to share exactly
what I did about her story is because I
was there for that small part and
physically present with her so I felt
like something I could share
truthfully in this comment Ashley is
referring to the false timeline that she
also repeated later on in 2020 in which
Ashley stated that Stephanie had
discovered her breast lump while
Stephanie was staying with Ashley in
2016 as we've shared many times this is
incorrect the evidence clearly shows
that Stephanie discovered her breast
lump on March 6th of 2017 a whole year
after the timeline of Ashley's fake
story Ashley was not with Stephanie when
Stephanie discovered her breast lump in
2017 as we discussed previously Ashley
admitted that she did not see Stephanie
once during the entire two years that
passed between the time that Stephanie
stayed in Ashley's home in 2016 and the
time that Stephanie passed away in
2018 Ashley did not visit Stephanie
during the time of her injury nor when
Stephanie was in the hospital Ashley's
even admitted that she barely kept in
communication with Stephanie at all
during the time of her injury on March
6th of 2020 she wrote
this stephani I didn't talk often during
her back
injury the truth is that Ashley was not
physically present for any single part
of Stephanie's entire Journey with her
breast lump her back injury her cancer
or her passing so not only is ashly
devoid of facts but the single leg of
credibility she tried to stand on by
saying that she was physically present
for a small portion of what Stephanie
experienced with her breast lump is a
lie after the release of our first four
podcasts in which we presented a large
amount of evidence that disproved
Ashley's false storylines Ashley got a
lot of push back for what she had done
and the falsities she was continuing to
try to spread in response to this push
back Ashley continued to Pedal the I'm
just sharing my truth narrative it's a
tactic to try to evade being held to an
objective standard of the
truth rather than presenting legitimate
facts or evidence Ashley constantly uses
and relies upon someone told me I was
there for it I experienced it personally
or I heard a rumor statements which
cannot be verified and of course can
easily be fabricated and even if it were
a valid pass that she's just sharing her
truth Ashley can't even get her truth
straight in all of Ashley's attempts to
make Anthony medical medium information
look bad she's told numerous stories
multiple times in completely different
contradictory versions that cannot all
be true at the same time here is an
example of a storyline Ashley told four
different versions of on February 11th
of 2020 when Ashley first started
posting false information about what had
happened to Stephanie she got a
commenter who said I find this very hard
to believe and Ashley
replied that's okay okay I understand I
worked really hard while writing this to
make sure everything I wrote was
absolutely true and not opinion the
truth is she was a close friend of his
for several years and had followed his
protocol more exactly than anyone else
I've ever met for that entire
time in this version Ashley's saying
that from her own perspective she
observed that Stephanie followed
Anthony's protocol more exactly than
anyone else she's ever met for that
entire
time those who actually understand
medical medium information know that
there is no one medical medium protocol
anyway so this is a problematic
statement in and of itself but then in
the second version of this same
statement Ashley says something similar
but adds to it on March 6th of 2020
Ashley posted
this and allow me to be clear I have
never met to this day anyone who
followed Anthony's advice more closely
than Steph not even Anthony
himself she told this version now with
the addition of not even Anthony himself
in at least two different places which
is ridiculous because Ashley had no idea
what Anthony was eating or not eating as
they were not nearly as close as she
constantly tries to portray it to be in
the third version from May 5th of last
year she says something
different also I don't want to be rude
but you're patently wrong some of us
here have studied and applied his
information more carefully than even
Anthony himself that's something he told
Steph
once so now instead of Ashley making the
statement about Stephanie like she did
in the previous two versions she's
changed the subject of the story to some
of us here have applied the information
better than Anthony
himself Stephanie passed away in 2018
and again Ashley posted this version
last year
2023 does she mean by some of us here
that her and her co- plotters have
followed and applied medical medium
information better than Anthony that's
laughable and instead of this being an
observation from her own perspective
like it was in the previous two versions
Ashley's changed it to this is something
Anthony told Stephanie
once in the fourth version Ashley says
this remember when Anthony claimed Steph
didn't follow his protocols well enough
what a lie from the pit of Hell Anthony
told me personally one time that Steph
followed his protocols even better than
he
Dead first of all because Ashley
literally gets everything wrong I have
to clear this up Anthony has never said
that Stephanie didn't follow his
protocols well enough absolutely never
said it in previous podcast episodes we
simply debunked Ashley's falsity that
Stephanie had followed medical medium
information to a te we used multiple
pieces of evidence to show that
Stephanie factually did not follow it to
a te there was no implication made that
Stephanie should have done anything
better or differently in fact we played
an audio message from Stephanie in which
she had said that she knew that Anthony
wasn't a fan of the Dr Morse grape fast
that Stephanie said she was quote hooked
on doing but that she was doing them
anyway and that Anthony was not pushing
her to do medical medium instead anyone
can go back and listen to our previous
episodes to verify that Stephanie
partook in lots of different modalities
and health approaches at times I would
say this is fine or that is fine because
Stephanie was on her own path doing her
own raw food thing and as she said in
the audio she was already hooked on
certain things so I was supportive of
Stephanie doing what she wanted to do I
did not control Stephanie's decisions or
even try to instead I supported her in
any decision she made with things that
spoke to her even if it wasn't medical
medium they're trying to punish me for
not controlling Stephanie's wishes and
health choices and then they're also
trying to punish me and blame me for
supposedly controlling them this is very
abusive behavior on their
part Ashley said that Anthony's claim
was a lie from the pit of Hell when
Ashley fully made up the claim he never
said it what we did share on the podcast
was hard evidence from Stephanie herself
far from a lie and Ashley saying all of
this at the same time as she herself is
telling an actual lie as part of a story
she told four different contradictory
versions of in this fourth version of
the same story from Ashley about what
Stephanie was eating and doing instead
of the statement being an observation
from Ashley's own perspective or
something Anthony told Stephanie once
like Ashley said previously now she's
changed it to Anthony told Ashley that
Stephanie followed his protocols even
better than he did so which is it all of
these four story versions contradict
themselves and they cannot all be true
at the same time that is because Ashley
is lying and she can't even keep her own
madeup story
straight Ashley did not know what I was
eating I didn't speak to Ashley about
how I ate I didn't tell Ashley that
Stephanie ate better than me I never
talked to Ashley about Stephanie at all
so it's not even possible I never told
Stephanie that Stephanie eats better
than me Ashley's just fabricating
stories
again furthermore Ashley has admitted
that she isn't really that versed in
medical medium information in a live
stream she did in 2020 she said
this all right will I read his new book
I honestly haven't read like the last
three probably if I'm being really
honest
she honestly hasn't read like the last
three books this was in 2020 in
reference to when the cleanse to heal
book was coming out so it was before
medical medium revised and expanded and
it was also before the brains saer books
that means Ashley basically only
supposedly read the first two out of
what's now nine books Ashley didn't read
thyroid healing Liver Rescue celery
juice cleanse to heal medical medium
revised brainsaver 1 or brain saver 2
Ashley has hardly read any medical
medium material and it shows which makes
her far from an expert on medical medium
information so how would Ashley know
that Stephanie was following medical
medium information to the letter or not
if Ashley doesn't even know medical
medium
information what's even more insane is
that there are more examples of Ashley
telling multiple completely different
contradictory versions of the same story
the one I'm going to unpack now is one
that Ashley has told nine different
versions of would you trust someone who
has nine different versions of the same
story about something this one is jam
packed with falsities and fiction so
bear with us as we unload this pile of
crap onto the public this is the
infamous cat
story Ashley's son was sick with a skin
condition in 2018 he was a baby at the
time and Ashley sought Anthony's help
with it in 2019 a year later Ashley
started publicly telling fake stories
about this experience she's changed and
adapted the story more and more with
time in 2020 right after Ashley came out
with her false story about Stephanie
Ashley did a live stream and said that
Anthony had gotten it wrong with her son
because Anthony missed the fact that it
was really a cat allergy that was behind
his eczema
outbreak this is a story that Ashley
told me on my recorded calls with her as
she was trying to convince me that is a
liar it's a story that I later found out
has been used many many times by Ashley
to intentionally try to break people's
trust and confidence in Anthony and in
medical medium
information most people who have turned
against Anthony have heard it it's a
story that Ashley is still telling to
this day it's the cat story the cat
story so as the real cat story was
actually happening in real time in 2018
there is is a documented record of
Ashley telling the story correctly and
consistently to four different people
when Ashley's son was actively dealing
with his eczema outbreak Ashley texted
with Anthony Anthony's wife and two
different friends about what was
happening I have all the texts and these
four truthful versions serve as a record
for contrasting with all of the
fabricated versions that Ashley has told
since now since 2019 Ashley has told
five false versions of the cat story
that we are aware of and who knows how
many other versions she's told that we
haven't seen not only are these five
versions false contradictory and
different from the four truthful
versions of the cat story from when it
was happening in
2018 but they're also each different
from each other and they contradict one
another I'm going to first play one
rendition of Ashley's fake version of
the cat story which was told during her
April 1st 2020 live stream we are
redacting the name of Ashley's son for
his privacy so every time you hear a
bleep throughout the series it's someone
saying Ashley's son's name or in one
instance the name of another one of
Ashley's
children in regards to it's interesting
I feel like it's another thing that just
stood out to me as concerning um when
got really bad eczema of course Anthony
and I were really close and I had
followed medical medium approach during
pregnancy and so it was like holy cow
what is going on of course I called
Anthony about it and um we talked he
changed my diet a lot uh well not a lot
but he was very clear about like you
need to cut out almost all fat except
avocado from your diet I was doing like
more of the cashews and the nuts and
seeds and stuff
um and so I did I I took that out of my
diet and
um and slowly started to get a little
bit better over the course of the next 6
months until he finally healed but the
actual turning point in his healing came
when we went to Hawaii and realized that
he was severely allergic to cats cuz he
was doing really well and then we
changed airbnbs to an Airbnb where there
was a cat and he started breaking out in
eczema again like the following morning
just like full body
hives um and so we realized oh he has a
cat
allergy um and that was causing like the
bulk of the problem and so I just find
it curious that in talking to Anthony
like why wouldn't he have mentioned like
yes you can make all these dietary
changes but also the fact that you got a
cat four weeks ago is probably the real
problem so Ashley was breastfeeding her
baby during this time and what she was
eating had the ability to impact her son
through her breast milk Ashley is saying
here that she was doing nuts and seeds
and that Anthony had told her to cut out
almost all fat except avocado she's
saying that when she did that her son's
eczema started to improve gradually
until it healed completely but that she
on her own realized that the actual
turning point was when they were in an
Airbnb in Hawaii with a cat in it and
her baby broke out in eczema again
Ashley is saying that she realized that
he was reacting due to a cat allergy
that Anthony had
missed sounds convincing right if Ashley
had reached out to you on Instagram like
she's doing to many people tried to
recruit you into her hateful group and
told you the story what would you think
why didn't Anthony catch that it was a
cat allergy he's supposed to be able to
do that he should have known that it was
a cat allergy he's obviously not who he
says he is well here's the real story of
what actually happened from Anthony's
text thread we know that Ashley baby
started having an eczema Outbreak on
June 19th of
2018 and then there's a text thread
between Ashley and a friend from when
her son was dealing with his eczema in
real time on June 28th of 2018 the
friend texted Ashley and said hey honey
how are you how's the rash Ashley
replied hey BB doing good here gearing
up to head to Dallas tomorrow it's still
pretty bad but but not getting worse I
think it's actually starting to scab
up the friend said a poor little Dallas
will hopefully be
nice Ashley sent a photo of her baby's
eczema and said
this I talked to Aunt and he said it's
most likely the
cat okay we have to pause here this is
the Smoking Gun Ashley texted her friend
saying Anthony told her it's most likely
the cat whereas in the 2020 version of
the story Ashley said she herself
discovered that the cat was causing her
baby skin problems and that Anthony had
missed it here it is again the 2020
version um and so we realized oh he has
a cat
allergy um and that was causing like the
bulk of the problem and so I just find
it curious that in talking Anthony like
why wouldn't he have mentioned like yes
you can make all these dietary changes
but also the fact that you got a cat
four weeks ago is probably the real
problem versus what actually happened
according to Ashley's own text messages
from
2018 I talked to Aunt and he said it's
most likely the
cat Ashley Foster is a liar
there you have it right out of the
horse's mouth Ashley's own words proving
that she
lied now we can
continue I talked to Aunt and he said
it's most likely the cat cat has been
gone 4 days but I'm sure there's still a
lot here so Dallas might actually help
it heal up further well I mean liver
issues but the cat as you know
the friend said a the poor baby so did
you give the cat away or just having a
break from it and Ashley
replied we gave it to our friends who
wanted it really badly I really love
having a pet around but they create so
much mess and our home just feels so
clean
now Ashley Sayang in these text messages
that Anthony told her that her son's
eczema outbreak was due to liver issues
plus the cat Ashley also says that they
gave the cat away on June 24th of 2018
this is 4 months before the Hawaii
Retreat remember that in the fake story
she told in 2020 Ashley said it wasn't
until the Hawaii Retreat that she
realized that cats affected her son's
skin condition but in reality Ashley had
already given their pet cat away 4
months before the Hawaii Retreat even
took place
again Ashley Foster is a
liar then on July 14th of 2018 Ashley
texted the same
friend poor little is so bad it's
breaking my heart anything I can do I'm
drinking celery juice nettle tea off all
green and oil and very low fat is
getting little sips of celery juice too
I'm taking zinc and vitamin C in high
quantities the friend said poor baby is
this worse than he was at the
start h no it was worse at one
point the friend asks it's been ebbing
and flowing then or just gotten a little
better and not gone up and
down Ashley says that's sort of what
it's done
the friend replies well that's normal
for a rash at least a bad one anyway it
could still just be that his immune
system is weakened still from the cat
and the allergic reaction and it will
get better soon if it's not worse right
now that's a good sign are you drinking
a lot of OJ and Ashley
says no yeah it isn't continuing to get
worse at
least just slower to Cal down than I
thought
Anthony had told Ashley already that the
cat was a trigger for her son and Ashley
had gotten rid of the cat nearly a month
prior to this
conversation as you can see everyone
Ashley spoke to was well aware that the
cat was a trigger because as Ashley said
in her own text messages that was
something Anthony had told her from the
beginning on August 15th of 2018 the
same friend asked how and Ashley replied
he's not great pal but I'm trying to be
patient we're having our whole house
cleaned top to bottom this weekend
including all furniture in our HVAC
system it still hasn't been as bad as at
its
worst the friend says a poor little
guy keep the date that Ashley got her
house and HVAC system cleaned in mind
for later August
15th in Aver ation that took place a
month later on September 19th of 2018
Ashley says
this still dealing with skin but I spoke
with Aunt and he got us on the right
track I think we'll be through it in the
next few weeks I was having very little
fat like maybe one tablespoon of cashews
a day but it turns out it's not the fat
itself it's the nuts he actually said
like olive oil would be better than
cashews in terms of helping heal so I
got completely off and he not seeds he
seems like he's starting to come through
it so now we're getting into what was
happening with the fats the friend
responded I'm thrilled about yippe keep
me posted on his continued healing been
praying for him next we're going to read
off a series of texts Ashley sent to a
different friend also in mid-september
of 2018
telling the true story consistent with
the last text thread we just read off of
what Ashley had discussed with Anthony
about her son
skin nothing crazy but he set to give a
little vitamin c 200 milligrams per day
and that I shouldn't be eating any nuts
or seeds he actually said olive oil is
fine but no nuts or seeds because of the
Arginine and then he said lots of squash
and green juices for
[Music]
me if you remember in the fabricated cat
story Ashley told in 2020 Ashley said
the real turning point was when she
realized her son had a cat allergy while
they were in Hawaii with a cat in their
Airbnb in the real story of what
actually happened the true turning point
was when Ashley listened to Anthony's
guidance to cut out nuts and seeds when
she realized it was not the fat that was
the problem it was the nuts and seeds
specifically when Ashley cut those out
as she said in her own words her son
started to turn the corner and get
better and then from October 15th
through October 21st of 2018 Ashley
hosted a retreat in Hawaii this is the
retreat that took place right before
Stephanie passed away I've spoken to
individuals who were at this Retreat one
of them shared with me first of all that
there was not a cat in any of Ashley's
air bnbs only an outdoor cat around one
of the airbnbs that was not allowed
inside this person also shared with us
that at the retreat Ashley started
eating nuts again and that is the real
reason why her son's skin flared up
again I have a copy of the menu Ashley
created for the retreat and it has nuts
in at least one of the meals for almost
every single day of the
retreat here are some examples from the
menu we've got a chopped salad with
Branch dressing which included Vil and
cashew nuts a taco bar with cashew cream
which is basically all cashew there was
a cashew curry sauce which is basically
all cashew as well there was a pasta
with cashew butter in the sauce There
was a macadamia nut parmesan which is
basically entirely made from macadamia
nuts there were potato pancakes with a
roasted garlic cream sauce which is
basically all cashew again there was a
pad tie with almond butter in it there
were sweet potato fries with a Sal
lantro lime Crea which is basically all
cashew there was a horseradish sauce
which included a lot of cashews there
was also an option for almond butter
sauce on Collard wraps this was a menu
again that Ashley created herself and
there are individuals who witnessed
Ashley eating these dishes with nuts
throughout the course of the
retreat when Ashley returned from The
Retreat she got off of nuts and seeds
again and that is when her son's eczema
cleared up for good
again there are
witnesses it is not possible that
Ashley's son was still being affected by
their household cat around the time of
the October Retreat like Ashley said in
her fabricated 2020 version of the cat
story I'm going to walk through the
facts of the timeline Ashley first
texted Anthony's wife when she was
thinking about getting the cat on June
7th of 2018 the text says
this okay we're thinking of taking in
our friends can possible to keep it on a
vegan
diet I have to put out a disclaimer
first that Anthony has shared publicly
that he does not recommend having cats
on a vegan diet and Anthony's wife
expressed this to Ashley at the time
we're just reading this off to show that
Ashley got the cat around this time in
June and then the thread we read
previously included Ashley confirming
that she gave the cat away on June 24th
of 2018 so between the time Ashley was
cons considering taking the cat in on
the 7th and the date she gave it away on
the 24th Ashley only had the cat for a
maximum of 18 days in June June 24th the
day she gave the cat away is 4 months
before Ashley was in Hawaii for her
Retreat this alone makes Ashley's 2020
fake version of the cat story entirely
impossible but the actual turning point
in his human came when we went to Hawaii
and realized that he was severely
allergic to cats cuz he was doing really
well and then we changed airbnbs to an
Airbnb where there was a cat and he
started breaking out an eczema again
like the following morning just like
full body
hives she claimed that she realized her
son was allergic to cats because he was
doing really well at first when they
went to Hawaii in October of 2018
and that it was because he got relief
from the cat that they had at home but
in reality the cat had already been gone
for four
months Ashley had sent this text on June
28th of
2018 CAD has been gone 4 days we gave it
to our friends who wanted it really
badly I really love having a pet around
but they create so much mess and our
home just feels feels so clean
now I will say again that Ashley Foster
is a liar the cat story she told
publicly in 2020 was
fabricated and she went on to tell more
fabricated versions of it keep the facts
and records of what really happened with
Ashley's son his eczema and the cat in
mind as I unpack several other
fictitious cat story versions the facts
are that Anthony did tell Ashley that
the cat was a factor in her son's eczema
he did not get it wrong or miss the cat
allergy Ashley only had the cat for a
maximum of 18 days and got rid of it 4
months before the October Retreat
Anthony only told Ashley to avoid nuts
and seeds specifically her son's skin
started improving when she implemented
that and then his exzema flared up again
in October because Ashley started eating
nuts again at the retreat in Hawaii Ash
as's son's eczema cleared up for good
when Ashley got off of nuts and seeds
again several months after she had
already given the cat away and gotten
her house deep
cleaned when the plotters made their
attempt to recruit me last year on a
call that I legally recorded Ashley was
trying really hard to convince me that
Anthony is a liar and a fraud she told
me a false version of the infamous cat
story that was even more fabricated than
the false version that we just played
from her 2020 live stream I'm going to
go through and actually count the number
of falsities from the cat story she told
me personally on the phone because there
are so
many um I then gave birth to my middle
son and he got like full body eczema
when he was born and I remember asking
Anthony what to do what do I do about
this I was a breastfeeding mom he put me
on a fat-free raw diet um which I Stay
gone for
months we've got falsity number one in
this version she says Anthony put her on
a fat-free diet in previous version she
had said Anthony told her avocado and
olive oil were okay in reality he said
nuts and seeds specifically were the
problem not fats as a whole falsity
number two Ashley added here that he
told her to eat raw food only this is
the only one of nine versions of the cat
story in which she mentioned this and it
is not true in one of the text threads
we just read from Ashley told a friend
while the outbreak was happening in real
time that Anthony had suggested for her
to eat lots of squashes and said that
olive oil was okay I'm positive Anthony
that you did not mean for Ashley to only
consume all of those squashes raw and to
only have olive oil
raw I did not tell Ashley to eat raw or
to eat fat-free for her son's xema
Ashley's flying
again right and we've also got falsity
number three here with Ashley saying
that she stayed raw and fat-free for
months someone I've spoken to who knows
Ashley witnessed her consuming both
cooked food and fats during this time
Ashley only cut out nuts and seeds for
about one month and then at her Retreat
she was eating nuts again as well as
other fats and cooked food even during
the one month that she cut out nuts and
seeds Ashley was still eating other fats
and cooked
food there is a publicly available
YouTube video that was submitted to us
of a vegan get together that took place
on August 14th of 2018 and the video
stars Ashley this is just under two
months after Ashley son broke out with
eczema Ashley is shown in the video with
a salad with avocado and cooked potato
cakes with dollops of cashew aoli cream
and avocado on top sitting next to her
son and you can see his
eczema a witness who was at the
Gathering saw Ashley eating the salad
with avocado and the cooked potato cakes
with cashew aoli cream and avocado on
top cashew aoli cream is very dense and
takes a lot of cashews to make this is
yet another piece of evidence to show
that Ashley's claim of being on a raw
fat-free diet is completely
false during my call with Ashley she
continued
on um and he told me all this different
stuff we had like a billion air
purifiers this is falsity number four
Ashley didn't have air purifiers until
after her son's eczema had cleared up
the air purifiers she got were four
remediation from the Malibu fires they
had nothing to do with the cat or her
son's skin and it was during a different
time period it's a whole other separate
story which we're going to cover later
that Ashley conflated with this false
version of the cat story when she told
it to
me we I was not eating I mean I wasn't
eating anything I was eating fruit and
some
greens falsity number five now Ashley's
down to saying she wasn't even eating
vegetables just fruit and greens that's
how the number two plotter Ashley's
friend Robbie Barbaro eats somehow it's
not restrictive to her when he does
it but there are witnesses who observed
Ashley eating many foods other than
fruit and greens during this time such
as plenty of potatoes and beans in
another version of this story Ashley
said she was eating nuts and seeds up
until a month before the retreat and as
we covered she reintroduced nuts at The
Retreat and at Ashley's Retreat there
were plenty of vegetables on the menu
that she created herself lots of
potatoes radishes yams asparagus carrot
red cabbage and more along with other
foods like coconut ice cream kelp
noodles raw honey maple syrup Wasabi
aerrow root and much more than just
fruit and
greens furthermore in a different
version of the cat story I'm going to
share from Ashley later Ashley says in
her own words that she was eating
vegetables during this
time obviously Ashley's purposely trying
to make it look like Anthony put her on
some kind of extremely restrictive diet
which he did not
by telling these falsities because she
has to convince people somehow that
Anthony's a bad guy or
something and he kept saying like just
keep going he's cleansing his liver is
cleansing my hair was falling out my
nails are
breaking oh the drama there's so much
that's wrong with this part of her fake
story from the false he's just cleansing
narrative to her false Health claims
that we're going to be packing further
in another episode for now I'm just
going to stick to the main falsities
falsity number six here Ashley's
omitting the fact that her son's skin
did clear up after she made the dietary
changes Anthony suggested she's doing
this to make it sound like what Anthony
suggested wasn't working while it was so
restrictive that it was harming her in
reality Ashley took some time to
implement what Anthony had suggested
which was to Simply remove nuts and
seeds and as you guys heard in her own
text messages from the true version of
the cat story Ashley said that once she
did that her son's skin started clearing
up and falsity number seven Ashley was
dealing with pre-existing symptoms and
conditions before she ever started
applying medical medium information
including hair loss and there is plenty
of evidence of that that Ashley maybe
doesn't remember I mean it's got to be a
full-time job at this point for her to
keep her lies straight when she's being
so obscenely dishonest all over the
place these pre-existing symptoms like
hair loss however presented long before
Ashley was recommended by Anthony to
remove nuts and seeds for the one month
or so that she actually did in total so
restrictive I
know in fact in one of the ebooks that
Ashley had sold to the medical medium
Community years ago Ashley wrote this
about what was going on with her health
during the time that she gave birth to
her other child that she had before her
son who had the eczema
outbreak after was born my health
crashed even more severely my depression
became so intense magnified 100 times
getting out of bed felt impossible and
at times it was my hair fell out my skin
grew dull and pale I felt horrible in my
own body and for a brief period I even
battle thoughts of suicide I weighed 185
lbs and my entire body seemed to Sag in
the aftermath of creating new life at 6
months postpartum I found help from
Anthony William who wrote the book
medical
Medium as you can see from Ashley's own
testimony of her healing Journey from
before she got mad at Anthony and
started telling these fake stories and
trying to rewrite history Ashley's hair
loss was happening after she had her
first baby which was six months before
she ever interacted with Anthony or his
information in the first
place Ashley's using this falsity as a
tactic to mess with other women's heads
it's a great way to scare women who are
applying medical medium information
women do not want to lose their hair or
the health of their
nails yeah
and that's real
fear-mongering somebody who has to twist
stories like this in order to try to
scare and mess with the heads of women
who are already struggling to serve
their own agenda is clearly someone who
is operating from a place of malice and
not from a place of
Sanity during our call Ashley continued
to tell me this fake cat
story um we went to Hawaii actually with
Taylor to do a retreat with Taylor
while we were there we were staying at
an Airbnb with a cat and halfway through
the retreat we moved to an Airbnb
without a cat we also had a cat um when
we moved to the Airbnb without a cat my
son's exema went away within like the
three days that we were there falsity
number eight what's funny is that this
is the opposite from other versions of
the false story that Ashley's told in
another false version Ashley said that
the cat was in the second Airbnb and now
she's say that the cat was in the first
Airbnb as we stated previously a witness
who was at the retreat said that there
was actually not a cat in either of
Ashley's
airbnbs falsity number nine in this
version Ashley's claiming that her son's
eczema went away within 3 days while
they were in Hawaii in the real story
from Ashley's own text messages remember
that her son's eczema actually started
clearing up 1 month before the Hawaii
retreat in October Ashley's son's eczema
flared up again while they were in
Hawaii because Ashley started eating
nuts
again so we got home we gave the cat to
a friend we had our um air conditioning
unit claimed his eczema went away and it
never came
back falsity number 10 if you remember
back to one of the text threads we read
from Ashley's real version of the cat
story sent to a friend on August 15th of
2018 Ashley said this
we're having our whole house cleaned top
to bottom this weekend including all
furniture and our HVAC
system in fact Ashley had her air
conditioning unit cleaned the weekend of
August 17th which was 2 months before
the Hawaii Retreat not after the Hawaii
Retreat and that concludes this version
of the cat story leaving us with 10
total falsities in just one one of the
multiple fictitious versions that Ashley
has told of this cat story Ashley has
adapted the infamous cat story more and
more with time right after we released
the first podcast about the plotters a
lot of people were shocked to figure out
that Ashley was behind this attack on
Anthony and the community because they
remembered how much Ashley has said in
previous years about how Anthony has
helped her and her family one woman
recounted what she had seen in a
Facebook group that she was in with
Ashley during the time of her son's
eczema problem in a comment thread from
April 20th of 2023 the woman said aw
helped Ash's baby recover from pretty
severe eczema I don't know if Ash had
issues herself or just her baby I
remember seeing before and after
piic Ashley replied with another version
of her fake cat
story respectfully can't let these
inaccuracies go un addressed and Anthony
did not cure my son's eczema he told me
to go on a fat-free diet as a
breastfeeding postpartum mom he
recommended it for months and months and
months he specifically told me that I
just needed to keep going to detox to
help my son we went on a trip and
realized that my son was allergic to
cats we came back and gave our cat to a
dear friend my son's eczema went away
within the week and has never come back
I however have suffered incredible
depletion from being on such restrictive
diet for so long I went on to have two
miscarriages while continuing to follow
Anthony's
advice wow this false version is even
more extreme than the last Ashley has a
pattern of escalating the severity of
her fake stories over time presumably
after not getting enough of a rise out
of people
initially here Ashley's telling the same
falsities about Anthony missing the cat
allergy and that Anthony had told her to
go on a fat-free diet this time she says
for months and months and
months Ashley also told the same
falsities about how Anthony told her to
just keep going to detox her son that
she herself discovered the cat allergy
at The Retreat that they gave the cat
away after the retreat and that her
son's eczema cleared after the retreat
none of which is
accurate now she's added in outrageous
Health claims to imply that not only
Anthony got the cause of her son's skin
problem wrong but also that his
recommendations were restrictive and
caused her harm she says that she quote
suffered incredible depletion from being
on such a restrictive diet for so long
all of this is
inaccurate again we're going to be
thoroughly addressing Ashley's
outrageous Health claims in other
episodes for now I'm going to share the
text message that Ashley sent to Anthony
when she reached out to him for help
with her baby's
eczema sweet is pretty miserable still
an I'm doing the basic things I can do
while breastfeeding celery juice low fat
green free zinc vitamin C he's getting a
little celery juice too any other
thoughts for me poor little bugs seem so
miserable I'm willing to do something
extreme like a melon juice and green
juice fast or something but I don't want
to detox and make him
worse Ashley has made it clear over and
over again that she's never understood
medical medium information Anthony very
much advises against things like melon
juice and green juice fasts Ashley said
herself here that she was willing to do
something extreme to help her baby that
was Ashley's input Ashley herself has a
history of extreme dieting that existed
long before she ever discovered medical
medium information in a post Ashley made
years ago to promote one of her ebooks
Ashley shared a photo of herself in a
wedding dress appearing very thin and
she said
this I was thin before my first
pregnancy but it wasn't a healthy calm
thin I used juice and water fasting to
control my weight and it swung wildly
all over the place even at times when I
was thin I experienced a lot of mental
chaos around
food Ashley's first pregnancy as I went
through previously was before she ever
connected with Anthony or medical medium
information for her son's eczema Anthony
said no to Ashley's suggestion of melon
juice and green juice fasting and
literally recommended for her to Simply
remove nuts and seeds from her diet to
help him millions of people with nut and
Seed allergies live without them every
day it's far from restrictive and nobody
made her do it she was pleading for help
from Anthony and again according to
Ashley's own text messages from the true
version of this story what Anthony
suggested started clearing up her son's
skin right away in the same comment
thread from last year Ashley
added for clarity sake AK you need to
know that during that entire time we had
the cat in our house while Anthony was
calling me and doing check-ins with
spirit and telling me that the eczema
was just cleansing and I needed to keep
on my restrictive diet weird that Spirit
never mentioned the cat to him 6 months
earlier
right I mean is this a joke this is how
dangerous Ashley is every single line of
that comment is wrong this is a perfect
example of blatant falsi Ashley is
pedaling to damage Anthony to plant fear
and doubt to deliberately try to
convince people that Anthony doesn't
have accurate information and that he's
harming people and she's trying to break
people's Faith she's a faith
Buster here she's saying the cat was in
her house the entire time Anthony was
talking to her but Ashley got rid of the
cat on June 24th of 2018
this was 4 months before she's now
claiming that she gave the cat
away she said weird that Spirit never
mentioned the cat to him six months
earlier right this is false ridiculously
false Anthony mentioned the cat as a
trigger from day one but this is exactly
how Ashley deceives and manipulates
people she's trying to rewrite history
here to create an entirely false
narrative I don't care if people believe
in my gift or not that's okay that comes
with a territory since I was 4 years old
but people should be able to make that
choice for themselves without a falsity
persuading them I did know about the cat
and I told Ashley plain and
simple as the comment thread goes on the
woman who remembered that Anthony had
helped Ashley's baby with eczema
continued to question Ashley's false
story she said did you have two babies
with skin issues I pulled up my notes I
have
414 pages of notes from our group found
a convo between you and Mana about you
getting a kitten and had a whole body
rash a week after you got the kitten
Mana suggested zinc and C for you not
him you asked about the cat and she said
yes totally about the
cat the group that this woman is
referring to was a Facebook group she's
saying that another woman had suggested
for Ashley to do vitamin C and zinc for
her son's eczema Ashley implemented that
and then Ashley texted a friend about
her taking these supplements on July
14th of 2018 months before the Hawaii
retreat in
October Anthony and people in the
medical medium Community all knew that
the pet cat was part of the problem way
before Ashley and her son stayed in the
Airbnb that Ashley's trying to claim had
a cat in it a woman who wasn't even
involved had 400 and 14 pages of notes
from the time that this was happening
and she knew that Ashley's fake cat
story on this thread wasn't adding up
and was contradictory to the notes she
had
taken in the same comment thread Ashley
tried to convince yet another person of
her false cat story to this person she
said
this here's my experience my son had
whole body eczema from a few weeks after
getting a kitten until a week after
giving it
away I'm going to pause to note that
Ashley's saying here that her son got
the rash a few weeks after they got the
kitten in another comment on the very
same thread Ashley said to a different
person that he had gotten the rash one
week after they got the kitten the
comment one
version my son had whole body eczema
from a few weeks after getting a kitten
versus the comment to
version we had a cat for a week when he
got the
rash which is it Ashley a few weeks or
one week after getting the cat it can't
be both this is getting embarrassing for
the woman who said that she would never
tell a lie and calls herself a truth
teller Ashley continued on with her fake
cat
story The Way We realiz realized what
was causing it is that we stayed in an
Airbnb without a cat and he began to
improve then we moved to an Airbnb with
a cat and he declined the difference was
rapid enough that we noticed got rid of
the cat his severe whole body eczema
that he had for six months of his life
went away and never came back so that's
my experience I feel like a broken Rec
but that's all I have to
share here we have a lot of the same
falsities from other fictitious versions
and in this version Ashley also again
flipped the order of the Airbnb with a
cat and the Airbnb without a cat
Ashley's saying here that they had the
cat for six months before giving it away
which is really funny because the woman
with 414 pages of notes from the
Facebook group Ashley originally asked
for help in called her out on that lie
by commenting PS no mention in my notes
that you had a cat for months just a
week this woman is correct that Ashley
did not have the cat for months as a
reminder for everyone of the receipts
and the timeline Ashley texted this to a
friend on June
28th cat has been gone 4
days which means that Ashley only had
the cat for a maximum of 18 days after
she texted about considering taking the
cat in on June 7th we don't have a
record of the exact date Ashley took the
cat in after the 7th it very well could
have only been a week before she gave it
away on the 24th but she did not have it
for longer than 18 days and she most
certainly did not have it for 6 months
Ashley Foster's lies are
pathological it's also worth mentioning
that Ashley interestingly deleted that
whole entire post along with all of
these comments a few short days after
she posted them that's the end of this
version of the cat story I hope your
head isn't spinning too much yet because
believe it or not there are still two
more the next false version is Ashley's
first ever public post about the
infamous cat story from
[Music]
2019 when started struggling with his
rash we had no idea what was causing it
but about a week later I started feeling
it was the kitten we adopted for our
daughter thankfully some friends of ours
fell in love with sweet Wendell Kitty
and adopted him he's so loved in their
home but even after the cat left the
reactions continued they got a little
better maybe but it was so hard to tell
because it kind of came in
waves okay right here she's admitting
that they got rid of the cat early on
not months later and that it still
didn't fix the problem which is true
she's leaving out the fact that Anthony
told her the cat was part of the problem
and that that's when she made the
decision to give the cat away she's
acting like it was her own Discovery in
other versions that she claimed the cat
allergy was her own Discovery in she
claimed she didn't make the discovery
until going to Hawaii later on here
she's claiming that she made the
discovery essentially right away Ashley
continues
on the advice of medical medium I
completely overh my diet and took out
nuts seeds oils anything that could
potentially be an irritant my diet
consisted and still does of fruits and
vegetables if you want to know more
about what I eat you can check out my
story highlights the diet change US
helped so much and were a critical
component Ash is admitting here at least
that the dietary changes did help and
were a critical component she's
misrepresenting the dietary changes as
if Anthony had advised her to cut out
oils and only eat fruits and vegetables
when in fact he said that olive oil was
fine and simply told her to cut out nuts
and seeds in this story version Ashley
wasn't clear about the timeline of the
dietary changes Ashley only implemented
getting off nuts and seeds after
September 18th in 2018 and that's when
she started seeing results in her son it
was only less than a month before she
went to Hawaii and started eating nuts
again then Ashley said
this but our guy kept on reacting we had
our whole house cleaned top to bottom
including our air ducts that helped some
but it still
persisted now she's saying that her son
kept reacting even after the dietary
changes
which is not what she said in other
versions and doesn't even make sense in
the context of the rest of this version
Ashley's also admitting here that her
air ducts were cleaned early on before
the retreat and that that still didn't
fix the problem which is true and
contradicts what she said in other
versions about getting the house
including the air duct cleaned after the
retreat she goes
on it wasn't until we went to Hawaii
that we found the final piece of the
puzzle we stayed in an airbeam be that
had a cat in it before we arrived and
within hours broke out in hives all over
his
body here's where it gets absurd because
this part makes no sense after what you
just heard her say Ashley's deliberately
leaving out so many things from this
story she's leaving out the fact that
Anthony told her that the cat was a
trigger for her son's eczema and that
that's when she decided to get rid of
the pet cat in the first place she's
leaving out the fact that she was off of
nuts and seeds for less than a month and
then she started eating nuts again at
The
Retreat she's leaving out the fact that
the menu she created for her Hawaii
retreat was full of nuts she's leaving
out the fact that the real reason why
her son broke out in eczema again in
Hawaii was because of the nuts she
reintroduced now Ashley's saying that
there was a cat in the Airbnb before
they arrived whereas other versions she
always said there was a cat in the
Airbnb while they were there Ashley also
contradicted herself with this one by
saying that the retreat cat was the
missing piece acting like it was such a
surprise when she said in the beginning
of this same story version that she
already knew their pet cat was a trigger
and that's why they had given it away
four months prior to the
retreat and now we have the ninth and
final version of Ashley's cat story
which she is still weaving and twisting
to this day Ashley posted this one right
at the end of last year 2023 As She was
rattling off a ridiculous list of
reasons why Anthony is supposedly a
liar um I have another one with my son's
eczema where he kept telling me it was
because I was eating too much fat I was
a postpartum nursing mom eating like
less than half an avocado a day um and
you know he had me testing our house for
mold and doing all this stuff and my son
was allergic to our cat and we figured
that out ourselves
and so that was another one where I was
like wait why why was he so
wrong why was he so wrong my son was
allergic to our cat and we figured that
out
ourselves versus what actually happened
according to her own text messages
I talked to Aunt and he said it's most
likely the
cat and she also said that he kept
telling me it was because I was eating
too much
fat versus what actually
happened still dealing with skin but I
spoke with Aunt and he got us on the
right track I think we'll be through it
in the next few weeks I was having very
little fat like maybe one tablespoon of
cashews a day but it turns out it's not
the fat itself it's the nuts he actually
said like olive oil would be better than
cashews in terms of helping
heal it turns out it's not the fat it's
the
nuts as you can see Ashley Foster is a
liar who lies about lying while accusing
Anthony of being a liar as she's lying
and has told nine different
contradictory versions of the the same
story yet another contradiction is that
in one of these virgins Ashley claimed
that her only fat Source each day was
avocado and in the other version she
claimed that her only fat Source each
day was cashews these two things cannot
be true at the same time and in this
most recent version Ashley also added in
for the first time the claim that
Anthony had her quote testing for mold
and all this stuff which is just
blatantly not true that is completely
false and it's very telling that she's
only adding that on now years and years
after she started telling this story
Ashley likes to try to play to people's
emotions because many people are
concerned about mold I never told Ashley
to test for mold in her multi-million
dollar Malibu
mansion furthermore in only one of the
previous false versions of the cat story
we went through Ashley mentioned air
purifiers
um and he told me all this different
stuff we had like a billion air
purifiers Ashley was trying to make it
look like she did everything right she
followed all of Anthony's advice she
spent a bunch of money on air purifiers
for the cat dander and still Anthony was
wrong but here is what actually happened
with the air purifiers in late 2018
there were massive fires devastating the
area of Malibu California where Ashley
was living at the time on November 9th
Anthony texted her to check in anony is
going to read the text he had sent to
her please be safe hang in their Ash
worried about you and your precious
babies hope you are okay praying for
your house to be safe too and putting
light all around
it so Anthony you told her that you were
putting light around her house can you
explain for everyone what that means
I asked Spirit to Encompass the entire
house with a force of light and I was
envisioning this force of light
inhibiting
Flames okay so you did that and then
Ashley texted you on November 21st to
say
this okay friend what are we talking
about here the devastation is immense
the house next to us burnt to the ground
obviously we want to do the highest
level of smoke remediation we can can
but with all of the ash in the
environment and the months it will take
to remove the debris do we need to plan
to be somewhere else for a few
months next Ashley sends a video of her
husband showing their house in perfect
condition and then her husband pivots
the camera so that it's looking through
the burnt part of their Hedges out at
the empty plot where the neighbor's
house used to be in awe the video gets
cut off a bit but he says
unbelievable next Ashley sends this
text that's our house versus the house
next door supernaturally protected and
surrounded by angels
so Anthony and spirit protected Ashley's
multi-million doll home with light and
the video shows that her house was
completely Untouched by the fires while
her neighbor's house was completely
disintegrated down to the ground it's
literally right next to Ashley's home
there's hardly any space in between it's
just a very tall wall of Hedges and only
a small part of the Hedge is burnt down
that whole thing should have lit up in
flames and taken Ashley's house along
with it it makes no sense
there's nothing left of the neighbor's
house and it's truly a miracle that
Ashley's home was left entirely
intact then Anthony texted her
back amazing your house was so protected
if you stay there you just have to stay
inside a lot because when the wind blows
there's a lot of Ash in the air that
will go into your lungs but if you're
inside a lot and the inside isn't
saturated with smoke smell then you can
stay there and work with with it once
the rain comes the outside will be so
much
better the conversation
continues okay I think in general we're
planning to stay away until beginning of
the year and have the whole house
treated with ozone and clean top to
bottom you think by January is a good
bet yes that's what I would do wait till
then and we're going to buy some of the
IQ air
filters it's important to note here that
in this conversation that takes place
one month after Ashley's Hawaii Retreat
and is about smoke remediation not about
Eczema or a cat Ashley brings up air
filters and says they're going to buy
some for smoke remediation Anthony was
not the one to bring it up the
conversation goes
on some rain could come in between too
yep
yes lots of rain
predicted get the multi-gas one plus
when the rain comes with no brush to
hold it back there will be lots of
landslides so best to be away
yes got
it thank
God Amen so many prayers covering our
home thank you
okay so as I said this was one month
after Ashley's Hawaii Retreat Ashley had
gotten rid of their household cat on
June 24th of this same year five months
prior to this conversation the air
purifiers were her idea and she got them
for smoke remediation not for pet dander
or her son's eczema like one of her
false versions of the infamous cat story
suggested it's also worth noting that
this convers on November 21st about
Ashley's home took place 8 days after
Stephanie passed away Ashley made no
mention of Stephanie or any problem she
had with Anthony around it but she
certainly wanted his help with her
multi-million dollar home I know that
this is a lot for everybody to take in
thank you Amber for doing this for the
community the evidence we presented
today shows that Ashley can't get
anything right even historical stories
that can be easily fact checked and she
has to fabricate and lie about her own
personal experiences with me to try to
convince people that I got it wrong to
call me a liar and a fraud when as you
can see here she's caught so many times
in just what has been covered in this
episode alone lying and telling
fraudulent Stories the story about the
10 booms and the Holocaust is a litmus
test to Ashley's inability to tell not
only stories about Stephanie and me and
the cat but clearly shows that she
cannot even get a historic story even
partially correct it's one thing when
people hear all these versions of lies
and falsehoods and her madeup stories
but it's another when you have a
landmark such as the 10 Booms to clearly
see how Ashley can't get it right it's
another reason why I wouldn't do
business with Ashley when she proposed
so many business deals she wanted to
partner with me on painfully almost
everything she said always had falsities
or mistakes or misinformation saturated
in it what Ashley's been doing with the
cat story is what she's been doing with
her entire smear campaign against me as
a whole it's an endless stream of sloppy
lies and psychological games how sad is
it that I actually did help her son he
recovered and I helped her out of the
kindness of my heart for free I wasn't
making any money from it I wasn't
gaining anything from it and because she
has nothing to show that I'm a bad guy
or did anything wrong she has to lie and
take something that was positive that I
actually helped her with and was
accurate about and perverted to make it
look like the exact opposite of what
really happened so that she can try to
take me
down there are people who have serious
mental health problems there are people
who are just inaccurate and get things
wrong there are people who attack and
intentionally set out to harm other
people there are people who FIB there
are people who are pathological liars
and then there's Ashley Foster she's
truly in a league of her own this is
unprecedented as we've said and in my
opinion it should be studied
clinically what's even more disturbing
is that this episode just barely
scratches the surface this is what
Ashley does with every story with every
claim with every rumor she spreads it's
all this distorted it's all this Twisted
it's all this
untrue and the other plotters have
followed suit and have the same patterns
we could do hundreds of podcast episodes
on twisting the lies and falsities like
this the evidence is all there and this
is just the beginning
with the Stephanie story Ashley and
Stephanie's brother are abusing the fact
that nobody else has access to the
entirety of Stephanie's text threads
with all of the people who were involved
or any of the other evidence to see what
Ashley and Stephanie's brother have
hidden manipulated taken out of context
and altered as they're making outrageous
claims against Anthony and trying to
rewrite history to push a fake story
we'll get to more of that in due time
the ten Boom story and the cat story are
examples that everyone can use to verify
for themselves exactly the level of
unimaginable reality Distortion and
perversion of the truth that Ashley and
her hateful group have continued to
employ with the Stephanie story and with
the other stories that they
tell one online commenter who has
observed the behavior of Ashley and her
hateful group said
this everything they accuse Anthony and
the mm community of being is what they
elves are doing to the mm Community it's
so frustrating and sad the amount of
gaslighting belittling and just pure
hostility from these people is hard to
Bear especially after years of suffering
chronic illness with no answers and all
the trauma that comes with that it's
painful and scary to witness how
committed these people are to twisting
reality and taking advantage of people
who don't know any better how do they
live with
themselves another online commenter said
this it's so despicable what are we in
high school this is something high
schoolers and middle schoolers do it's
Petty and narcissistic behavior it's a
narcissistic smear campaign it's got
narcissists written all over it only
people with hatred in their hearts would
do this it's obvious but then comes the
fakeness the lies the smearing of
another person's name and reputation
Without Regrets they are heartless
you're supposed to take everyone into
consideration before you act and speak
that is what adults do
they will die a slow and lonely death on
their socials and they should regret
this the rest of their lives but Ashley
probably won't she's always seemed like
she doesn't actually care about others
which is
depressing and a third online commenter
said this it has become ridiculous now
Amber I truly hope the plotters just
fade into the background and leave this
wonderful mm Community alone they are
cruel very childish obsessed with
revenge and embarrassing not forgetting
the Carnage they leave behind that you
mm and the community have to pick up and
repair for those that sadly fell for
their
lies Ashley has formed her hateful Group
by taking advantage of people who
already have an ulterior reason why they
don't like medical medium whether it's
pure spiritual discrimination or
somebody who sells ionizer water
machines for example who got mad at
Anthony when he started sharing about
the downsides of ionizer water machines
because of how much influence he has in
the health industry
they're also taking advantage of the
fact that when people are dealing with
chronic illness they often get confused
about their
symptoms when somebody's confused
they're may be not reading the books or
understanding trajectory or flare Cycles
or new exposures they're may be having a
hard time implementing the information
they're frustrated with their symptoms
they're emotional they're vulnerable and
then they come across a post from Ashley
Foster that says Anthony is a liar and a
fraud he missed the fact that my son had
a cat allergy he put me on a restrictive
diet that made my nails break and my
hair fall out it strikes a cord it
instills doubt and fear and that is
Ashley's goal when in reality the story
she told is the opposite of what
actually happened it's all lies designed
to play on people's emotions it's sick
it's manipulative and it's
self-serving Ashley does not care about
the chronically ill Ashley doesn't care
about people healing Ashley has publicly
attacked shamed and humiliated the
chronically ill and women and children
which is going to be exposed in this
series this is all about Ashley getting
what she wants and she will lie and use
and harm anyone that she needs to in the
process there's no other way to say it
it is abusive behavior and Ashley needs
to be held
accountable as we are in the process of
exposing Ashley and her organized
hateful group for who and what they
really are it's important to take note
of their tactics and patterns that are
likely to follow the plotters have a
documented history of initiating attacks
using lies and misinformation and then
upon getting called out and corrected
trying to flip it and play victim that
is not going to work here all this group
has done is spread verifiable lies and
falsities they've carelessly attacked
and harmed many innocent people they've
used and exploited deceased individuals
and others in the process of trying to
get what they want they've repeatedly
explicitly expressed the intent to harm
medical medium and they've even
deliberately tried to stop Anthony from
doing a free event to support and raise
money for the community we have every
right to set the record straight and to
defend the truth with facts and evidence
and to defend the chronically ill
against the malicious attacks of this
group and we are going to continue to do
so we expect the plotters to evade and
ignore what they have done wrong we
expect them to continue to lie and
spread falsities we expect them to Pivot
onto something new they'll make up and
we expect them to skew and alter data
and to hide critical pieces of evidence
that undermines their entire campaign we
also expect the plotters to fabricate
explanations as they do everything they
can to try to discredit what we're
exposing them for having done and said
in their own words but we are using
their own text messages voice messages
social media posts words that they spoke
on recorded calls and other published
materials there's no use of any AI in
any of these episodes and never will be
all of the information was fact checked
and forensically investigated if you've
been harmed deterred from your healing
process bullied shamed emotionally upset
or physically hurt by flareups of your
conditions from the stress induced by
the plotters attacks like hundreds of
others have reported please go to
medicalmedium.com
SLS safespace to submit your report and
share your story if you've been
contacted by anyone who's tried to deter
you from using medical medium
information please take screenshots and
Screen recordings and submit them to the
same place medicalmedium.com
slsa space