how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about the soul and
emotional Soul healing everyone is soul
searching whether they know it or not
but what are we really searching for
happiness peace tranquility
stability and can we heal the soul yes
we can grab some lemon bomb find a comfy
place to relax and let's get to
it so everybody is soul searching
someone once told me you're either soul
searching or you're not and then Spirit
of compassion
said you're either soul searching or
you're soul
searching because that's the truth even
if somebody doesn't know it even if they
don't call it that so that's another
thing like you may run into somebody and
doesn't seem they don't think they're
soul searching on any level they're just
doing their thing living their
life but they don't know they're soul
searching they're soul searching but
they don't call it that they're not
aware that it's soul searching right we
Soul search because part of us feels
lost how many how many people do you
know have that feeling of being lost
that lost sensation like a
sadness at a certain time of day what if
it's like 3 4:00 in the afternoon and
then a strange sadness comes over I know
so many people that have it at different
times and it's this thing you can't
really explain but it's there we Soul
search because part of us feels lost or
we don't feel whole like there's a piece
of us missing like we're not all of our
pieces aren't there in place right it's
just there's a piece of ourselves
missing or because we feel like we're
not living up to our Soul's potential we
Soul search because of life's
hardships that's another thing too is
life's
hardships make it so we want to go and
soul search as well right often a
negative experience or a series of them
will prompt a person to feel broken or
depleted did you ever feel broken or
depleted like you just had something
happen in your life right something
happened in your life and it just pushed
you over the edge like you were on your
last Heather if you were a bird you felt
like you were on your last feathers I
mean where you just felt like you were
pushed over hanging on the cliff like
done did you ever use that term where
you're like I'm done I'm done
right so many people have felt like that
where they're at a place where they like
okay I'm done or this relationship so
many people they're in a relationship
that's toxic there's a lot of emotional
turmoil in the relationship there's a
lot going on in the relationship and
they're just like I'm done I can't take
this anymore I can't handle this anymore
so often a negative experience or a
series of them will prompt the person to
feel broken or depleted and want to feel
complete again it's like I want to feel
whole again I want to feel like myself
again and maybe I don't even know what
myself felt like but I want to feel it I
want to feel like I got all those pieces
of my soul back I want to feel like I'm
not
lost I want to feel like connected to
something I want that sensation I want
that feeling and if you have chronic
illness and you don't feel good and
you're struggling with chronic illness
then it really amplifies it and makes
the even harder that feeling of wanting
to be complete again that feeling of not
wanting to feel lost that feeling of no
one understands me that feeling of
something's
missing that's when we need that soul
searching that's part of soul searching
right there it can take the form of
attending Retreats how many people
attend Retreats they're looking for
something how many
people are looking for something thing
so they'll go anywhere and they'll do
anything they're looking for answers or
they're looking for that piece of what's
lost to come
back sometimes it takes going to hear
inspirational speakers seeking advice
from loved ones enrolling in therapy how
many people are in counseling how many
people have had so many counselors
emotional
counselors
therapists
psychiatrists different forms of
counselors because they're like trying
to find an answer why am I thinking like
this why am I struggling how come I feel
so sad inside how come I feel so lost
why am I going through this I need to
find another therapist I need to find a
therapist that understands me and can
crack me because I'm hard to crack why
am I such a tough nut to
crack how how come it feels like nobody
can crack me me no professional is there
something wrong with me did I do
something wrong am I crazy is something
going wrong I mean these are feelings
that we naturally feel that everybody
feels at some point in their life and
maybe they don't feel it now but they
might feel it at another time it's what
we do when we're looking to heal and
Elevate our souls to strengthen our
purpose in life we we look for help
because we want to strengthen that
purpose we want to unlock something in
our soul and we want to heal your soul
resides in your brain something people
don't know now this is going to sound
kind of gory I know it's kind of a
little off topic but it's not really off
topic it's a little
gory but back in the olden days the
reason why they beheaded people that was
a very popular popular technique is
because back in the olden days they
sensed there was an energy all around
here so what they would do is Medieval
times they would put it they would chop
people's heads off and put their heads
on spikes right or Pikes or something
they would put their heads on sticks on
the sides of roads and all that or they
would behead people with Guillotines
right for some reason they felt like
that was the most satisfying way to end
somebody's life because there was
something more satiating about it in the
medieval days and what they what they
were actually tapping into without
realizing it there was a lot going on
here but they didn't know that's where
the soul resides and that's why they had
a desire to behead people because the
soul resided in the head they didn't
know
that they didn't know the soul resided
in the head but they had this innate
desire when they wanted to end
somebody's life to behead them to chop
off their head that was what that is why
they did that and then they had this
innate desire to exhibit
someone's head chopped off they had this
innate desire to actually exhibit it so
exhibit the head on a pike on the sides
of Roads or in villages where they would
slay a village and then they would chop
off everybody's head and put it on Pikes
because they felt that a message was
sent
more and what it was was what they were
detecting yeah it's gory but what they
were what they were detecting was there
was more energy here even though the
whole body there was more body weight
and body mass everywhere else there was
more energy
here so what they were detecting without
realizing it they were detecting the
soul was here inside the brain so they
had a great desire if they wanted to end
somebody's life back in the in the
medieval the Dark Ages they would chop
off the
head your soul resides in your brain
where your soul stores memories and
experiences that's where your soul is
storing memories and
experiences they're in the soul when our
soul leaves our body it
takes these experiences with it when you
pass from this Mortal
realm your soul
carries those memories as it moves
onward your soul carries those memories
as it moves onward so when we pass from
this Mortal place this Mortal realm
right our soul carries these memories as
it moves onward even if someone has a
brain injury or brain disease that keeps
her or him from remembering certain
things so hear this for a second so if
somebody has Alzheimer's
dementia if someone is losing their
train of thought losing their mind and
they pass away from a brain
disease even if someone has a brain
injury or brain disease like Alzheimer's
or dementia or something like that
incopy right that keeps her or him from
remembering certain things the soul will
bring all those memories with it when
that person passes on if you have a
grandfather a grandmother or a family
member or a friend that is losing their
mind because they have the Alzheimer's
they have dementia they're really
suffering they don't even know who they
are they lose their memory completely
and they pass away you have to remember
something the pain and suffering a loved
one has says where did their memories go
don't they remember me how come they
don't remember me how come they don't
see who I am my grandfather's sitting
there and he knows me I he raised me I'm
walking into the room and my
grandfather's saying how are you I don't
know who you are you have to remember
that every me memory that that
grandfather has grandmother that friend
that mother father that brother sister
every memory that they have about you
and their life is still trapped in there
it's in there just because the brain
disease is eating away neurons it
doesn't mean the soul doesn't take those
memories with it that's the whole point
and what I learned from Spirit of
compassion is the soul takes those
memories with it as it
leaves so it's not like that family
member their lives are just completely
wiped out and completely gone it's not
like that at all it's the opposite yes
in that moment it feels that way but
when they leave and their soul passes on
they have all the memories there they
didn't lose that they know who you are
when a grandfather grandmother a friend
or a family member soul is leaving them
as they pass in that moment even if they
lost ability to understand who you were
as they were fading away they still when
they leave and that Soul lifts up from
that body they instantly know you who
you are every memory they shared with
you everything about you all that
they've done with you every experience
they've ever had with you they know and
they see it and see you as their soul
leaves the body your soul also stores
your hope people don't realize that that
their soul actually stores their hope do
you think you're hopeless you're not you
think you have no hope anymore uhuh
that's not true you think you've lost
all your hope no no no no no you didn't
lose all your hope your hope is stored
it's
stored in your soul there's a well of it
in your soul your soul also stores faith
if you have faith in God your soul
stores that faith if you have faith in
Jesus Christ your soul stores that faith
if you're a Christian and you have faith
in Jesus Christ if for some reason
you're a Christian and you lost faith in
Jesus Christ I promise you this your
soul still has faith in Jesus Christ if
you're someone that's not a Christian
and you just believe in God and God God
is who you believe in and you have faith
in God and you have tremendous faith in
God and then all of a sudden something
happens to you in your life and you lose
faith in God I promise you this your
soul still stores your faith in God if
you think you lost trust and you had
trust and now you can't trust anything
anymore and you can't trust anyone
anymore you can't trust anyone you can't
trust anything anymore cuz you lost
trust I can promise you this that you
have trust stored in your soul reason
for that is it helps to keep us on the
right path so we stay stay present here
ideally we would all have fully intact
Souls over the course of life's
hardships though a soul can become
fractured and even lose pieces of itself
but that's okay because we still never
lose our soul this can be caused by
traumatic events traumatic events can
fracture our soul but that's all right
because our soul can mend and heal our
soul is
unbreakable it is unbreakable regardless
of a fracture regardless of hardships
beating it down and wearing and tearing
on your soul it is
unbreakable this can be caused by
traumatic events such as the death of a
loved one so many people go through
betrayal by a loved one or betrayal of
oneself as well as ongoing traumas such
as the loss of freedom and trust that
comes with experiencing chronic symptoms
and illness I think so many people have
been beaten down with their illness you
guys know about that you had
symptoms or you still have them because
you just found medical medium and you're
working on your healing process but
you've been down that road and you had
so many symptoms and suffered greatly so
bad and that wears and tears on the
soul to throughout the years I
would through a process that Spirit of
compassion has has taught me to
scan
someone and spirit of compassion would
show me if they had any fractures on
their soul and it resembled cracks in a
cathedral window that's what it
resembled when I would see it through
Spirit of compassion's eyes because a
soul is made out of light our souls are
a form of light that when a soul is
fractured
it looks like the sun it looks like the
inside like you're inside a church and
the stained glass windows there's light
coming through the Sun as for a soul
with missing pieces it's like a house at
night that's meant to have all its
lights on except some of its rooms are
still dark when Soul injuries are fresh
they can result in the feeling of being
lost or loss of connection with oneself
loss of Desire or inspiration to
preserve or thr
so many people lose their Inspirations
they feel like they're dead inside they
feel like they died inside they're numb
and they don't feel like there's
anything left in them they feel like
there's nothing there anymore they feel
like they are not being seen by anything
and they're completely alone and
completely in the dark and that's what
happens when Soul injuries are actually
fresh it just
happened I just got let down that person
broke my trust I feel so injured I feel
so misunderstood and not heard so when
the soul injuries are fresh they can
result in feeling like you're lost or
there's a loss of connection like
where's the connection there's no
connection a loss of Desire or
inspiration to persevere or Thrive or
even like life force how many that you
guys know that where you feel like you
lose your life force because you just
had such a hard time that's why
important to be aware of our soul and
that's how you heal emotional support is
understanding our own soul because
people they don't realize they have this
connection to their own soul they don't
know how to connect to their own
soul when you understand your soul and
and understand where it is and and if
it's been injured and how strong it is
and how powerful it is when you connect
to your soul that's how you can really
do some emo healing and rise out of
something that's why it's important to
be aware of our soul wounds from
hardships betrayal and broken trust or
emotional hurt often exhaust a person's
immune system adrenals and other bod's
defenses triggering a physical issue
that could be residing deep within our
organs and body so it's twofold if you
guys go through a hard time if somebody
goes through a hard
time I know a friend that just got
betrayed so bad just so bad the Betrayal
was just horrendous and he didn't want
to live
anymore but when he really understood
the soul connection that I was teaching
him
about it was giving him a chance to say
you know I could get through this you
can't you can't take my soul away no
one's going to be able to take my soul
away but at the same time adrenals can
get beaten down and our immune systems
can can be lowered because we're going
through a lot if we're betrayed it does
play it does take a hit on our immune
system and our physical body it can beat
us down our adrenals you go into this
point where your adrenaline just spikes
and feels like it gets out of control if
someone's messing with you or you had a
hardship someone just
you you know your trust you don't trust
them anymore something happened and all
of a sudden it's like adrenaline you can
even feel like you're shaking you get so
upset and hurt where you're
shaking and that's the adrenaline now
being released and takes a toll on the
body sometimes a person's soul
injury and resulting emotional state
isn't a physical problem yet symptoms
often take time to build quietly in the
back background so a soul injury at an
earlier time in life could be the
trigger for the future symptoms or
full-blown conditions to come if you
don't have the right knowledge tools and
resources to take care of your soul and
physical body we can get in trouble the
medical medium tools are there to
support your physical body and your
emotional body that's how you win it's
both they're there and even if you don't
support your your emotional body
and you heal physically it naturally can
help to heal the emotional part of what
you're going through in your life it can
help heal the
emotional
injuries let's be clear emotional wounds
and soul wounds are not the reason for
physical suffering that's important to
know they are not the cause of physical
suffering they're not the cause of
fibromyalgia they're not the cause of
thyroid cancer they're not the cause of
multiple
sclerosis or lupus or lime disease
rather they can act as
triggers for underlying
susceptibilities when we go through
emotional hardships it can knock us so
hard it lowers our immune system and it
triggers us when we go through emotional
hardships our adrenaline can really get
kicked into high gear because we're
emotionally injured and then we get
knocked down a notch it knocks us down I
can't tell you how many people that got
into a difficult relationship and it was
there was so much turmoil in that
relationship there was so much fighting
and cheating and betrayal in that
relationship that it lowered the immune
system and when it lowered the immune
system it broke them down and other
things they had residing inside of them
pathogens rose up and now they have
chronic fatigue syndrome they become
triggers but you're stronger than you
know have battled this long and gotten
yourself this far in life now you can
rise
above all this is knowledge so you can
rise above your wounds you can rise
above the injuries physically that
you've
had the
pathogens the exposures you can rise
above that and heal your emotions too
and Rise Above any kind of Soul injuries
a person with soul injury is vulnerable
if you ever hear a friend say I'm not
ready for another relationship I'm still
hurting from my breakup she's
acknowledging that her soul needs time
to heal before she risks putting herself
out there again so many of us know when
our soul is is vulnerable we know that
we're susceptible we know it's like whoa
I can't do that right now I can't go
through that again right now I I need to
step back a little bit my soul isn't
feeling that strong my soul's not
feeling strong enough along the same
lines if you ever observe someone who's
sick with symptoms or conditions and
hasn't been able to find answers you may
see this person hungrily pursuing
spiritual learning in any form like
religion spiritual gurus self-help books
meditation Retreats breath work it's
likely because that person's soul has
been injured from all the trust lost
along the way and she or he is
instinctively searching for ways to make
the soul healthy and complete again when
we fall ill with symptoms that won't go
away or that continue to come and go we
lose trust in our body and in others to
help us there are people who have been
sick for years who turn to soul
searching when they can't find answers
and that's another thing too I I watched
this for decades people are looking for
Spiritual answers because no one knows
why they're sick physically what was
really popular back like 30 years ago 25
years ago was because nobody knew of
course why anybody was sick with chronic
illness you go and find
somebody and then you try to find some
kind of healer to to give you any kind
of answer and there's a good chance
they'll tell you it's because you had
your head chopped off off in
1733 in England somewhere and that's why
you're actually sick or they'll say you
drowns they will say like in the 1600s
you
were you were deemed a witch in the
1600s and you were put to death by
Drowning because nobody knew any answers
right I remember people would come to me
and they'd be like well I've been to
every doctor and now I've been to every
every psychic and healer I can find
around the planet and I have some I have
some good good leads one lead is I was
drowned as a witch in 16 in the 1600s
and because of that that's why I'm sick
and I have all these problems and
everything else and spirit of compassion
would say that's not why the person's
sick person has real real reasons why
they're sick and those are the answers
you find in the medical medium books
sometimes soul searching will bring
people closer to themselves many times
it will leave them feeling more lost
than ever did you ever go soul searching
and then you feel more lost than ever
did you ever try to find yourself but
yet you feel more lost did that ever
happen to you where you're you're going
to try to find yourself right and you
think you're going to find yourself
you're trying to find yourself and then
you're like ah I think I found myself I
do I think I found myself but then then
all of a sudden you feel more lost than
ever and then you feel like you're down
a rabbit hole where it's
worse many times it will leave someone
feeling more loss than ever under the GU
of help you may have heard the false
theory that illness is just a cry for
attention did you guys ever hear that
the false theory that went around for
decades that medical medium information
had to
disprove did you ever hear that where
it's a cry for help that's why you're
sick you were looking for attention did
you ever hear that one where you were
looking for attention that's why you
were sick that's another one that has
tortured people for years that medical
medium info had to disprove to help
people they give them answers I can't
tell you how many times I've heard that
like you're just you're just want
attention that's that's why what you're
doing right that's what everybody's told
it just breaks my heart when I even hear
that you may have heard that when bad
things happen to us we cause them by
thinking the wrong thoughts did you guys
hear that one bad things are happening
to you you're sick because you caused it
with your by having the wrong thoughts
like by having the wrong thoughts that's
why you're sick you caused your sickness
by thinking the wrong thoughts see these
are all made up things made up theories
here by Men by men here on the planet
and women here on the planet it's made
of theories and spirit of compassion is
not from here so has Clarity on this
because I can't tell you how many times
I've had to rewire someone because they
were positive they were sick because
they had bad thoughts and that's why
they were sick I've said it before and
I'll say it again if you are ill or
going through a trial like a divorce or
a loss you did not manifest it if you
are are going through a sickness you did
not manifest it if you are going through
some type of feeling of like being
disconnected feeling lost feeling
hopeless and depressed you did not
manifest it if you feel sadness that you
can't explain and you feel like no one
understands you and you can't understand
yourself you feel and you feel like you
lost all trust in yourself you did
not manifest that you did not attract it
it is not punishment or payback it's not
Karma if you guys have struggled and you
suffered and something happened to you
along the way whatever you do don't
think it's karma paying you back in this
lifetime if a child is sick you mean to
tell me that child's karma is why that
child is suffering the one thing you'll
find in the medical medium information
is about freeing the brainwashing and
freeing you up of the brainwashing and
mind control that has been out there
forever and that mind control is in the
alternative arts and alternative healing
I'm so sorry to say I really am it
breaks my heart and kills me it's also
in the conventional healing too in the
conventional world that mind control and
brain conditioning is unbelievable
there's a spiritual war out there it
really is and it just controls
people purposely so that those people
can control everybody else it's like
it's
unbelievable you did not attract it it's
not punish or payback it's not your Bad
Karma you have to know you're not sick
because of your karma whatever you do
you can't fall into that you do not
deserve to be sick or unhappy it's not
your fault you didn't manifest it it's
not your fault and it's not Karma I can
promise you
that you don't need to travel the world
trying to find yourself I've seen people
who have money travel the world to find
themselves and they're still sick Soul
healing is about reclaiming who you
are because you are already good enough
who you are already means more than you
know you are already good
enough it's just about healing now you
are already good enough you deserve to
heal you deserve to be happy you deserve
to feel whole your heart serves as the
compass for your actions guiding you to
do the right thing when your soul
becomes
lost when our souls become lost we feel
like we're disconnected we feel like our
soul is busted up and broken our heart
serves as the compass for our actions it
guides us to do the right thing when our
soul becomes lost our heart matters in
that situation your heart is also a
safety net that can compensate for soul
injuries that means when we get broken
down so hard and we had a really bad
relationship or something happened in
her life our heart Stands Strong this
means you can have a tattered soul and a
warm loving heart I can't tell you how
many people that I've met that have the
tattered they've been tattered along the
way but their heart is warm and their
heart is loving and their heart is
caring I've been through a lot in my
life and I still care and I still want
to help and I still care about people
and love people and I know there's a
whole bunch of people out there they've
been through Helen back and they still
have a heart that's warm and loving and
they care when your soul suffers losses
a strong heart will get you through with
Selfless Love
compassion and joy under the soul until
your soul has managed to heal compassion
is
critical superficial love that's a
matter of the Mind self selfless love
that comes from the heart you guys know
about superficial love right The
Superficial love love is not
absolute love is not
everything unless compassion is attached
to it that's why you can see somebody
and they'll fall in love with someone
and then they can fall out of love with
someone like what was it was it just a
change of heart a change of mind what
was that how can you be so in love with
someone so in love with them and then
not love them anymore that means that
love had no compassion in there it
wasn't
attached they were
separated if you have love for someone
and it's lost that means that the
compassion is gone compassion is the
glue to love love isn't enough you have
to have compassion as the glue for love
or love won't stand a chance love won't
hang in there love won't even Last Love
Won't Be Strong Enough Love is just an
empty word love is a totally empty word
if compassion isn't intertwined or
attached or somehow involved if you
don't have compassion involved if
compassion's not part of love then love
is not strong enough isn't everything
just a lesson we try to learn from it so
we don't get burned by that stove again
but no everything's not not just a
lesson unfortunately it's not it's like
you don't need your arm chopped off to
teach you a lesson is that a lesson I
know a lot of war vets that lost their
legs I'm intertwined with a lot of vets
I have vets in my family the whole bit
and losing both your legs is not there
to teach you a lesson we can certainly
try to grow from it and learn from it
but it wasn't done on purpose to teach
us a lesson child abuse isn't there to
teach a child a lesson so yeah no things
aren't there for a lesson that's not how
it
works we can try to grow we can try to
better ourselves we can try to rise
above it we can try to use tools to rise
above it but it wasn't there to teach a
child a lesson child abuse and it wasn't
there for a a soldier who's trying to do
something good it wasn't there that
Soldier to lose their legs being killed
isn't lesson either for us to learn
abuse of any kind for someone isn't a
lesson for us to learn we're not that's
not a lesson we're not supposed to learn
that as a lesson but it
happens our soul is strong only God
knows what our soul went through and if
and when it was
wronged our soul is her life's song
walking in the woods it's you and just
your soul birds can feel it and they
sing a Love Song and your soul sings
along our soul is our eternal power a
light that can never die out a light
that shines bright long after we leave
this place our soul can be tall so tall
it can Tower there is no wall your soul
can't stand above and see all it stores
all of our
experiences deep within itself the soul
can store your faith you once had so no
matter if you lose your faith and path
with God it still holds true in your
soul thank God it never forgets it never
waivers Soul memory can Outlast
mountains as the rain slowly erode the
Rocks the soul still stays true long
after the Earth decays and oceans have
long since been blue the road isn't
always easy for a soul in a physical
body enduring life's ups and downs we
step on a nail yell and shout it hurts
so much our foot begins to swell but our
soul stays strong throughout
we break up with a friend it hurts the
heart again the pain can be unbearable
but our soul sits alongside of us and
rises above the Betrayal and holds a
candle to rebuild and heal while we once
again restore trust there comes a time
when we realize how much deeper our
light resides and how we are so much
more than we ever knew we are more than
any Earthly storm we are more than the
sun the moon and the stars Earth soul
forever lives on long after everything
else is
gone original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
spaced together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place
appear p untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion