hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 or 30 years
to wait for answers to their illnesses
life is precious and there's no time to
spare someone told me recently you
always say that who has 10 20 30 years
how many times can we hear that I said
how many times can we hear that how
about the person who's waited 20 years
for just a simplistic answer that I mean
that literally could could change
somebody's life and the answer isn't out
there for 20 30 years it's no joke I
mean sure if you're feeling great and
you got nothing wrong with you and life
is just you know darn
perfect on all kinds of levels well good
for you good for you you know absolutely
but hey you know if you haven't felt
good and you've been to a a zillion
doctors a zillian doctors I mean it
could feel that way for so many people
and you you know you've been everywhere
looking for help no one really cares
anymore and some I have people tell me
look Anthony nobody even cares anymore
I've been telling my same friend for
years I got this this going on and she
doesn't want to hear it anymore and you
know I've been telling this family
member that I got this going on and they
don't want to hear this anymore and you
know it's been a struggle it's been
really really hard for people and you
know you going to the different doctors
your different practitioners you have
all these different symptoms you got
unexplained chronic fatigue everything
else around it skin problems you know
restless legs can't sleep good insomnia
brain fog can't think confusion can't
function can't do what you need to do
catching colds and flu all the time I
could go on and on and on and so yeah
you know who wants to wait 10 15 20
years I'll say it over and over again
who wants to wait for something
simplistic a simple answer that could
change your life and that's what the
source that came to me at age for
allowed me to have for everybody is
answers finally some answers you know I
talk about Epstein bar a lot you guys
know that and I talk about other things
too obviously cuz you guys know that too
but you know I mean the upstein bar
thing I'm hearing out there like oh yeah
Epstein bar you could look online
Epstein bar yeah and just so everybody
knows yeah you can look online and
everything but no one matched up the
symptoms to Epstein bar until I brought
it to the table it's that critical to
know so you can get help it's it's one
of these things where we've known about
Epstein bar and and there's there's
information out there and there's some
data and you can get you there some
citations to different um studies and
stuff but there's nothing there it
wasn't until we matched up meaning here
right here okay we matched up the
symptoms to the problem to Epstein bar
the different stages if you've guys read
you know my first book you know there's
stage one stage two stage three stage
four goes into the thyroid that you know
we brought that to the table spirit and
I um same thing with all the different
tingles and numbness all the different
problems all the different brain fog all
the different issues all of it you know
the weight G all of that it all comes
down to Epstein bar and and um and we
had to bring those symptoms to people so
they could say oh my God and oh my God
moment like wait a minute this is
Epstein bar I had Mono this is a later
stage Epstein bar I am having
neurological problems it is Epstein bar
so people can heal and who has 20 years
to wait for that information not you're
not going to find it online somewhere or
in some new fancy printed book unless
it's came from me and it's not CIT to my
book because you know so it's no joke
when it comes down to people who haven't
had help haven't had answers need the
answers to heal no matter what it is
that we're talking about on the show no
matter what topics no matter what issues
we're talking about on the show it
matters it so matters it's not even
funny it's no joke it matters that much
and so what have had to do my whole life
and this the if this is the first time
you've logged on to the show ever and
you're like who is this if you want to
know what I've had to do I've had to be
the voice for people I've had to be your
voice your voice to getting to getting
people to you know to getting heard to
getting these problems heard so that the
information can get out there and you
know I've had to be the voice for people
to say hey look we don't we can't do
this anymore we can't take this anymore
we need help and I've had to be the
voice to say hey look this is real this
is what's going on it's not in your head
you don't have crazy women's syndrome
which is what they they documented years
ago and they said women were all crazy
that had a symptom you don't have that
you know it isn't just hormones cuz
hormones are blamed on everything now is
it isn't just genes because genes are
now the new thing blame everything on
genes see what happens is the medical
Industries they just don't have answers
so then they sell even alternative
medicine they sell them Concepts okay
now it's your genes everybody of course
we have genes of course genes are
actually real of course genes are in our
bodies of course we have hereditary
traits of course we have DNA but that's
not why we're sick that's not why we're
sick that's the newest crap being fed
into everybody so we have to wait
another 30 years for real
answers and then we're told you know
it's blamed on us once again you have
faulty jeans you just got crappy junky
dirty jeans and that's why you're sick
okay and oh yeah let's improve on your
jeans let's write a whole bunch of books
on how your jeans could get better it's
ridiculous There's real reasons why
everybody's sick so yeah when it comes
down to it who has 10 or 20 or 30 years
to wait for answers that's right I'm
going to say it over and over again and
I got to be the voice because that's
what Spirit intended that's what
happened when I came into this world
that's what happened at age four when I
diagnosed my grandmother of of lung
cancer and and it it it has never
stopped so we we need these answers
Today's Show so let's go on to Today's
Show hey sorry about that you guys I'm
going on a rant you know today going on
a rant today this afternoon so so hey
look Today's Show is about the hidden
antagonizer heavy metals again toxic
heavy metals heavy metal detox today
show is about the heavy metal detox you
know you folks might be doing some of
those heavy metal detoxes the heavy
metal detox smoothie that I've actually
put out there it's important because
there are these hidden antagonizers
theyve wreak havoc on our life they they
really knock things down they feed
viruses these tox toxic heavy metals you
got Mercury aluminum copper can you guys
name a few cadmium lead arsenic nickel
and there's probably more I'm not even
thinking about chromium Okay Chrome not
chromium but like Chrome okay yeah
Chrome alloy you name it Steels Steels
you name it they get into our system
they find their way in and we're going
to talk about how they find their way in
we're going to talk about you know how
long they've been in there and that's
what's really interesting how long these
medals have been there and you're
probably thinking well I don't know as
long as I've lived so far no no even
longer than you've lived so far in your
life isn't it
interesting so we're we're going to head
in there listen how is the life-changing
Foods book did I let you down I just
want to know I hope I didn't let you
down I killed myself on that book think
so if you're unhappy with what's in
there I just my apologies but I'm hoping
you're happy with what's in there and if
you haven't gotten the book yet get it
it's over 50 Foods all this information
about what the food does for you but the
book has more than that check it out out
it's really I mean I I think it's a
really good book because Spirit gave me
the information um and I I got it all in
there and uh and I I was even blown away
I was blown away by spirit's information
I was blown away and that's what happens
when spirit gives me the information I I
that's that's one of the perks about the
job of hearing Spirit since age for is
you know you get to hear this stuff
coming in this new profound information
coming in from Spirit and then you know
I get to hear it and be like whoo that
that blows me away so it's exciting so
um I I I love the book I hope you guys
love it I really do um so okay let's go
into this show let's do this show uh I'm
excited about this I really am heavy
metals um am I obsessed about toxic
heavy metals maybe so sometimes okay
maybe so but there's a real valid reason
and I've given you some of the history
before I've talked a little bit about uh
about that history in book one so you
you're probably aware of some of that
history already I've talked about it
before and I'm going to talk about it
again but give you a little bit more um
to it though cuz this is exciting about
the heavy metal detox and heavy metals
and everything else first of all you
know when it comes down to toxic heavy
metals do they give us symptoms yeah
they can they can give us ADHD add they
can give our children ADHD add really
easily Focus concentration problems they
can increase our viral issues like
viruses like Epstein bar feed off of
toxic heavy metals and then when that
happens we get more tired and more tired
and more tired we can get brain fog
irritability frustration we can get sibo
from toxic heavy metals and what's sibo
do you guys know by now probably you
folks know by now sibo is uh strepa
cacus even though practitioners don't
know that yet they just don't doctors
don't know that they just think it's an
overgrowth of bacteria they don't really
know what kind it's antibiotic resistant
strep strep Aus and that's you know
that's exactly what sibo is so um toxic
heavy metals tend to per uh like grow
and overgrow and bring that back in um
UTI okay that's you can when you have
elevated toxic heavy metals urinary
tract infections sinus infections sinus
problems you can easily catch more colds
and flu acne yes acne too on top of it
because acne is strep and an underlying
chronic systemic strep and affection
that's just percolating in the body for
years and years and years even from
childhood fatigue you can get headaches
migraines anxiety different bouts of
anxiousness different BS of anxiety
different forms of depression all from
toxic heavy metals and you can get OCD o
OCD can develop and get worse over time
do you know anybody who deals with OCD
do you know anybody who's dealt dealt
with it have you dealt with it and it
goes on and on and on so let's go into
some history a little bit let's go into
some history first of all I said earlier
I said before I said we have these toxic
heavy metals and they're in inside of us
and they're inside of us before we're
even
born what does that mean and and and how
does it work first of all the heavy
metals that are inside of us are older
than us they're older than us so the
original ones that we come into the
world with and we we're born with these
original toxic heavy metals such as
mercury and even some lead and you know
and some aluminum but especially Mercury
could be as old as a thousand years
thousand
years now it doesn't mean what I mean by
a thousand years the earth created that
mercury um you know before it was mined
long before a thousand years okay but a
thousand years ago and a little bit past
a thousand year i' probably go back even
two 3,000 years ago it was starting to
be mind okay it was it was worked
meaning there was there were people
digging it out of the earth digging it
out of the earth and um and not
cultivating it but Gathering it for use
and there was never a good use for
mercury ever was definitely one of the
blunders of humankind of mankind without
a doubt but the Mercury that's inside of
us can go back generation Generation
generation Generation generation and
keep on going 50
Generations okay 60 Generations 80
Generations 80 great great great great
great great great grandma and grandpas
okay and keep on going you know you can
use your imagination on that one and see
how far it takes you you can even play
with the math can go back a good couple
thousand years and so you know that's
that's basically how it works with us so
this toxic heavy metal goes for the ride
doesn't leave the body of anybody it
stays in the bodies stays in the cells
it gets passed on generation and we get
more intolerant to it in fact this time
around in the last 30 years we're more
intolerant to it than ever before in
history and our children are paying the
price and and I'm talking about new
Mercury that's entering into our bodies
now too through all all kinds of
different facilities I mean all kinds of
different ways uh it's falling out of
the sky it's dropping out of the sky out
of the air out of PLS it's Dr it's
floating in the sky it's in the
waters okay it's all over the place it's
in um our food okay it's in medical
stuff so it's in medical you know
medications it's in you know uh things
like that it's in places it's all over
the place I mean just look at
antibiotics antibiotics Harbors
petroleum so petrol fuel oil engine oil
as in
antibiotics engine oil and lots of
pesticides too because they're you know
genetically altered corn grain grown on
the planet for pharmaceutical use
sprayed with IM immense amounts of heavy
metal laced copper um aluminum Mercury
pesticides okay um mixed with petroleum
based engine oils yeah crazy right put
into an antibiotic capsule antibiotics
can be uh created without all that by
the way antibiotics you can you can make
an antibiotic and minus all that garbage
every bit of it just so you know so it's
there and and here's the thing that's
just literally an
antibiotic but when it comes down to
having Mercury in our systems from long
ago you might say well would if what if
nobody used mercury in my family in my
family line you know like how can I have
mercury in me from the old day you know
we can have mercury in us for the new
day did you ever have a can of tuna fish
did you ever have tuna did you ever have
um something else I'm trying to think
now what other options and which other
ways I know people who played with
broken thermometers I know people who uh
who family-owned dentistry and they
played with you know Mercury balls
running in their hands and running on
the floors when they're children and
little girls and little boys playing
with Mercury and there's just ways of
getting it it's in other places too it's
in pesticides sprayed inside homes so I
mean you could be growing up in a home
that was heavily sprayed before you your
family bought the home or owned the home
or the apartment heavily sprayed
Apartments Apartment complexes there's
still mercury in everything you know uh
pesticides aren't Mercury free it's not
like there's a big S on them Mercury
free there's anything goes in a
pesticide herbicide fungicide
rodenticide uh uh you know herbicide I
think I said that one already I can't
tell now so you guys where does the Old
Mercury come from let me give you an
example back in the
1800s at 7 19 and 1800s if you went to
the medical doctor so if you had an ache
a pain a stomach ache you broke your leg
twisted your ankle hurt your back um you
know had a bad tooth AE uh had a
migraine um let's see felt dizzy
whatever it was and you went to the
medical doctor you know un Medical
University Doctors okay conventional
ones if you went there first thing thing
they would give you is well they would
look at you for a moment and then they
would mix a nice big glass of water
mixed with part Mercury and you would
drink this Mercury Elixir this Mercury
tonic it's all through the 1700 and
1800s now well you could argue and say
well you know what my forefather
probably didn't go to a doctor that gave
a Mercury tonic no not true every single
doctor every medical doctor every
conventional
doctor U Mand
upon entering that doctor's office
getting exam you ingested a Mercury
tonic didn't matter what what what what
when where who you are what you are
child adult baby it didn't matter you
drank a Mercury tonic now the problem
with this is that it was not only
dangerous but it caused a lot of trouble
and the trouble it caused was before
you'd go to the
doctor you would get ready for the
Fallout if you were married and had
children um chances are your wife and
kids would lock down the house locked
the doors before you came back home and
made you stay away for a week before you
entered the home again so it meant loss
of work loss of family communication you
name it because when you went to the
doctor's office and you had a Mercury
Elixir you you became insane this is
well known you became insane it was
called quack quackery being quacked now
I'm going to tell you right now about
the whole quackery thing the whole quack
thing right now in our modern day in the
moment if you hear the word quack you
think it's an alternative doctor an
alternative
healer um an herbalist chiropractor that
has different thinking Homeopathy
homeopath that has different thinking
because quack has been associated with
anybody in alternative medicine that's
that's what quack has been associated
with so the whole quack thing's been
dumped on good doctors practitioners and
healers but let me tell you where quack
came from quack came from medical
doctors the term quack came from if you
went to the medical doctor they would
quack you they would quack you that's
right because they were the quacks they
were the quacks because when you went
into that that medical office and you
drank that mercury tonic for whatever
ailed you you went insane you became
quacked that was the quackery you went
home quacked and what happened is that
you'd go home chances are you could kill
your family you could do something
horrible you can there's there's stories
of just drooling for weeks and talking
Rhymes and R riddles and children's
Rhymes you end up in you can end up in
an alley for a week 3 days 4 days
depends on how severe the quackery
occurred this happened for hundreds of
thousands of people through the 1700s
and 1800s both abroad and here in the US
Okay the reason why you don't hear a lot
about it is because it was an absolute
epic disaster of I mean Epic Proportion
massive
disaster Abe Lincoln was Ill from
quackery himself meaning he had severe
depression from mercur Mercury Elixir
everyone experienced quackery at one
time it was horrendous so what happened
was everybody got wise they got wise and
they stopped going to doctors didn't
matter if they broke a darn leg they
wouldn't go to doctors and the medical
industry fell apart lost all its money
and hit rock bottom hit rock bottom you
won't hear that anywhere oh of course
not cuz we don't want to visit that God
forbid we don't want the truth to come
out the fact that in the 18 by the late
1800s nobody went to the doctor in men
medical universities weren't funded
anymore and everything was on such low
battery it was literally at a crash
point of non-exist existent doctors had
empty offices across the country no
matter what the case was because
everybody got wise to it they didn't
want to lose their lives anymore they
didn't want to lose their wives and
their kids and their families and their
jobs and that was quackery Quicksilver
is what it was it was so detrimental so
devastating to the people and that's
where the term came from guess how guess
what it was flipped it was flipped all
of a sudden you're alternative
practitioner oh you're a quack flipped
what a great way of flipping that what
happened was by the late 1800s because
nobody went to the doctor anymore and
the medical universities were out of
business and there was no funding
anymore and everything crashed the
alternative movement exploded it came
out of
nowhere homeopaths the first one
chiropractors the very first ones thank
God naturopaths naturopathy very first
ones meaning they were always there in
the in the back doing their thing but
they were ostracized they were beaten
down for a long time herbalists came out
healers came out and the birth of
alternative medicine was
born and in order to actually get the
conventional world back the conventional
medicine world back in order they put
out advertisement saying you go to the
chiropractor you're you're going to a
quack because decades a couple of
decades later people forget you know
decades two decades later you kind of
forget about some of the mistakes and
the main medical world advertised we no
longer carry Quicks over we no longer
deal with the Elixir so people trusted
him again went back to them again and
then the word quack was pushed on the
alternative doctors now the reason why
I'm talking about this is when your
great-grandparents and and your family
in the olden days in the 17 1800s they
drank those toxic Elixir and they
suffered consequences for a little while
and that mercury is still in their that
was in them passed on to the next
generation passed on Next Generation
Next Generation could have got passed on
to you and it could be in your cells CU
it is in your cells it's in all of our
cells you can't can't excape it so why
don't we get some of that Old Mercury
out of us because we're getting
intolerant to it and we can get that
stuff out of us and we can also get the
new stuff and here's here's something
about how Mercury works just so you know
Mercury gathers on its on itself it GA
it gathers it it um comes together you
can have Old Mercury in you or Mercury
that you got in you 10 years ago and if
you get new Mercury in you it comes
together it comes together it finds
itself it it's like two raindrops next
to each other on some glass and then you
just kind of rub them together and they
come to one you know two drops of water
can come together become one
drop that's how Mercury works so just so
you
know Mercury keeps on building on itself
and it could get more toxic over time if
you have a little bit of mild OCD and it
seems like it's getting worse part of
that could be it could be collecting
some more Mercury so we have to get it
out if you have anxiety and it tends to
get a little bit worse or it's getting
worse over the years could be collecting
a little bit of more Mercury there same
with depression now here's how it goes
everybody has toxic heavy metals in a
different area
of their
brain in a different area it's not all
the same you can have it in left
temporal load lobe you can have it in
the frontal lobe you can have have it in
the bottom of the frontal lobe you can
have it near the pituitary gland you can
have it in so many different places in
so many different
ways okay you can have it
anywhere anywhere in the brain and you
can have different different levels of
heavy metals little bit of mercury a
little bit of lead a little bit of
aluminum a little bit of copper someone
might have more lead some arsenic some
nickel and some Mercury someone might
have all Mercury a little bit of
aluminum everybody's different the apple
pie is different the recipe is different
for every single person so what does
that mean someone's depressed but in a
different way someone's got anxiety in a
different way hey you know how's how was
your depression working well mine is
kind of where I feel lonely all the time
well that's not my depression my
depression is I feel an emptiness well
that's not my depression my depression
feels I feel like a like a dark Cloud's
over my head raining hey that's not my
depression my depression is I I can't I
it's a it's a depth of Sorrow that can't
be explained that's not mine and it goes
on and on and on and
on and then we just classify it as just
depression same thing with anxiety I'll
say what's your anxiety like someone
might be like well I just can't sit
still I'm like really that's not bad at
all because that's different than
someone else I've heard where they feel
like jumping out of their skin and they
want to jump into a lake you know
everybody's different some people say
hey I my anxiety is so bad I haven't
eaten in a week I can't put food in my
stomach it's flipping too many times
everybody's anxiety is different to a a
a serious degree and why is that because
the toxic heavy metals can be in
different parts of the brain on
everybody but not only that they could
be
alloy alloy is a mix they're running off
each other they're they're helping each
other they're ricocheting off each other
they're reflecting frequency of the
different heavy metals are reflecting
off of each other aluminum reflecting
off of Mercury Mercury reflecting off of
copper you know an alloy is like a mix
of metals to make something stronger so
and lighter your bicycle you know they
don't make bicycles like they used to
bicycles like they used to were just
like
iron were they were like go to a tag
sale or an old antique shop and pick up
an old bicycle and break your back
putting that damn thing in the uh back
of your truck or car I mean it weighs
weighs a 400 lb I mean I'm sure it
doesn't weigh 400 lb but it could feel
like that and now bicycles today they're
light as air you can pick it up you can
put it on the back of your car it's
alloy it's it's a of metals make it
lighter and stronger well we have Alloys
in us at this point there's so many mix
of heavy metals plus alloy itself is a
group of metals we can get contamination
from all on its
own so there's a reason why we have all
these different symptoms and these
different levels of symptoms different
levels of brain fog and then when you
put viral components to it you guys you
put viral components to it like a virus
eating some toxic heavy metal a virus
eating Mercury a virus eating aluminum a
virus eating some arsenic then you have
something entirely different you get a
lot of different symptoms got a lot of
different Epstein bar symptoms because
Epstein bar likes a lot of heavy metals
and then it eats them bugs eat heavy
metals um chews them
up um goes the bathroom releases them
and they become more methylated
dangerous and they interfere with their
own
methylation which we're doing a
methylation show uh coming up I promise
we're going to do the MTHFR gene
mutation which is com total complete
confusion and has to be corrected at
least here at this show to start with so
that there's some hope that there's
actually some hope so we're constantly
not going down the wrong direction all
the time with misinformation out there
so so what happens is you know when the
virus feeds off heavy metals it releases
neurotoxic versions of those heavy
metals causing more anxiety more
Depression more memory loss more brain
fog and it can do that even without
viral intervention you can still have
OCD you still can have anxiety can still
can have memory loss with just heavy
metals themselves because they can run
off they can oxidize
oxidation these Metals oxidize and leech
they Lee into other tissue of the brain
liver organs the pancreas spleen they
get everywhere so we want to clean these
Mercury aluminum lead components out of
our body because it's really that
important because it could really get in
the way and I'm not just talking about
anxiety and depression I'm talking about
you know irritability frustration I'm
talking about like I said bacterial
overgrowth the brain fog of course
dizziness
anything um you can get migraines
headaches chronic migraines and
headaches you can have the shingles
virus involved eating a lot of heavy
metals we can have both things happening
at
once and this intolerance that we have
to toxic heavy metals is what's is is a
big part of what's happening and I talk
about it life-changing Foods you have
the um unforgiving for toxic heavy
metals are one of the unforgiving four
right we did that show on it you got you
got the radiation you got the viral
explosion that occurred in the last 100
years and 100 plus years and you have
all this going on but the toxic heavy
metals are kind of like a foundation
kind of like where you know where do you
want to go with your health to jump
started how do you want to change your
life how do you want to make something
better let's get the heavy metals out
and you'll start seeing things getting
better I want to tell you another story
of where we can get you know toxic heavy
metals from the past could say hey look
I did research on my genetic line my
family line we didn't drink any toxic
Elixir what what are you talking about
Anthony well did anybody in your family
line ever wear a felt hat at all ever a
felt hat going back from
1950 on down to,
1800 to 1780 do your research see if
anybody wore a felt hat somebody because
it was practically mandatory to wear a
felt hat as a man and what was soaked
into that felt hat Mercury lots of it
too off the charts we're talking off the
charts dangerous levels and amounts of
mercury were soaked into felt hats hat
makers had a 3 to 5ye
life um or what I should say you know um
we have 3 to 5 year uh sentence life
sentence is what I'm trying to say that
means that they had 3 to 5 years before
they died or became so ill from the
Mercury dipping the hats in the Mercury
Solutions when you became a hat maker it
was called and I'm not just talking
about say one aspect of hat making I'm
talking about the area of hat making
where you actually have to treat the
hats if you entered into that area of
hat making you didn't live long it was
called Mad Hatters so that's what it was
called Mad Hatters disease so you you
know was Mad Hatters mad is a Hatter
because you went utterly insane when you
worked with felt hats for a little while
but wearing felt hats lots of mercury
absorbed into the brow of every man in
every country Europe to the US so that's
also in our past and does this matter
yeah it matters because here's the deal
what you
see doesn't hurt you I guess that's the
that's the society we're in today and
planet Earth right here today it's like
you don't see it then it can't be
hurting you I don't see it so it can't
be hurting you oh you got symptoms Mrs
Jones um I think you're crazy or lazy or
bored because I can't find anything
wrong with you at the doctor's office so
maybe you're making it up maybe it's all
in your head back in I mean this has
happened in the 20s the 30s the 40s the
50s the 60s how many people went to the
doctor oh your exam looks fine so your
depression your hot flashes all the
different things that you're going
through your night sweats your anxiety
um your pains your aches and pains your
fatigue your chronic fatigue everything
must be in your head until the hormone
movement came on and then everything was
blamed on menopause which is a whole
another thing um which is all botched up
which is you know a whole another
botched up thing that we can talk about
that we have talked about we could
always talk about again down the road
but you know if we don't see it this is
the kind of world it is if I don't see
you catch that fish you said you caught
and you don't have a photograph of it to
prove it I don't think it
happened and that's the kind of society
we live in you know oh you're
storytelling oh maybe you're
storytelling on how sick you really are
there's a lot of teens and 20year olds
and um and young adults and and that are
actually suffering they go to college
they get sick they can't function
anymore they come back home they're
bedridden there's nothing wrong with
them doctors can't find anything and
they just lay they sick and they get
told they're making it up that they just
don't want to engage in life and then
the lime disease Saga came into town
where since now no one knows what's
wrong with anybody everybody gets a lime
diagnosis everybody does doesn't matter
what you do you just get a lime
diagnosis now we're going to do another
lime show down the road um so but the
point is it's got to see it to believe
it and if you don't see it it didn't
happen it's not true or it doesn't exist
it doesn't exist you can't see heavy
metals you can't see them I mean you
just can't see him if you saw the
mercury in a can of tuna then you would
you would know you would see it it would
shine it'd be like you open your can of
tuna and say whoa that's a lot of
mercury in this tuna today guess I'm not
eating it but you can't see it it's a
lusive it's the hidden
antagonizer that's the whole point and
so it's hard to say ah maybe I got some
heavy metals in the past maybe it's
creating a symptom I don't know can't
see it Dr can't see it got to take it
seriously because it's not genes that
are taking us down right now it's the
intolerance to toxic heavy metals being
one of them we're getting intolerant to
it our children are this is why children
are suffering with autism at this point
autism and you know um an ADD and ADHD
and more than that all kinds of
different disorders hundreds of them
actually could name them list after list
because of mercury intolerance toxic
heavy metal int tolerance we're at this
this point we're at this crazy point
right now in time in history where we
have to clean up so what do I like to do
what do I like to use to clean clean the
metals up the heavy metal detox the
heavy metal detox some of you guys are
probably doing it you folks are probably
actually doing the heavy metal detox
right now I'm sure and so what's in the
heavy metal detox what makes it so good
why does it matter because in the heavy
metal detox there are five components
five components that grab metal hold on
to it and take it to the end they take
it to the end what that means is it
doesn't let the metals go and
redisperse back into your bloodstream
redisperse back into your organs
redisperse back into places in your body
back into your brain and so forth so
let's talk about these
ingredients one is spirulina I don't
care what you've read I don't care what
you see what someone told you it is by
far way by far better than any Corella
I'm going to talk to you about Corella
for a second Corella is the clumsiest
most
irresponsible incompetent
substance not anybody who recommends it
it has nutritional value like Corella
has nutritional value it is good for you
in many ways I don't recommend it
because it really stinks at Gathering
heavy metals I'll tell you why because
it drops them Picks Them Up drops them
that's what it does it doesn't pick them
up out of the brain it can't go that far
so it's not one of those kind of heavy
metal reboot removal systems you know
Corella it doesn't pick it out of the
brain it doesn't get it out of the liver
really it's basically its only option is
to get it out of the intestinal tract
but when it picks it up out of the
intestinal tract it drops it again
before it can even take it out before it
can even bring it out of the body
Hawaiian spirina won't do that it
doesn't have that dropping effect and if
it does have any dropping effect at all
it's going to synergistically work with
the barley grass juice extract so that's
why you need the barley grass juice
extra extract I like vimergy that's my
favorite one but the barley grass juice
extract combined with the spirulina work
off of each other the
spirulina likes to get the metals out of
the brain it likes to get the metals out
of the central nervous system the liver
the barleygrass juice powder um that one
likes to get it out of the spleen
intestinal tract the pancreas the
thyroid the the reproductive system and
they work off of each other and then
cilantro it's another one to throw into
the to the bag of goods here cilantro
goes into Deep hardto Reach places it
goes back for the Mercury of the past
the Mercury of the past I'm telling you
about that's tormenting our world as we
speak now people giving them symptoms
that you can't explain so Sal goes deep
in the deep down and gets them gets it
from places of yesty year and then just
when cilantro gets a little lazy and
it's trying to make it to the finish
line and if it drops that mercury now it
drops that toxic heavy metal that
aluminum the wild blueberries are there
and the wild blueberries are the most
powerful by the way powerful ways of
getting toxic heavy metals out of the
body out of the brain they go right to
the brain they pull them out of the
brain but what the wild blueberries do
is they fill in the spaces Where Metal
was left Where Metal left off I mean
metal oxidizes leaves little pockets and
if you've heard that somewhere else that
came from me it came from here it's the
only place that ever came from along
with a lot of the information we we
share here I say that in case you get
lost you might go somewhere well they're
talking about that too but what's going
to happen is there's a trap probably
going to be laid out where then it goes
off into Corella or it goes off into the
MSO or it goes off to something else so
just you know this is the way to do it
right here so the wild blueberries goes
deep into places pulls out toxic heavy
metals in Pockets hard to- reach places
where it's oxidizing and leeching off
causing memory issues causing you to
forget your car
keys and then it starts to fill in those
Pockets by repairing tissue radically
repairing tissue with the antioxidants
that wild blueberries
possess so that's the power of the wild
blueberries and the wild blueberries
pick up where others may drop along the
way the barley grass the cilantro the
spirina they work off each other it's a
team and then you got the Atlantic douls
it's a sea vegetable Atlantic douls it's
a sea vegetable d u LS e and you can get
Atlantic Sea dolls I like main Coast sea
vegetables for their
that's my favorite but you might be
somebody out there that reads something
and you might find that seaweeds or dos
or any kind of seaweed comes from the
ocean so the oceans are getting polluted
they got mercury in them and they got
radiation in in them and everything else
so you might say well I'm not going to
eat any seaweed what's he talking about
you're just going to pollute your body
that's not how it works you can take the
dirtiest piece of Dos out of the
slimiest ocean we have on the planet and
chances are if you consumed it it would
draw more out of you then it would leave
behind all the way to the end cuz
seaweed doesn't let go it doesn't let go
that's how seaweed works it opens the
capacity to pull in more absorb like a
sponge and take out that's what it does
so Atlantic Sea dols is not slimy and
it's not dirty and it's amazing stuff
and incorporate a little bit of that too
and what you can do is pull Metals out
from yester year I like it look I like
my heavy metal detox smoothie I like two
bananas two cups of wild blueberries I
get the Frozen wild blueberries two cups
one cup of
cilantro one cup of orange juice okay I
use the fresh stuff I'll squeeze oranges
I'll just squeeze them with my hand
right into the right into the cup and
then scoop out the pits or seeds you
know or you can you orange juice you
know um squeezer whatever an orange
juice squeezer juicer or if you don't
have any other options get your purest
healthiest orange juice even if it's
pasteurized get your purest healthy
pasteurized orange juice um that has no
preservatives whatsoever in it and
nothing else in it and you can pour use
that if you really had to you can also
in the rest of the um ingredients would
be like the barleygrass juice powder one
teaspoon one teaspoon of Spirulina you
don't have to use a lot if you don't
want to one small handful of Atlantic
dolls and you got yourself the heavy
metal detox now you know you can you can
make a smaller one if you want do what
you feel that you want to do I like
doing celery juice too I like having
that on the same morning because it's it
with that the heavy the the mineral
salts from the celery juice they provide
like a secret weapon of flushing helping
flush the metals out of the liver while
you're extracting them so it's you know
kind of gives everything kind of a heaw
push uh heave along the way and gets
things out so I like the the um celery
juice so I want to talk about what like
why we be these heavy metals out and why
this is so important to do this heavy
metal detox because
neurotransmitters are getting affected
in us from these toxic heavy metals
neurotransmitter
chemicals are being destroyed when we
have memory problems when we have brain
fog when we have confusion when we just
have kind of brain fatigue when we have
even other kinds of kind of just not
feeling like motivated mild depression
to severe depression you know anxiety
different levels of anxiety and the list
goes on
neurotransmitters get damaged and short
circuited from toxic heavy metals so you
have a neuron in your brain okay
electrical nerve impulse is running
through that neuron running across that
neuron it's
driving with the use and help of a
neurotransmitter chemical that's sitting
on that neuron so the neuro the
electrical nerve impulse is running
across that neuron running across that
Highway
and it's and it's it's fuel is that
neurotransmitter and our
neurotransmitters are getting burnt out
in this day and age it's not
genes that are given up on us you know
we don't have these bad genes cuz since
nobody knows what's wrong with anybody
in chronic illness I'm going to be
straightforward and honest I'm not
talking about when you break a leg and
there's bone fragments and you get an
x-ray and the doctor knows where they
are I'm not talking about you know um
liver transplants and heart transplants
I'm not talking about when your
gallbladder explodes cuz it got you know
obstructed from a big Stone I'm not
talking about obvious stuff that we
catch on CAT scans and we have you know
ways of measuring it ways of weighing it
I'm not talking about neurosurgery for
getting an aneurysm out of somebody's
brain these things are
incredible you know and and and I have
tremendous respect and admiration to
doctors and surgeons and conventional
medicine and I'm talking about chronic
illness literally almost everything else
is a mystery it's a mystery right now I
don't care what anybody says it's a
mystery and and we need to put the
answers out there I got to be that voice
like I was saying for everyone I have to
and then hey you can be the voice too
with me that's what I'm hoping just deep
down inside I'm hoping you're the voice
with me uh you know and that because
that's the whole point if we're the
voice together that's even that's even
better it doesn't get any better than
that and and so it's about this kind of
information that's so critical it's
about that oxidation that's happening in
the brain the neurotransmitter chemicals
in the brain it's not genes going wrong
that's just another way of of everybody
you know if con the conventional world
and it falling back on the alternative
world now because there's so many
conventional doctors that went
alternative that they kind it all comes
over shifting over that blame on us is
being driven
over to the once complete and total pure
view of the alternative M movement it's
been flipped over on us these ideals
like for instance you know autoimmune
disease is your body attacking itself
wrong we know that we've explained that
a million
times a bunch of times it feels like a
million times but I'll just keep on
going a million more same thing with the
genes like that it's all blamed on genes
now it's not so we got these toxic heavy
metals burning out
neurotransmitters it's fixable
it's it's
healable it can get better we can get
our neurons better we can get rid of the
oxidation the corrosion of the metals
out of the brain we can get the
electrical nerve impulses stronger and
better we can get the lights back on in
our bodies we can get the lights back on
in our bodies and we can heal and head
in the right
direction and I've said this before once
before if you had a street
and it was blocked with a whole bunch of
metal barrels and you ran your car right
into it you'd smash right into it and
that's what heavy metals like when it's
in our brains and it's in our liver and
it's in other places when these
electrical impulses these frequencies
they're driving through our body to give
us Vitality they run into these metal
barrels and they just short circuit they
crash they s short circuit do you ever
know anybody it could even be you do you
ever know anybody that's like like well
I had a short circuit I couldn't get
that thought I couldn't think about it
anymore or I got post-traumatic stress
syndrome from this whole thing going on
or I that's too hard for me even to go
there or to think about you know I can't
that's just it's blowing up my head do
you ever run into anybody like that
where something's like blowing up their
head and they can't go there because
their emotions take over because what a
lot of what's happening is when you have
high heavy metals you get these short
circuits because electrical impulses
start flying in different directions cuz
it's hitting different various metals
and the information of what someone's
telling you or something happening or
something emotional is happening you
can't bear it you can't bear it you
can't handle it cuz all kinds of you
know short circuiting is happening this
doesn't mean that you're crazy no this
means that you're totally sane and then
some and then some it just means you got
some things that are toxic heavy metals
that are in there so when something is
too much
or when something when something's too
heavy on you it's hard because the
neurotransmitters can't handle the load
the electrical impulses are running into
little deposits of metal and this
doesn't mean a lot of metal you know
when I do scans on
people and and we're going to do we're
going to do some more of that too we're
going to have some fun and take on
callers in the future not in the show
but in the future and when I do scans on
people I see the heavy metals inside the
brain they reflect like Christmas tree
lights like if you were outside looking
inside a warm house you know on a
December day or December evening and
it's dark outside and the lights are on
in the house and the Christmas trees
through the window the big picture
window and all the lights are coming
through I can kind of see it like that
these lights light up all through
somebody's body and the deposits of
metal they have and when if I go into a
place that's busy and there's a lot of
people around and man I see those lights
lighting up everywhere we got lots of
heavy metals in us and it's time to get
them out and so we're going to work
together on this this this is exciting
you can unfasten your seat bels now you
can take a deep breath and relax and
take your seat belt off the heavy metal
talk is always always
intense so look along with the heavy
metal detox which is seems so simplistic
once again it's two bananas two cups of
wild blueberries one cup of cilantro one
cup of orange juice one teaspoon of
barleygrass juice powder one teaspoon of
Spirulina one small handful of Atlantic
dolls okay just listen what you can do
and there's also with this heavy metal
detox smoothie you know it's optional to
add water to blend if you need to so if
you need to add a little water to blend
you can put it in a high-speed blender
blend all the ingredients until smooth
if a if a thinner consistency is desired
add up to one cup of water if if you
need to maybe a little coconut water if
you really want to if that's something
you like start with this and take out
some foods that don't help when you're
getting rid of toxic heavy metals take
out the eggs take out any dairy products
milk cheese butter yogurt take those out
if you can okay don't have any pork if
you if you love animal products lower
them to once a day so if you love animal
products and you're eating free range
chicken and grass-fed beef lower it to
once a a day and if you if you're
plant-based vegetarian or vegan or
something or plant-based um lower your
nuts and seeds down lower your oils down
a little bit and so that you're you so
you're not on a lot of blood fat so when
you start getting these heavy metals out
they leave you but don't go hungry make
sure you bring in a lot of fruits and
vegetables and other things in there I
stand behind you 100% I love you guys
dearly you need to know that know that
in your heart I care about you I love
you dearly I believe in you I stand
behind you 100% I know what it's like
not to get answers hang in there one day
at a time love you
bye-bye