we're live right now talking about the
mm 1500 it's on sale right now but we're
making hummus which is gonna be really
fun
we're making banana ice cream i might
make some mango ice cream too got some
frozen mango right here you guys this is
gonna be great i'm juicing
you're going to talk about the power of
celery too why it's so critical to juice
why is everybody drinking it everybody's
drinking it every influencer is drinking
it they're all drinking it you see it
it's everywhere you see it with them
holding it oh i'm drinking celery don't
want to say anything no everybody's
drinking celery juice we're going to
talk about that
and we're going to be doing what else
we're going to do an ice cream hummus
the fat free hummus
and low-fat hummus with the machine so
that's really going to be cool so we're
doing the low-fat hummus with the
machine what you see in front of me
right here is you see some beautiful
kale right here it's from the garden you
see some celery that's not from the
garden that's actually conventional
celery you guys it's conventional it's
not even organic that's conventional
celery right there
got some cilantro right here from the
garden right here okay got some herbs
too i'm going to show you how to run a
few herbs into the machine while making
the hummus you guys that's going to be
sick it's going to be insane because the
hummus is going to be coming out
and i'm going to be dropping some herbs
i'm going to throw a hot pepper in there
this is going to be really fun i got my
lemons right there i got my frozen
bananas here because we're going to make
ice cream right now i'm just giving you
guys a rundown on what i got going going
on
it's good to see everybody coming on
here so this is exciting this mm 1500
you guys
food costs going up going up i said it a
year ago i said it a year ago the reason
why i like the mm-900 and the mm 1500
right here is because it saves me money
and i know it's saving other people
money too so when they're juicing it's
saving saving the money so what happens
is when you go to a juice bar
you're paying more now for the juice
than ever before in a juice bar right
when you make it at home to help heal
yourself you're paying away less when
you use a juicer that squeezes more out
of the celery and out of the greens
right
when you use a juicer that's squeezing
more and more out of it you're saving
more money that's the whole point before
the food crisis like where the food food
prices are going up right before that i
was already saving myself a few thousand
dollars a year more
with actually doing like the mm-900
right
you guys by the way we're live on
medicalmedium.com we're live streaming
on the website we're live on tick tock
you guys we're live on facebook youtube
we're live on twitch we're live on
rumble we're live on we're live on
telegram we're live which is incredible
good to see you guys so we're live on
getter too as well
so what i love about
saving money with the juicing is because
i'm seeing friends going to juice bars
right they go into a juice bar and
they're like why was my juice 20
why was my celery in green juice 20
why was my green juice in la 25
now right the price and that's all over
the country and around the world the
prices are going up right so what i love
about juicing at home
myself is the juicer pays for itself and
it's saving me money and that's what's
happening so every time i'm juicing
every single morning i'm saving myself
money it's paying for itself which is
incredible so the juicer pays for itself
over and over and over again i get big
glasses of celery juice that i'm not
paying 25 for
because it's squeezed this juicer
squeezes so much out of it so that's
just cool all on its own man so
important so let's start making some ice
cream right now
so you guys
we're gonna do banana ice cream lynn
hannah says
want to thank you for all your great
amazing books and i have healed from
toxicities and chemicals i had the heavy
metal smoothie and the celery juicing
had been a game changer
i had eczema and asthma as a kid and
then sinus
and then
mind brain issues and then psychiatry
got me and told me i had all sorts of
things all before the internet but eight
years ago i healed it all
and now off all meds and still learning
more ordered your two new books for
october which is the brain books
i have them over there right there and i
can't wait good to see you on here thank
you for being on here let's make some
ice cream
so what i love about the ice cream
okay is it's actually so clean
so good for you it's insane when you
think about how clean and how good for
you it is that alone right there and
then it's great for kids and everything
else and you know today's father's day
right
right happy father's day to all the
fathers out there today is father's day
and the one thing
i've seen over and over again all these
years
right
guys don't take care of themselves
they don't take care of themselves good
they get the heart attacks they get the
heart problems they get the bad livers
they get the prostate problems
they get the kidney diseases the kidney
problems they get the diabetes to get
all of that
what better for dad to start juicing
that's what i always tell people i say
every day of the year never mind
father's day but every day of the year
right
so we're gonna make some ice cream right
now i'm gonna turn this thing on okay
but
you guys
let's have some fun let's do it i got
some frozen bananas right here
and
i'm gonna take this
i'm gonna put a banana in here
right
here we go let's get that banana down in
there let's make sure everything's
working
all right
there we go we got the ice cream going
right now you guys you know i love
banana ice cream guilt-free baby
guilt-free
how many times have you seen somebody
eat a whole bunch of fatty dairy cow ice
cream
in front of the tv or in front of a
movie every night and then you eat a big
bowl of ice cream and you're like uh
boy did i just mess up
boy i just mess up
well don't worry you can have some ice
cream you can have some fatty cow heart
attack ice cream and liver disease
creating ice cream
right
you can have that cow milk cream ice
cream in front of the tv every night
you're not messing up
we don't want you to have to worry about
it you can have that
no you're messing up right it's terrible
right here this is fat free
clean ice cream
this is so
so good it really is right
i'm gonna put one more banana in here so
what i'm gonna do
you guys
i love the mm 1500 the stuff you can do
with this machine is insane like i'm
only doing a couple of things today like
i'm gonna do the hummus
i'm gonna do the green juice how about
if we get it in here
all right
we're making a tall one
because that's what i do over here
at aws bar and grill
you want an ice cream
at aws bar and grill we can get you an
ice cream
no problem
let's just shut the machine down for a
second
all right
at aws bar girl we aim to please here
yes so i have this banana ice cream
right here which is really awesome can i
show you guys up close can you see that
on tick-tock you guys
right
this isn't disease-creating ice cream no
that's why i call this the medicine
machine you can green juice juice do
this make hummuses make salsas make nut
milks
make ice cream right it's the disease
fighting machine is what it is like the
medicine maker that's what it is right
which is incredible all right so let's
get a little bit of seasonings and stuff
like this on here you guys by the way
we're live streaming
even on medicalmedium.com which is
insane i got a little cinnamon right
here i want to show you up close what i
got here okay
and you guys know i work with omega
right look
i'm putting a little cinnamon on top of
this ice cream right on top here let me
get this in the view yeah nice
yeah man
nice i got some cinnamon on top
you can put as much as you want on there
right now i'm going to put some ginger
on top of this ice cream you guys on
tick tock if you tried this you would be
like that dude's got something
he's got something going here cinnamon
on top of here too right
yeah or do that hey
how about some vanilla extract on top of
here
let's do that excited about that
a little bit of vanilla extract how
insane is that
okay that's that's that's insane
you guys this is going to be so good
vanilla extract on top of here with
cinnamon and
and ginger okay
that's crazy
that is crazy
for sure
if you guys don't mind i'm gonna have
just a little
tiny
little tiny bite right here if you guys
don't mind all right
oh my god that's that's that's off the
charts
that's off the charts
that's out of bounds man
samuel says
all that is is the ice cream it's just
frozen banana sandy it's just frozen
banana
you can use mango i'm gonna run a little
mango through there right now let's make
a little sorbet okay
link is in the description check it out
ah this is so good
this is so good you guys i just want to
like
i want to hang up the internet right now
and i just want to go sit somewhere with
this
and just like tank out and just just
forget about everything just forget
about everything and just tank out and
just be like
what what was i doing
live look live
all right
let's turn this thing on
let's go
just going to get the rest of this ice
cream out of here
and put it over here
all right let's make some sorbet
i got frozen mango
pop them in here
a little banana ice cream left that's
fine
that's a little treat at the bottom of
my sorbet
hey guys this is
insane okay all right all right
out of control
yep
so easy
so easy it's insane
like dude it's so easy
you guys i call this the medicine maker
because it's like you you're doing the
anti-aging with all this
the beta carotene in there
right
incredible
i'm making some sorbet frozen sorbet
with mango right
gonna back this out a little bit because
that thing is frozen like no other
there we go
nice
look at that
you know i really love the sorbet
because
it's just guilt-free guilt-free
look i get it though everybody you know
teach its own man everybody's own right
to what they want to do and eat but i'm
telling you i love this so let me show
you this right here sorbet i'll give you
an up close right there that's the
sorbet you can actually smooth it out if
you want you can make it look any way
you want to make it look
that's there you go there's no cream in
here
there's no like bad sugar in here
there's nothing it's just frozen mango
and it's incredible just as it is stands
just like that right there
it's so awesome you guys just made some
sorbet
we got some banana ice cream we made too
and i'm gonna try the sorbet let me try
a little bit of it right
so good
cold brain free
brain freeze man
brian freeze
michelle l thank you aw the newsletter
was amazing sign up to my newsletter you
guys when you get a chance newsletter
videos exclusive every sunday excuse the
videos check it out link is in the
description
all right you guys let's move on a
little bit we got more to do
and i got a guest coming today by the
way
because i'm excited i actually have a
guest coming
so you guys might want to hang around
and the guest isn't dr nesbitt
it's another guest all right you guys
let's just kind of move these over a
little bit it's another guest
one of my friends
all right
so let's do
some juicing right here
millions are juicing celery right now it
is saving lives
sandy torrence says what is the name of
the machine again
mm-1500 right
link is in the description
mm-1500 megajuicers.com but the link is
in the description
it's on sale 20 off free shipping right
now
this is a complete nutritional system
which is incredible complete nutritional
system the mm900 is on sale too which is
incredible celery juicer this one's an
incredible celery juicer too
so
benefits of celery juicing
i mean you can just go on forever with
the benefits as far as what it's doing
for people it's incredible so look i got
some kale here i'm gonna run a little
bit of kale through here as well but
we'll just do a little straight celery
juice to start with so if you're doing
straight celery juice
here we go
i washed this celery really good this is
conventional celery
just so you know
if you got organic celery
incredible
right
couldn't get any organic right now
so i was like you know what
still incredible to juice
this
conventional celery absolutely wash it
really good
so what i'm doing right now
is i'm doing straight
celery
what you'll notice is the pulp is not so
sloppy wet
because it's extracting so much out of
the celery
yeah
now
the whole thing about celery in itself
is it's turning lives around
here's the here's the point that's
actually kind of funny there's a lot of
people juicing celery it's keeping them
afloat while they're doing all this bad
stuff
so they're doing all this bad stuff
they're doing supplements that are bad
like supplements that are actually not
good for them they're doing other things
that are bad they're eating things that
aren't good for them they're drinking
things that aren't good for them and
then they're juicing celery and the
celery is keeping them afloat while
they're doing all this other bad stuff
the celery juice is keeping them alive
it's keeping their skin clear it's
keeping their mind working better
the electrolytes and celery is like no
other when you're doing celery juice
it's critical to do it by itself in the
morning
and then you can do celery and like a
green a leafy green i'll show you how to
do that at the end of the day
you guys just came on here sale mm-1500
i'm going to make a few things
so
right now i'm making some killer celery
juice
germ theory you're worried about mineral
deficiencies that's a great way to clear
up mineral deficiencies is by using
celery juice because of the trace
mineral salts are so
so over the top that's one of the things
that really helps santara's healing good
to see you
you see celery juice all the time
keeping them afloat right you guys
hundreds of millions of people are
drinking celery juice around the world
they're feeling better they're getting
their lives back their inflammation is
dropping because they're knocking down
their viral load they're helping to
detox their liver they're helping to
detox their body
that's the difference that's what celery
juice does you can't get that from other
things it doesn't work
one of the most powerful tools it's one
of the most
powerful tools for chronic illness it's
a medical medium tool
people are closet drinking it everywhere
and i'll tell you what
everybody everybody right all the
influencers they're all trying to sell
their potion they're all trying to sell
their stuff out there right so they
don't want to talk about their celery
juice anymore because they can't make
any money off of celery juice and they
don't want to make celery farms rich
so but they're drinking it everybody's
drinking it it's the largest crop in
produce there is right now in the world
the health food stores get deliveries
where it's just a truck of celery that's
never happened in our history it's just
really amazing how it works okay so we
got
we got some celery juice right there
we're also going to do some kale juice
too
so i'm going to run a little kale in
there now
so
we can actually do some kale now what i
recommend is you do celery juice by
itself in the morning on an empty
stomach you guys know 16 ounces 8 ounces
16 ounces try a minimum 16 ounces 32
ounces if you can every single morning
on an empty stomach to start cleaning up
the liver to start cleaning up the
organs to help kill off all the
pathogens that aren't supposed to be in
your intestinal tract the bad pathogens
right
you want to get rid of all that
so
i'm just running a little kale through
here
jenny tinkle boss says best juicer i've
ever used loved it aw
honored you're here
now what i'm doing is i'm running a
little bit of dinosaur kale through here
this would be an afternoon or at the end
of the day or evening drink right here
because you want the celery by itself in
the morning
but now i'm doing a kale
santara's healing said oh my god the
recent hits on celery juice while
selling their coffee products yeah i
know
know all about it and thank you for
mentioning it too it's a good reminder
that that's what they're doing they're
selling their
they're selling their coffee
the drug dealers are really out there
heavy right now you guys because so many
people are depressed so many people are
suffering emotionally so the drug
dealers are taking advantage of all
those people
so they're selling all their caffeine
products so the drug dealers are really
out there right now
selling like their caffeine products
left and right to try to keep people
high
it's like it's it's really sad actually
when you think about it so i'm running
some kale through here
so this is a kale celery juice but i
started it out with straight celery
and
that's what you want you want straight
celery is what you want right pulp nice
and dry i mean you guys got to see this
i'll show you up close right here
see this bulb
see how like dry it is it falls apart
right
it's got that like real dry kind of look
to it that's where you're saving money
right there so when you buy a juice they
just keep on going up in price in the
stores because that's going to happen in
about six months when you go to the
health food store in about six months
from now when you go to right any kind
of juice bar or health food store you're
gonna see if you ever want a green juice
of any kind even the crappy junky green
juices that are all pasteurized right
when you go
and get your green juice you're gonna
see the price of the green juice go like
three dollars more
and then four dollars more they already
are right
when you have your own juicer and you're
squeezing everything out of it you're
actually saving money and you're doing
the reverse of that right so it's really
that's that's what i love about it
so let's
get this uh set up right here
rosvita says on facebook celery juice
has changed my life for the better thank
you i need that juicer right the mm-1500
let's get this celery juice
let's get this poured out
seskia says dermatologists said to take
antibiotics and topical steroids to take
away perioral dermatitis from mask and i
said no thank you awesome and i started
celery juice and it healed it in two
weeks completely
incredible
so happy for you are you kidding i'm so
happy seeing you come out of any kind of
suffering right is it's what it's all
about
i don't want you suffering i want you
free from suffering that's the whole
point this is the chronic illness
fighting you know strategy right here
that's what it is decelerates juice the
really incredible food all of it amy
says i just made some banana ice cream
with my knee juicer thank you for
inspiring me yum yum mine's over there
kind of defrosting a little bit right i
just made it
and
get a close-up on this if you can you
might not be able to get you might not
be able to see it so easy there you go
voila
that's a kale celery juice right there
right
yeah it's medical medium clumsy
i think medical medium is clumsy
he's done this too many times
all right
that's the celery juice right there you
guys now like i said before i put kale
in there
and that's great because that's a kale
celery juice something you do in the
afternoon or at night or something like
that if you want which is incredible
right it's an entirely different weapon
for chronic illness but celery juice on
its own
is unmatched in the morning especially
when you do it in the morning that's the
point that's when it grabs on and goes
into the brain gets into your glial
cells gets to the neurons cleans up the
liver digs the poisons out
helps people reverse their depression
depersonalization their anxiety their
ocd their bipolar their schizophrenia
all of it and that that's the key right
there so many people feel better from it
wendy
i've healed my eczema panic attacks
migraines fibromyalgia digestive issues
hair thinning neurological symptoms and
other with cj celery juice you guys and
medical medium protocol thank you so
much on facebook wendy thank you for
being here incredible so you guys let's
make something else let's work on
something else we're making right
so i'm going to move my celery juice
over
just right here for a moment
pierre says i drink celery juice but
some people say that celery juice
damages the kidneys every day oh they
would know huh they would know and this
thing is this the case anthony question
mark what should we do about that
damages the kidneys really it doesn't
damage the kidneys it turns lives around
heals people gets people better
so many people are healing so many
different things with their celery juice
right
that's made up there's no study that
shows celery juice damages a kidney
there's no there's no study there's no
review study there's no
paper that can prove it there's nothing
out there i'll tell you what kills your
kidneys and kills them fast high protein
high fat
you want to kill your kidneys high
protein high fat i'm talking vegan or
animal you can you can high protein your
kidneys to death as a vegan and a
plant-based person
you can high protein your kidneys to
death
as an animal protein person keto animal
protein whatever animal protein doesn't
matter what what brand what style
whatever
you can kill your kidneys with high
protein your kidneys get a viral
infection that starts the process off
and if anybody has a viral infection in
their kidneys nobody knows about for
years and years and years we end up
killing the kidney because the kidney
can't keep up with the viral infection
so we end up killing the kidneys with
high protein high fat that's how we
damage kidneys that's how we get kidney
stones we get the kidney stones from
high protein high fat destroying our
kidneys and then the other thing is
caffeining our kidneys to death high
caffeine caffeine consumption every
single day coffee that's how we kill our
kidneys and you know what i can
guarantee you anybody that said hey
you're gonna hurt your kidneys with
celery juice is selling caffeine
i can guarantee you they're selling
caffeine
okay and they're the drug dealers right
so listen
here's the thing don't add anything to
your celery juice make sure you do it on
an empty stomach in the morning if you
can that's best
don't purchase a celery juice off the
shelf be like
yeah can i can i get that off the shelf
there okay i got my celery juice off the
shelf at the health food store
it's hpp
if it's on the shelf in the health food
store unless they juiced it that day and
then put it up in their own bottle
but it's if it's not and it's a brand if
you find a celery juice brand
on the store shelf somewhere out on the
shelf
it's hpp'd you guys it doesn't work
it's high pressure pasteurization you
think it's raw you think it's fresh
uh-uh
it's not
it's not raw it's not fresh if it's on
the shelf
and it's got a due date on there and
it's a brand it's high pressure
pasteurization okay
i can't tell you guys
i'll tell you the difference with
medical medium
and the others out there
right
here's the difference okay
i wasn't in it
to just make peace
to just get along with the cool kids
the cool kids in the industry
right that's why i wasn't in it for that
i was i was in it instead to get you the
truth it didn't matter how many people
didn't like what i was doing it didn't
matter
okay
it wasn't about being with the cool kids
it was about working for the chronically
ill but the problem is the cool kids
broke into the business
and they're selling their caffeine drug
dealing stuff and trying to get you on
it they're selling all their garbage
they're selling their hpp celery juice
because they want a bank
they're selling all their crap
they're selling their
right
psychedelic mushrooms they're selling
anything and everything
and then they're selling their apple
cider vinegar they're selling everything
that hurts people
because it's the cool people out there
so it's all the cool people and i what
happened was
i didn't want to play that game and be
like oh i don't want to piss off the
those dudes that are selling their apple
cider you know chewy you go means i
don't want to piss off the coffee guys
and all the coffee business guys that
are getting into this you know getting
into the health scene
i don't want to piss off
right sick psychedelic mushroom people
man because you piss them off they stop
following you i don't want to piss off
everybody out there but guess what i
have i have pissed them all off
i have because it's not about hanging
with the cool guys
and trying to be cool and screw the
people who are sick like screw the
people who are sick with chronic chronic
illness who cares just sell them the
caffeine sell them the apple cider
sell them the whatever
just you know sell them the shoelace
heat so they dry out their intestinal
tract and get chronic dehydration in
their bloodstream
just sell all their garbage right you
know sell their pearl powder which tears
up the lining of the intestinal tract
i didn't want to be like you know always
like dancing around and trying to like
oh cool kids can i come on your podcast
because i'm going to talk good about
your caffeine cool kids can i go and
hang out with you because i want to look
like i'm cool
it screws over the chronically ill it
knocks them back it hurts the
chronically ill and i didn't want to do
that so it's all about giving it
straight to you and i still can't
understand why i have to be the only one
out there that's still giving it
straight where everybody else is they're
all just trying to please the cool cats
screw the chronically ill they just want
to please the cool people all right
let's get going i want to make some
hummus
bev says i love you i love your sunday
video on hives last sunday i am right at
the start of it and can you talk more
about it yeah i mean i can i could talk
a little bit more we got some stuff to
do and i'm gonna be doing another live
maybe i'll talk about it on the live
coming up as well okay because we're
gonna do another one after this
okay and check out the newsletter when
you get a chance because that's where i
talked about the hives right
moving the celery juice over a little
bit let's make a hummus which will be
really fun you guys fat-free hummus and
i'm gonna also do low-fat in the hummus
how about that low fat in the hummus
real low fat versus oil and your hummus
all that intense oil
so
what i love about the mm-1500 you guys
it's on sale 20 off right now check it
out link is in the profile up on tick
tock link is in the description you guys
the mm 1500 love it like i said saves
you money when you're juicing squeezes
more of the juice out of the pulp i
showed you guys how dry the pulp was
right
but it also makes a ton of other things
which is incredible
so let's do that right now
let's make some
let's make some hummus
fat free now what kind of hummus do you
guys like
i'm at your service that's your service
here
i want to make sure i give you guys the
best hummus you've ever had
would you like some hummus ice most
certainly will
have some thank you
i have hummus right here it's not hummus
yet it's chickpeas so i want to show you
right here okay
so here's my chickpeas i'll give you a
close-up you can just get regular canned
regular packaged chickpeas make sure
they're cooked off you can cook your own
too
you can do that as well
and
i am going to get a little bowl
so
[Music]
now we're doing beans right here okay
you don't have to have beans if you
don't want just for the people who do
eat hummus people who like hummus
right that's how incredible the machine
is i love it i love some hummus once in
a while what i do is i make it for
friends i make it for family that's how
cool it is you notice how quiet the
machine is
why is this machine so quiet how come
it's not screaming every time i'm using
it
it's incredible you don't wake people up
in the morning when you're juicing now i
got some black beans do you guys like
black bean hummus that's another thing i
can make too
so i have that which i'm excited about
so let's start with some chickpea hummus
first
let's do that
all right
now
you can do anything with your hummus
okay do you like garlic in there
you can get a garlic clove just like
this right
get a little garlic clove which is great
grab this one it's bigger
okay you can put garlic in there which
is great
you can put anything in here through the
machine with your hummus which is
exciting so i'm gonna put hot pepper a
super chili i grew out of my garden
i'm gonna put that in the hummus
just peeling back a little bit of this
garlic a little bit i got a garlic clove
here's a red hot pepper that's gonna go
in there as well
so i'll give you a close-up on the red
hot pepper right here so i got garlic
clove that's gonna go in here it's just
gonna go straight in the machine i got
oregano
you can do that i got sage
i even have something called garlic
chives i don't know if you guys ever had
a garlic chive right these are all fresh
herbs this is a fresh hummus fresh herbs
that's what i'm gonna do here so let's
start by putting in a few beans
now i'm making a fat free hummus but i
have these sesame seeds here now here's
the difference when you put sesame seeds
in your hummus through the machine
you're not getting a whole bunch like a
tablespoon of tahini oil sesame oil
this is it gives you the flavor of the
sesame if that's what you like it gives
you it doesn't it's not a blob of tahini
with all that added oil they put in the
tahini this is the best way to do it
that's why i call this like the medicine
maker because you're making the
healthiest version of the food you can
ever have or imagine
see i won't go out and buy a hummus out
there because they're all unhealthy for
a million reasons they got citric acid
in them they got additives you can't see
right they got carrageenan and they have
msg they have natural flavors in the
hummuses now so when you go buy hummus
there's all the stuff in there that you
shouldn't be eating and then they dump
all this canola oil in their hummus
and other stuff too like canola oil they
put too much olive oil in their hummus
they have too much tahini in their
hummus they have nutritional yeast in
their hummus nutritional yeast is msg
right they put citric acid which is corn
so that's what they i won't buy a hummus
if i walk by the hummus section in the
store
all i'm seeing is bad that that that's
not good i would never give that to my
kids that's a bad hummus right there
that's a vet look what's in this one and
you see it over and over and over again
right
and that's what i love about this it's
like you break away from that it's like
freedom
which is incredible so
let's put some beans in here
some chickpeas
okay
now you can put a little bit of um
sesame seeds right in here too check
this out
it's not all that oil it's not all that
bad stuff in there putting some beans in
here it's effortless man
check this out you guys this is insane
right i got this hot pepper i got this
garlic
now you can chop everything up and put a
little at a time of anything you want in
there i'm going to put a little sage in
here too
i like a little touch of sage so
medicinal right there
i put a little sage in there right
you can put a little bit of sea salt
that's what you like too
i'm going to put a little bit of oregano
in here check this out right drop some
oregano in there you see the fresh herbs
come out with it watch check it out you
guys
watch the fresh herbs come out with it
too
look at that
incredible
right a little bit of sage
look at that
you can do time i'm going to do some
rosemary check this out
dropping some rosemary in there isn't
this crazy
okay
i'm gonna drop some more
sesame seeds in there too to give it
that like flavor but yet it's not over
run with oil and fat
right this is a fat free hummus actually
low low fat hummus is really what it is
right
so i'm gonna pop the garlic clove in
there right now boom garlic clove just
went in there
right
i'm gonna pop
a red pepper in there too that's a chili
pepper a super chili
so that's that's a um
super chili i just put in there that
came from my garden right these herbs
came from my garden i actually picked
these herbs just to
just to do this show with you guys right
here let's do some garlic chives in here
how about that
you ever have you ever tried garlic
chive fresh herbs like this
not only do i have a clove of garlic in
there look at that red pepper
that's going to be hot
this stuff is going to be like blazing
hot right
so i'm just putting some garlic chives
in there i'm going to drop some more of
these
chickpeas in here
i'm gonna drop some more of these seeds
in here
right sesame seeds check it out
so good you got fresh herbs you got hot
pepper you got garlic
right rosemary sage i'm gonna go with a
little bit more sage because i'm a sage
fanatic i like sage in all my salads i
like sage and all my food i like thyme
too but i don't have any right now in
the moment
accidentally left it out but that's life
right i'm gonna put some more oregano in
here and pop some more beans in here
you guys it's incredible
lori says will my older version of the
omega juicer do the same thing or the
newest version mine is a year old this i
don't know what which one you have lori
you might have a different omega
altogether the medical medium omegas are
the mm-900 and the mm-1500
and nothing does what this does
this is the mm-1500 it's the full
nutritional system you make the ice
cream you make salsas you make hummus
you make anything you want practically
it's it's insane you guys i'm gonna put
um
i'm gonna put some more sesame seeds
down in here just a few more
when you think about how little that is
with those sesame seeds like that but
the flavor pops
and you don't have it's not coated with
oil
all right that's it
i'm gonna squeeze a little lemon in it
mix it up
and i'm going to make some black bean
hummus too
so i hope you guys are ready for that
here we go
let's let it finish up
and shut it down
right
move this over
i just made some hummus
right
so what i'm doing is i'm just mixing it
giving it a gentle mix how incredible
i'm gonna pop this lemon
juice in there now so i got this nice
lemon
you can do lime i got some limes right
there as well
so i'm going to put a little bit of
lemon juice in here
if you guys don't mind
right
nice
look at that
i'm going to do a little bit of a mix so
what i'm doing is i'm mixing up
and then i'm going to show you the
crudite i have set set up which is
really incredible
so i'm mixing this hummus up right now
right
and you got the fresh herbs in there
you've got the garlic chives you've got
the sage you've got the red hot pepper
you got the garlic a little bit of
sesame seeds
i mean honestly this is a whole nother
game
big time
so i want to show you what i have over
here i got this beautiful little set i
just want to show you
i'm going to put the hummus this is a
beautiful herb hummus
right here
boom
check this out you guys
can get a camera on here too and i'll
show you
so that's the hummus right there in the
middle tik tok i want to show you guys
take a look
right
so here's how i do it okay i have
friends and family coming over this is
what i got a friend coming over he's
gonna be here any minute
so he's coming over and he's gonna try
the hummus i told him i was making a
really good hummus
right
so here's the thing
i mean i put hummus on top of onion
slices i'm an onion fanatic i love onion
that's something i do i put it on top of
tomatoes so let me pop this on on here
for a second
you guys can take a look
so what i like i mean i like eating it
in so many different ways now this is
something you probably won't like but
hey it's just me
i like putting it on the end of an onion
so good
you can do cucumber
dip your cucumber into it right
so good as well there we go
that's a really amazing one
i'm going to make a black bean one real
quick
so you guys you can do a cracker i'll do
that with the black bean one okay
all right
really really good stuff right
so let's go with the black bean
and if you want to use a different bean
and that's what you want to do for your
hummus like sprouted lentil is something
that i'm going to make one time with
this
austin says never thought to put the
herbs in it it looks so good it's so
good
so fresh so amazing low fat which is
incredible right there right
so what i'm doing is i'm drop dropping
in some black beans
there you guys
a little bit of leftover chickpea hummus
is coming out
but who's complaining
there we go
okay
you can you don't even have to do the
sesame seeds you don't have to
i'm just doing it
right little flavor going in there
so this is the black bean one right here
and do your fresh herbs in the black
bean one too at the same time
i don't like using blenders for hummus
ever since the mm 1500 i won't use a
blender
for hummus
i won't sit there you know with that
it's just it's not it's not the same
experience there's so many reasons i
don't like using the food processor with
it either
it's really not a fun experience
i love doing it this way i'm going to
put some garlic chives in here
the flavor in here is insane
it's much smoother with this that's why
you can't get it any smoother than this
some rosemary going in there
it's so smooth
right and there you don't have to use
the oil
and that's the thing when you do the
blenders you gotta put that's what they
do they put all that oil in there that
nutritional yeast
you don't have to do any fat in here
whatsoever fat free so you're protecting
your liver
which is so good
your liver doesn't like fats so you got
to be careful yeah you know sure you can
do some healthy avocado some healthy
hemp seeds some
sesame seeds some pumpkin seeds
sunflower seeds right
it's fine because you can make nut milks
in here you can do nut butters in here
with this machine which is incredible
that hot pepper got me before you guys
i'm gonna throw another one in here
this is a super chilly dropping that
super chilly in here
but the point is you can do low fat too
really give your liver a break
when you need to give it a you know a
break once in a while
there's still there's still fat and
beans
i always do it to myself with those hot
peppers
i'm gonna put a few more sesame seeds in
there big difference with just putting
the sesame seeds in there like that
versus sesame oil
right and all that tahini
really big difference
so this black bean hummus
is like a
friend and family's favorite over here
at the aw
household i'm gonna put a little bit
more oregano
in here
there we go
all right looking good
i'll drop a few more in here
and you see aw what causes extreme
drowsiness right after eating food i
noticed that drinking coconut water
helps to relieve the drowsiness and dc
that's neurological
[Music]
that central nervous system
right i was telling a doctor the other
day when people get really tired when
they're eating food
their nervous system
is not getting the full energy it needs
because it's going to all your digestion
so your all your reserves go to your
digestion versus your central nervous
system so then you get tired right
that's your central nervous system a lot
of people it everybody's different if
you have health issues sometimes it it
only takes a little bit of food and you
feel tired because you have you know
neurological issues right but then
there's somebody that doesn't have any
neurological issues yet they can eat a
whole turkey dinner and they only get
tired when it's thanksgiving when they
eat a gigantic turkey dinner and they're
in insulin resistance and they're
falling asleep on the couch and they're
like what can i have another turkey
drumstick what you know they're falling
asleep on the couch right
so this is a black bean hummus right
here
i'm gonna put a little bit of lemon in
there as well
cold white spring says it depends what
you are eating too right true may you
you are so right if you get tired
absolutely
that plays a role too
and if you have nervous systems symptoms
of any kind
right and you eat food that's much
harder on the system
then you're really going to feel it
if you have nervous system issues and
you eat food that's really good and
healthy still might feel it because you
have nervous system talk about way less
right
because all your reserves they go to
your digestion and then your nerves are
like whoa we gotta wait a little while
until things start leveling out all
right so i just mixed this hummus up i'm
gonna put it in a little bowl
i could actually put it right here too
just a little black bean hummus
so i'm gonna put a little bit next to
this hummus right here so you got like
one side you got the black bean
the other side you have the chickpea
right
there you go
and then you got like these crackers
right here
try them all out with a little brown
rice cracker and that fruit brown rice
cracker
but you don't have to use that
oh wait bryce is here
so my friend bryce
he's really cool
he just came back from a
uh from a big gathering
he was hanging out with a bunch of
friends
let me uh let me let bryce in
okay
i'll be right there you guys hang on we
got more stuff to talk about
bryce hold on
i'll let you in
surprise you coming in
good
hey bryce make yourself at home can you
try out my hummus
hey
where's the hummus
hey where
is there
hey where's the crackers
this hummus looks good eh hey is he
having it yet
he's good
i'm really good
hey man
man you spike the hummus man
i just like you
i just like you egg
you always do this to me man
never
hey
hey are you parking my car man
dude i ran over your mailbox
i ran over his mailbox man
who cares man he could just get a new
one
oh then is there silver simon in here
man
hey hey i just came back from a
psilocybin
the suicide uh gathering
gathering
yeah you can call that
oh man
i'm not feeling so good now
dude
i'm getting the visions again man where
i just start seeing all kinds of colors
wait a minute
wait a minute i think it's just my uh my
my this is my
my shirt
hey
hey man i'm getting tired now man
well i can't wait to tell them a story
about
me and summer
me and summer um
me and summer were like
we're hanging out
um
and summer gave me like this thing to
smoke
and i smoked it
oh my god
i saw jesus i swear to god i saw jesus
hey
hey i'm eating it all
christ you should go sit down and take a
little nap right
okay
can i take a nap right here
one thing about bryce is that
it makes a mess everywhere
all the time
and i don't know where bryce has been
because
do you guys know what he touched
do you guys know what he ate
did he double dip
did bryce double dip
all right
you guys
check it out when you get a chance okay
you got the celery juice talked about
how that works saving money what how
that works we're squeezing all the
celery juice out of the pulp
talked about everything else you do the
kale in there i talked about how all of
it we got the hummuses we got the
sorbets ice cream i'm gonna move for a
little bit of
sorbet right here you guys
you guys we're going live by the way 20
off mm 1500
we're going live on instagram going to
turn tick tock back on and telegram back
on we're going there in just a few
minutes just got to straighten up a
little bit
mm 1500 20 off free shipping it's on
sale right now full nutritional system
the whole bit it's an incredible machine
it's 20 off which is really helpful i
told you i'd always i would only mention
the machine
if it's on sale because you know that's
that's how you do it man that's how you
do it because it saves people money
and then what happens is once the sale's
off everybody's asking me what was it
that you use what do you like and i'm
like
dude just i already told you the sale
you gotta wait for the sale are you guys
going live in a little while
i'm gonna talk about some other stuff
too all right i love you guys
i'm gonna have a little bit of this
that's so good
brain freeze