we're live
pretty sure we're live we're definitely
live if you're new here anthony william
the medical medium number one new york
times best-selling author got cleansed
to heal right here too i'm gonna answer
questions
but you know what's funny is the health
scene is like the wild wild west
it always was like that in the past and
it's still like that now
and it's like the blind leading the
blind when it comes down to so much
going on i see my monitor to the right
i'm looking at all the
the comments coming up so i'm gonna
answer questions it's what i'm gonna do
so it's like the blind leading the blind
you guys you get sick
okay and then you're on your own all
right
you get sick and you're on your own and
you might be somebody that's like
that's not true you know i had a symptom
i went to my doctor
my doctor's giving me some information
you know i have support and that's good
but what happens if you're
on your fourth doctor and your fifth
doctor and then your specialist and now
your neurologist
and you're now you know at another
doctor and so forth and it goes on like
that
and it ends up like oh my god i really
am on my own research in science doesn't
know why i'm sick
and how come i'm still sick yeah i go to
my doctor and i'm getting help but why
am i still
sick and it's because you know the
health and wellness uh health scene
all of it's always been the wild wild
west
and don't get fooled by flash and
trends that are like you know the
recyclable
they're like recycled and they're in the
out of the old trend recycle bin from
the past
you know and they can those trends can
actually be really deceiving they can
appear like
they work or they're good or you know
hey apple cider vinegar
can fix your lupus no it can't um
activated charcoal can fix your
gastroparesis no it can't
um you know it's like you know it's like
it's always been like that
and research in science doesn't know why
people are sick and it's really sad
and if you're not sick and you're not so
sick and you only got a little bit of a
symptom
you can play around in that land and
those mirages seem
real you know it's kind of fun hey do
some fermented foods
hey do a little apple cider vinegar
whatever and you can do that but the
bottom line is when you're really sick
and you're really looking for answers it
really has been the wild wild west and
you know what i think about in the past
all like 35 years of being in here and
doing this
35 years of this and i think about it so
many people
their stories what they've gone through
being really sick and they
tried all the things you see out there
now
they've tried it all they've tried the
food combining they tried the
they tried to you know they tried to
know wheat and the food combining and
the apple cider vinegar and activated
charcoal and the fish oil and the
probiotics and
you know in the candida cleanses and
did all of that and they've tried that
and the parasitical cleanses and
and their stories haven't been heard
because it's
long before social media and now
everybody's swimming in the same stuff
the same recycled stuff
that old stuff that's come back people
are playing in it
people are you know doing stuff but when
you're really sick we need more than
that
and it's important so what kind of
symptom do you have
you know what's the symptom do you have
what's the condition do you have like
you
have let's talk about it because i want
to answer some questions and everything
so um so that's let's do that so let's
do that
and the bottom line is for so many
people out there
when you really get sick and you're
really bogged down and you lose that
quality of life with your symptom
and then your condition and you're
getting a diagnosis after diagnosis
after diagnosis
and you know it's really difficult and
what i like is i like to know where's
the answers
where are they like are there answers
because reasons research and science
doesn't have the answers since that's
what medical medium information has
always been about if you're new here
you're you're in a land of let's get
down to the truth let's get down to the
answers let's down to
get down to the root causes and you know
let's not get lost and have the blind
leading the blind
so let's answer some questions i'm here
so i'm going to look over here to the
monitors and
i want to look at questions and some um
lost 20 pounds so linda says i lost 20
pounds feeling healthier
thank you so much for opening my eyes to
a lot of misinformation
okay that's an incredible that's an
incredible comment
right there there linda in you know i
hope everybody
like sees or hears that comment and
what's that about it's like
there's tremendous amounts of
misinformation out there and
but it seems like all that
misinformation is good because when not
so sick people
use it it's deceiving so linda must have
really been through something she must
have been really going through some
things like the weight
and and you weren't feeling good and you
must have tried some things right linda
because that's the whole thing and
but what you'll find right now with
social media and everything is that
you know the same old recycled stuff all
swimming around out there and when
you're not so sick and you're a person
with a symptom and you're trying this
and this and you're
selling this or doing that what happens
is it looks like hey
maybe that person's got the answer maybe
that's it but when in the end
it's all back to the same old recycled
bin of old health information
and never got people who really were
struggling better and that's that's
it makes all the difference it just does
you guys
is there anything you would so um surrey
tuck says is there anything you would
recommend for a seven-year-old boy
who has just started developing ticks so
okay so what i would do okay if my child
was developing ticks okay um you know i
would i would bring this
information to the doctor first of all i
would bring the information to the
doctor with ticks and spasms because
ticks and spasms and twitches
all that's neurological so what i would
do is i would bring
the medical medium information to my
doctor but i would look into the book
and you start seeing that
toxic heavy metals play a role they're
the cause of so much of that and i get
asked by doctors all the time
and what happens is people don't realize
half of my day
like a big part of my day is answering
doctor's questions
so that's what happens so doctors
contact you know they contact
us i get on the phone with them and
they're saying what do i do when i have
children with ticks what do i do and i
have children with spasms and i'll tell
the doctors look
you're looking at toxic heavy metals
you're looking at mercury you're looking
at aluminum
so what i tell the doctor is look here's
the stuff here's the different protocols
you can work with
and so they learn about this and and and
so a big part of my day is answering
doctor questions and that's one of the
questions that i answer for doctors all
the time
and it's really important so and i tell
doctors hey
heavy metal detox smoothie heavy metal
detox cleanse in here
um you know and that's what i tell
doctors to help their patients with so
it's a really good question
why do i keep getting sinus and ear
infections that's from tina thomas
um so you obviously been to your doctor
you've been to your practitioners and
you know you've been to your ears nose
and throat doctor and you're still
getting these
you're still getting these sinus
infections still getting these ear
infections
and i mean once again though i would i
mean if i was dealing with that dealing
with ear infections dealing with sinus
infections
um and i had an ent that that uh
contacted me last week i usually get
one or two ents um a month that that
contact me
contact me and and so what ents are
always what they're always um
ears nose and throat doctors are always
concerned about is look i don't want to
use too many antibiotics on my patients
that's what i hear
you know and they'll ask me like how do
you do this how do you avoid the
antibiotics because doctors don't
want to keep on prescribing antibiotics
every 10 seconds i mean i talked to so
many doctors they're like look
i've been prescribing antibiotics for 20
years in my practice
all the time for all these different
things what do i do and i said well
first of all
it's about getting down to the true
cause of the root cause like if it's
bacteria you're concerned about
what bacteria is and so the doctors
think and i had me and he talked to me
last week and he said what do you think
and i said well
would i would the information i got from
spirit of compassion is it streptococcus
and and the cnt was like you know that
makes a lot of sense
because um in in his wheelhouse it just
made tremendous amount of sense
and there's over 50 groups of
streptococcus and there's hundreds of
strains
hundreds of strains but there's over 50
groups many of them unidentified by
research and science
and and they get antibiotic resistance
so at this time i talked to the cnt
about it and everything i was talking to
them and i told them what happens is
they get more antibiotic resistant
and then you take antibiotics again and
you got the years nose and throat
infections take the antibiotics again
and the sinus infections chronic
sinusitis
but i talked about in cleanse the heal
when i was telling him i talked about it
that it's down to figuring out
streptococcus what to do to support it
i'm not against antibiotics you know i
never were because what happens is when
people
they haven't learned how to take care of
themselves and they haven't learned how
to heal and they haven't learned what to
do
and they get into a jam and it's whoa
what do i do i gotta get to my doctor i
gotta get the
antibiotic for my uti i gotta get the
antibiotic for my
my sinus infection i have to get the
antibiotic for the sty i have
and this all streptococcus you know and
so um
so it's good to learn in everything if
you don't have cleanser he'll go to the
library get it for free and i tell
everybody
i'm going to look at more questions
we're going to answer food questions too
but if you don't have it go get it for
free don't even buy it if you don't want
to
and get it for free at the library it's
also amazon.com
united states amazon.com 51 off 16.99
don't quote me on that i think that's
the last time i saw it on there it was
that price it's amazing really
um i have your books natasha says i have
your books needing to read it
all and start um busy busy work full
time and four kids oh my god that's
that's a lot
i want to lose 60 pounds can you see
what's wrong with me
um well you know if you're if if it's
about weight if that's natasha if you're
dealing with weight issues i mean you
can
when you're a busy mom you have four
kids and you're working full-time
you know and people don't understand a
lot of people don't understand what
that's like you know i talk to people
and they're like
you know they're doing self-care all day
they're doing self-care they got the
luxury for that it's amazing like
you see it on instagram too it's like
self-care they're like
like just the whole day is just
self-care
and it's like in my world of like
where i've grown up and stuff and
everything else it's like
um yeah that's that's amazing that
people can do that right now in their
life i can't
and i don't have the time i have to use
the time for just getting this
information out so i know like if you're
working a full-time job
and you got four kids and a lot of
people right now don't understand this
it's like that is like heavy duty like
you don't have that time and energy for
your self-care
and frightfully so i mean you're in big
demand you have four children and you're
working hard
and um and you don't have a luxury in
the moment to be like okay let me just
spend the next six months
just making peanut butter smoothie bowls
and taking instagram pics and i get it i
get it so just
what i would do what i would do though
with with with that is
morning cleanse is something you can do
it's easier
that's something right there so uh
you know when you're that busy and you
got that much going on maybe just start
with the celery juice you want to lose
weight
start with the celery juice to get the
liver less stagnant less sluggish
and you know just do that and that's one
thing you can start
i'm not saying that's going to get the
weight off it's a place to start so you
can get improvements wherever you can
and then maybe move into the morning
cleanse where it's just the morning
cleanse
because i know you have to work hard i
know you have kids i know you're you're
in you have 10 jobs
so that's what it sounds like you have
10 jobs going on and so
with that just maybe maybe look into the
morning cleanse go straight to that
in cleanse the heel that's what i
recommend and just say what can i do in
here whoa i could do the lemon water
how about that that could at least flush
your system in the morning
so the liver starts waking up so you can
start losing a little bit of weight
that's one way of doing it you do lemon
water maybe try to get a celery juice if
you can't do the celery juice
do the lemon water and then and then do
the rest of the morning cleanse where
you just eat some fruit in the morning
to get you through the morning so you're
not doing any fats in the morning
so this way your liver gets a chance and
you can start losing a little bit of
weight that could really help
and maybe it you know in the lemon water
is not eight ounces
it's 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water kind
of keep that in mind like
that's a really big orange juice right
here fresh squeezed orange juice from a
dinner tonight
and that's really big one i still have
some celery juice left right here but
okay angela hi i've been drinking celery
juice for two years
finally some relief from migraines thank
you so grateful okay angela
first of all you're my hero remember
this right here
you're drinking celery juice for two
years you didn't
let any kind of stupid talk out there
about
someone saying i tried it for seven days
it didn't work for me oh
okay great you know i love when people
do that out there when they're not so
sick
when you suffer from migraines that
means
you're really struggling you got a lot
going on there and
what i've noticed is the people who pick
on celery juice
the people who pick on celery juice are
people who
they don't know what it's like to suffer
from migraines you see
you see what i'm saying right they'll
just be like they got a little bit of
this or a little bit of that and they're
trying all these fun things and they're
doing their social media thing but
then they'll say i tried celery juice it
didn't work or
they won't talk about seller juice
because there's no money to be made off
of it you know you can't get a
sponsorship for celery juice on social
media you know so there's no money to be
made
so people keep it quiet you know and but
the point is is you stayed with it
you know what it's like to have
migraines you know what it's like out
there how the blinds leading the blind
you know what it's like when the
research in science what does research
and science have the answers for
migraines
they don't and that's the sad part
celery just for two years and
are you doing some other things too so
are you still are you getting into the
medical media information are you doing
other stuff too are you working with it
you look into the headaches and
migraines section
um and i'm proud of you i just want you
to know that just blown away
fibroids um okay
so jacob jackie so if i so the thing is
with
fibroids is i talk about what causes
fibroids
and so when you go in here you'll see
what causes them and then
you'll learn what foods to avoid for
fibroids
fibroids are hungry they are hungry
they actually have these little blood
vessels that come out of them
and they they draw in nutrients
and nutrients that they like that
fibroids like and
in order to stop growing fibroids what
happens with a lot of women that gets
fibroid surgeries
um and and that's really difficult to go
through that
and what i like to do okay and i have a
friend that came to me recently with
fibroids and i said
you know um how are they doing my friend
said well my doctor says you're getting
better and better from
from all the stuff that you're
recommending and so they're avoiding
surgery
because her fibroids are getting better
and so she did a check-in recently an
old friend of mine she says look my
doctor's amazed
my you know i'm doing the celery juice
i'm staying off of eggs
i'm staying off of eggs my doctor was
very worried about that thought i needed
the egg protein
and then um i let my doctor know that
the anthony you said that eggs feed
fibroids the doctor learned something
and learned that
fibroids actually eat um eat by products
from eggs
and draw them up their draw them up
their blood vessels and they grow grow
grow
so that was just one example there so i
would just learn i would learn what
causes the fibroids go into the section
here you'll see the different
supplementation and protocols
you can take it to your doctor too
whatever works
so and there's there's thousands of
combinations
in here in cleanse the heel and medical
medium information medical medium books
it's not one protocol
customize it to yourself whether you're
plant-based whether you're you know
vegetarian whether you're animal protein
based whether you like animal proteins
whatever whether you're keto
keto animal keto plant whatever you like
the whole point is it's about answers
and what to do and the protocols that
you can
go into your diet belief system with
because everybody gets sick
that's the whole thing you guys
everybody gets sick whether anybody
likes it or not
or knows about that or not everybody
gets sick so that's what happens out
there
so i'm just looking through the
questions right now on the monitor and
there's there's there's so so much to
answer jamie says fibroid issues too i
hope you catch that what i just talked
about
um i hope you caught that
see um so mary's
mary c you see fatty liver and
hashimoto's remember with fatty liver
and you'll read in the medical meaning
books like fatty liver
that's a stagnant sluggish liver and
high fat diets
years of high fat diets will lead to a
fatty liver and
hashimoto's is viral so you go in here
into the back of the book and you'll see
hashimoto's thyroiditis
thyroid nodules hypothyroidism
hyperthyroidism
and you're learning here that
epstein-barr virus creates all those
thyroid problems and you learn about
that and you'll learn about well what do
i do
and the book talks about that it walks
you through
um and so much information about that
of how it works epstein-barr isn't just
this one virus so
medical medium information is very
advanced extremely advanced and far
ahead of research and science by decades
and what research and science doesn't
know
is that there's over 60 varieties now of
epstein-barr virus
and in those 60 varieties there's
different kinds
and they're not easy detectable they get
into the thyroid
science research doesn't know this or
how it works um it creates hashimoto's
it sits in the liver first makes the
liver all stagnant and sluggish then
when you're doing the high fat diets
you get you know it gets problematic if
i had a fatty liver
um i would be like no eggs no butter
no milk no cheese that's what i would do
no eggs milk butter cheese
gone right and if i was an animal
protein person
i would i would minimize my animal
protein i'll just drop them down
and make sure i'm getting more of other
things i talk about in the books
go to library get the book for free so
you can learn that's what i recommend
don't even buy the book go to the
library get the book out so you didn't
pay for it
and start learning you know go do that
too you'd also get it on amazon if you
don't want to
try to get the book out of the library
and you really want the book or
something say amazon it's a sale 51
off um so lena says body swelling and
chronic bloating so you know it comes
down to chronic bloating which is really
hard for so many people i talked about
bloating because
bloating can make it so you can't
breathe you feel like you can't breathe
good you can't feel like you can't take
a deep breath
you can't get air in it gets in the way
when you're walking
it gets in the way when you're just
driving when you're driving the car
i know people that when they're driving
driving their car and they're bloated it
just makes it so difficult and so hard
carrying things makes it so hard so i'm
so sorry you're going with you know the
chronic bloating and the swelling
um and you know and i've talked about
this for years and what i
i this is a question that i always get
asked by doctors
um that's another thing too so and
doctors would be like well i got this
patient you know and what do i do
and chronic bloating and and you know
and so i'm like okay first of all
we we got a liver issue and that's what
i would tell you know a doctor and they
would also send me looking they're
looking for liver enzymes they're
looking for liver problems
and that's one thing that's really
helpful um the other thing with
with that kind of bloating and that kind
of uh everything
is just know that your hydrochloric acid
is low and i've taught doctors that how
hydrochloric acid becomes really low
um and learn the true cause of bloating
so what i would do is
once again cleanse the heal learn the
true cause of bloating you can bring it
to your practitioner
but there's so so much you can do with
that there's so much you can do
um but bloating is one of those things
where if
i had bloating i'd get rid of milk
cheese butter
eggs gone i'd get rid of gluten gone
because those are gonna feed
any kind of bugs so with a lot of
different bloating cases you'll have
streptococcus in the intestinal tract
that's causing the bloating your
hydrochloric acid is low
so i get rid of those foods is what i
would do and then i would get the celery
juice going every single morning lemon
water going every single morning and i
would
start to rebuild my hydrochloric acid
because i start getting my liver bile
reserves back up getting my liver back
i mean that's already the start right
there which is so
important um karen says
inflammation i've tried your celery
juice it's helping
so okay karen so that's awesome because
inflammation is a mystery
to science research so so alternative
medicine doesn't know what causes
inflammation they think a
food causes inflammation so they're not
really advanced yet i know that's going
to get someone upset right now you're
like how's he saying that
well it's true it's true alternate
medicine they don't know what causes
inflammation it's mysterious to
alternative medicine
it's mysterious to conventional medicine
unless you've been injured that's
different
so with alternative medicine they'll say
well gluten causes
inflammation not true how come there's
all these people that could eat
all the gluten they want all the cheese
pizza
and they can eat dairy and they can eat
whatever they want and they can have
they can eat and you probably people you
guys probably know some friends that can
eat whatever they want they're not
talking about inflammation are you
kidding
and because what it is it's not the
gluten
that causes inflammation it's like
gluten and things like
that that help feed a buggy in us that
causes inflammation so it's
bugs inside of us pathogens that create
the inflammation
not our body and not the foods and
that's why i don't have a food diet
belief system because i think someone
can eat it whatever they want they got
nothing going wrong with them
i also you know and i also think they
need to be eating really clean
in the right way information in here if
they got something wrong with them
so um but that's amazing i'm glad it's
helping incredible celery juices helping
wonderful
so
so we got um some mallory
okay got a question here chronic lyme
disease fatigue
chronic headaches neck pain daily
so do you know the cause of lyme disease
have you learned about that yet and just
wondering
because the cause of lyme disease is in
the cleanse of heel book whole section
on it
just wondering if you learned that yet
about what's going on so
go to the library get the book out for
free okay um people say i'm always
trying to show the book because i'm
trying to sell the book or something
like that well can i tell you something
i could break this book up in pieces and
sell ten thousand dollar programs and
have people come
i mean i'm worldwide known we know that
millions of books are out there around
the world
i can turn this into two thousand dollar
programs tomorrow and
forget selling a book i can sell massive
amounts of programs and have paid
people pay tons of money i don't i try
to make this a free resource
it's a medical textbook i killed myself
basically to write it with spirit of
compassion because
to put this together in just a year is
is unheard of and so when
when you get this book though i mean
just look go to the library get it for
free or amazon.com or something so i'm
not trying to
push a book on you but what i do want
you to have is the answers and with lyme
disease
so we've got chronic lyme disease you're
dealing with fatigue chronic headaches
and neck pain
and what happens is that science
research doesn't know what causes lyme
disease anymore so they moved it out of
the category of bacteria
and they moved it into autoimmune now
that's partly because of medical media
information all the books
that went out talking about the truth
about lyme pushed it out of the bacteria
category so now it's in the autoimmune
category right where
it belongs for science and research
because they don't know the cause of it
so learn the cause
it's viral so lyme disease is viral so
when you look at the symptoms fatigue
that's viral so you can actually find
that information in here you'll see
you'll see in the lyme section you'll
see protocols you'll see dosages of
protocols take it to your doctor
take it to your doctor and you can take
a look at it if i was diagnosed with
lyme disease
i'd be going through here in the
protocol supplements and dosages and
learn
how to do it you can read all about it
you know talk to your practitioner about
if you've got a practitioner you love
dr you love but um and that's the
biggest
that's the biggest question i get with
doctors doctors contacting me
like every single day i have to donate a
certain part of my day and talk to
doctors
um because they reach out and when the
biggest question is
lyme disease anthony you you basically
pushed lyme out of the bacteria category
because now
science research doesn't know what
causes lyme the lyme labs still don't
want to lose their business
they don't want to lose their business
so they're still testing for they're
still saying they're testing for
bacteria
what a scam that whole thing is and then
with with all that but it's really viral
and it's really sad how it works i want
you to have the answers you know it's
not about
i don't care who i get upset out there
you know in the industries
it's i just want you to have the answer
because when you're sick
and your body hurts and you get fatigue
and you have all these diagnoses and
you're still sick and still sick and you
probably are smart enough to know at
that point that
the health trends aren't what's fix it
going to fix it no apple cider vinegar
is going to fix that
i mean what a joke that is right i mean
what happens is when you're not so sick
and you can play around with all these
fun things on a circuit and spread
it around and everybody thinks it's an
answer to have apple cider vinegar as an
answer
it's amazing but the bottom line is i
know you've been through hell and back
if you're that sick and you dealt with
lyme
i want you to have the answers
so linda says i'm trying to figure out
what causes my husband's ulcerative
colitis
ulcerative colitis is brutal i here's an
example here
is that people don't really get it
unless they've gone through something
like that
it's like same thing with like the lyme
disease before they like
you don't know what it's like to be sick
unless you've been there you know i've
really been there
ulcerative colitis just awful and
um it's women get ulcerative clients men
get ulcerative colitis it's really a
tough one and
um and that's a question i also get
asked by doctors too is colitis and
different things like that and there's
different levels of colitis there's
there's mild bleeding with ulcerative
colitis there's
heavy and extreme bleeding with
ulcerative colitis there's cramping
brutal pain and there's also there's
also
forms of colitis that you don't
hemorrhage and you're not bleeding at
all
but you but you got colitis and when you
look and cleanse the heel
you'll see the shingles section so
that's where i would go in the shingle
section you'll find colitis
and what i've always recommended with
anybody
like any any doctors that have sent
their people to me
years ago when i used to help people out
and you know years and years ago
what what i would always do is is do the
mono eating cleanses when it comes down
to colitis it'd be the mono eating
cleanses
and that that i found was always the
best options
and and i get asked it all the time by
doctors now they're always like well
what do we do for colitis
what do we do with our patients for
clients and i'm like look the mono
eating cleanse is for colitis and
take a look at that and so it's just but
yeah it
the shingles virus is behind the whole
colitis thing it's
it's it's in the lining of the in the
intestinal tract so shingles sits in the
lining of the intestinal tract
you can talk to your doctor bring the
information i recommend that all the
time
so rebecca you got neurological stuff
going on so your question is involuntary
movements
yeah that's the jerking um the whole
jerking thing is really
really hard for people when they have
that so right sometimes it happens when
you're right before you even fall asleep
but it's like crazy where the jerks keep
on waking you up you're falling asleep
and then you're jerking waking you up
you're falling asleep and then you're
it's just unbelievable what happens and
you're probably having them during the
daytime too from what it looks like
voluntary movements vibrations
vibrations when you feel like your
body's humming and buzzing and your
body's like vibrating and you're
you're doing this hummingbuzzy vibrating
thing that's really difficult too those
are
mysterious neurological symptoms to
research in science they
don't know what that stuff is and back
like oh my god like and that's the
difference right there where you're
dealing with all that rebecca and
so you're no fool you know the wool's
not pulled over your eyes as far as
research and science having all the
answers you know
you know that you've probably been to
god knows how many doctors with that how
many neurologists is worth
like with that so just know my heart
pours out to you
rebecca for going through that and you
understand not the person who's
a troll or not so sick or not sick and
they just
don't even understand just throw like
fish oil out and do probiotics it's all
in your gut like all the stupid stuff
non-stop
meanwhile it's candida or something
meanwhile you're suffering and there's
real issues so
come down the involuntary movements
vibrations hair loss tingling hands and
feet
neurologists said anxiety that right
there
is tough for me tough tough tough to
hear that to hear that because
i heard that for over 35 years
from patients right that you know where
the doctor will send somebody to try to
find me for help
that somebody you know that somebody
would tell me all the different
neurologists they've been to and how
certain neurologists would be like
it's anxiety it's all in your head
you're making it up
you know what the new thing is right now
rebecca is that
what you know young women are being told
now
is that they're creating it with their
thoughts you know and they're not
good enough they're creating it they're
not thinking positive and that's why
they have tingles and numbness and
that's why they have all these symptoms
of vibrations it's so sad what's
happening that's the new crazy
you just you tell young women that
they're just creating it with their
thoughts
and they're they're with their they're
not positive thoughts and they need to
better themselves that's a new way of
saying it's all in your head and you're
crazy to a new generation it's just it's
actually sick
um and but yeah so just know that
i feel for you so what i would do
there's a neurological section here
you'll see with body vibration
with body vibrations you'll hear tingles
hands and feet
so what i would do is get the book out
library for free if you want
and take a look at the different the
your symptoms and line them up to
symptoms inside the back of the book and
if you're new here and you're wondering
what is he even talking about well in
the back of the book
you'll see look i just opened it to just
whatever and it says
glaucoma gout um guilt and sadness hair
thinning and loss i actually just opened
it up to hair thinning and loss and it
tells you what's causing that
and i just turn the page fibromyalgia
and so forth and it keeps them going but
there's neurological
section in here so and you can learn
what's causing it so you can get a
chance to get better and all that
and it's just not easy okay so
so angela you're doing lemon water proud
of you incredible
celery juice per your instructions still
seem to be having some congestion
breathing issues asthmatic like symptoms
and coughing mucous inflammation doctors
can't find anything any suggestions
angela um what are you what are you
eating that's one thing
think about that i ask everybody this so
i'm asking everybody this right now okay
you got some symptoms going on you're
doing some good stuff though
so you're doing the lemon water you're
doing the celery juice that's a part of
it there
are you eating any eggs um because
that's not that's gonna
are you doing one one or two eggs a
month
will keep those symptoms there is what
they'll do because
because with the doctor so no these are
pathogens because they talk to doctors
all the time and i teach doctors about
this what your very question have been
asked
i have to talk to about five ten doctors
every single day
so every morning so i have a like that's
what i do
and it's to teach them so they can help
heal more patients and more patients and
and you know many of them don't set it
back to the medical medium information
it just spreads out and spreads out so
then when i say metal somebody says oh
he didn't
he didn't start out the metal talk
metals are around you know it's crazy
so but the bottom line is um with what
you're dealing with
are you doing eggs are you doing butter
are you doing dairy products
is gluten in there once in a while these
will all feed pathogens to keep these
symptoms there
and so keep that in mind there are you
doing nutritional yeast are you doing
natural flavors are you doing
corn are you doing soy those will
make or break when you're in this
condition where you're dealing with all
this stuff going on
those will make our break so how clean
is it are you plant based have you done
the 369
cleanse yet the 369 advanced cleanse
so how far have you gone have you done
the mono eating cleanse
you talk to your doctor and say look i
want to do mono-eating cleanse but your
doctor doesn't know
they can't find anything but you can
still talk to them about doing any of
this and
mono-eating cleanse and then see where
that goes after a while you know
you don't have to be plant-based you can
be doing animal products
but but try not to do certain ones like
eggs and dairy products
but there is a way out there is a way
out and
so you've got to customize the protocol
try to get some guidance if you can
from a practitioner of course if you
want or do it on your own but i
completely understand
what you're going through so
guinea hernia please discuss protocols
sand chad one one protocol
don't overeat don't overeat small meals
small meals every two hours i get asked
this all the time
all the time um doctors ask this all the
time
and i'm saying that a lot because
basically
people say well be transparent anthony
what do you do in a day
you want to know what my day is my day
stinks
so my day is waking up really early in
the morning hearing spirit of compassion
writing down information from for the
next book so i can work on getting
people better
and then i gotta go okay who's lined up
all the doctors that need to talk to me
and ask questions because they're
they're they're
trying to contact me that's a part of
the day it's exhausting
and then and then the next part of the
day is just
all the other projects and things to do
and it's it's just
it's just and how to get disseminate
free information out constantly it's
just
it's just endless but um first of all
with the hernias
don't overeat small meals that that's
critical
small meals and um and be cautious
you're not eating foods
that will bloat you up because you don't
want that
one like moment where you get
extra bloated and you pop the cork and
now you're getting surgery
emergent emergency surgery or something
like that you know and i always tell
tell you that i got a friend who's got a
hernia and it's like
any guinea hernia and i'm just like look
just of course don't lift anything heavy
but if you're bloated or you're stuffed
that's when it could go wrong you know
when you're really stuffed so you just
want to you know you want to eat light
but consistently
so it's not like all in one moment
that's just one thing i can
give you anyway that's helpful
candida so alan so candida
okay well candida was a bad idea
and a bad theory back in the 80s and 90s
and it led
thousands and thousands of people astray
into never never land of
never getting better so if we're still
playing around in candida land
it's amazing how these dead theories
are just they just recirculate and they
they're still out there it's beyond me
that they're still out there because
candida is not the problem of why
somebody's sick
and so when when you still see that out
there candida cleanses i'm like
dear god dear god i mean it's the land
of just stupidness out there it's it's
amazing not you
but the information and all the the you
know going out there all the
misinformation
and so it's easy to get trapped in it
it's easy to get trapped into the
candida thought and candida what they
did was
no one got better with the candida
thought so now they call it microbiome
and they're going to call it sibo like
they call sibo and then microbiome and
it's like okay and then
you know and that's but that's not why
people are sick it's really sad
and but what they will offer is they'll
say stay off of gluten stay off of this
they'll stay off of medical medium no
foods
that i've been teaching about for 35
years they'll say stay off of this stay
off of the stay off of this
and then the person's getting a little
better and then they think hey that's my
candida is getting better my
my microbiome is getting better and
that's not how it works it's just that
when you're staying off those no foods
by default
you're not feeding streptococcus that's
creating your intestinal
tract problem so they don't know it but
you're starving your streptococcus so
it's just
it it's incredible how it works out
there but um
just really i mean if you're into
candida you're into anything you just
got to read clensic your mind will be
blown you go to amazon it's 51
off 16.99 if you want go to the library
get it for free
but it's yeah your mind will be blown
when you actually read this this is the
most advanced
gut book there is to date hands down out
there
so melissa says hello why is my anemia
such a huge problem these days so why is
your anemia
that you're dealing with huge problem
well you know what what happens with
anemia is iron feeds the epstein-barr
virus so
and this is something i've talked about
forever i talked about this in books
i've talked about this in other
other places and i've lectured about it
in many places and have lectured that
that with anemia that's what happens is
iron feeds pathogens if you have
pathogens so once again it's like wait a
minute here you know like what can i do
i would start with the anti-bug cleanse
i would talk to you can talk to your
doctor about it get cleansed of heal
okay melissa high blood sugar not
genetic
high blood sugar is not genetic that's
an example of
they don't know why someone has a
problem so research in science will
peg everything genetic it's body shaming
it's like your genes are bad so
you got crappy genes how about that
that's what they that's what they want
you to think
i mean think about that isn't that sick
it's like you
this is what they do if you get sick
they say your body's attacking itself
you have autoimmune
okay now i'm not saying people don't
have symptoms and they're not suffering
but autoimmune theory is actually
a botched job total body shop it's not
even real their theory about the body
attacking itself because it doesn't so
they'll just say
your body's attacking itself body
shaming
they'll make you feel like crap that
your body's bad and it's attacking
itself they'll say it's genetic
right they'll say your condition's
genetic make body shaming again make you
feel like
a piece of crap because that's what they
want you to feel like not the doctors
but the industry
and then they'll say you they'll also
say um it's your hormones
come on i mean you know what i mean like
unbelievable it's your hormones
that's what they'll say they'll pull
that card because it's blaming the woman
now
she has bad hormones or she's just i
mean they're they're great hormone
doctors don't get me wrong incredible
ones that actually
naturally work with hormones to to to
help
actually band-aid everything but the
point is the industry loves to think
it's all hormones
then the industry loves to think it's
all in your head so they just want to
body shame body shame body shame but not
give you answers and diabetes
is not um genetic it's not that's not
genetic
you know um blood sugar problems high
a1c not genetic and all that
but you got to get your liver in a
better place
you got to drop the fats in the diet
down got to learn how to maybe eat a
little differently
and then you'll see all that stabilize
you'll see it stabilized
floaters just so you know i got a whole
floaters thing in the back here there's
there's floaters in cleanse the heel
what to do all
the different stuff what's the cause
what i don't
what i don't like out there okay there's
all this advice out there
all of it in the health scene okay and
it's interesting
but yet nobody knows what causes
anything so why is
why is someone really an expert when
they don't know the true cause of why
you're sick
if they don't know the true cause of why
you have floaters why are they an expert
oh here's apple cider vinegar here's
activated charcoal
here's corella here's fish oil here's
probiotic
here's whatever here's collagen i mean
it's it's insane really here's bentonite
clay
all that stuff's bad but the bottom line
is it's it's
it's really amazing you know oh here's
food combining but yet you don't know
why somebody's sick
not like you know ranking on everything
totally i'm just saying that
it everybody's a health expert is that
what it is now when nobody knows why
anybody's sick
no one knows why you have tinnitus
ringing in the air nobody knows why you
have vertigo or
clothes in the eyes the tickles and
numbness and that's the difference
between medical medium information
whether anybody likes it or not it's
just the truth
it's tammy white i have heard you say at
one time or in your books
that some people who do celery juice
might get diarrhea
i get it so bad and this is all i can
figure out that might be causing all the
intestinal distress
um options that will do similar to
celery juice first of all so you never
had
tim you never had intestinal distress
before and you never had diarrhea at all
before
um or is this like your intestinal tract
and gut problems
all perfect like your gut's great you
had nothing wrong with your gut
everything's stable with it no bloating
no anything and then you did celery
juice and then you have the diarrhea i'm
just
just asking questions so you can think
about it and the other thing is
do small amount do a really small amount
so what i would recommend
because what happens is if you're
getting diarrhea first of all i'm really
glad that you got the books and you're
reading them
when you're when you're getting the
diarrhea from celery juice lower the
amount of celery juice because that
means
that celery juice is killing something
so it's it's killing something it's
killing a die off so what happens is
what everybody walks around with they
walk around chances are if you're
taking care of yourself and you're
getting these books that means you do
have something going on in your body
that you're concerned about you're not
just feeling perfect and then you
decided to do medical medium information
most everybody does medical mean
information they get sick so they need
to do mental health information so
what's happening is
is realize that is that you got
something that the celery juice is
actually
destroying pathogens and when one
little bug dies like one little bug
dies we can have a reaction to that bug
dying
so when you kill off one little tiny bug
kill off a little bit of streptococcus a
little bit of staph
a little bit of c-diff you kill a little
bit of you know all this
and then that's that's something right
there you kill a little bit of
um shingles a little bit of epstein bar
but bacteria especially any of it when
that celery juice is going through
your intestinal tract it's it's a
cleanser it
people underestimate the amount of power
it has it's different than a celery
stick a celery stick
that's not going to do anything but when
you do the celery juice so what i would
recommend is
first of all are you don't do any eggs
don't do any dairy don't do any gluten
no corn no soy make sure that stuff's
out
and be cautious with all that stuff do
small amounts
of celery juice if you want to try that
that's what i would recommend to
somebody asking me this if this was me
happening i'd be like okay four ounces
so i'd be like well what's this is this
four ounce six ounces what is this so
i would do a small amount each day
and see where that line is drawn because
it's going to go in there it's going to
start
breaking down pathogens killing off
bacteria and all that is what it's going
to start to do so that's what i would do
so um
yeah anyway so but i'm proud of you for
even drinking it
start really little if you need to
graduate go right to
um you know i don't recommend
ever having something mixed with your
celery juice okay
but if you really have to i mean i have
mentioned if you really have to
acclimate
do some apple in there do a little bit
of apple a little bit of celery juice
and see if you still get the same thing
and you just work your way up back to
where your straight celery again or just
a little bit of celery
so there's a couple questions um
i'm looking at my monitors for questions
you guys so erica
i bought cleanse the heel and reading it
now
amazing incredible i can't really find
any info on balancing hormones
i'm i am going through early menopause
and all the doctors keep telling me to
do keto can you give me any advice
so if you go into the protocols you'll
see in the back of the book
menopause symptoms
and i'm just looking hormonal hormonal
problems and i'm just looking for it now
so they're both in this same section but
i'm just trying to find it as we speak
because
i'm wondering if i wonder why that's not
there for you
so i have two things going on here so i
want to show you one
here
so you'll see hormonal problems right
there
and then
sorry about it's taking so long isn't
then you'll see
and then you'll see menopause symptoms
right there
[Music]
but um so we can do is you can talk to
your practitioner doctor you can take
this to them
and you can look you can you can but if
you read the whole chapter
you can learn how to take the
supplements as far as how to do it
but learning the true cause is the key
so when you see this
you'll see menopause symptoms but you'll
you'll read it you'll learn what the
true cause because
menopause is supposed to be like it used
to be
before the 1940s which was women
just their period stopped and they felt
better than ever
that's what menopause used to be so that
was the change back then
it was called the change you just felt
better
so but then because of pathogens and
viruses like epstein-barr
stagnant livers causing hot flashes and
all this
we've gotten to the age of menopause
symptoms
and it's being blamed on menopause but
menopause isn't why
you have the symptoms you have to
realize wait a minute what's going on
here so you'll look at all the different
supplement protocols you'll see what
angle to take
you can talk to your practitioner about
it if you wanted to too that's what i
would do if i was going through it
um keto keto will make it worse so keto
makes menopause symptoms worse
because because the keto is high fat
so what you'll find is the higher fat
you go because that's part of how the
the menopause symptoms are even here
it's because your whole diet your diet
throughout your life was probably just
high in fat because everybody says it's
just everybody says
whether it's milk cheese butter eggs
meat chicken avocado nut butters
oils olive oil whatever you know
whatever it is coconut oil whatever it
is
peanut butter all of that is high fat
and we we tuna fish
tuna fish salmon whatever right we tend
to be all high fat and that's what we do
so keto is just
yeah you're removing gluten but you
should be removing that anyway
so what i would do is is anybody dealing
with like
the hormonal issues menopause symptoms
try something like
try just the mono eating cleanse for a
little bit or try maybe the anti-bug
cleanse or
do 369 original the original 369 cleanse
if you want or advanced and you'll
notice that
as you're doing that and then you look
at some of the supplementation and
menopause symptoms and hormonal
imbalances
you'll notice once you bring some of the
subs in the supplements in
with doing the foods and not having to
do keto
you'll notice some of these menopause
symptoms going away
and you'll be like oh my god why are
they going away because it
menopause is different than the symptoms
menopause is
the change of life the period stops
you're getting older that kind of thing
it's normal you're really getting
younger and
your period stops and then what happens
is you're not supposed to have symptoms
if you have symptoms that's other things
really being the problem
and that's advanced information and
teaching a lot of doctors that now a lot
of hormone doctors that too
reggie says anthony what's the problem
with ionized water
i've had a machine for years the problem
is reggie that um there's a bunch of
problems
a bunch of them one is the filters on
them are terrible so you're just getting
sink water and so
and you're getting you can get toxic
heavy metals from your sink water you
can get other things that it won't it's
not a purifier
so the alkaline ionizer water machines
aren't pure fire so i recommend a
purifier so you're not
drinking water that has stuff in it that
shouldn't be in there so that's one
and i know the ionizer sales people the
pyramid scheme and all that that's
happening they'll just tell you that
yeah it's clean water it's clean water
it's just not true um and you can even
look into it it's not true but
the thing is the other problem is it's
ionized so
what happens is their metal plates are
in the machine and those metal plates
they get corroded over the years
so if i took apart your ionizer i would
find these two corroded plates and where
did all those metal particles
go and off those titanium plates and you
know platinum titanium whatever you
where did all the metal go they turn
they turn black they get all pitted and
decayed
and and um and so that has to go
somewhere
and it it goes in us so what i would do
is i would
i would you know consider like you know
the heavy metal detox cleanse may be
bringing into your life pulling out some
metals that might have been in there
the other thing is charge so you got the
metal plates in the machine
and then there's electricity going to
the metal plates and it's
it's it's charging it's changing those
structure of the water
through experimentation it's like and so
that ionization
is means it changes the water it kills
the water so
you know and i get it i mean we get sold
these
and but we never get taught taught
what's happening or how it works or
what's going on
so and there's actual research on this
there's actual this isn't just me
i mean there's actual research and now
science
looking into this and figuring it out
and there's
researchers out there there's a there's
a lot of
water researchers out there that
actually check the wall they test the
water what happens when you ionize it
how the water dies
versus water that wasn't and then it's
also like i said you got those plates
and those metal plates
are conduct you know electricity going
to the metal plates look i know it gets
people upset
i hope you're not upset i'm just looking
out for people i you know i would get a
water purifier
any other water options are better than
that i'm just you know
but um but i mean i hope this helps i'm
just looking out for everybody you know
it's
it's the whole point is i have to have
your back if i don't have your back then
what do i have you know what i mean
because i'm not in it it's not i'm not
in it for myself anybody who's known me
known me all these years through all the
work i've done it's all about you guys
it's never been about what's my whole
life like let me get my selfies 24 7.
let me get in the gym and show you my
body
working out when all that's great but
you know it's all about usually the
person who's building their platform
me it's all about you guys it's just you
guys it's just
how can i protect you how can i get you
better how can i have your back i
understand your pain and suffering and
what you've been through so
so i can't hold back if i don't think
it's good i'm going to tell you
nicole says can you do the heavy metal
detox with uh hyperthyroidism
uh have headaches every day please uh i
would if i had hyperthyroidism because
once you learn what hyperthyroidism is
and you look in the book and you see
what hyperthyroid is it
is then yeah it's it's it's helpful of
course it is it's so gentle it doesn't
do anything
wrong it just only does the right things
shelley says thank you so much for
helping us and taking all the negativity
for us yeah you know what's funny my god
i do and it's
it's hilarious because you know i got a
thick skin
so and it's kind of hilarious because
you know when you're discriminated
against your whole life for hearing
a voice think about that okay if you
really think about that
okay at age four spirit of compassion
started speaking to me
okay from the outside of the ear
perfectly clear so it's not inside my
head
and when i was six seven years old i was
sitting there reciting information
okay reciting information to my family
to my parents
that was advanced medical information
about viruses and how they mutate about
toxic heavy metals how they oxidize in
her brain
this is when i'm 60 years old because
it's coming from up here
my life has never been easy because of
it and what happens is i found out that
when you get more and more people better
and they recover and heal
there's an opposition that builds
against you and they make up lies
and they'll say i tried zarya juice it
doesn't work or whatever or they'll say
anthony's a bad person and they'll make
up a story but what happens is you you
learn quickly that you're not allowed to
get millions of people better because
that's what medical media books have
done
you learn that you get a lot of jealous
people in the health field and held
scene that don't
understand the gift or they're jealous
because
why is he allowed to get all this
advanced medical information so the crap
i get
for breaking all the rules and letting
you guys know the true causes of
conditions and
and you know going against you know
popular trends that are only popular
because there's millions of dollars
behind them
and they don't work and it's just sad
you know what happens and yeah
thank you for recognizing it i just uh i
just i love you for that
means a lot means a lot
um shoddy my two point my two and a half
year old daughter is so restless
anxious so much tantrums hardly goes to
sleep
that's that's so sad you know no naps
daytime oh my god no daytime naps either
get scared easily delayed
talking no two words together
also gina vegas but very smart okay
so um one of the things is that what you
one of the things that i've talked about
and i've talked about the medical medium
books for
for any of this that's happening like
that is um
toxic heavy metals they and i've been
talking about this for years
i actually a pediatrician uh
friend of mine it runs into this all the
time
okay runs into this all the time and um
and this pediatrician friend of mine
which i'm gonna have on
so what i'm gonna start doing you guys
and i had dr alana
um zabloski i had her on i don't know if
you guys remember but i had her on
instagram
but i'm gonna start bringing with dr
friends on
and in all that i'm gonna be doing that
soon so i'm gonna start having doctors
on here and
and they can help you know with because
they know the medical medium information
and so toxic heavy metals is something
that i talk to pediatricians about all
the times friend of mine's patrician and
and it's about getting toxic heavy
metals out that's part of
of what can be really helpful so you can
go and talk to your doctor a
pediatrician
and and ask them about that and show
them the medical medium information if
you'd like
and um and and maybe look at some of the
no foods and then some of the foods you
could bring in
but talk to your practitioner for sure
bring the information to your
practitioner
and i'm gonna i'm gonna have a
pediatrician on eventually
and i'm gonna ask that pediatrician
these very questions so you can hear it
straight from a doctor
so yeah
blanca can celery juice help with
glaucoma
i am tired of using so many drops and
having my eye
lasered glaucoma what if you go inside
the book cleanse the heel if i had
glaucoma i'd go inside the book here
and i just opened it just now right here
so what you'll see is
you'll see is glaucoma i don't know if
you can see that right to the left
or to the right if that's what that is
on your on your side your guys's side
but yeah so glaucoma and it looks and
you'll see the true causes of it see
then you learn well what are the true
causes
um with with eye problems i tend to love
to do
food stuff too of course the different
food stuff you might want to pick out a
cleanse that maybe your doctor
recommends out of here or
likes or feels is is adequate for you
you can go into the food sections
i would avoid eggs dairy milk cheese
butter
which is dairy i would avoid that on a
diet keep the gluten out of the diet
that's the first step i would do
personally
whether your animal protein or your
plant-based just obviously plant-based
you're not going to be doing
those foods but gluten you would be
doing so i would avoid that if you're
plant-based but
and um i would clean some of that up
just to start with and over time you
might see just with that alone because
it's not
feeding the very true cause which i have
listed in here is a virus
once that virus isn't getting the food
it likes the
the eye pressure tends to come down so
i've watched this for years where
then the eye pressure tends to come down
in the eyes and the reason why is
because the virus isn't
taking advantage of all of the foods and
other stuff
okay admiral hi anthony how long does it
take to get
the body's trust back the body's
trespass is a really good
question i have a history of eating
disorder sometimes
i'm afraid i'm not gonna get it back um
your your body loves you unconditionally
okay your body loves you unconditionally
you always need to remember this
you're a good person too you didn't do
anything wrong
none of this is your fault really
important to know okay
so keep that in mind have compassion for
yourself all right and
and be light-hearted like it is not your
fault there's reasons why
we get we get eating disorders there's
re real reasons why
and i talk about that in the medical
medium books right here and
and you know and so there's
sometimes we get really sensitive
hypersensitive nervous systems and our
vagus nerve gets sensitive and we get
anxiety
because we're either low grade viral or
we got some toxic heavy metals and then
it triggers off an eating disorder or
you know we've been through hell
you know and back we had a really
difficult experience
an emotional experience or a really big
upset in our life or a loss
and that can trigger it off and when i
talk about how
you know your your your body loves you
and it's working with you on this so
just just
try to keep a light heart the best you
can and um
and you do what you can't you do you can
but um but
but try to look into some of this you
can learn i'm gonna do more about eating
disorders and everything so i'm gonna
talk about that just know i'm proud of
you if you try any of this stuff
as you're trying to get yourself back
and and and ground it
um anyway incredible i'm glad you guys
were with me tonight
and bless your heart and uh
may the angels be with you tonight just
watching you over while you're sleeping
okay think about that when you're going
to bed at night that's what i like to do
right before bed just think about those
angels that are going to just be there
all night while you're sleeping and
they're just going to be by your bedside
and they're going to help you heal and
be there for you
and you're a good person it's not your
fault you're sick it's nobody's fault
here
why you got any symptoms conditions and
and it's
you just gotta just gotta know that i
care about you guys
and believe in you take care