i'm sorry
you'd like to drink
coming up sir
why am i taking so long
i'm not taking you wrong
am i experienced yeah highly experienced
as a bartender
now at aws bar and grill we might get
interrupted so just
bear with us a little bit i still have
customers here i haven't served yet
uh what would you like
you would like
would you like a shot
yes yes sir i have a lot of customers so
i'm trying i'm trying to keep up so bear
with me here
aws bar grill is very busy right now
i'm going to
move things around things are getting
dizzy here the phone i think is running
too so just
okay you're coming right up sir yeah you
guys just got married
oh congratulations
[Music]
i am not confused at all don't say that
i have just a lot of customers i'm very
busy here
good to see you guys here
i'm just going to move this out of the
way and i will be right back shortly
i'm going to take your shots
i'm gonna roll you guys over here for a
second here we're just moving the bar
around
don't you worry i'm bringing you guys
right back
[Music]
are you comfortable in your seats
fantastic
[Music]
i want to make sure you guys
so sorry i had to show the customers
where the guest room for the bathroom is
our little guy here needed to go potty
i needed the restroom
your drink is right here sir
two whiskeys
madam what would you like
a whiskey
oh
would you like one more drink
i will coming right up
oh i spilled some
i spilled some
i am a good bartender
i know you're upset now i know
everybody's upset we have a
spillage here
aws bar and grill
yes
yes lots of customers today what would
you like
um
i'm trying to keep everybody happy
who is this anyway dr nesbitt
why are you calling me when i'm working
right now
yeah we're very busy i have a stain
on the cutting board
dr nesbitt there's the phones ringing
constantly all day long i don't need you
adding to it i'm going to hang up
are you coming by later okay for drinks
good
yeah i'm sorry sir
excuse me my boss is
my boss sal is asking me
i'm sorry sound i i guess i spilled the
whiskey are you gonna take it out of my
pay
okay
it was only about a quarter of an ounce
of whiskey
you were you will be deducting that for
my pay okay
and the cutting board is stained yes
deduct that from my pay as well
i have i have 20 sure i have 20 years
experience
your food is almost ready sir
did you order the fish sandwich at ew's
bar and grill you did i have it coming
right up onion rings too
sir i have the
fish sandwich delight at aws
and
i have the onion rings the aw onion
rings too so
um
you want me to put it over here
are you gonna have
anything else
uh what would you like
you would like buffalo chicken wings
you too
you guys want to share buffalo chicken
wings okay
you guys haven't touched your drinks yet
i noticed
is there something wrong with the drinks
you're not liking the drinks so much
you are liking the drinks
[Music]
i have the buffalo chicken wings coming
right up i think the
i think they're coming right up there
buffalo chicken wings right here how
would you like these would you like
these here anything else with it
okay
you like the buffalo chicken wings
fantastic one of my favorites too
okay you have your drinks everybody
ready sure you have yours
no hold on
hey w's bar and grill
yes we're very busy today
we don't sell pizzas here
buffalo chicken wings
okay
we're live right now
and there's a sale right now in wyman's
everybody's having fun okay
check it out when you can wymans.com
we're going to be making drinks i'm
making the honey orange and wild
blueberry refresher here at aws bar
grill also making sparkling
wild blueberry
juice and lime sparkling wild blueberry
juice and lime let's get that straight
okay
we are gonna make some drinks you guys
good to see you guys
yes so let's get started