i just released medical medium podcast
at apple podcast and also you can listen
to it on spotify too
so the breathing light meditation it's
really powerful and i hope you guys try
it when you get a chance
and some people have some people have
already i've heard i got some comments
here some people have tried it i'm blown
away i'm so happy about it because
light has been a big deal in my life for
decades since age four with spirit of
compassion communicating with me and so
it's very dear to my heart and i wanted
to
i wanted to give you guys this
meditation because i know there's
other light workers out there i know
there's other light stuff out there i
know that but in this meditation though
it's a little different because you're
learning how to control the light use
the light and then pinpoint it and
that's the key right there is
pinpointing that light
and the only way you truly can pinpoint
light
is if you actually move
your nose
and your mouth
away from your face so you have to check
out this meditation i'll talk about a
little bit i want to read some comments
read some points too
i want to answer some questions if we
can along the way too if you guys just
got here we're live right now i'm
talking about the breathing light
meditation right for the emotional
spiritual physical parts of our lives
for the mental emotional physical all of
it spiritual part of our lives so
i know and when we use the light
and we actually take our consciousness
and we connect to the light right
and we use our consciousness to do so
we can then control the light
and guide it into areas of the body that
you need any assistance or you need aid
and that's what i love about this
incredible meditation you guys medical
medium podcast at apple podcast i would
love for you to try the meditation now
here's the great thing
it's free
it's free this could have been packaged
up and sold this could have been
packaged up
turned into a program meditation it
could have been sold
10 different ways
i don't want to do that i wanted this
accessible i wanted this tangible i
wanted you guys to have this with no
cost
no charge not a penny
and that matters to me and
what's incredible about this meditation
no
advertisements
no commercials
so i keep the commercials and
advertisements out i don't do that stuff
you guys know that and
the other thing is is i want to keep it
out and then the meditation you can
listen to it clear and free
so you can work on healing and that
matters to me i did not want to do a
subscription charge for this meditation
i didn't want to do a package a bundle
where you have to pay for this
meditation i didn't want to do all those
things everybody does out there
right
i didn't want to do that i wanted you
guys to have free access to this
incredible tool because that's what it
is
alicia said this is the most interesting
and most incredible meditation i've ever
experienced thank you so much melissa i
want to talk about it a little bit too
why this thing is so powerful
why this spiritual meditation has so
much power to it because
in it
we do something in there that nobody
does and you know i've been doing this
for a long time my whole life right you
guys know that for decades i've been
teaching about spiritual and physical
right teaching you what's wrong right
so you guys if you know medical medium
information you know about all the
medical books okay most popular health
books in the world right the medical
medium series and i've been teaching
about what goes wrong inside of us so we
can heal so that's what i'm known for
but i'm also known
for the spiritual aspect too right and
and then but
what this is this meditation
it's a powerful tool that you can
control
you have control and empowerment here
that's the difference
i want this to be a surprise it's a very
special meditation
and
it's dear to my heart this meditation
i'm getting choked up i'm actually
getting choked up you guys
i'm getting emotional here
because
i know that when you have something like
this in your hands
you can make changes that are
unmeasurable
like
i taught you guys how to heal your
bodies right physically how to heal your
bodies with all the different tools that
i taught you guys to use right
and then
but this tool
right
takes it to another level because this
is a tool that you have full control
over
and then anything's possible because
you're using the light so anything's
possible anything
right
who am i to say anything's not possible
because i've seen
what it has done for people in my life
throughout my
years i wanted you guys to have this in
your hand but i needed to be
in a space
able to do it right now you guys know
that i worked on the brainsaver books
and i finished the brainsaver books
right
it took a toll on me
and i could not
i could not just give you this breathing
light meditation just like i'll just
throw it out i'll throw it out there and
i'll just blab it out and
i had to make sure i was connected
to soc i had to make sure that i was in
that light when i did this meditation
and recorded this meditation for you
guys and i knew i had to get past the
brain book because that was a different
place i was in that was about taking
tremendous amounts of information from
above right
ahead of science information that
science will then fuse and take or
whatever right and i had to make sure
that the brain books were done and soon
as they're done
i had to get i had to get moving into
this and i had to make sure you guys had
this tool in your hand so this is the
meditation if you guys just came on here
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
or you can listen on spotify if you want
and it's the the link is in the
description and on tick tock the link is
in the bio and it's breathing light
meditation i want to talk about it a
little bit if you guys have a minute so
i hope you spend a minute and i hope you
click that link
and do the meditation sometime today
sometime tonight if you can or whenever
you can get a chance
because
it's a very special meditation i know
all the medical media meditations are
special i know
if you've done them you know what i'm
talking about and you know the power
right that they have okay
but
this one here
is going to be definitely
something you haven't experienced and
there's a reason for it there's an
absolute reason for it because
you're
becoming empowered in a different way
you're using the light you're
controlling the light
to work for you you're using it as a
tool
to direct it so if you guys check out
the link in the description please check
it out when you get a chance this is the
breathing light meditation right for the
healing the mental emotional and
physical
jennifer dalton says will you be at life
mastery of course i will of course i
will
yes yes i love it and
so i just i just want everybody to know
if you had a chance to do this
meditations olivia letz's love says this
was just dot beyond words god bless you
i'm so glad that you did the meditation
it makes me so happy because seriously
you won't be disappointed when you try
it now every time you do the meditation
the breathing light meditation it builds
on itself
and there's a spot in that meditation
where you can choose
the place on your body that you feel
like was injured that you feel like that
maybe something happened in your life
and you can choose that moment to direct
the light to that spot that you want to
direct that light to now in the
meditation all right there's different
areas i talk about where you direct the
light into so you'll know like where you
can direct the light into
and
what you what you can do in this
meditation is then right when it comes
to the point where i say now choose a
spot that you want to bring that light
in
right you can even think about it before
you do the meditation what spot would i
like to bring the light in so when you
do the meditation you can then drive
that light into that place that's very
important to you like something that's
ailing you something that's
something that you feel like you've been
harmed or hurt throughout your life any
kind of place
maybe you had an accident maybe
something happened in your life maybe
you've been wounded in a different way
emotionally physically you can take that
light and direct that light into that
place
inside your body
and inside your soul if you need to
inside your heart your soul your mind
your body all of it so it's really
important
to know you have that control so
i want to read a couple of comments here
too is well first of all let's let's
just go into this here so what i like
about this here's one thing right here
discover the power of the light as it
moves through your body and destroys
disease darkness toxic emotions guilt
shame fear doubts and worry now a lot of
us
we we put boundaries up
because we've been hurt so we have to
put boundaries up that's how we protect
ourselves right but when we put
boundaries up
because we've been hurt
right we also
don't know how to heal we can't heal so
easily we need the boundaries up
sometimes
because we need them to protect
ourselves but at the same time once that
boundary is built
and it's there it's there in our
consciousness it's there in our memory
banks it's there in our brain and mind
right and that boundaries there
then it's hard to do some healing that
needs to be done behind those boundaries
and people
they don't know how this works a little
bit where whoa they're like they got
their boundaries up but yet there's a
wound down in behind that boundary
there's a wound in there and how do we
reach that wound and have access to
healing it
this meditation
allows you to take light go through the
boundary
and into that place that you've been
hurt physically emotionally spiritually
mentally in that place where you've been
hurt and harmed in some way
so that you can still keep the
boundaries up that you've had to
throughout life because you've been hurt
throughout your life but at the same
time you can bring light through the
boundary
into a place where you want to heal
can bring that light into the heart you
can bring that light
into the places you want to bring that
light into
you can bring it into that consciousness
right bring that into the
subconsciousness which is incredible
michelle stinnett says i'm finally able
to focus on meditation since healing my
physical symptoms with your life-saving
healing meditation that's a really good
point right there medical media
meditations
very gentle powerful but gentle it's a
different form of meditation than what's
out there in the meditation world
it's there for the chronically ill and
the chronically sick who have a lot of
sensitivities
and so these meditations are geared for
someone who's been through a lot
physically
with symptoms and conditions they've
been through so much
right so that's the kind of meditations
these are it's like the moon meditation
is powerful in all the medical medium
meditations the fruit picking meditation
right you guys know that when the
stargazing meditation but this breathing
like meditation is very special i wanted
this here for you guys as a tool so you
can learn how to use the light for your
healing process
right
jorah says can this help with
self-sabotage behavior
absolutely because what happens is that
when we get light into places
right that have some kind of injury that
we don't have our finger on that we
don't know
we don't know where that injury is we
just don't know you know the
consciousness and the subconsciousness
right and what's inside our brain we
don't know where our injuries are
when they're emotional and spiritual
right
and mental so we don't know where those
injuries are we need light to go in
there and ha ha do the work for us help
us do the work for us so we can do that
healing and that's what's incredible
about this meditation
now what's amazing about this meditation
is you'll feel it
as time goes on after you've done the
meditation so once you do it the
breathing light meditation
you then can
feel the results as you go along you'll
start being like whoa
wait a minute that's starting to feel
like i feel lighter now and emily
marshall said i did the meditation and
it was amazing i need to keep practicing
the visualization so here's what's
incredible about the breathing light
meditation you'll notice it has the word
breathing in front of it right
now but yet it's not a breathing
meditation
where it's just all breathing
that's not it
this is
very powerful very gentle
this is about the light so when you do
this breathing like meditation you'll
notice in the title breathing
light
meditation
there's a big difference right there
dr fon md hey aw can you direct the
light into a loved one yes you can you
can right in that meditation where it
says where would you like the light to
go
you choose
an option to where you want to drive
that light
inside that meditation right when you're
doing the meditation if it's a loved one
that's where you send that light so when
you're doing the visual visualization
when you're in that meditation and your
consciousness is all connected to the
light and you're in there
then you can say i want to direct this
light to a loved one
and that's where you send it and imagine
and visualize and see and connect to
that loved one when you're in the
meditation
and then have the light drive into now
the difference with this meditation
is something that's spirit of compassion
taught me
like more than 30 years ago okay when i
was young when i was a child and it's
taking your nose
taking your mouth
and actually moving it
moving it to a different place on the
body
to a place you want that light to be
pinpointed divine light says can we
choose the whole body instead of just
one spot
you can on that one time right and one
powerful time because you're building up
in that meditation and when that one
powerful time comes
and
where do you want that light to go
if you want it your whole body then
that's where the light goes your whole
body in that place
and that's where you can do it
which is just amazing stephanie chu says
hi anthony i did the meditation last
night pain in my gallbladder was not
there when i woke up
i focused on that area extra that's the
whole point that's what you can do with
this incredible tool i had the pain for
three days straight and now it's gone
thank you so much i am working on
healing every day even when i fail
sometimes
there's no failing there's no feeling at
all
right which is the learning experience
as we heal and we grow and we do the
things we need to do and then sometimes
everybody doesn't have it easy and
it's not our fault if we get kicked back
a little bit or we try or we go back to
some kind of an old habit or whatever it
is so you never fail you're always
moving forward
each time you try something new and you
you know put forward your head
jola says where can i find the link
please link is in the description
breathing light meditation don't miss
out on this i wanted to do a live just
now and talk about the light talk about
this meditation the power it has
all of it
and
i wanted to make sure that you guys had
this tool and it was accessible really
was medical mean podcast and apple
podcast you can also listen to it on
spotify too now the cool thing is
it's free i could have packaged it up
and i didn't want to i don't want to i
could have packaged it up it could have
been on an app it could have been
whatever it could have been just
something you buy subscribe to and then
buy
the breathing light meditation i don't
want to do that
i need this thing free i need it
accessible i need it in your hands
i don't want money attached to it
i want this to be
about you and your healing and i want it
free and accessible and that matters to
me and the healing light
that happens within this breathing light
meditation is profound you're
controlling it you're a part of it and
they don't want you missing out if you
get a chance i know you guys are busy
you've got a lot going on but if you get
a chance right
it would be incredible
and you get a chance and you try the
meditation
joanne says how often can you do these
meditations you could do them every day
you could do them twice a day you could
do them every day you can do them every
other day
right
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast or or spotify if you want to go
you know those are two two platforms
right there breathing light meditation
okay
and so
look i explained in this meditation how
limitations taught by others block
profound information from entering our
being now so here's what happens
we can have boundaries bestowed upon us
from others and not even realize it
because we've been conditioned so what
happens is we go through life and we end
up getting conditioned we can have
boundaries bestowed upon us by
institutions we can have boundaries
bestowed upon us by organizations we can
have boundaries bestowed upon us
blocking our ability to heal
right heal emotionally
by others
and these boundaries can be set up not
even by yourself or who you are these
boundaries can be set up by others
and so and institutions and other
organizations can literally set these
boundaries for you so then you're
blocked
you end up getting blocked and it
interferes with your decision making so
when you want to make the right decision
there's this boundary blockage that
stops you from making the right decision
it's really painful it can happen to a
lot of people so
this meditation is there to just be like
you know what you know what
no organization
no
institution
nobody of some type of institution
organization
right no something else and what their
belief system is
that created a boundary whatever it is
these boundaries that could be in me
that were created by so much that we're
brainwashed about here
this is like the on
brainwashing meditation the breathing
light meditation because what it does is
it puts everything aside
everything aside that we've been
messed with or entrapped with in this
lifetime because of so much darkness and
so much evil that's happening in the
world right we don't know it but we get
thrown into that spider web this
meditation is about moving all of that
away you become this free spirit
and then you're using the light to
pinpoint and direct in places of the
body that you want like you can do that
and put it in a place that counts that
you feel that's where i want that light
and so the goal of the meditation of
what happens the reason why it's so
profound is because once you're in that
meditation you're now connecting to the
light
and if you if you want this is important
too okay whatever you like whatever you
like about the light meaning if it's
god's light then that's what you connect
to if you believe i just talked to
someone the other day like well i
believe in a creator i don't i don't use
the term god i just believe there's a
creature okay well that's the light you
use i talked to another person and
they're like well i believe in the
universe you know universal light this
is the light from the okay well then the
universal light that's what you use
inside this meditation then it's the
universal way
you know another person i believe it's
the light of jesus christ well then
that's that's what you actually channel
you make sure it's that light
so
you know so what you can do with the
power of this light is you can just make
sure
you use this light in the way that works
for you but it's there it's at your
fingertips
it's in this meditation it's this is a
way look we all have access to light but
this is a great tool to really connect
with it because we get so busy we get so
stuck
we get so stagnant
we get trapped in so many things and so
this is a way to move all that aside and
bring that light in
joanna gristo says can you direct this
to a pet absolutely a hundred percent
you can direct that light to a pet when
you do this incredible meditation this
is the breathing light meditation link
is in the description link is in the bio
over there and to talk to you guys
rachel says do you just visualize moving
your nose and mouth to a point on your
body yes we're moving her nose and her
mouth both
we're taking him
and we're moving them
so here's what we're doing we're taking
our nose and mouth right and we're
moving them
removing them all of a sudden here
so now when you're doing that breathing
light meditation
you're actually breathing here because
your nose and your mouth are now here
and then
we're taking our nose and our mouth
we're removing it from here we're
putting it here
right
right in that belly button we're putting
it there and then we're bringing that
light in
it's a technique spirit taught me back
when i was a child
i've used it in my life
right
but there's so many tools i look
if we can just have a heart-to-heart for
a second
if that's okay you guys
soc has given me so many tools since i
was a child to help us all heal
so many powerful tools
everything from things like foods right
and leafy greens and the herbs and the
wild foods
all of it okay
all the way to light and the meditations
all the way to nature my spirit of
compassion has given me so many tools
but there's so many of them that it
takes years and years and years
to get them in the books like the brain
books too which i don't have one right
here on me right in a second but
it takes years to get these tools out to
you guys there's so many of them this
meditation is one of those tools it's
not that i've been holding out
not at all
because there's that many tools and i'm
only this one
person it's one human being
and i'm trying to get them out when i
can as fast as i can and they have to be
right in the sense where
i have to make sure i am connected
beyond when i'm doing this so you have
you guys have this this powerful tool in
your hand tracy said this live review of
the light meditation and how to do it is
extra helpful i want it to be helpful i
want you guys to understand this
meditation in in the best capacity
possible so i wanted to make sure i'm
here to give you guys any guidance
whatsoever so
use this meditation to course correct
so i wanted to tell you about that
you're using this meditation to course
correct your body's healing path and
process now all medical medium
information is about course correcting
if you're sick it's about
finding the cause and healing right
knocking down pathogens taking out
metals getting out chemicals
doing the right thing right and removing
things that we shouldn't be consuming
it's course correcting
well this meditation is course
correcting with the light with the light
the power of the light and that's the
course correcting right there so i
wanted to kind of talk about that a
little bit
feel how the light changes you and feel
how it lingers and stays with you
purifies and clears you like you can
feel that after the meditation
this is a meditation that you just don't
do once
make sure this becomes a part of your
life because it's a part of my life you
think i did it once you know what's
funny is when i was taught this
meditation when i was a kid by soc
and i did the meditation
right
that soc taught me i didn't say okay did
it
did it
i did it once i'm never going to do it
again
right
maybe i'll i'll teach somebody how to do
it
but i'm not going to do it i've been
doing it my whole life
it's the kind of thing where i brought
it into my life i've been doing it my
entire life
it's not the kind of meditation where
you do once you get bored you don't use
it this is a profound meditation
and
it's there for you along the way now the
thing is here's something to know about
the medical media meditations
i just have to be clear about this
because i know there's a lot of new
people and they just don't know and i
understand
it's not man-made
this meditation
the breathing light meditation is not
man-made
so it's not like someone like kind of
knew about another meditation that was
made by another man by another
meditation made by another man another
meditation made by another man and then
well i'll add a little thing to it too
because i'm i'm a guy in the spiritual
movement let me just create a meditation
here look let me man-made it
let me man make it
it's not man-made
and that's why
the meditations do what they do
because they're not actually made by a
guy
who decided to start
you know getting into the spiritual
movement at a certain time in his life
went to some retreats
and decided to make a meditation so
a whole bunch of women can try
because
women make meditations too but really it
started out with guys making meditations
this is not a guy's meditation it's not
a woman's meditation either it's not a
man's meditation it's not a woman's made
meditation
so
and this is important to know
it's from above so this meditation is
made from above
so it comes from above
and so that's the difference with this
there's nothing wrong when a guy makes a
meditation
there's nothing wrong with it at all i
got a friend who makes meditations he's
like check out this
it's like aw
i got a meditation that'll that'll
totally you know
totally put yours to shame check this
out i'm like all right what do you got
he's like what you do is you sit there
you got your legs crossed you got your
hands like this
and here's what you're doing you're
you're trying to knock out all the all
the voices in your head you're trying to
knock out all the noise in your head
you're getting rid of all the noise in
your mind you're clearing your mind
you're breathing in and then you know
you see the sun and you clear your mind
and i'm like okay been done a billion
times made by men
okay that's fine
there's nothing wrong with it i support
it i was like i was like dude do that
meditation for sure when you get a
chance
try this meditation that wasn't created
by a guy
so
it's really a special tool is what i'm
saying and that's what i want you guys
to know and have in your hands it's
important to me
because
it this is got a
personal connection to me it really does
and these meditations aren't just thrown
out there
like lightly you know like meditation
apps and stuff like that meditation
podcast what happens is they're just
literally they're there so people can
get into them but the personal
connection
and it comes from above that's
what helps me with the meditation
it's not sterile
so
the thing is is what you'll learn and
what you'll know when you do this
meditation it's not sterile
it's not sterile
this meditation
right
it becomes a part of you
because guess what
you're the person who's in control and
empowered you're the person that's
gaining that control over the light and
using it to place into a part of your
body or your soul
or wherever
you feel you want to bring that light in
and
yeah be prepared to feel some changes
christina
do we move our nose and mouth to the
other person when we want to direct it
to them yes you do you have to you do
that or how do we direct it you have to
take your nose and mouth
and your nose and mouth is going to go
on to that other person
so you're going to place your nose and
mouth onto the other person
wherever you want
wherever you want wherever you want that
light to enter into the other person do
you want it to enter into their heart
do you want that light to enter into
their brain their heart to their third
eye do you want it to enter
right into their abdomen
into their leg do where do you want that
light to enter into their body you want
it to hit their whole body so you put
your mouth and nose on your body and you
want to hit the whole body if you want
but having the nose amount that's where
it has to go in though
um
alexandra sophia good to see you aw will
this meditation help heal deep grieving
that's what it's for
loss
right trials and loss hardships
right
betrayal that's a big one
chelsea floyd i love that your
information doesn't have any shame link
to it it's all empowerment light and
love chelsea thank you for being here
and bless your heart it means a lot it
really does
so what i was saying before allow
yourself to break boundaries in
unproductive belief systems because what
happens is we fall into all these belief
systems that end up controlling us
because there's money tons of money
behind those belief systems out there
and they end up just controlling us and
brainwashing us and this is about
clearing that which is incredible
right
and
see how the supernatural powerful light
source that's what i call powerful light
source supernatural powerful light
source from above aids and provides
transformation like transformation means
something changes
something changes within us
like it really does
something changes
amber i did this meditation this morning
thank you incredible i'm so proud that
you tried it i'm so proud that you did
it
amazing
it means it means so much to me you guys
truly anyway guys i i really appreciate
you guys being here link is in the
profile on tiktok link is in the
description you guys check out the
breathing light meditation
and
it's free no charge
you can just you know go to medical
medium podcast at apple podcast go find
it
try it when you get a chance right i'm
going live on
tick tock again
and instagram and telegram so you guys
i'm going to telegram instagram and tick
tock in just a little bit and we're
going to talk about the breathing light
meditation again and i didn't even get a
chance to read some comments so we'll do
that there thanks guys for being here