are incredible you guys you guys do the
robot with me
[Music]
SOC says you guys do it so much better
one
talking about the brain we're in the
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
we're day nine
we're doing the nerve shifter which is a
miracle miraculously stealing people
which is incredible when you think about
how powerful that is and what people go
through with their health to think oh my
God this is incredible you guys
Davis is too much truth I know totally
[Music]
we're here you guys I'm excited to talk
about the vagus nerves all of it we're
in the brain saver books incredible
right there
nerve shifter that's what we're doing I
want to read a couple things to you
about it
use the nerve shifter when you're
feeling shaky or anxious how many people
are feeling shaky or anxious and when
you use this nerve shifter when you're
feeling shaky and anxious boom
boom it's incredible
If you experience random spasms Twitches
ticks or shifting and moving pain
throughout your body I hear it all the
time I hear it from Doctor friends I
hear it all the time twitches and spasms
aw my patient has all these Twitches
they can't get rid of them we don't know
what's wrong we did MRIs we did
everything CAT scans we did all the
different ultrasounds we don't know why
they're twitching they're spasming while
they're doing all this moving pain
throughout their body what is going on
AW and I would tell them
cranial nerves all this stuff about it
and that's what we're talking about
today cranial nerves so if you're
experiencing those kinds of spasms or
Twitches or anything like that it's like
boom nerve shifter time Bring It On in
the thing is about the nerve shifter it
can work
in that moment I'll talk about how it
does instant relief and it can work also
along the way if you're doing the nerve
shifter and that's what you choose and
that's what you pick and you're doing it
every day the power of that brain shot
therapy
it's just incredible like it can build
upon itself that's what I wanted to tell
you guys earlier that it can build upon
itself and build upon itself and that's
a big deal right there because that's
healing that's actually moving forward
You're Building upon itself all of it so
here we go when struggling with any kind
of neurological onset or episode
now that's a big one right there a
neurological onset or episode
what does that mean
one migraine coming on
boom get the nerve shifter out
right twitches and spasms coming out of
like getting out of control boom get the
nerve shifter out tingles and numbness
that's happening get the nerve shifter
up so it what it is is like if you got
neurological symptoms and you feel an
episode coming on
of any kind of neurological problem
and you feel it coming on and you're
like oh no I'm going to be dealing with
this again this is why I went to five
doctors this is why I went to the
specialist in the neurologist and it's
coming on again then you get the nerve
shifter out how incredible is that
here's one right here to break a nervous
feeling
about the moment you're in like you're
going to be going somewhere you're
meeting a friend you're going to a
wedding you're going to a party
you have an appointment somewhere and
you're nervous you have a doctor's
appointment and you're nervous you have
any kind of appointment then you bring
in there the nerve shifter how cool is
that
to help calm restless legs syndrome
restless legs and that's what people are
going to notice how incredible the nerve
shifter is for restless legs and any
kind of other issues
some people are already saying I'm
sleeping better because of it
so Kimberly Ann asked the question what
is in the nerve shifter you are looking
at what's in the nerve shifter right
here but it's the specific combination
and the amount
that makes the incredible Miracle happen
so it's the cilantro the kale the
spinach The Parsley the asparagus by the
way asparagus can be called a spear
right
it can be called a shoot too that's
something
it can be called a stock so I'm just
letting you know but there's no
difference it's it's either or right
lettuce in the celery and the lime when
you put those together
and a certain amount in a certain order
and these ones that's when it happens
which is incredible
so to break a nervous feeling like I was
talking about how about this one to calm
your restless legs and then how about
this one before you go flying and taking
a trip a car trip if you're nervous
about a car trip nervous about a plane
trip but these are just some reasons to
use it
if you have anything neurologically
going on and you feel like you need that
boost
then you can bring in the nerve shifter
now this is part of the shifter family
10 shots are in the shifter family 10
different ones this is the nerve shifter
but there's nine other shifters so
there's 30 brain shot Therapies in the
medical medium brain saver books
Miracles is what they are
so if you don't know anything about the
brand saver books pick some up if you
can amazon.com us 40 off right now 26.29
dollars
it's incredible there's 12 books in here
in these two books
that's how big they are
so you guys the website is working now
medicalmedium.com you can see me on
there live as we speak I just want
everybody to know we have some funny
stuff happened so we're back
so let's go let's move into this a
little bit
so we're in the medical medium brain
shot therapy
and we're doing the entry level
so I want everybody to know what this is
so if you just came on here and you
don't know what's going on this is a
10-day
brain shot therapy challenge cleanse
challenge challenge that's free
go to medicalme.com download your free
PDF to find your grocery shopping list
you are not too late even though we're
day nine tomorrow's day ten so if you
can be here for tomorrow for day 10
incredible
just that one day
can help change your life Candace says
you and SOC have truly changed my life
and saved me from a life of pain and
misery I no longer have ra or symptoms
from chronic illness the brain shots are
taking my healing to a whole other level
amazing so glad you're here
I told you guys when I was in my office
the spirit of compassion was giving me
the information
and I was just mind blown
and then and I and when you think about
it
you know and I knew you guys were gonna
get this experience
because of what they are because Spirit
compassion was saying it's instant
relief of my incredible incredible this
is how it works
Erica says I find this shot works beyond
what it says it helps it does work
beyond what it says it helps and that
that's another thing too the nerve
shifter does really a broad spectrum of
neurological problems
and what I love about the nerve shifter
is it can give relief instantly to some
symptoms while offering
long-term relief happening with other
symptoms
so what I like about the nerve shifter
is if you drink it
it builds on itself and then not only
gives you relief for say one or two
symptoms or something that you're
dealing with but it gives you long-term
relief because it builds on itself so
all of a sudden you're doing the nerve
shifter for a couple weeks and you're
like what is happening and then
life-changing results are happening in
other areas
which is incredible all on its own but
the shifter shots can do that you get 30
though you got the stabilizers to shift
your shots right and you got the
exposure shots you guys know now you
have the books
and how incredible that is medical
medium brain shot therapy offers instant
relief because it goes into the blood
vessels of the mouth absorbs instantly
and heads to the brain as fast as
possible
so it heads to the brain quick but it
isn't just that factor alone it's the
combination that nobody knew science or
research didn't know or anybody else in
health in the world and ever will
that the information that came from
above is cilantro spinach kale parsley
asparagus
lettuce celery and lime put together
just right in the combination of the
order makes it so that a certain group
of neurons
get the medicinal effect what the brain
shot therapies do is pinpoint groups of
neurons for specific reasons and healing
that right there can't be done anywhere
else that's how incredible this healing
tool is
Deborah said my brain is feeling so much
clearer from taking these shots
and that is so important because if that
can happen for us what does that mean it
means everything less doctor
appointments less stress less everything
that gives us a hard time Jenny Jen I
took the trauma shock and lost shot last
night and it helped my back pain I
wasn't expecting that that's how it
works it works like that because they're
that powerful and when you're dealing
with potent medicine entering the brain
really quick in certain regions
other things can start to improve
what happens is with that potent
medicine that's going there and it's
delivering their fast and that's
something too to think about
because the combination makes the
absorbent power quick
when you have a quick reaction occur
where it's driving to the brain and the
brain stem fast
you can get
reset and rewired fast
so what the brain shot therapies are
doing is they're a therapy that's
rewiring your brain
how incredible is that a therapy that's
actually rewiring your brain
and when you think about that it's
extraordinary really it's incredible the
healing shots of the medical medium
brain shot therapy are tools that come
from above you guys know that from
Spirit of compassion I talked about that
in the last eight days before today
these brain shots are composed of
specific combinations of ingredients
working together systematically for
specific reasons that only a source
above could know
incredible
the relationships among these
ingredients are intricate and unknown to
anyone until now this knowledge from
above has remained untapped but now it's
out in the world
and it's incredible if you guys share
about it put medical medium in front of
it like medical medium obsessive thought
shifter medical medium nerve shifter so
people know where they can get the rest
of the information which is volumes of
information so they can heal and not all
of a sudden start switching the
ingredients and doing all kinds of
strange stuff
Chrissy says Where do we get the brain
shot therapy Chrissy from the brain
saver books there's two of them right in
front of you right here
amazon.com us 40 off right now which is
incredible or go to the library and get
them for for free from the library if
you want head there and ask them where
are the brain saver books
would you get them on Amazon if you're
somewhere else around the World Book
Depository and other things you could
also go to medicalme.com sign up watch
watch the last eight days of the brain
shot therapy cleanse Challenge and even
partake in the night the ninth day today
or tomorrow the 10th day how incredible
yep all right you guys we're in the
entry level cleanse I just want to run
that by you
entry level cleanse
10 shots
10 days
but here's the thing one to three shots
a day you can do like the nerve shifter
here's my first nerve shifter
I'm going to do my second nerve shifter
later
how about you guys I'm gonna do my third
nerve shifter later later later
alligator
so I'm going to do the third one later
later so I'm going to do three shots
that's what I've been doing so every day
of this brain shot therapy lens
challenge why do I say silly stuff every
single day
I'm doing three shots
so that's that's what I'm doing you can
do one shot every day of the 10 day
cleanse challenge you can do two shots
you can do three shots
I'm doing three
now this entry level brand shot therapy
cleanse
you have your choice of what shots you
want to do in the therapy cleanse we're
doing you know I'm doing the ones that
spirit and I picked but you can do the
ones you want too
that's okay we're in the entry level
here's the cool thing you can keep your
foods and your diet and your whatever
regimen that you're doing whatever your
routines are that you do whether they're
medical medium or something else you can
keep them all
and that's fine and still do this
challenge with us that's the entry level
Robin young says I did the sleep and
recharging stabilizer shot last night
what an amazing night I had that is
incredible
I'm so proud of you too for doing that
and experiencing that it's just
incredible Donna says it's curing my
excessive hunger too well
there's a craving shifter I mean
yeah these can do so many things now
remember 50 ounces of water a minimum
through the day so it doesn't have to be
right when you take your shot so if just
pretend I just need the nerve shifter
now and I'm going to send it down
right
bartender give me another one right and
I just sent it down I'm not going to do
50 ounces of water right now I'm not
going to dilute it I'm not going to eat
a whole bunch of food I'm not going to
go out get a double cheeseburger I don't
eat double cheeseburgers I'm not going
to go out and eat that right when I sent
that down
you can also make them all at once store
them in a jar with the lid if you really
want
that's okay best to make them fresh that
best to make them on the spot best to
make them right now when you make them
each time but you can also do that too
make them ahead of time if you have to
and do other things
what the brain shot therapy does is it
gets to the brain stem the neurons in
various areas of the brain the emotional
center of the brain too gets there quick
and starts to Target and pinpoint areas
that need help it's almost like they
find their way
they're driven by light
comes from above so it just goes to the
brain and areas it's a miracle it's why
we're having Miracle results
how incredible
Debbie says did aw say when the mm-1500
will be restocked it is in stock so I
don't know why they're doing that did
you call the company because it's so
strange the mm-1500
should be in stock
and it's 20 off
incredible so what you'll see out there
you guys and I'll give you a rundown
we're going to talk about the vagus
nerves and everything else in a second
but I'll give you a quick rundown on
this
why is the mm1500 Great
it's great because it saves you money
what I'm noticing is everybody's all
pumped up about the MLM and affiliate
marketing juicers that are out there now
that have all this money behind them and
all that and they've the sharks have
gotten into the medical meme community
and everybody's buying these other
juicers fine buy them it's great but
you're going to spend
double the money on produce long term
so you lose money as you're using the
juicer
the difference is with the mm-1500 is
the high compression
and what's happening it's a masticating
slow masticating juicer so the nutrients
get preserved
now what people don't realize when you
use the the other juicers that are like
breaking into the community fine and
dandy right
what no one realizes it's not a slow
masticating juicer
it's not a slow cold pressed juicer
so what you're doing is you're losing
nutrients
the other problem
is you're not squeezing enough juice out
of the pulp
and so what you're doing is you have to
buy more so that means if you want a
juice with your juicer it's all great
and all but you'll have to buy more kale
more parsley more everything and the
cost of food is going up the reason why
I backed Omega and I work with them
is because the concept
of food going up in price like it is
in the concept of being able to save
people money why they use their medicine
machine
was a big deal to me because the
chronically ill they're not made of
money
and so saving money wherever they can is
critical so be careful if you unless
you're rich if you're totally rich and
you want to just throw produce down the
Chute of your in your machine
and all that and it doesn't matter how
much of it you buy every second
then yeah then then don't worry just
don't worry about the 1500 I guess but
I'm just saying that's what this was 20
off has a high compression slow
masticating juicer to preserve the
nutrients
and it pays for itself so that's why it
was all about that I haven't talked
about it in months and stuff and all
that and
I've been so busy with the books and
everything else it's good for you guys
to know if you did buy another juicer
just so you know that down the road you
could save up get the mm-1500 and save
money and it'll pay for the juicer you
once bought that didn't save you money
so it'll pay for that plus your new
juicer
choose your talk
okay let's get into it vagus nerve
your inflamed cranial nerve section
inside the book is epic I say that
because it's Advanced it's ahead of
research in science it's mind-blowing
and it basically
tell us the story of why we're dealing
with so many neurological conditions so
if you're anybody that has struggled
with neurological fatigue like fatigue
or anything else in your life
the information in this section is just
it's so important it's just epic so
let's go into it a little bit
inflammation of the cranial nerves play
a large role in chronic mystery illness
and that's what medical research and
science doesn't know
that the cranial nerves being inflamed
the subtle inflammation that they don't
realize plays a role in all of our
neurological symptoms
this is a huge deal right here
I also say mystery illness is a much
broader category than anybody realizes
you know what I was talking about
earlier you guys you can get a diagnosis
of vertigo but you don't have an answer
or know why you have vertigo
a doctor can give you a diagnosis for
vertigo but not give you the answer that
it's your vagus nerves being inflamed
and why they're inflamed so not only
unless they took medical medium info
right
but not only when you get that vertigo
diagnosis or feeling like your balance
that mystery balance issue you've been
through all the MRIs you got all the CAT
scans
you got all the brain scans it's still a
mystery but you got this bit dizziness
and balance issues and vertigo and all
that even if it's temporary in your life
the point is
is they can give you the label of
vertigo or Meniere's disease
but they can't give you how why or where
it doesn't exist in the medical world
both alternative and conventional
same thing if they give you a Bell's
Palsy diagnosis or a fatigue diagnosis
or an anxiety diagnosis they still can't
give you the answers to why you have it
and they don't know it's the cranial
nerves being inflamed or which cranial
nerve is in flame that can give you the
anxiety
anyone who has struggled with any
chronic health issue knows this isn't
how it works you guys know if you've
been to the doctor you know that when
you get an answer
of a diagnosis or not even a diagnosis
maybe you didn't even get one and you're
on your tenth doctor but when you do get
a diagnosis it's still not an answer to
why or how
so you're being handed a label for your
set of symptoms
that's not the same as receiving answers
about why those symptoms aren't
interrupting your life in the first
place
so that's important to know and I wanted
to run that you like when I read this
section there's so many places to talk
about but that was a really
important Place cranial nerve answers
your cranial nerves include your vagus
nerves your trigeminal nerves and your
facial nerves among others right
hypoglossal nerve that's another one
right there olofactor nerve right
Factory nerve and then your optic nerves
you got all your cranial nerves
these are the places that get inflamed
and then we have problems we end up with
the brain fog we end up with the
Twitches spasms we end up with the
tingles and numbness we end up with the
migraines we end up with the trigeminal
neuralgia we end up with the bell's
palsy we end up with all kinds of
different things
twitching nose blurry eyes where your
eye doctor's like well there's nothing
wrong with your eyes you got the blurry
eyes right
so whatever happens the cranial nerves
get this mild inflammation and within
this mild inflammation we end up with
symptoms we go to doctor to doctor and
nobody knows why we're sick
viral nerve and brain stem inflammation
so let's cover that for a couple of
minutes too
most people with chronic illness don't
have physical injuries to the cranial
nerves keep that in mind so someone has
a chronic mystery symptom or condition
they don't have an injury to the vagus
nerve itself
and what you'll find out there that
people say vagus nerve
and so every time I say vagus nerves to
people they go Oh you mean Vegas Turf so
I have to flip it sometimes so that
they'll understand I'll run into this
all the time
but what
people don't realize that the vagus
nerve it's vagus nerves there's two of
them
and so when someone has a vagus nerve
injury that's only one of the vagus
nerves
if someone has a vagus nerve
inflammation it's only inflammation of
one nerve not two
if someone has Vegas
influence if someone has inflammation to
the vagus nerves it's both nerves but
there's two nerves it's important to
know and what you'll find out there and
all the lectures that I've had to do but
the vagus nerves and the information of
the books and everything
what's so crazy is when you talk to
somebody that's like trying to learn
about the vagus nerves out there and
everything they'll never say nerves they
think it's one only
had someone tried to lecture me pretty
recently about that saying that they
knew all about the Vegas room like
there's two right and they're like no
there's not I was like yeah there is
there's two
so what is this mysterious inflammation
that happens in our cranial nerves that
actually takes us down to a situation
where we can be in our darkest hour and
I mean that here's the crazy thing when
we're dealing with chronic sickness you
guys
for the most part the cranial nerves
play a role especially when it's
Neurological on any level
this is where people can be literally on
their hands and knees and praying to God
like God I'm dying please help me
this is when people really suffer they
have severe fatigue that's your cranial
nerves
they have pain in their face that's
their cranial nerves they have pain in
their ears
cranial nerves severe tinnitus ringing
in their ears so bad they can't sleep at
night that's their cranial nerves
burning tongue burning mouth so bad that
they can't even they can't Rectify it
they can't find help that's their
cranial nerves
people out there have been pushed off
the cliff
because their suffering was so great
because their cranial nerves were
problematic but no doctor or
psychiatrist or healer knew it was a
cranial nerve causing that problem but
there was a problem even Underneath It
All the true cause to why the cranial
nerve was inflamed see how advanced this
information is it's incredible
and a lot of people suffer greatly
because of trigeminal nerve being
inflamed facial nerve being inflamed
optic nerve being inflamed
have a glossal nerve being inflamed
cochlear nerve being inflamed
all of it like suffered greatly to the
point of can't function can't work they
have 50 100 symptoms
it all adds up they've been to 20
doctors 100 doctors all because of
mysterious inflammation in the cranial
nerves
when you think about how much that
affects people in their suffering and
struggling
oh my God
let's just talk about it anxiety is a
big one right there there's people with
crippling anxiety
I see stories all the time I hear
stories all the time I have doctors
contact me all the time about crippling
anxiety cases
and we're dealing with cranial nerves
with the crippling anxiety
of course you guys know in the medical
mean books there's anxiety chapter in
the brain saver book that's mind-blowing
when you read that it's like whoa It's
so detailed
so let's go into the little bit the tree
branch effect right here
the cranial nerves where inflammation
can be the most common are the
trigeminal nerves
facial nerves
vagus nerves
right vestibular cochlear nerve right
optic nerves
right well Factory nerves right
hypoglossal nerves right
anyway all of these can be inflamed the
tree branch effect that's the spirit of
compassion calls it
as I mentioned earlier our cranial
nerves occur in pairs which is why I
refer to them in the plural here
which is why I refer to them that way
you'll often hear these nerves referred
in the singular that is the vagus nerve
as though it is one single rope of a
nerve running through your body I say
vagus nerves in the books
because there is a pair of vagus nerves
branches stemming from your brain stem
just as there is a pair of trigeminal
stemming from the brain stem
cranial nerves are like tree branches
you guys and it's pretty cool to
actually see them like tree tree
branches
which can make symptoms complicated and
which also spares us from even greater
pain or debilitation
the human body is designed specifically
so that if one nerve or one branch of a
nerve is damaged
whether viral inflammation or car
accident or something else that you have
the other nerve to survive
so what research and science doesn't
know alternate medicine doesn't know is
we were designed with two nerves
protect us
so that if we get injured maimed hurt or
inflamed through viral infection
or inflamed and irritated
from complications of toxic heavy metals
that we have another nerve
that's why when we get Bell's palsy it's
usually one nerve that goes down
and then our face goes like that
Jackie B says oh my God that makes so
much sense I have I've had ear issues
for a long time ringing pain Etc you can
get the pain in the ears here that's the
cranial nerve so you can get the pain so
bad in the ear in the weirdest places
and you go to all these different ears
nose and throat doctors and they don't
know what it is or what's going on they
give you an antibiotic send you out the
door
they can't tell if it's otitis media
they can't tell anything
I mean it's credible information though
about this in through this book and
you'll see how like cool it is and how
much is in here
if someone says oh he doesn't know his
books or anything like that but the way
I read them or anything you have to
realize that
I took the information down word from
word from above I had to learn it just
like you guys have to learn it
it's two huge massive books of
complicated incredible Advanced Medical
information
I am a student
of
Spirit of compassions
information I'm a student and messenger
I've written the books with my own right
hand
from getting the information from above
but I still have to memorize and study
and become an expert the books are that
fiercely filled with Incredible
information
Mary Kay says I've only ever heard
people refer to them as the vagus nerve
never Vegas nerves until you
and mark my words right here you will
eventually see it out there being
referred to as vagus nerves as soon as
the vagus nerve experts so they say
learn the truth
from these books and hearing people talk
about it they'll then reset themselves
and they won't cite it back to the books
okay the biggest nerve insights what
you'll hear called the vagus nerve is
not just one thick nerve this is
mind-blowing if you want to know a
really powerful vagus nerve piece of
information here
what you'll hear called the vagus nerve
when it's really vagus nerves
is not just one thick nerve that runs
from one end to the other in a perfect
line
the vagus nerves are a larger pair of
nerves that leave the head region
and travel down to the Torso right
but get this check this out you won't
hear this anywhere
the vagus nerve size and reach make them
more complex than shorter cranial nerves
which is why they deserve specific
attention here and get this it's coming
right now you'll be blown off your seat
if you want a new Vegas nerve
information about the Vegas nerves Susan
Oren says I'd spend 25 years going to an
ENT doctor and dentist chiropractor
appointments crazy I'm finally learning
this today after all these years
I had to learn it too but I have to
learn the information in all eight books
the medical medium books it's a lot of
information to to remember it's a lot of
information to learn I'm a student and a
messenger
the Vegas they're Grapevine check this
out
we can think of the vagus nerve
structure as a grapevine like the other
cranial nerves the vagus nerve Grapevine
is split in two as it leaves the brain
stem with those two main Vines branching
off on their own pathways
one vagus nerve vine branch could be
inflamed while the other vagus nerve
vine branch is not inflamed
I mean that's insane when you think
about it because think about how
powerful of a piece of information that
is that's why you have a symptom here
but you don't have one here that's why
you got a problem here but you don't
have one here that's why things are
moving too
one Vegas theravine Branch could be
inflamed while the other Vegas theravine
branch is not inflamed this is a
critical part of the human design that
protects us it means that if one of the
vagus nerves is completely inflamed or
damaged there may still be a chance of
survival why the other Vegas Fair shares
its functions
besides of research doesn't know that
yet they share their functions that is
not known they don't have a study they
don't have a test they don't have any
ability to know that
medical research and science here it
says that and here interesting medical
research in science haven't yet
discovered all aspects of the vagus
nurse that came from above
that's not my words
that's the words that Spirit of
compassion specifically made me write
in that moment medical research in
science haven't yet discovered all
aspects of the vagus nerves
there are still new discoveries to be
had one future Discovery is Vegas nerve
regeneration vnr that is certain parts
of the vagus nerves can regenerate and
regrow themselves if the conditions are
right
medical research and science will also
discover that the anatomy of the vagus
nerves is not definitive this is where
it really gets crazy ping says yes it's
a lot of information it's like learning
to be a neurologist it's mind-blowing
yes it is
that's exactly what it is because I know
somebody complained and says he doesn't
even know his own books it's like
if I was another Health author my book
would be this big
it'd be one book every three years two
years
it would be one concept you hang your
hat on in the book The Concept would be
a theory from some study that didn't
work out right
there'd be some keto stuff and some eat
better stuff in there
and then I would take a half a million
dollars and shove it into the in into
getting the book out there through like
the system because that's what they do
and medical medium we don't do that here
but with here's the thing this is this
is actually
but with this information neurologists
in science research don't know yet
so you're getting
like a class
in this a training and education in this
but science research doesn't know this
information yet
okay ready this is really cool medical
research and science will also discover
100 years from now that the anatomy of
the vagus nerves is not definitive
surgeons don't even know this yet the
vagus nerves are not designed the same
way in every person for example the
Vegas nerve branches don't completely
connect in the Torso for everybody oh my
God
so the vagus nerve branches don't
completely connect in your torso the
same way somebody else for everybody
in some people the two Vine branches
merely cross over and touch each other
not actually connecting
that's Advanced Medical Research and
science
I remember when Spirit compassion was
making me write that part down and I was
just like it what
the vagus nerves also vary in length in
each person what
what
the vagus nerves think about that also
vary in length in each person
Melanie says oh my God that's why I have
restless legs only on one side correct
the Vegas nerves also vary in length in
each person I could read that line 100
times because that is so mind-blowing it
is unbelievable you can go to any course
or class you can go to medical school
and they won't teach you that there
you can spend a million dollars in the
best medical school there ever was
some ivy league medical school and they
won't teach you that bit of piece of
information right there
if anything's glitching there will be a
replay you can watch this again at
medicalme.com under brain shot therapy
video replays you have to find that
section on medicalme.com click that part
and you can watch it the replay
okay
this discovery is going to be forced
upon the medical industry due to robotic
surgeries what where robots programmed
to perform surgery end up injuring
patients vagus nerves because the
calculations are so unpredictable from
person to person did you hear that
did you hear that like what
I forgot that was even in here
and I've like gone over these books
day in day out 20 hours 22 hours a day
this discovery of the Vegas nerves
varying in length and each person is
going to be forced upon the medical
industry due to the robotic surgeries
where the robots programmed to perform
surgery end up cutting injuring patients
vagus nerves because the calculations
are so unpredictable from person to
person can you believe that
my God
a health author can hang their hat on
that one little Discovery right there
and write a book about it and put it out
there that's how just that concept alone
and there's hundreds of these these
incredible pieces of Truth in these
books
this chapter belows me away
medical communities are going to start
finding out that the vagus nerves length
length growth size and directions of
travel are not as cookie cutter as
previously assumed how do you like that
but don't worry once these books are out
which is now
some vagus nerve experty person who does
exercises or whatever is going to take
that piece of information and teach in
their classes and never tell one of
their students where it came from and
originated from
please share these Challenge videos by
the way
the vagus nerves are made up of tiny
strands and strings of nerve cells that
run the length of the nerves a vagus
nerve is not just one solid nerve
it's a complex weave of nerve cells this
is similar to how the other cranial
nerves work although not identical this
is this complexity Works in our favor
when vagus nerve inflammation occurs it
may affect multiple strings within a
vagus nerve yet not every single string
of the nerve no one knows that part ever
Natalia says that's not that's how
medical discoveries happen by injuring
people
brilliant brilliant no brilliant that's
incredible
you're over there on YouTube
that's how medical discoveries happen by
injuring people
oh you're asking
um yes
for instance like the robotic surgeries
the surgeries that they're developing
right they're creating they're building
and perfecting trying to perfect robots
for surgeries
but they've had to put the robots aside
because
robots are also really dangerous what
happens with the Vegas nerve they're
going to discover the vagus nerve is
different length in everybody because
they're going to accidentally be cutting
the nerve in half through robotic
surgeries so when a patient's on the
operation table
the robot is going to accidentally when
it cuts it's going to cut someone's
vagus nerves in half not realizing that
each person's is a different length
that's how they're going to learn about
the different lengths through it to
catastrophe like that epic you know epic
Carolina says what page are we reading
from 102 page 102 of brain saver right
here not for brain saver protocols
medical communities are going to start
finding out that the vagus nerves length
growth size and directions of travel are
not as cookie cutters previously assume
the vagus nerves are made up of the tiny
strands I talked about which is another
incredible thing this means inflammation
does not take over an entire vagus nerve
I talked about that okay here we go it
also means symptoms can move and shift
so vagus nerve cells are in these
strands so one section of your vagus
nerve can be inflamed like through like
Epstein-Barr some kind of viral
neurotoxin that we talk about in all the
medical mean books that that advance in
information that's very compassionate
gave us for years now in these books you
can have this inflammation in half your
vagus nerve causing symptoms to vary and
go actually causing neurological
symptoms to make you feel like you're
going insane and the doctor doesn't
understand you
I can go on you guys there's so much
information in here about the vagus
nerve
and cranial nerves you guys
we're in the brain saver book we're in
the brain saver challenge let's start
making the nerve shifter shot I think
that's someplace we can go we talked
about a lot of different aspects of it
we're in shifter shots let's read about
shifter shots for a couple seconds
because that's what we're doing
the world is getting so complicated in
so many ways and we've been being pushed
in so many different directions it's
easy to get confused or stuck in a
pattern and to shift your shots like the
nerve shifter break that pattern
how incredible is that
when you think about that right there
breaking that pattern
are we in half time right now we're in
half time before we make the shot
you guys want to do the robot with me
[Music]
that's not the robot
that's not the robot get it right
[Music]
we're doing the talking robot
you guys can do a better one break dance
all right so let's get you guys we're
out of the half time right now
if robots will cut through the vagus
nerves why aren't regular surgeons
already cutting them regular surgeons
are already cutting them but the problem
is with regular surgeons regular
surgeons already accidentally cut a lot
of things in people but the regular
surgeon is looking at the Vegas nerve
but doesn't know it's a different length
than somebody else's but what's happens
is they dial in the robots
how the body's built and the robot
accidentally cuts through because they
can never calculate each person each
person's vagus nerve is a different
length but an individual surgeon opens
you up and sees a Vegas nerve not
realizing it's a different length but he
sees it but yes he can still
accidentally cut it because surgeons
accidentally cut everything
all right guys we're out of our halftime
intermission
so we're in the
let's make the shifter shot right here
we're day nine if you just got in here
how cool is that
I'm pumped about the day nine
MB Doom I didn't expect it but I think
this shot might be the most important
one for me it's clearing so much pain
that's why I do what I do because if I
can give you pain relief
with sfc's information it means
everything Christine says just order the
mm-1500 gray is sold out I got the blue
I love the blue one I have the blue and
gray one the blue and kind of like
silver gray one
I love the blue one
it's incredible
all right
let's get into it a little bit
let's start with the lime
let's peel it
so I'm peeling the lime right now as you
can see
so it says
Porter lime peeled
so
now if your lime is not that juicy use a
little bit more
if your lime is really juicy you might
use just your quarter if your lime is
huge like you got a big lime
you can like gauge that as well they
don't have to be Precision perfect but
you want to get close to it so I'm going
to do a quarter of a lime right here
peeled
getting my ingredients ready
all right
so we got the lime I got a quarter of a
lime peeled right here quarter cup
tightly packed spinach
[Music]
let's get you in there
so quarter cup tightly packed that's
about it right there
if I was to pack that in
all right so now we need a quarter cup
roughly chopped kale
get a quarter cup going
okay
now you know what I've measured a
billion times because obviously I've
made these
so I've got a really good idea with my
hands of what that is plus I also
have a voice talking to me
quarter cup tightly packed are roughly
chopped lettuce is next
try to get any lettuce that you like or
whatever I mean honestly butter Leaf I
like so I'm doing butter leaf I love it
for that
Green Leaf is fine
quarter cup tightly packed Cilantro's
next
so
that's about that right there for
quarter cup
got that in here quarter cup tightly
packed
parsley
foreign
medium asparagus stocks
that's kind of a smaller one I'm gonna
go with a medium right there
there you are
now you can call them Spears stalks I
might go with this one there you go
shoots
awesome and then a half a stalk of
celery now okay let's get this straight
I see some of you guys social media have
been when when you're thinking like half
a stalk of celery I see some of you guys
are using half of a whole bunch of
celery so say you got a bunch of celery
instead of like taking one stock off
breaking in half like you're supposed to
and running it through
[Applause]
you're doing a whole half a bunch
that's not gonna work
so you have to go with a half a stock a
half a stock is one really important to
know okay we got it
incredible I love how quiet that juicer
is too foreign
[Music]
that's where you save money right there
incredible
[Applause]
[Music]
this is a nerve shifter and I I can use
a nerve shifter
I get nervous sometimes when I come on
here and I go live
this is not pre-recorded I can make a
terrible mistake by saying a bad word
foreign
[Music]
so I'm nervous when I go live
so I would like the nerve shifter
indeed
I'm really excited about this
[Music]
the nerve shifter hits me on the first
tip
Monica says this is an amazing shot face
came gone in 10 minutes oh yeah
I got the tingles I got the tingles from
the first set
[Music]
second sip
smooth
[Music]
a third sip
this is when I need it today I needed
this today
give it time to just give it a second
give it a minute
it's instant
bartender
give me another
please
[Music]
why thank you
you know this is an incredible shifter
shot
remember when Spirit of compassion gave
me this one
[Music]
wrote it all down you know what I did
five in the morning I ran
into the kitchen
I got everything I needed I just made it
and I remember when I took that first
sip that did the same thing to me it
puts a smile on my face
it's going to the brand fast
why does your face pain go away in 10
minutes
because
the nerve shifter goes into the neurons
where the brain stem is and it hits
those cranial nerves
and it's really a miracle it's a miracle
these books
are the greatest books of all time
spread the word they are and and you can
be proud that you're actually straight
up being truthful because these are the
greatest books of all time it's
undeniable
when you read them and what you see in
them and the Miracles that are in these
books
they are the greatest books in health
history
I can judge these books
and I've I've known that the medical
medium books are all incredible books
and the best health books that we have
in history but I've never said that
I never said that these two like this is
different or these are the greatest
books
in health history right now that were
released
because it was the next level and of
course all the medical media books have
saved lives and they're all Next Level
and they're all Frontier information
Advanced science and against science and
research Advance far above it but the
point is is that these books are the
greatest books of all time you'll know
you can be the judge yourself when you
get the books you guys have you ever
tried the brain shots have you tried any
of them
have you tried this one just now
let me know what you're feeling what
were your results what did you
experience please share your story maybe
a reel a post or a story
tag at Medical medium hashtag medicalme
so I could see them and I can repost
them you named keep an eye on
medicalmedium.com my website I am
enhancing it every day it is an
incredible incredible place to be and
it's free free free free
it's all free and that's the way it
should be no subscription fees no pay
walls no nothing you go there you get
information to heal for your friends and
family and the people that you love and
care about and leave some reviews about
the books on amazon.com if you can
this way people can find their way and
they see these reviews and it matters
people make decisions and I can't tell
you every time the trolls come in and
try to hit the books on the one stars
and then people come in and they go well
I'm not sure about that medical medium
I'm not sure about his brain saver book
because this one star called him you
know a putz and says he's just ugly and
stupid and everything else and I don't
think
I don't think I want to get the book now
well you just lost your chance to heal
you're going to see another 10 doctors
and maybe 10 years later you'll come
back to the books but the point is is
the reviews helpful so people can find
their way
if you like the books if you like the
books
and how do you clean your book they come
dirty sometimes through Amazon because
on the Amazon conveyor belt they get
thrown on the conveyor belt the conveyor
belts are greasy
so your brand new pristine books
depending on what Warehouse or where
could have a smudge on it take a you
know a damp washcloth put a little soap
on there and clean it off incredible
right and look out for imposters
they're imposters
look out for the imposters they act like
me they have my profile they have a
picture of me they say I'm doing
consultations when I don't and they go
and they ask you for stuff and money and
everything else look out for those guys
you guys I'm doing private or what I
call private on telegram because hey it
feels that way it's like crazy when I do
the telegram like exclusive telegram
messages it's it's really intimate it's
really like close it's different it
catches me in a different part of the
day it catches me where I'm in this wind
down moment right before I get revved up
again for the night to work some more
there's this little spot where I
actually calm down
I'll do I'll do one of this one of the
shots the brain shots like right now I'm
gonna do nerve shifter today so it's
three today so I'll do that and also
gonna come down I'm winding down a
little bit it's a certain part at the
end of the day and then I get on
telegram for those exclusive messages
and it's heart to heart I read out of
the books talk about some fun stuff and
I've been really loving that because
it's a great great to have that
connection with you guys so that's like
almost every day look out for telegram
on there right check out the website
medicalme.com like I said
and check out the mm-1500 tell people
about it you guys know I work with them
I fully endorse them because of the fact
that it's that good slow masticating
cold pressed juicer saves people money
it's juicing more the the pulp is dry
the other juicers don't do that even if
they say they do they actually don't
that's the game played it's a dog eat
dog world
that's what it is
and they come in and they just take
advantage of people
and they lie it's a dog eat dog world
um
so yeah
the question there can't you have a
phone call or you can answer emails so
you can personally help the list of
people that were trying to reach me for
help reached into the millions many
years ago a lottery system that we had
many years ago
the whole thing was just sad
I could not reach that many people
millions of sick people around the world
my doctor friends and many other people
through the years said aw when are you
gonna write the Books
Spirit of compassion wanted me to start
writing the books over 20 plus years ago
situation in life didn't lead me to be
able to write them over 20 25 years ago
because I was busy helping out people by
the thousands one-on-one seven days a
week
and what happened was
the too many people needed my help and I
could not keep up with it it was
virtually impossible seven days a week
for years no vacation ever for decades
including on call throughout the middle
of the night for emergencies an
emergency line for doctors
to reach me in the middle of the night I
didn't sleep for decades I worked very
hard and spirit of compassion said it's
time to get the information to the world
so Millions can receive that information
in the books so they don't need a
consultation and so they can educate
their doctors themselves become their
own experts and work on their healing
process and have access to these Miracle
tools which is happening
so I hope that answers the question
the books are one book so you have to
get both
but it's two books
see
it was one book originally and the
publisher couldn't publish it
where they couldn't put it out there and
print it
and so it had to be split in two it's
two massive books 600 pages
there's 12 books in both books meaning
six books and six books 12 books worth
it's packed and jammed
I wrote it mostly in one year
and I did 20 hour days
and
they are done and in your hands
incredible
anyway I do free lives I do free
podcasts free information on the website
everything's free free you can become
your expert for free you can get the
books in the library for free
that's how it should be because the
chronically ill
most everybody who's chronically sick
doesn't have a lot of money
I want free wherever we can because it's
the mission to get people better I could
put a paywall in up front of everything
I do
everything
and you can get real creative with
paywalls and subscriptions and all that
real creative
how we can do merch merchandise and
creative pay walls left and right
and no one will have access to the
medical meme information unless they pay
whether they like me or not we won't do
that nope in fact
what you'll notice on my YouTubes
there's no commercials and advertisers
before you watch a YouTube what you'll
notice in front of my podcast at Apple
podcast
you'll notice there's no commercials and
advertisers in front of my podcasts
so even with all that said and done
we're the only podcast at the level that
we are because it's a number one podcast
there's no advertisers and commercials
in front of it
and it's very special
I pay out of pocket to do my podcast
I pay out of my pocket to do everything
that's the mission and the books costs a
lot of money to print and ship around
the world so people have access to them
and so that's why there is a fee for the
book unless you want to go to the
library and get it for free
and someone said hey why don't you just
put a PDF on your website well then
someone in a bookstore is not going to
be able to see that PDF and somebody
who's in the library is not going to be
able to see it as someone who's looking
for the books not going to be able to
see it the books are shipped around the
world
and they're in almost they're gonna be
in all the countries in the world
medical mean books are in almost every
country in the world now
around the planet just giving you guys
the mission and a little bit about it
it's about helping many more people and
many more people
and just when you don't have to rely on
the internet too because the internet
could go bye-bye
for everybody
that's how the world works
so and then you got this and you can
protect yourself and heal
you guys this has been incredible this
has been day nine we did the nerve
shifter tomorrow's day 10. get ready
tomorrow's the last day of the medical
medium brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge
tomorrow is it and that's it we
completed 10 days I hope you guys also
do it past those 10 days you never know
you guys might they're incredible tools
for healing
but I'm excited tomorrow is the dream
shifter are you ready for the train
shifter what kind of dreams are you
having let's do a robot what kind of
dreams are you guys having
did you do the dream shifter yet have
you tried it the dream shifter is gonna
blow your mind tomorrow I'm gonna do
three of them tomorrow it's gonna be
incredible
Melvin says love the books
love you too
the dream chip shirt
kind of dreams are you gonna have when
you guys did the dream shifter you guys
want to find answers in your dreams
do you want a soul search through your
dreams will the dream shifter Spirit of
compassion told me creates that and
that's tomorrow it's day 10 it's gonna
be mind-blowing you won't be
disappointed okay
it's gonna be amazing
when you do that dream shifter this dirt
shifter's making me feel so good ah it's
incredible tomorrow's dream shifter
the nerve shift just got me going
it's incredible
[Music]
amazing you guys incredible love you
guys you love the dream shifter Erica
amazing
all right guys I'll see you tomorrow
can't wait
signing off
bartender give me another