we're live right now live on facebook
live on youtube live on tick tock
live on clubhouse as well making nori
rolls cauliflower
nori rolls it's a raw dish i'm making so
i'm not going to cook the cauliflower
it's a great raw dish we're talking
about what causes illness what causes
sickness why is someone sick why is
everybody sick and we're going to talk
about the difference between
the not so sick and the so sick there's
a big difference right there
the not so sick can afford to play
around
and dive into all the different trends
that don't really work
they might feel a little bit better they
get rid of processed foods
they might go vegan they might go clean
animal protein
and they think they got it all down
they're not so sick they get some
improvements and then they go on that
merry-go-round out there with so many
different talking heads in the industry
and they can pick and choose
what talking had to listen to oh this
person looks like they know something
this person looks like they know
something
this person looks like a health expert
look at that this person looks like a
health expert and they're allowed to
play in that land and not so sick
especially if they're not sick they can
play in that land and play in that land
they want to lose a couple pounds
do some more exercising the minute you
cross the threshold though
into getting sick is a whole new game
it's a whole nother game and that
happens out there good to see you guys
coming on
we're making um cauliflower nori rolls
which is really fun
we're live on youtube live on facebook
live on tick tock live and club house
and so we're get we're getting ready
here we're going to make some food good
to see you guys coming on
incredible hey everybody on tick tock
great to see you guys
same on facebook youtube glad you guys
here on clubhouse as well
great stuff to talk about today
important information
and um i think i think it'd be fun i
think today will be a little fun too
so good to see you guys come on uh chris
you're here today
you seem fine to me you know the handle
is really cool your handle because it's
like
chris you're fine when you probably got
sick right is that what you heard chris
you're fine
you know you're okay you look great
chris you look great nothing wrong with
you
nothing happened in there you seem fine
to me right
nothing going on there and it happens to
so
many people so many people out there you
know who get
sick you know you seem good to me you
seem fine to me
like you you look okay like what do you
mean like what do you mean you got the
tingles and the numbness and you don't
feel good
and you got different things happening
like what do you
you know what do you mean so that
happens to a lot of different people out
there and
i totally get it it's that kind of
hidden illness the hidden illnesses
right where it's hidden and you can't
see it
it's not like you have a limp or
something or you're walking with a cane
or something or you know it's instead
it's like here you go you're you're
living
you're living your life a little bit
they don't know how much you aren't
living your life because you're sick and
you have all these different symptoms
but when someone sees you a family
member or a friend
they're like you should you seem okay
you know that hidden illness
the mystery to it all right and and the
struggle with it
um i'm gonna start making some stuff now
okay you guys i got the food processor
right here
let's see what else we got going on so i
like nori rolls
i make a lot of nori rolls uh so that's
what i do
i do it it's so easy you can put so many
different things in here here's fresh
cilantro i'll give you guys the rundown
right here just some beautiful fresh
cilantro right here
the leafy green that's what it is the
leafy green
how much cilantro are you guys eating
every day because
right there you can eat this much of it
every day you can make it your salad
and how healing is that how healing is
that that's a really powerful healing
tool
that alone i got some green onions i
don't know how you guys feel like
about green onions throw that one in the
air a little bit
right but the green onions i got going
on i got dolls right here look at that
atlantic coast dulce in my hands that's
medicinal all on its own
that's a great one we got some beautiful
tomatoes right here too
i could see we're totally being shadowed
today i heard that too
i heard that too michelle totally
michelle l
totally shadowed lately right and got
some beautiful cauliflower
and um got some oranges
two lemons we'll do stuff with that got
some hot peppers
got two nice hot peppers here these are
sweet and hot put together
these are all different medicinal
foods the dulce is a medicinal food
the dolce takes toxic heavy metals out
of the intestinal tract
really easily so that's some medicinal
food
onions are anti viral anti pathogen
antibacterial
so what the onions are cilantro helps to
get rid of metals too
but it's also a highly mineralized
alkalizing green
so this is really really good lucy cone
good to see you
and we got tomatoes anytime you see them
this is a prime example of what we're
talking about today
you go on the search you're looking for
help you're looking for answers
you're maybe you're not so sick maybe
you're really sick
maybe you got a lot of different
conditions diagnosed with like a few
different conditions you got
neurological lyme you've got the lupus
you may be diagnosed with fibro
hashimoto's thyroiditis
maybe you're diagnosed with all eczema
really bad and then you hear don't eat a
tomato because somebody in the health
movement who seems
prominent somebody in the health
movement who seems like they know what
they're talking about even though they
just started in the health movement
pretty recently
like just just like five years into it
that's all or six years into it
they decided to just get into it and
they're a doctor or something
and they tell you don't eat tomatoes
tomatoes are really bad for you they can
they're so bad for you they're
problematic that's a mistake all on its
own
and then you get other people in the
health movement too
that say hey night shades they're really
bad for you the calls
cause problems they'll cause problems
this is a private example why people
don't heal
and sure if you're not so sick and you
get rid of processed foods and you kick
those out when you get rid of the fried
greasy foods and you start exercising
and you start juicing something or doing
some green powdered shakes somewhere and
you're
you're in you know you're seeing
improvements you're doing the keto thing
or maybe you go plant-based keto
and you're picking up a notch you're
like hey oh wait i got it i got it all
sewed up now
but if you really get sick it doesn't
work that way you'll find that keto it
doesn't work you'll find that even
plant-based vegan doesn't work you'll
find that all these things don't really
work
and then start stuff starts happening
your teeth start falling apart over time
the weight comes back on and you're out
there listening well listen to people
it's like don't ever eat a tomato people
in the health movement like don't eat a
tomato don't eat a tomato
this isn't this is one prime example of
the misinformation that's out there that
stops people from healing and
here's the most important part if i can
get your ear right now you guys
okay the most important part tell me if
i'm wrong
you guys tell me if i'm wrong about this
i can handle it
i can take it so you can tell me okay
you can be like you're wrong aw
you're wrong and check this out
okay so you get told not to eat the
tomatoes
you get told not to eat a potato the
nightshades
you get told not to do this or that or
stay away from fruit with all the fruit
fear
but you're being told by people that
don't even know why anybody's sick
they don't know why someone's sick with
mystery neurological symptoms
neurological fatigue
that's a term for medical medium that's
medical meme information that's got out
there neurological fatigue
that means that medical medium
information discovered that fatigue was
actually
neuro neurological and then we put that
information out there and published it
and everything
and but think about it
here we're taking all this guidance from
all the gurus and all the people in the
health movement and all the special
doctors and all the people right lorena
good to see you
we're taking all this guidance
but yet they don't know why someone's
sick with lupus they don't know why
somebody's stick with fibromyalgia
hashimoto's they don't know why you have
nodules on your thyroid you guys
they don't know why you're dizzy and you
got balance problems and vertigo they
don't know why you got ringing in the
ears
nancy miller i was told for years to
avoid tomatoes
until i really started to learn from you
i have completely changed my diet
and feel amazing and love tomatoes
love tomatoes so this great comment
thank you for um
talking about that but so
we got so-called experts out there
shannon
says thank you for getting me over my
nightshade
fear been enjoying many yummy steamed
potatoes
but what happens is we get told you guys
we get told that we should avoid certain
things
and that's what we're told but we're
told by people that don't know why we're
sick
they don't know anything about
epstein-barr unless they learned it from
medical medium
they don't know why any they don't know
anything about viruses unless they
learned it about they learned viruses
from the
plague that's been happening in the last
year year and a half
a year and whatever a few months so they
they now they know the term virus
patina says nightshades don't agree with
all of us i break out in eczema but
that's only with
um auburn's always been that
way since a child even though it was
homegrown
so the thing is with nightshades fatima
is what i've seen
is people don't use them right right
they don't use them really use them
right so
what to do is they'll have tomato sauce
filled with all this other bad stuff and
that's aggravating on
eczema psoriasis because there's all
this fat in the tomato sauce that's one
thing right there that's a mistake made
they'll take potatoes and they have
butter in their potatoes no one eats a
plain potato unless it's medical medium
unless it's medical medium information
nobody eats a plain potato
nobody eats a steamed potato nobody even
steams them
if people steam them now it's medical
medium information
very few people i've ever met in the
world out of the hundreds of thousands
i've talked to over the last 35 years
very few people ever just steamed a
potato
very few people and so what they do
though is they stick things in potato
and on potato that feed
bugs and then the person gets a problem
and then they think the potato caused it
but the potato didn't cause it
same thing with tomatoes they'll have
chicken parmesan
with cheese right mozzarella cheese
sauce they'll have and the sauce
the tomato they'll think to tomatoes
aggravating them when it's not it's all
the fat from the chicken
all the oil thrown in the sauce and then
it's of course the cheese feeding any
kind of viruses
and things like that so that's important
to know
if you take a fresh ripe tomato if
you're somebody with eczema
psoriasis you take a fresh ripe tomato
and you cut a piece off and you eat it
nothing's going to happen to your eczema
nothing's going to happen to your
psoriasis
but nobody eats a tomato by itself
and another thing too is i'll take it
down a little further when it comes down
to peppers
if you eat your pepper green it's not
ripe that's like eating a green banana
it's not ripe it's not gonna agree with
you something that's
so not ripe won't agree with someone
because it's not supposed to be
you're not supposed to be eating a green
bell pepper or green pepper
those are not ripe at all you're not
supposed to be eating a green
banana you're not supposed to be eating
apple off a tree
early in the season when it's hard as a
rock it's not even ripened
it's not going to agree with you you're
not supposed to eat a berry
that's red when it's supposed to be
black
or a berry that's green when it's
supposed to be blue
if you eat the unripe stuff
you're it's not going to agree with you
and here's something that happens with
tomatoes people eat them not ripe enough
it's not going to agree with someone
tomato sauces are made with
unripe tomatoes sometimes green tomatoes
are in tomato sauces
and so all these mistakes are made i'm
just going to say this
you guys in the medical meme community
community have heard me say this before
details matter or you're just
lost and then you're gonna tell someone
oh nightshades didn't work for me so
stay away from it and you're gonna then
compile that fear
and you're gonna validate the
misinformation that other health
practitioners put out there every single
day you're going to validate
their misinformation and then a whole
bunch of other people aren't going to
heal
because they're not going to know that
there's foods that you can eat that are
critical like antiviral foods
in the nightshade family so the potato
really important antiviral food for
instance critical for colitis and
crohn's and
tomato tomatoes are antiviral too but
you're not going to know
to eat an antiviral tomato anymore and
you're not going to note eat
an antiviral potato anymore and you're
just going to get lost
and you're going to get lost because the
misinformation is so rampant and the
misinformation is so off
so we got to keep that in mind how it
works
i love it when there's so many geniuses
out there
when you guys i don't know if you know
this
but up until outside of my
private my private work that i've done
all these years where people there was
we had a waiting list
over a million people around the world
trying to get to talk to me
i started in the 80s doing it
i started when i was a kid doing the
readings and working with people who are
sick doctors were sending patients to me
all through the 1990s just droves of
patients coming to me through the 1990s
through the 2000s
and because i was known as the bizarre
symptoms guy
that's what i was known as i was known
as the bizarre symptoms guy because
nobody
knew when they were sick with all their
fatigue and their aches and pains and
all the strange symptoms nobody knew
what caused any of it
so i had to teach individual doctors all
through these years
i had to teach individual doctors about
being low-fat
you know and it bit me on the butt a
little bit it bit me on the butt to give
out all that info
and not book it put it in the book
earlier on in the early 90s right
so i gave out a lot of medical medium
pieces
and those pieces really needed to find
their home so you can get the whole
puzzle and know all the details right
details matter to heal
when you're really sick but
what i've learned is until medical
medium information taught everybody why
somebody has the tingle or the numbness
or the burning mouth and burning pain in
the burning jaw the pain in the neck
that's mysterious
the sciatic problems when you don't have
a back injury
when all that information when all that
information got out there we finally
knew
and when the medical medium books were
published right
so this one right here in 2015 right the
medical medium new edition
that's that's the revised and expanded
version you guys got to get that if you
get a chance revise and expand it the
new edition
and it's on sale at amazon.com us right
you can get it free of the lever if you
want to
i heard there's a long waiting list i
wish i could do something about that
at the libraries but the thing is is
that this book right here blew
the doors off of lyme disease so people
can heal
fibro chronic fatigue syndrome
hashimoto's
that's just some of the things right
there right the candida
problems out there in the world and it
blew the roof off of all that
and then then well right around that
time
2015 all these newbie professionals got
into
health and wellness certain doctors that
had a lot of money
got a lot of advertising pr marketing
put out a book saying hey don't eat
tomatoes
or put out this and that they never even
knew to begin with why anybody was sick
ever ever ever and the millions of women
that have struggled and suffered and
been into doctor's offices with mystery
conditions and symptoms that were just
given steroids and antibiotics
until medical medium came out with the
answers nobody knew anything about this
this is just fact it's a published fact
it's just fact
so what i see now is hey
go do corella that's what you should be
doing as krill oh that's funny because
you don't even know how cruella works
and you don't even know why anybody's
sick to begin with you should do butter
in your coffee oh that's funny because
you don't know why anybody's sick to
begin with
hey you should do you know fish oil oh
that's another funny one too because you
don't know why anybody's sick to begin
with and
you know tomatoes are bad for you if you
have gout
that's funny you don't even know the
cause of gallon
until medical medium information
so it's not tomatoes it's whatever
tomatoes are swimming in
oil and fat and grease karen says so
true
i used to think that spaghetti sauce
gave me problems
because of the tomatoes wrong it's all
the other stuff in the sauce
i eat tomatoes now daily with medical
medium 369.
there's no dairy there's no gluten in
there you're eating
the tomatoes daily how come how come
medical medium information
has to be that window into sanity
like i wake up every morning and i'm
like i i can't even believe it
how come with all the smart people and
highly intelligent people and so smart
health professionals and doctors and all
the different
stuff out there and everybody thinks
they're a genius or they're or
everybody's portrayed as a genius right
but any but no one knows anything in the
health movement
yeah sure you can get a hip replacement
but look what happened there with the
hip replacements too
they all got metal on metal and i
remember those days i remember people
filing into my office right they had a
hip replacement
they were sick as goats they come into
my office
and spirit of compassion would be like
this person's hip replacement is eaten
up they have to get to the doctor they
have to cut them open
look in there and see that the the
joint in that hip is rubbing and
grinding into metal
right but those are nuts and bolts
replacement parts chronic ill which
became chron which is
a mystery to people when they don't know
what's causing in the moment but
chronic illness is way more pets way
past that
but it's one thing if medical medium
information knows a lot about chronic
illness
which is the mysteries to it all and
teaching it out there but it's another
if i have to correct the little stuff
the little stuff like the mistakes made
about fresh tomatoes the mistakes made
about
simple things simple things
that's when it's just all ridiculous i
remember 10 years ago like i'm gonna i'm
gonna make
sure that you know i was talking spirit
compassion i'm gonna make sure i fix
this
nightshade problem because it they got
it all wrong out there
just give me a decade and i'll have that
fixed just give me a decade and then
every single year some other new
comes out
some kind of practitioner or some doctor
that writes a book or somebody that gets
on some you know
some show because they're pr marketing
people they hire puts them on some show
some when they start talking bad about
nightshades
here we go again another 200 000 people
see it
another 50 000 people see it how do you
help people you guys how do you actually
save them
how do you save them from the
misinformation that's out there it's one
thing
i can tell you what's wrong with you
right the information
i can't protect you from what's out
there though
all you have to do is just boom see
pop-ups come up everywhere
ads everywhere for all kinds of what
seems like geniuses and they're just
going to be trying to sell you all your
stuff
right there she near good to see
you
and so when it comes down to it all
it's really sad it just is
let's make a little food we got lots to
talk about glad you guys are here
um okay so let's do that i got nori
sheets by the way
check this out right got a whole thing
of nori sheets
so that's what i'm doing there right
let's grind up some cauliflower
let's do that i'm gonna cut this
cauliflower in half right here
you guys following me we're making nori
rolls what i like about knowing rolls
it's easy
it's it's fun unless you guys think it's
not fun and i got
got respect for you it's if you don't
think it's fun of course of course it
may not be fun for somebody
i like doing it i like it a lot
some grinding up some cauliflower and
put a little bit more in here too
amy so i'm allergic to celery well
what happens when you have celery
right what happens when you have celery
did you go to your doctor because your
throat's closing up did you go to the
emergency room
is that why so you ate a piece of celery
your throat closed up
no right no so you went to your doctor
and they just threw that on the test
um food allergy tests the ones where
they tell you you're allergic to 10
15 20 things but yet you can eat those
things and not have a problem
uh those things i've always seen as
corrupt
for sure i mean listen to your doctor
dude he tells you he tells you to stay
off celery you stay off celery
but if it was me i i you know i
i would just am i am i choking when i
have a celery stick all of a sudden my
throat closes up and i can't breathe and
i'm having anaphylactic shock
if that's happening then yeah stay away
from celery
stay away from celery
but when it comes down to tests for food
allergies and the all-cat test and
everything else around it all i've never
seen things so skewed
i have a doctor actually calling me any
minute too
because he's he's gonna he's a doctor
that does all the tests and
he did he pulled some blood work and i
asked for all the food allergy tests so
i got a doctor coming in right now
calling and
but i still want to make this stuff here
so hopefully it doesn't interrupt us too
much
i think what happens is when you're
doing the food allergy test it's easy to
get thrown
really easy to be thrown on that
and i think that here he is
hey dr blott so hey how did my blood
work go
by the way i was i was really bummed out
that the phlebotomist
took took 27 vials of blood from me i
was so sick
i was sick for days and days
oh my god yeah remember i called your
office and i told you how sick i was and
you guys said i wasn't sick from the
blood draw
27 vials was fine no i don't think it
was fine it was actually disastrous
because i was
anyway what is my food allergy test what
have they come back
all my food allergies okay i'm allergic
to what
i'm allergic to cumin
okay what else cabbage
okay allergic cabbage didn't know that
tomatoes oh bummer i love tomatoes
i'm allergic to tomatoes potatoes
is this a nightshade thing peppers some
allergies to peppers tomatoes and
potatoes okay what else am i allergic to
i'm allergic to cilantro oh really
i never had a problem eating cilantro
but
okay all right well what else i'm
allergic to gluten
okay good good that's on the test oh
good phew i'm allergic to gluten phew
that's good okay what what else am i
allergic to
ragweed all right but i don't know
i don't know anything about the rag
fireweed
okay okay i don't eat fireweed but it's
on the test okay
parsley really parsley oh my god
carrots i'm allergic to carrots
well what else i'm allergic to
buffalo i don't eat buffalo
i don't eat buffalo i'm allergic to what
what else
uh venison oh bummer i was gonna
have i was just about to kill my friend
right here oh
hey buddy i was just about to kill my
friend
yeah yeah how you doing
yeah how are you doing yeah i was about
to kill him tonight to see if we can
take his guts out and then we can hang
him upside down by his hoofs
it's yeah it's a deer and then i was
gonna
have some venice steaks venison sticks
some allergic to venison oh wait
oh i am okay well looks like you're off
the hook what else am i allergic to
i'm allergic to capers okay
you know what a friend of mine had this
allergy test too
uh from another doctor and my friend was
allergic to a whole bunch of things too
yeah and they threw in celery uh-huh
yeah anyway all right thanks dr blott
all right guys i'm gonna gotta keep on i
gotta keep moving make a little food
here's how it works when you're allergic
to gluten whether a test shows it or not
the gluten feeds bugs nobody knew
that medical medium information is the
first to tell everybody
that the reason why anybody sensitive to
gluten on
any level is because it feeds pathogens
it feeds pathogens 35 years ago
i was telling everybody stay off of
wheat stay off the wheat stay off of
wheat stay off of wheat just constantly
stay off a wheat wheat
wheat stay off a week everybody looked
at me like i just came off of the
spaceship
i had 10 heads because it was the most
craziest bizarre thing anybody's ever
heard is stay off a wheat so they would
all go wait a minute whole wheat
whole wheat whole wheat is good for you
right did you guys know the health
movement
believe that whole wheat was incredible
for you
the health movement it was processed
bread people here's you guys got to keep
in mind
the only thing that the health movement
was worried about
30 years ago the only thing
with bread was that it was stripped of
nutrients
not that it did any harm it was just
void of nutrients this is really
important information right here that's
the only thing
the health movement thought about with
bread
they didn't they didn't know anything
about all these different things with
gluten or anything they just knew
that bread was processed so that that
white bread that was squishy was bad for
you because it was void of nutrients
that's the only thing the health
movement knew about it
and then me came along and i said it's
the wheat it's the wheat it's the wheat
it's the gluten it's the wheat it's the
gluten it's the wheat and they'd be like
no no it's not
wheat because we're doing nutrition and
nutritional wheat
we're doing the whole grain wheat whole
grain wheat berries whole grain wheat
fiber bread
whole grain wheat germ you guys
the health movement believed in wheat
germ lorraine elle says this is true
they ran out and the whole movement
believed in wheat germ it didn't matter
if you were plant-based didn't matter if
you were vegetarian
didn't matter if you were the cleanest
eater the animal protein eater you can
find
the entire movement believed wheat germ
was good for you
i'm the one that was screaming top the
top of the mountain tops
that the gluten and the weed is all bad
it's all bad
then everybody hated me for it but took
years of that work for us to get to this
point now
but here's the funny thing even with all
that i've done
they still don't know why gluten even
does anything
it feeds the bugs i've been saying this
and what you're going to get out of me
is consistency going all the way back
from childhood it's always going to be
consistency it's not going to be
non-contradictive and everything that's
medical medium
is never proven wrong it only eventually
gets proven right
but it never gets proven wrong it's got
the track record
medical medium information has never
been proved wrong once you guys
never ever been proved wrong once by any
doctor by any
by any institution by any sciences
institution by anywhere it's only been
proven right
and a little bit at a time it's proven
right
gluten feeds the bugs that are inside of
us
so the bugs eat it that's the only
reason
why wheat gluten or gluten is bad for
you
or problematic because
narashini and throw info from above
exactly since i was a child has been
saying the same thing since i was
a child all of it it's consistency
not like the podcast doctors that say
tomatoes are bad you should see what
they were saying five years ago
or two years ago or last year or three
months ago
they change but nobody holds them
accountable for it's like no one's awake
watching them or listening to them
because i think
too they're circulating all these new
people from all their ads
so it's almost like a fresh start every
10 seconds they screw up and they get a
fresh start
because they got a million dollars a
month going into ads did you know that
do you know that all these guys have a
million dollars a month going into ads
to sell all their garbage and everything
and to get new people on board to hear
about tomato being bad
they get a million dollars a month going
into ads
it's it's incredible you guys you
wouldn't even believe it
you wouldn't even believe it there's a
difference between anaphylaxis
shock hives
there's a difference between that and
what happens when
you're getting real food allergies in a
different way so there's two kinds of
food allergies the food allergy
if you get anaphylactic shock that means
whatever that was like peanut butter
was in something when it was injected
into you from the outside of the body
okay this is why i tell people do not
get b12 shots
do not get b12 shots do not get b12
shots i say this all the time do not get
b12 shots
you will eventually get anaphylaxis
shock
from your b12 if you've had too many b12
shots as the years go by
your body will build an antibody to the
b12 because it's entering on the outside
of the body which is through your skin
on the outside of the body not
intravenously in your vein but on the
outside of your body
and eventually because of that your
immune system is just gonna be like
that's an
enemy that's an enemy because it's
coming in the wrong way it's not coming
in through the mouth orally and we're
going to build an antibody to it and
when that's going to then that's going
to depend on how someone's going to
react to it eventually
so that's how things work it's like a
bee sting
you get stung by a bee the reason why
the pain is there
reason why the pain is so bad when
you're stung by a bee is because
your body your body is like sending an
army to that spot and then it swells up
it swells up because you're not supposed
to enter things
and that's that's the skin at least so
there's a different alarm bells for that
but when it goes into a needle and
passes everything and goes into the
muscle past the derm and now it's a
whole nother game
yeah and so people can have people can
have
anaphylactic shock with the b stick but
bee sting
similar to that because it's coming from
the outside a lot of people their body
doesn't like that
so i tell people it's like with the b12
shots
really important antibiotic shots as
well i tell doctors all the time
do if you're gonna if you're gonna
prescribe i tell doctors all the time
if you're gonna prescribe an antibiotic
to your patients
prescribe it orally don't
do a needle i'm not talking about
intravenous i'm talking about a needle
into the arm
into the butt the butt muscle
glorio the you know into the glute i'm
not talking about
that way right i'm not i'm talking about
that way not into the
intravenously so what happens is when
because
antibiotics when they're driven into you
like that by a needle your body's gonna
they eventually build some type of
antibody towards an antibiotic and now
you're not gonna be able to handle
penicillin you're gonna be allergic to
penicillin
a lot of reasons why people are allergic
to penicillin is because penicillin was
injected
through a needle through their arm or
through a needle on their behind and
that's why they become allergic to
penicillin
yeah all these things matter if you're
allergic to shellfish that means somehow
shellfish entered into your body the
wrong
way or a component or a
compound of shellfish entered into your
body the wrong way
somewhere along the line there's there's
there's
there's reasons why we have that
anaphylaxis shock or that serious
serious hive issue or hives
too part of it is because their liver is
all sluggish and stagnant everybody's
liver is sluggish and stagnant and just
completely congested with all this
garbage and junk
just filled with tons of stuff filled
with all kinds of things
and that's where the hive part comes
into play the hives
the hives come into play because the
liver is so stagnant and sluggish and so
gunked up and when it's that gunked up
and that's sluggish and not stagnant
then we get in trouble we get in trouble
that means all you have to do is start
exercising a little bit and boom that
blood rushing through that liver is
going to bring out all that gunk and now
you're going to be
hived up every other day
you can get hives easily just just
eating anything because you eat
something too
that's flushing the liver a little bit
you get hives that way too
the hives are really a difficult one
sometimes easy to fix once you clean up
your liver and you get past them for a
while it's easy to fix
medical medium style for sure
constance you caught the live let's
grind up some cauliflower
right here let's do this guys so i'm
making cauliflower and nori's
making cauliflower rice so on tick tock
you guys i know you can't see this right
now but making cauliflower rice i got
the
got it over here now you don't want to
turn it into
you don't want to make your rice into
something smaller than rice you know
i like i like the food processor here we
go you guys see this on tick tock
clubhouse i'm making cauliflower rice
right now
i'm gonna get a spoon you guys don't
mind
just get a tablespoon
let's do a couple things first is i'm
going to cut my scallions in half these
are real fat scallions
raquel s i'd love to see anthony
dealing with an actual emergency like a
doctor can
that's a funny one to me i'm scratching
my head on that
because i had a 24-hour hotline for
years
what were you doing when i wasn't
sleeping for all those years
you know i mean i'm i'm sure that's like
that's you know a compliment in your
and you're being nice about it and
that's not that's not a insult or
anything but check this out right
does this help though with that a little
bit i had a 24
hour hotline hardly slept a wink
you know what my emergency hotline was
for it was for doctors and their
patients
so i had doctors waking me up all night
long for years
and years with emergencies with their
patients
and that's what my life was like and my
life
isn't much better than that now it's
just a little better where i do sleep
more
because you know i'm not i i don't sleep
as much because i'm working 20 hours a
day now
before i was working you know 15 18
hours a day
and then up throughout the night with
calls all the time
so i had the 24-hour hotline for years
years you know the beepers do you guys
know little beepers
the beavers you'd have on right the
beavers you'd have on
they beep yeah i had one of those by my
bed
right by my head right there and doctors
all had the number
every single night and i still get
people calling me with emergencies all
the time
all the time i do and i still help out
some people i still i
do still help out some people some of
the most powerful people in the world
because what what the only reason why i
do that people say well why would you
help
some of the most powerful people in the
world why would you do that
like what would that matter it's because
it's a way to also reach more people
reach more people so we can heal the
world
it's critical that there's some
something like that
you know out there i don't i don't have
pr
and marketing i don't i'm not like the
podcast doctors they spend 500 000 a
month a million dollars a month
so people can listen to podcasts and buy
their products i don't have that going
on
so none of that happens here so that's
critical to know
and so you know my reach even though
millions of books have gotten out there
thank god because of the publisher
in the world and have been the number
one health
author for six years running even with
all that
still i don't hire all the pr and
marketing and all that stuff
to do the reach so i do help out some of
the most powerful people in the world
though
because i've been helping them out for
30 years
um yes does yes does help doctors
i met a doctor who consulted with aw and
this is totally true
in case you're here to doubt and be an
ass
angela thanks i appreciate it
and so yeah so how does aw handle
emergencies
well give you kind of a window what the
hotline used to be
okay let me go back a little earlier
real
real quick too which is important if you
guys want a window okay
let's go back to 19 to say any of 1993
i'd say
there's a knock on my door it's two
o'clock in the morning
and a mom is holding a baby with a fever
of 105.
how about that happened on a regular
basis
so how does aw handle emergencies okay
the hotline rings
and beeps and someone's in the hospital
and the doctors don't know if they're
about to do an appendicitis for
you know if they're the appendix removal
because of an appendicitis issue
right or it's severe food poisoning and
i have to talk to the doctor to give the
decision to the doctors the doctor can
make a decision for the surgeon
how about that for emergencies and it's
a four-year-old
all the time this happened all the time
i worked with doctors all the time and
that happened so how does
aw do it
okay so we're looking good here
so what i'm going to do is i think i'm
going to go with
some lime in these so i don't know how
you guys feel but these normals
i'm gonna go with some lime so what i do
is i wet
the sheet like this
with a little bit of lime juice right
and now i'm going to put some
cauliflower rice in here look at that
this is a raw cauliflower rice it's it's
a raw meal
it's light it's delicious now i don't
want to put
too much i just put too much rice in
there
right so this one's gonna be a fat one
and i don't i don't like sometimes when
the rolls are that fat
i cut some scallions up so that they're
not too crazy i'm gonna put one across
here one across here what do you guys
think
how's this look right i love these green
scallions these green onions i love them
when they're like this
let's do this now let's get a little bit
of dulce in here now the dulce isn't
moist
so what i'm gonna do is i'm gonna run a
little bit of water in here
like this a little touch of water and
i'm gonna moisten
the dolls okay
not get it too wet not get it too crazy
wet
so that's a goal i love when i have wild
foods
in my in my dish whenever you have a
wild food in here it's like hey
that's a big deal remember that
okay so let's get a little dulce in here
you don't need a lot
just a little bit that that might be
probably a lot for somebody
i'm gonna be like whoa that's a lot of
dull boy does it taste good let's cut a
tomato
okay just so you know the medical medium
book one new edition is 17.39
it's 51 off i think it's something like
that 53
off actually 53 off it's a new edition
it's a medical textbook
it's already saved countless lives
around the world fact
it's known to it's an incredible book
and it's packed with information you
guys should take advantage of the sale
or get a free the library
amazon controls the prices not me
so let's put a little tomato
in here so i'm slicing up some tomato
right here
okay should i be afraid of this tomato
so what you guys so some of you guys are
telling me i should be afraid of it
don't be afraid of a tomato
there's pandemic information in this
book by the way
pandemic information in this book it's
mind-blowing
and it's the original information it was
taken originally it's published here
first but was taken here and used
recently
by a couple different doctors so they
took it from medical medium didn't cite
back medical medium and they're
using my pandemic information that was
published first isn't that incredible
though when you think about that
what do you think about that you know
discrimination
there's a lot of doctors that do cite me
all the time and there's doctors that
use the medical mean books in their
practices
but when you don't cite me it's just
it's just spiritual discrimination it's
also
greed because you're so hungry for new
thought and new ideas
so hungry that you think you can rob and
steal
and then you know because you get this
just they're so hungry for
new stuff so just take it from the mm
and don't
cite them it's just like who does who
would do that right
talk about integrity let's put a little
bit of cilantro in here
check this out you guys cilantro's a
leafy green
it's an herb but use it as a leafy green
okay now i'm going to add a little spice
to this the spice isn't raw
it's it's obviously not it's spice right
so what's the name of the celery juicer
again i saw in tik tok
it's the mm 900 hds
that's the one that rocks that's the one
that squeeze out every last bit of juice
that's the machine is just awesome it
pays for itself just love it you see how
dry the pulp comes out it's it's
incredible
there's ones that look like it but it's
got to be the mm-900 hds
the celery juicer machine if you see bad
reviews
on mine but nobody else is it's troll
attacks that's all i get
all day long it's just trolls attack
trolls attack trolls attack
um yeah so anyway put a little spare
a little bit severely in a little bit of
paprika i don't know
paprika is good
yeah yeah i caught that i caught that a
little bit of
cumin powder right i'm tapping it
lightly because i don't want a ton of it
on here
so i'm giving you like a light tap right
okay a little bit of garlic powder in
here too
you're welcome on tick tock a little
garlic powder
everyone is saying it's awesome right
you know everybody's saying it's awesome
the juicer is incredible
the juicer's incredible
i just love it love it
really do really do so i put some
paprika on there a little bit of garlic
powder
i got some chili powder too but you know
i'm gonna hold that one back
because i'm gonna make a quick sauce and
the sauce is gonna have
these hot peppers in there some garlic
in there too
bear with me guys i'm gonna roll this up
if you guys are okay about this
so if you're not so sick you can play
around
in frog land you can play around in frog
land
there's a ton of frauds out there tons
of them you can play in that land all
day long you can do your fish oil and
your
charcoal and you can do your you know
oil pulling and waste 20 minutes every
single day doing your oil pulling
which encapsulates the bacteria in your
teeth and gums which is disastrous you
can
play around in fraud land do your
kombucha tea which turns your blood into
acid
fraud land you can play around with
fraud land all you want if you're not so
sick
you'll probably improve because you'll
actually be cleaning up stuff not eating
junk food anymore
not eating fast food anymore you can be
putting your cacao in your shakes
fraud land again drug dealers want you
to put cacao in your shakes
like you can play if you're not so sick
or not sick you get sick
you gotta learn the details matter you
gotta learn
you gotta learn all right that's a
beautiful nori roll right there let me
put it put it aside for now
let's make another one let's do it again
so i'm gonna put instead of lime
as the juicing this up i'm gonna put a
little bit of tomato
juice on here from the fresh tomato
check that out
let's get some more cauliflower let's
make another one
don't use too much cauliflower rice you
don't need to use that much rice because
we're putting a lot of other stuff in
here keep that in mind
real sushi
everybody thinks they they're so proud
of themselves when they do the sushi out
there right
so everybody thinks they're so so proud
of themselves i see it all the time
so when you do your real sushi you got
your
tuna right it's your rice your tuna
you got all of that there you got your
wasabi
got your pickled ginger so you got your
little plate you got your sushi plate
right
so people are taught right now to think
that's eating healthy
and you'll see people out there like i
had sushi i eat sushi three times a week
that's really healthy
but sushi's not healthy so what happens
is with sushi
is you get all that mercury you got that
and you got all that vinegar and you got
all that bad sugar and you got all the
dioxins
so when you put that all together this
is not a health food this is disastrous
but when you're not so sick you can play
in sushi land i guess all you want until
you get food poisoning
eating you know your sushi one day and
you're barfing for three days
and you're just sick but what happens is
the people don't realize it but here's
another mistake it's like sushi so but
people are taught that it must be
healthy it's a healthy
alternative you know and here's what's a
funny thing hey i don't get
i hear this all the time i don't get the
traditional sushi at the sushi bar
i get the vegan vegetarian sushi they
don't use any fish
in there they put avocado in there they
put all this
cool stuff they put watercress in there
it's all vinegar
it's all vinegar just turning your blood
into acid
that's what it is it's all vinegar
so i just put some rice in here
cauliflower rice this is great
let's cut another scallion because these
are so fat
these are really big scallions they're
thick so i'm going to flip it like this
one on that side right here one on this
side check that out you guys
okay all right let's put a little bit
more adults in here
look at that
isn't that great little dolls right
across the
the back of that this is fun today
but you can play in the fraud land is
what i call it
it's what i call it you can be doing
your fish oil your corella you can do
your diatomaceous earth particles which
should just kill you
stuff is so bad for you all this you can
do your corella i think i said that over
and over again you can do
you can do your colostrum your collagen
which is just
it's fraud land it's all fraudulent
stuff
and there's more more i mean i'm just
naming the few basics
right there's tons of do your protein
powders which has all this msg in it all
this garbage and msg
fraud land again
but you know what keeps all the stuff
around you know why medical medium can't
crush this stuff
he tries but he can't crush it third
person
you know why is because they're putting
millions of dollars of ads out on all
this stuff
over and over and over again and as
people get a little sick
not so sick not so crazy sick they're
just jumping into it
fermented foods are not a health food i
hate to break it
to you guys it's not a health food it
was never a health food it was a
survival food
and if i was if this was 2 000 years ago
when i was in china
you better believe i would take
everything out of my garden
before the before the freeze came
and i would throw it into a big vat a
big
ceramic clay vat shut the lid on it
and let it turn to mush that's what
that's and let it ferment
you know why they did that they had no
refrigeration no freezers they had no
food stuff and they had nobody
no food stores you right when the season
ended
you live or die that's what it was like
everywhere around the world not just
china
everywhere around the world that's what
it was like
but we always say it's ancient it's it's
a health food no it wasn't it was like
live or die
so that's what they did they took all
their fresh food by the end of the year
that they had left and they stuck it in
massive vats because guess what
you would eat that fermented slop all
winter long because it was the only way
to stay alive until spring until you can
get your new crops going
it was a survival mechanism it wasn't a
health food
it was putrified and the bacteria that's
involved with fermented food is
is bacteria that lives on death
did you know that all the bacteria
that's on fermented food isn't the kind
your body normally has or naturally has
it all
did you know the good bacteria inside
our body has nothing to do with any of
that fermented stuff that's not the back
the bacteria in fermented foods bacteria
that comes when something dies
when an animal dies in the woods it gets
engulfed by bacteria
bacteria of death
if you want to ferment a vegetable or
anything ferment anything or ferment
fish or ferment anything
you what happens is it's bacteria that
rides on death
right so when they do hanging meats this
is medical medium info so you know when
they do hanging meats
when they hang meat what is what is the
ham they hang
is the pork they hang right was it
pancetta or is it something else what is
it you guys i can't remember
you hang you hang meat and you age it
the bacteria on that meat got bacteria
that's death but none of this bacteria
that's on death of any kind
bacteria on kimchi is death none of that
bacteria
is naturally inside our bodies ever so
when you eat that fermented food you
think that's camping out
that bacteria doesn't camp out inside of
you that's all bacteria that dies from
your hcl your hcl just kills it fast
because it's
the wrong kind the wrong kind
i know you guys right i'm told every day
why don't you make programs disappear
for a year
show up again make programs sell them
for three thousand dollars a piece the
amount of information you give for free
is endless
endless and no one even has information
to give you like that so
and they're just stealing your
information and charging everybody for
it anyway
all the potty has doctors everybody else
they're all stealing your information
and charging for it
everybody's stealing medical medium
information and charging for it why
don't you do the 3 000
programs you can be rich in no time
you'll be all
everything will be great and people will
wait for it and they'll want to do it
because
they will you'll get just you know
plenty of people
i can't do that to you guys i can't
let's put a little tomato on here
so
derek says derek amber says my
autoimmune doctor told me to get rid of
eggs because i have ebv
do you agree derek
that's medical medium information didn't
he cite me
so he didn't say medical medium that's
medical medium published information
my autoimmune doctor told me to get rid
of eggs because i have ebv do you agree
well look i agree with your doctor's
advice your that's your doctor giving
you advice
so i i can't give you advice like that
because your doctors he's giving he's
your doctor he's giving you advice
right and but i can tell you
that that advice he's giving is medical
medium information
that's what that is it's medical medium
information
and pretty cool but uncool
uncool ask him where he got it he might
not have gotten it for a medical meeting
he might have gotten it from another
doctor that got it for medical mediums
i'm gonna roll this up but first of all
epstein-barr feeds off of eggs there's
no scientific study that shows that
so your doctor's not using science on
any level so your doctor is not using a
scientific study he's not using a study
from the mayo clinic or
study from john hopkins he's not using a
study stolen kettering he's not using a
study from anywhere
he's not the cleveland clinic there's no
study there's no study anywhere he's
using medical media published
information it's only place that comes
from this
and there's no scientific study for it
at all eggs
feed viruses viruses such as
epstein-barr the epstein-barr feeds off
of eggs
that is mm-info
i'm honored you're here by the way
epstein-barr being a problem with any
kind of autoimmune is medical medium
information not just the egg part
so what i suggest is you show the doctor
this book
bring the doctor this book and tell them
where it all stems from
published here first medical medium new
edition
revised expanded it was published in the
original medical medium book
so i would advise you bring the book to
your doctor and you tell them a medium
came out that information and it's not a
scientific study
that's what i would do the other thing
too the other the other thing too
okay is that autoimmune in general
and problems with autoimmune caused by
epstein-barr is medical medium-published
information as well
there's layers of just mm info all in
that wrapped up in there
so we got two nice no re rolls let's
make a sauce
let's do that
you think i would be happy about it but
how's someone get going to get the
complete story and all the details that
matter so they can heal their ebv
when they're only they're only throwing
out tidbits that come from medical
medium
the sighting's critical so you can get
the full story so you can heal
but i guess that doesn't matter if a mom
out there is sick with epstein-barr
doesn't get the full story she's just
debilitatingly sick she's disabled she's
in bed now she can't feed her kids
anymore she loses her job her husband's
doing everything
he's freaking out he's he's just you
know can't handle it anymore
the family's falling apart the little
kids are being wounded forever because
of it
and the doctor doesn't want to give that
mom
where all the information comes from so
she can actually heal her epstein-barr
get her life together instead they'll
give her fragments and then
offer fish oil and some corella and some
other things too
which aren't medical medium and she'll
stay sick and the kids will be miserable
the family would be miserable and that's
where it goes now do you see why
sighting is so important or did i just
did i miss
did i miss something there or is
exciting important
okay let's make a quick sauce i gotta
grab a bowl and that's what i'm gonna do
right now
let's get a bowl right here let's do a
sauce first things first i think i'm
gonna do an orange
right let's squeeze some oranges right
here
so i'm going to squeeze some laundry
with my hand
honored you guys are here today
truly live on facebook live on
youtube live on tick tock it's great
please tell me when where can i find
many
uh meditations at full moon
so georgina go to medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast
it's a medical medium podcast apple
podcast you can you can get the
meditations there there's a moon
meditation at medical meeting podcasted
apple podcast
the link is in the description check it
out you'll find it
so i'm making a sauce i'm going to use
orange what would you
are you guys cool if i use honey are you
all right from honey if you're if you're
into the whole thing where honey's bad
if you're a vegan or plant-based or you
can't eat consume
honey you know what's really crazy is
you get the vegans and plant-based
people who are
really die-hard vegan right and i
totally respect that totally but what
happens is
they get their teeth starts falling
apart because they don't know
other things they need and something
goes wrong or they get their first
symptoms or they get symptoms again
after being vegan for a while and they
freak out and here they were the person
saying i can't have honey
because it's from a bee and now they're
eating eggs again because they because
they've they freaked out and now they're
eating eggs and dairy and raw dairy and
eggs
happens all the time meanwhile for the
first two years of being a vegan they
were ripping everybody apart for eating
honey
if you're a vegan eating honey if you're
a vegan the next thing you know now
they're eating eggs because they got
sick
here's the thing about if you're
plant-based
why i think it's okay for you to eat
honey and you don't have to you can
totally just do maple syrup i like maple
syrup too but honey
honey is it first of all a bee is not an
animal
critical to know a bee is not an animal
it's one thing that's very important so
i'm making a sauce
a bee is an insect and a bee doesn't
have a soul
the all bees on the planet at once have
a collective soul i know that's
that for some people i get it you know
some people that might be a little too
much for them and they're like oh how
can that be how's that possible like
you know but that's what it is it's all
bees have
one soul lot of insects have
one soul there's not an individual
soul per ant there's
the soul of all ant
all ants kind instead of humankind all
ant kind
there's a soul for all the ants
you can stomp out all like lots of ants
can stomp them out they're still gonna
have that one soul right
it's different but a deer
has an individual soul i know this might
be a little too much for a lot of you
guys i get it
it's very spiritual some of you guys are
like you know with that stuff it's just
like you want to see the cooking or
something and
you don't want to go there a lot of you
guys are really spiritual here of course
i know that
um okay so i got that in there
let's put a little honey too making a
nice sauce here now i'm gonna make this
one hot
let's throw a pepper in here let's do
that this is a sweet hot pepper
i'm not even going to dice it up
it's going to do its thing just being in
like little circles in here
on tick tock you can see that right
let's see if you can see this down low
on youtube you see that there you go
i think you can see it so let's put a
little garlic in here too
you don't need a lot of garlic
i love garlic and i i do use a lot of it
for
you know many times but this i'm gonna
not have this thing be so crazy
i'm gonna just chop mince up one clove
of garlic for the sauce
boom and then i'm going to mix it up
with a fork
[Music]
i'm honored you guys are here truly it's
just
we're in the medical medium kitchen it's
really fun
we're talking some cool stuff right
talking some cool stuff and i always say
to you guys look
the information saves lives you don't
have to like me
i was talking to a scholar the other day
his wife is
sick he's a huge scholar i've known him
for years
and he said you know it's funny how you
say things like cool
and awesome and stuff i go yeah yeah
says you know we don't talk like that at
the university
we just we're just you know and
and he goes but yet you have the
information so that my wife can get a
life back
aw we're honored you show up for us over
and over and over again
kat thank you for showing up here are
you kidding
thank you okay so i think this sauce
might be together got the orange in here
i got the hot pepper the garlic and the
honey it's a simple one
it's a basic one so let's cut up these
two nori rolls
now you guys have probably seen me do
before sometimes i'll cut i'll have like
six of these in a row and i'll i'll cut
them on the board six in a row
so i'm going to do just two now i'm not
cutting real large pieces
i'm cutting kind of
i'd say three quarters of an inch
is what i'm doing maybe yeah maybe three
quarters of an inch
somewhere around there right so i'm
doing just doing that one's gonna cut it
close over here so let me just do this
i think i butchered one okay let me get
a little plate out
if you guys are cool with that
let's plate these up
now what happens if you don't cut good
enough of course the uh
nori is going to be connected it's going
to be a hassle right
so i'm going to put these ends in the
middle
that's what i'm going to do
doing a sloppy job
did that one even make it there putting
the ends in the middle let me put these
all around the edge here
i'll show you guys
hey there's no rules there's no rules
with this
have some fun these are coming out
really good
one fell apart i was
overzealous
that was overzealous when i was cutting
them i was trying to be a little bit of
a hot shot right there right
cutting them too fast
being sloppy there they go right there
check it out
those are the raw cauliflower nori rolls
right there and there's dipping sauce
here
now i'm kind of curious about this
dipping sauce i don't know
how hot this pepper is really going to
be but let me just pop one in
right here
amazing tara appleman good to see you
amazing
you guys that's so good it's ridiculous
you know what i'm psyched about
i'm heading off to ig right now i'm
gonna turn tik tok back on and i'm gonna
turn clubhouse back on
i'm gonna make another round i'm pumped
maybe i can find something else to put
in here
um anyway you guys yum yum right pretty
incredible
it looks great it's so healthy for you i
mean if you really think about like
what's in here i'm just letting you guys
know if you think about what's in here
okay you got anti-viral foods there's a
sulfur compound in cauliflower
that helps to stomp out viruses in your
thyroid
it's the opposite if you want to talk
about one more silly thing real quick
what about the goitrogen stuff right
stay away from the kale and stay away
from the cauliflower if you have a
thyroid issue stay away from broccoli
that's misinformation terrible
misinformation another reason why
people don't heal your thyroid
desperately needs
the cris cruciferous
family it needs that it needs
cruciferous it's critical that you have
that
that's a sulfur compound that you need
it's so important so that's what
saturates into the thyroid
nodules tumors cysts thyroid cancer
hypothyroidism hyperthyroidism graves
hashimoto's thyroiditis all of those is
because of epstein-barr viruses
inside the thyroid and in order to help
you need some broccoli you need some
cauliflower you need these things it's
really important
important enough and then you got the
dolls in there which is
so highly mineralized so highly
mineralized
and it helps to take out toxic heavy
metals out of the intestinal tract which
is cool you got your cilantro
which is a leafy green alkalizing but
more than that trace mineral salts in
that too
plus chemical compounds to help with
your immune system and build your immune
system
yeah and all of this
so
so i see somebody teemo says check your
personal messages
i'll school you i think you're i think i
have an appointment with your
psychiatrist
he's calling any minute timo
timo i really do have to talk to your
psychiatrist he said he was calling me
so
but maybe he's not gonna call today but
you never know he might call
these are so delicious
hello dr phosphorus
yeah you're t you're team most
psychiatrist
yeah so what's the prognosis how
mentally ill is he
is timo what do you propose
dr phosphorus straitjacket
that's terrible that's sick you don't
put anybody in a straitjacket
but you're saying teemo has to be in a
straitjacket
why why he
he can't be that bad he is
you sent the paddywagon for him what are
they gonna do are they gonna knock on
his door did you section eight him
you section eight you section eight
teemo
is the paddy wagon coming to get him
what are they gonna do they're gonna
knock on the door and they're gonna pull
him out of there
by his hair if he's screaming
that you're a terrible psychiatrist i'm
gonna recommend teemo talks to another
psychiatrist because i'm worried about
him now
he said he was gonna school me yeah
i know i know that's how he is probably
but you think it's worse than that
i i don't judge people i don't judge
teemo
he says he'll school me and he says
check my private messages he'll school
me
so he must be really maybe he's just a
smart guy no he's not
what do you mean he's he's not he he's
got a really low iq too
yeah but i don't have a high iq i get
all my information from spirit of
compassion so i'm a bad guy too
yeah but he what did he do he ran in the
streets naked
with red paint on him oh my god
okay all right listen i i think you
probably do know what you're doing
dr phosphorus maybe you can't help teemo
all right all right i i gotta go i got
work to do thanks for calling me and
letting me know how he's doing because
we care about timo
i care about him yeah i just don't want
you locking him up paddy wagging him out
dragging him out out by his hair
putting him in the straight jacket and
in the padded room i just don't think
any of that's right
because i care about timo he says he's
going to school me
so what all right all right you do what
you got to do
okay dr phosphorus okay
guys i'm heading over to instagram now
heading over to instagram heading over
there and turning tick tock back on
can't wait
i'm bringing clubhouse back on too hope
you guys are there
just know i love you guys i might snack
on a couple of these in between but i
gotta
set the stuff up just give me a few
minutes i love you guys bless your heart
okay
and take care truly take care