groundbreaking boom bam
you're ready I'm gonna make the medical
medium vitamin C shock therapy
right off the kettle some warm water
nice gonna squeeze an orange in here
amazing I'm gonna drop some honey in
there too
this is not
nice putting a serving uh the micro seed
powder when I see out there vitamin C's
I shrill I shrug and there's a reason I
think about the stomach aches the kids
are gonna have I think about the belly
aches the adults are gonna have I think
about the acid poops people are gonna
have the acid runs the squirts because
you can't take enough of the other
vitamin C's out there without crapping
your pants without burning your stomach
no anti-caking agents no MSG no natural
flavor crap no alcohol no caffeine none
of the junk never mind you know when you
see products go no soy no whatever it's
like yeah but you got you got
anti-caking agents in there buddy and
you got natural flavors in there buddy
and you've got citric acid in there
buddy which is really bad vimergy isn't
that and that's the difference and
that's why I support them I could
support any company I want companies
knock on my door day in and day out over
the years thousands of companies get aw
on board but I won't support anybody I
won't support any company unless they go
so Advanced and so ahead of the curve
and they do it in a way that's good for
the customer in every way possible and
that's what I'm talking about you guys
know I've worked with these guys because
of that I want this company to stick
around for The Chronic Leo because I
know the people behind the companies out
there I know what's going on behind the
scenes I talk to a lot of people and I
know the bull crap that's out there
okay why is it so good so what you see
in front of me is a blender
and in this blender I'm going to make a
green smoothie we're gonna do three cups
we're going to get a decent amount of
mango in here one to two stalks of
celery four cups tightly packed spinach
and add a cup of water
we're gonna add this there we go
green smoothie with the immune powder
the micro C immune powder when you take
all that spinach with that vitamin C
together so all those trace minerals
from the spinach oh it's incredible
incredible there it is so not only are
you actually getting the micro C powder
collagen building effects right there
you're bringing it into the green
smoothie how good is that and what you
won't see in this green smoothie is a
whole bunch of fat you don't see a whole
bunch of oil put into here or coconut
oil because that inhibits what you're
trying to do you especially if you're
dealing with something or trying to
battle something or you got a cold or
you got something you're under the
weather you want something as clean as
this green smoothie without all the junk
in it not all these natural flavors we
need powerful tools what I call weapons
against the microbe world and what's
incredible free lemon balm it's insane a
free large lemon balm almost four ounce
bottle of lemon the best stuff actually
out there in the market when you get the
micro C the immune
powdery the link is in the description
right there they already put the lemon
balm in the cart for you
can't even tell you what this means for
The Chronic wheel what this means for
people who are sick what this means for
people who struggle with a lot of
different things this is really good