anthony william the medical medium
live right here we're live streaming
apple cider vinegar
the teeth dissolver episode is out
episode 11. and before anybody gets
upset about that i just want to talk
about all about apple cider vinegar and
before you make a judgment call i want
you to hear the information
so live right now we're talking about
apple cider vinegar episode 11 medical
medium podcast at apple podcast you
don't want to miss this episode it's a
really powerful one it's jam-packed with
information about apple cider vinegar
and i've always been pro apple cider
vinegar just so you guys know because
i've always known it's the best vinegar
to use if you're gonna use one but
i also know the drawbacks and i know the
potholes and if you're really sick or
struggling or have any symptoms and
conditions and you want every edge you
can get because like i said in the
episode it's make or break if you're in
that position where it's make or break
you might want to avoid the apple cider
vinegar as far as internally you might
not want to do the tablespoons of it you
know and doing the tablespoons of it but
before you make a judgment call or get
upset you have to listen to the episode
so important see apple cider vinegar
episode teeth dissolver that's what
that's what this episode's called and
it's at medical media podcast at apple
podcast i'm live right now live
streaming
um michelle l says acv kills me yeah i
mean uh hi deanna hi back to everybody
and
whoa watching from egypt whoa incredible
i'm so glad you're here um and the
bottom line is when it comes down to
apple cider vinegar i want you guys to
know that i've always told people if you
can't let go of your vinegar if you
can't
yes use the apple cider vinegar and if
you can't let go of the grape vinegar if
you can't let go of the you know the red
the the you know the red grape vinegar
if you can't let go of that or balsamic
vinegar if you can't let go of that then
use the apple cider vinegar but
something has happened that's changed
over the last 10 years now and people
are using apple cider vinegar they're
using it in large quantities like one to
two teaspoons i mean one to two
tablespoons really one to three
tablespoons one to four tablespoons
they'll take it in the morning they'll
put it in water they'll put it in
smoothies they'll put it in something
but what happens is they don't know
what goes on internally with apple cider
vinegar it's acetic acid
and you have to listen to this episode
about acetic acid and what happens in
the body when that acetic acid enters
and
and i want to tell you something if
you're somebody where it helped your
acid reflux if you're somebody where
apple cider vinegar helped your acid
reflux or apple cider vinegar helped
your bloating there's a reason why it
helped
but
there's also backlash that occurs later
when the teeth start to actually fall
apart or the the enamel starts to wear
off later and i want to forewarn people
because when you're chronically sick
the last thing you need now is teeth
problems later on when you're already
dealing with fatigue and other issues
and everything so that's one thing right
there um
kate dillon delorenzo says i used acv
for months
morning night one teaspoon morning one
at night
but it killed me i ended up with
digestive problems and lots more and i
want kate i want to talk about that for
a second because what that means is
exactly what i talked about in the apple
cider vinegar episode so you have to
listen to this episode you guys now
here's how it works your stomach glands
if they're strong enough
what happens is you can take the apple
cider vinegar and then see some benefits
if your stomach lands are strong enough
but a lot of people their stomach lands
aren't strong enough the stomach glands
that produce gastric acid that's your
hcl hydrochloric acid and then when you
take acetic acid which is apple cider
vinegar when you take that vinegar and
it what it does is it puts stress on
those stomach glands and if they're not
strong enough those stomach lands
because your hcl is weak your stomach
glands are weakened and and they're
depleted then they just blow out and
when they blow out you get real sick
from acv
and you might be somebody that's not
there yet your stomach glands haven't
been that compromised yet but here's the
problem they will get compromised so if
you're doing your apple cider vinegar
for five years then you do it every
night or you do it every morning
eventually those stomach glands will get
burned out and when they burn out boom
you don't know what's causing your
problem you'll still do your apple cider
vinegar not knowing it's the apple cider
vinegar that made the stomach lands
really bad to begin with or really made
them worse actually because our stomach
lands get depleted anyway but this
pushes it over the edge so when you hear
this episode
you're going to be blown away because i
cover in detail i talk all about it so
episode 11 all right apple cider vinegar
teeth dissolver episode episode 11
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
link is in the description
do not miss it you guys are going to
love this episode it's packed with
information now before before you make a
judgment call and you throw shade at me
you throw hate at me and whatever it is
because here it is anthony william the
medical medium is talking about apple
cider vinegar now because he you know
he's always getting in trouble for
talking about something or another
because i'm always going to step on
somebody's toes by accident well you
know not by accident but just
automatically is what i mean it just
happens when you have information about
things so
and it just so happens though it gets
people upset um good to see everybody on
here right now so here's the thing about
apple cider vinegar if your stomach
glands are really strong and they
haven't been weakened yet and you want
to take apple cider vinegar internally
on a daily basis you're not going to
notice a problem yet you'll even see
that your acid reflux could back down
you can see which you could have fixed
it other ways but you'll see your acid
reflux back down you'll see you're
bloating back down
you might see what seems to be some
weight loss too because there's an
appetite suppressant but as the stomach
lands get tired from the acetic acid
and they start to blow out they start to
pickle so you have to know how this
works i'm going to talk about the pickle
process with this too when your stomach
lands start to pickle in there okay what
happens is they blow out they also get
depleted and they they get way far gone
then when you take your apple cider
vinegar it kills you it feels like oh my
god this stuff is killing me why am i
bloating more why am i feeling horrible
why why do i have all these other
problems now but if you're really convi
if you have real conviction towards your
apple cider vinegar where nothing can
tell you different that this this stuff
works so good for you and it's the best
thing ever for you when you're convinced
while your health is having problems
you'll never know apple cider vinegar is
making it worse or even created some of
your problems you won't know so you'll
sit there being like oh wait apple cider
vinegar i better take some more every
day i better take some more and oh
wow i'm getting sicker here but i better
take some more and you won't know unless
someone becomes the messenger
to actually give you that option because
i want you to have a choice a choice to
be like wait a minute you mean to tell
me uh that could be contributing to my
problems so it's so important to know it
really is and
it's great to see you guys on here
everybody on here so um
here's the thing
it's like
that that episode apple cider vinegar
teeth dissolver episode
it has all the do's and don'ts i talk
about what i like about apple cider
vinegar what i love about it
how it's mineral rich so it does at
least have that it's the best
vinegar there is and i talk about why
apple cider vinegar is the best vinegar
there is outside of all the vinegars but
even with that said i talk about why we
have to look out and be very cautious
with it and i know that gets people
upset but there's reasons now here's one
reason right here okay and you'll hear
more in detail in the episode but
what happens with acetic acid it has a
chemical reaction with calcium calcium
calcium is in your teeth calcium is in
your bones acetic acid depletes calcium
there's a chemical reaction that occurs
when acetic acid hits calcium now i'm
just going to say this okay
there's vinegar in cleaning products
so remember that there's a reason why
vinegar is in cleaning products
and
vinegar can clean hard water stains yes
calcium stains hmm
think about that one for a little bit
okay now i know that gets apple cider
vinegar people upset by even you know
talking anything bad about it but i just
want you to have a chance to protect
yourself in case you got sucked into the
apple cider vinegar trend you know and
so this is how it works
why does vinegar
clean water stains
why does it do that hard water stains
it cleans them because
it can decalcify it can actually have a
reaction to calcium and start wearing
calcium away
so you have to hear this podcast episode
medical medium podcast that apple
podcast that's the uncensored version
the link is in the description please
check it out so you can hear the episode
share it with others so you can help
other people too and also there's the
brain meditation the moon meditation
there's the neurological symptoms
episode and i want to talk about
neurological symptoms in a minute to you
i want to cover all the different
neurological symptoms as well why i got
you guys here so important so
so let's talk about this a little bit
a lot of people actually everybody is
concerned about enamel
concerned about cavities concerned about
their teeth and i will do a teeth
episode too but they're concerned about
their teeth about receiving gums about
all kinds of things regarding teeth well
apple cider vinegar okay so we have to
keep this in mind where is the enamel
down i discussed this all in the episode
podcast now listen
i know guys i get it so many of you just
love your apple cider vinegar you don't
want to you don't want to give it up you
want to even get mad at me possibly i
get it i know i've already seen some
comments where some people are like
apple cider vinegar is the greatest
thing ever and you're wrong you're wrong
but i want you to get a chance to listen
to the episode if you can and hear the
information and i'm actually not totally
against it i talk about what uses i like
it for one use is for acne surfacely by
putting it on a wall making a warm
compress with a towel putting a little
apple cider vinegar on the towel and the
hot water and the towel and putting it
on acne okay so and putting it on spots
hot spots that you have and that's with
apple cider vinegar i talk about that i
talk about some other uses too so you'll
see that i actually do believe in it and
going back 35 years you guys i have
always said if you're gonna do vinegar
and you're not to let it go it has to be
apple cider vinegar and this and and
that's that's the one to use
so it's not like i'm sitting here trying
to say oh this is bad oh don't do this
ever and whatnot i'm just saying what
happened is over the last couple of
decades actually the last decade last 10
years
a a surge was happening about taking it
internally and it's really sad because
when you're struggling with you know any
kind of thing like severe fibromyalgia
you're struggling with ms you're
struggling with just fatigue you're
struggling with all kinds of different
symptoms and conditions
whatever they are eczema bad eczema bad
psoriasis vitiligo endometriosis pcos
fibroids if you're suffering with
something pretty intense like really
struggling whatever it could be
you know lupus lyme disease neurological
lyme whatever's going on you don't want
to have that apple cider vinegar shots
you don't want to have those tablespoons
of apple cider vinegar so important to
know because if you do that
what happens
is that we end up hurting ourselves in
other ways and i talk about all the
different ways it doesn't help somebody
who's really struggling and really
hurting you won't notice it if you're
like young indestructible you've got
nothing going on with you and you're
doing vinegar and any food you want to
use you're doing apple cider vinegar
shots if you want because you want to
suppress your appetite or something
whatever somebody told you it does
and i get it you won't notice the
difference but by the time you're 30 by
the time you're 34 by the time you're 35
all of a sudden the dentist says what
are you doing wrong here what's going on
your teeth are starting to fall apart
your enamel is wearing down your gums
are receding and you're like what i got
something happening in there and no one
wants to no one wants to know or no one
would want to know really it's the apple
cider vinegar or the vinegar and all
vinegar reacts the same inside the body
that's for sure so medical media podcast
at apple podcast you've got to catch the
episode you guys
it's so important the episode is episode
11 the link is in the description it's
apple cider vinegar tooth dissolver
teeth dissolver so really important to
know and i talk about the calcium
reaction with acetic acid i talk about
how acetic acid is really really
aggressive on her body internally and
why and how and i talk about why you get
relief somebody gets relief from acid
reflux while so why somebody gets relief
temporarily for some of these different
conditions but i talk about the flip
side of how it just gets worse down the
road with other problems so i get it you
know i mean look
this is really an intense episode for
people who are big into apple cider
vinegar i don't want to like cause any
waves that's not what i want to do
but you know what when you're not well
it's make or a break i talk about that
in the episode link is in the
description so important to know
um listen to it at apple podcast that's
the uncensored version so if you go to
any other platform that you're used to
hearing one of my old radio shows too or
something and you say well he's here
it's it's it's censored so make sure you
go to apple podcast link is in the
description apple cider vinegar
um
and so so you know please share the
episode if you can
share so others can hear it it would be
so helpful it would get other people to
to learn about it subscribe to to
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
subscribe so you can get notified you
know sign up to my newsletter so if you
haven't at medicalmedium.com
so we're going to apple cider vinegar a
little bit more i think we should it's
an important one
um samantha says you're so right i got
so sick after a month on acv
absolutely
it really does and there's people who
don't get sick yet but they do get sick
and don't know it's the apple cider
vinegar
messaging with angels what a cool name i
dropped vinegar and oils and it helped
my acid reflux if i do eat it i get the
acid reflux that's because
stomach lands when they're already
overloaded and you're trying to heal
them
and and when you when you throw that
acetic acid in that apple cider vinegar
oh forget it what it does is it
completely blows them out it squeezes
every last drop of hcl out of your
stomach lands these tiny little stomach
glands sitting in your stomach that's
what produces your gastric acid when you
drop those tablespoons of apple cider
vinegar down in there and you just it
pickles them and squeezes them out uh
ashley alexandra i knew a girl that
loved to faithfully drink regular white
distilled vinegar every day for many
months about a cup a day and it pickled
her insides and she went through major
stomach surgery it does so what happens
is that that acetic acid causes that
much trouble so look look look i get it
you guys if you really love your acv
if you really if you're really really
attached to it please listen to the
episode before casting judgment because
i know the minute i start posting about
it minute i start putting it out there
man the hate
comes flying in
people judging before even hearing the
episode they won't listen to the episode
but they'll just still just be throwing
all kinds of hate the pitchforks will be
out the torches will be out and um
so you gotta hear the episode okay it's
episode 11 adrienne said dude thank you
i have never heard anyone address this
adrian you're so cool you're so cool um
mandy says listen to it this morning
yeah loving all the new in-depth info
thank you for for keeping us informed
so um let's go into a couple of
different episodes neurological symptoms
that's a big episode please tell your
friends about that share that
information out there neurological
symptoms okay that's the one right there
talk about brain fog i'll talk about
that too deborah we'll talk about that
in a minute i want to talk about that
so neurological symptoms that right
there is an incredible episode at
medical media podcast at apple podcast
link is in the description for the
podcast please check out neurological
symptoms that's a big one i talk about
dizziness feeling like you're on a boat
tingles and numbness jaw pain neck pain
um
blurry eyes you know eye floaters in the
eyes brain fog
to with that um all of that i talk about
all the different neurological symptoms
restless leg syndrome ringing in the
ears buzzing humming popping uh burning
skin
uh body pain
uh everything from neuropathy to all
that fibromyalgia i talk about the
neurological symptoms no one understands
out there truly fully understands out
there wait till you hear that episode
neurological symptoms it's a really good
one and anxiety included that's a
neurological symptom and i talk about
that so check out neurological symptoms
episode please if you get a chance
that's one right there
then you got the eggs episode i know
everybody gets mad about that hearing
the truth about eggs and talk about that
one talk about the air fresheners
episode there's that one too i talk
about um
the brain fog episode let's go into
brain fog a little bit
so what you'll find in the brain fog
episode is information of why we have
brain fog
so if you have brain fog if you're
dealing with any kind of focus and
concentration if you're feeling like the
words don't come out of your mouth the
way they're supposed to because to the
thoughts in your head so you feel like
they're not matching the thoughts in
your head the words that you're speaking
or you can't really understand people
that are talking to you because you're
forgetting what they're saying or that
you can't compute it and you can't
register it or something meanwhile
you're brilliant you're smart you're a
good person you're not you're you're not
uneducated you're not you're not any of
those things you know a lot of people i
had a friend tell me that that told me
it's like you know
that told me that they feel like people
think she's like she doesn't she's not
smart and she's uneducated or something
and she's just doesn't have it together
and she's a ditz and that's not at all
she's suffering struggling from brain
fog and she was telling me how people
they underestimate her they misjudge her
they misunderstand her
and it's just not fair it's just not
fair
so brain fog is a great episode so
medical media podcast
at apple podcast that's the platform to
see to sorry to hear these to listen to
these please catch these the information
is vast packed jam-packed and that's the
whole thing so we'll talk about apple
cider vinegar for a little bit danica
says thank you apple cider vinegar
worked well for a while and then
developed digestive difficulties okay
okay
that's what i talk about in the episode
is it could work well for a bit for a
little bit and then you get problems
from it and i'll tell you why it was
what i was saying those gastric glands
of yours those little glands or stomach
glands what happens is when you dump
that acetic acid down in you so i'll
take a couple tablespoons okay let me
have my apple cider vinegar here i'll
take a couple tablespoons here and and
put it down and and send it down whoa
it's helping a little bit it's helping
what it's doing is it's blowing out
those glands what that means is it's
making them squeeze every last drop of
all that hcl out and then you get a max
out point so you get a max out point and
a leveling point where your stomach
glands go can't take this anymore i
can't do it anymore and then all the
digestive problems start coming back and
coming back coming back plus the acetic
acid is so hard on the lining of the
intestinal tract lorena
i love how in the end poem you say the
body will never saunter that really
stood out to me you know
when when spirit of compassion gave me
that that poem at the end and used the
word saunter i was like saunter you know
and and it was just it was so special um
the medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
check out these episodes it's a free
resource i mean i don't know what else
more i can do
more or else i can do the link is in the
description if you guys are interested
in the medical medium books
that's cleansed the heel right in back
of me over 200 symptoms and conditions i
talk about the true causes i have all
these protocols in there i have the 369
cleanse in there the mono eating
cleanses in there i mean that book is
packed it's a medical textbook right
behind me amazon.com
51 off u.s u.s amazon if there's a sale
right on that book cleanse the heel
please check that out if you want get it
free at the library but that book will
blow your mind that's sitting in back of
me right there if you don't already have
it
sarah says the episode for neurological
symptoms uh organized by nerve affected
was fantastic thank you keep these
podcasts coming thank you for listening
to that one honestly
i don't know which one's my favorite at
this point because i had a favorite and
then i was like well i don't know if
fruit fear is my favorite anymore
because i love the air fresheners
episode well i don't know if the air
freshener sent the candle episodes my
favorite anymore because apple cider
vinegar that's my favorite now
neurological symptoms are my favorite
janice says
janice ellison says if you ingest acv
use a straw to protect your teeth smart
idea
but
you'll still get other problems too
though janice listen to the episode it's
really good to do and by the way janice
that's really that's really a good idea
but
that's not how you protect your teeth
entirely
because the apple cider vinegar it gets
in your bloodstream it gets everywhere
so it has a chemical reaction with
calcium altogether bones included so
even though you're bypassing the apple
cider vinegar and you're not letting it
touch your teeth it's bypassing your
teeth it still finds its way to your
teeth because it sucks calcium out it
vampires the calcium out it leeches it
out of the body so even though you're
kind of bypassing it with a straw which
is a great idea because at least you're
not getting direct contact to your teeth
so it was really smart
at the same time your teeth will still
be affected by it uh just just happening
because it's in your body and you're
drinking it and consuming it and it
still finds its way because
your teeth will still get hit with it it
will still touch your teeth so unless
you take the straw and kind of stick it
down further
and just try to suck that way so it goes
down your throat it's not really an easy
option it's not a great one um
yeah and so the thing is with with the
whole thing with apple cider vinegar and
any vinegar is it pickles organs too
because there's this chemical reaction
that happens inside the body with salt
so how do you pickle something well you
need vinegar and you need salt and we
have salt in our bloodstream naturally
occurring wait to hear about that and
check out that info so the medical
medium podcast at apple podcast you want
to hear the apple cider vinegar episode
the link is in the description the teeth
dissolver episode you want to hear it
please share this one with others so
they could hear it and it helps out
greatly for me because when you share it
with someone else then i know someone
else is healing i know someone else who
needed the information is out there
who's getting it and then i could be
like oh it's working we're helping more
people it's a free podcast there's no
commercials in it there's no
infomercials it's free free it's just
about healing powerful information you
don't want to miss it all the episodes
are powerful all the episodes are
amazing you got the neurological
symptoms got the brain fog episode catch
that and you might want to hear them
again if you heard them because that's
how much info is in them that's really
really it's really great so um you know
i know some people are going to be upset
but i talk about what i like about apple
cider vinegar i talk about
how it is helpful and in what ways so
hear the episode so you can hear that
too and you could be like well wait a
minute he does like it to some point
wait he does like it for some some
reason and look if you're never gonna
give up your vinegar if you're never
gonna just
not do vinegar apple cider vinegar is
the way to go i've been saying this
forever
dr fond good to see you wow
before mm i used to recommend acv for gi
issues initially it helped for some but
people had to stop because it caused
worse reflux after a period of time dr
fan
amazing thank you for being here today i
know you're busy with your schedule with
your patients i know you're working hard
and you're here commenting right now i'm
honored that you're here uh giving your
advice and your your experience and
which is which is incredible thank you
for being here and offering that truly
it will really help people um
and uh so yeah so the bottom line this
episode apple cider vinegar teeth
dissolver i know i get flack i know i
get people upset
i know that happens but look it's about
protecting people who aren't well if you
don't if you feel great and you're not
so sick and you just have a little
symptom here and there and you're into
health and you want to hack health and
you think apple cider vinegar is great
and you're dumping it down
the problem is with that is later on it
will bite you in the butt that's what it
will do what will bite you in the butt
and then who's gonna say well i'm really
sorry you used it for 10 years and
didn't know
we didn't know it wasn't good for you
who cares if your teeth have all these
problems you're in the dentist office
every day more than ever who cares if
your stomach lands are blown out who
cares see so that's the whole point no
one's gonna like you know it's
no one's gonna care so let's care let's
look out for you that's what it's about
check out the other episodes the medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast this is
a live stream right now
i'm here you know and i love spending
time with you guys live like this i
really do if you're interested in a book
that could really help save lives you're
looking at cleanse the healing backing
me
uh
nasal says acv episode is amazing whoa
thank you for listening to it
that's that's that's mind-blowing that
you heard it and you you you totally
know you hear all of it margie says i'm
here hey margie i'm glad you're here
today great
um so
we'll do a quick we'll do a quick
rundown on this a little bit
why was this episode named teeth
dissolver
because
unfortunately apple cider vinegar will
wear down the enamel on your teeth i
talk about why and how that happens
check that out and unless your teeth are
important and the apple cider vinegar is
more important than your teeth if it's
more important than your teeth then just
you can use it if you know
jeff says that's the problem it can make
you feel better at first yes exactly
jeff that's what i was saying in the
episode it can make you feel better at
first but then down the road symptoms
reoccur and you think nothing of it in
fact you may believe it is time to
increase acv but it is the acv causing
damage that's what happens you think you
have to increase acv meanwhile it's
causing the problem
oh my god you know you know jennifer
mccall good to see you thank you i have
played the brain fog in neurological
podcasts over 15 times each
thank you because i can explain it to
anyone they don't understand i'm honored
thank you for listening to those so many
times ashley's ashley apple's applesauce
that's a really cool name um
neurological episodes was great my
family has all the all the symptoms
awesome so glad you guys are listening
to a neurological episode
um the podcast the the episode uh make
sure you share it where you can share it
whenever with anybody else you can share
it with all of it you guys um you know i
believe in you i'm proud of all of you
you're working so hard and you know i
know that and i'm just proud of you guys
you're working so hard chris woods says
the poems at the end of the podcasts
are beautiful so the poems at the end of
the podcast are beautiful uh you know
i'm honored you feel that way it's so
funny because there's you know people
there's people that love them and then
someone would be like why are you doing
a poem at the end of the podcast episode
like why are you doing that i'm like huh
what do you mean why i'm doing that
there's actual messages in there from
above in that in that information in
that poem rachel says caffeine episode
is my favorite uh rachel
caffeine episode was my favorite for a
long time now and then the apple cider
vinegar i'm kind of stuck now where it
was the caffeine episode is my favorite
and the apple cider vinegar one now is
kind of it's just really hard
um the caffeine episode is mind-blowing
you guys i release a secret just like
i've done in these episodes because this
is all information nobody knows out
there you know that are in these
episodes you guys know medical medium
information is unique and original
because you know you guys know that um
but in the caffeine episode i do release
a lot of secrets about caffeine that not
only nobody knows but just mind-blowing
mind-boggling really i talk about the
farms and stuff all of that so you got
to really check that out you know um
that episode is is definitely yeah i
gotta listen to that episode again i'm
gonna go and listen to the episode again
later on tonight so the link is in the
description you can check out the
caffeine episode which is coffee matcha
and chocolate okay that episode the
neurological symptom episode with all
the different aches and pains tangles
and numbness floaters in the eyes right
um uh body pain burning gums burning
tongue i've seen people with vibrating
tongue seeing people with vibrating
vibrating humming and buzzing throughout
the body ears ringing popping buzzing
ticks and spasms
all of it back pain nerve pain feet pain
i talked about it all you want to check
out neurological symptoms and and all
that too
ken russell says came in the live stream
late so is apple cider vinegar good or
bad for you
you gotta hear the podcast ken you gotta
hear it it's mind-blowing it's packed
the link is in the description thanks
for coming on i'm glad you came on this
live stream late i'm just glad you're
here check check it out because i talk
about the teeth issue with it dissolving
teeth and why the chemical reaction
happens with acetic acid i talk about
how it blows out the gastric glands and
gets us in trouble but that's just some
stuff that's just some stuff i talk
about you know and there's more to it
than that there's more to it than that
um so please share and and leave a
review at apple podcast for the medical
medium podcast you guys so medical mean
podcast at apple podcast please leave
reviews if you can it helps out it helps
people find the message and find the way
to get the information it also helps
because you know trolls like to do
things and blah blah and everything and
that doesn't help so knowing that
there's positive support wherever you
can is actually one way we can keep on
you know winning the battle against
chronic illness and help people heal and
and all that uchoda says i love the acv
episode i listened three times to catch
everything in it it was so packed with
information i'm glad you enjoyed it um
i think somebody just said where's the
book i saw it come flying up so there's
the cleanse the heel right there over
200 symptoms of conditions it's 51 off
in amazon.com us you guys
it's 51 off it's just 16.99 on amazon
right now u.s
it's unbelievable it's a medical
textbook it's really heavy it's a big
book so be prepared when you get it it's
a really big book 75 recipes over 200
symptoms conditions i got all the
cleanses in there you guys got to check
that book out if you can get a free the
library if you want to go that route
um
and anyway so i'm going to be doing a
thyroid episode eventually going to be
doing a lot of different oh elizabeth
says mine are the meditations those are
my favorite elizabeth i'm honored you're
doing those
i love you guys and thanks for being
here just keep on taking care of
yourself i stand with you i believe in
you we can rise out of the ashes
together we can beat our symptoms we can
heal we can move forward and take care
talk to you