let's get some sound we didn't have
sound this whole time until just now so
there we go so you
guys we're B making baked mac and cheese
here we are I'm excited about this I got
the pot of water right here boiling
up and I was just talking about right
here what we're going to do so there we
are baked mac and cheese right there
check it out you guys that's what we're
going to make out of the brains saer
protocols going to make a dressing a a
ranch dressing Green Sal with a ranch
dressing which I'm excited about as well
so this is going to be great good to see
you guys making some food right here
this is kind of a really comforting dish
really yummy and I'm going to talk about
chronic illness symptoms and so forth
because it's critical to know what's
wrong if you don't know what's wrong how
are you going to heal if you don't know
what's wrong if you don't know why
you're sick how are you going to heal
how's it going to happen it's Hit or
Miss it's Hit or Miss if you don't know
what's wrong it's just hit or miss out
there right somebody can have a symptom
for a little while it comes and goes
they think they're doing stuff and they
think it's going away if it's coming
back they think it's going away and
finally you're like what is wrong so you
go somewhere else and somebody says well
it's this this this it's sibo it's this
or it's that or it's your microbiome or
it's this and or it's Lyme disease or
whatever it is and now you're trying
that out and you're trying some
different things that's kind of you know
waffling back and forth you don't know
what's wrong you got aches and pains
your neck tingles and numbness weird
feelings all kinds of feelings all kinds
of panic and depression and whatever
whatever else is happening headaches
migraines and then you're just like wait
and then you're moving on from there
it's like but what is really wrong
what's creating it some people be like
ocular migraines somebody's like okay
it's this it's that but if you don't
know what's wrong for real how are you
going to get to the finish line and
really heal and get out of the woods how
are you going to move forward and really
Excel with your healing and really push
forward and get out of the woods and see
that beautiful field that green grass
growing and that beautiful field and the
sun shining and that air just being so
crisp and clean there's no Chemtrails in
the sky there's no smog and garbage
you're just freed and you're healed and
you're better how are you going to get
there if people don't know what's wrong
how it happened you know why are you
sick if people don't know that how are
you ever going to get there so let's
make some baked mac and cheese I'm going
to start out I got the oven on that's
happening I'm going to get some pasta
right here and here so I have some
elbows because it's baked mac and cheese
let me pop this in here you guys all
right so I'm going to drop these suckers
in look at
this I'm making a decent amount so
you don't want to overcook it it's easy
to do if you're not paying attention if
you got something going on it's easy to
overcook keep that in mind right there
real easy to overcook like blink your
eyes and your pasta is shot it's just
gone right close your eyes for a minute
and then your pasta just dissolves so
keep that in mind always like be on
it hey W David hey W can you tell us how
the book signing was for you hey it was
[Music]
incredible
incredible I mean right I mean how many
of you guys were there because there
were thousands of people there thousands
of people there it was insane it was
insane I'm not going to kid you I had
some snow blindness not going to kid you
there okay there was a time where I
thought I could fall off the
stage because you know Spirit of
compassion is talking to me a mile a
minute about
everybody about what's going on with
everybody it's intense it can it can
take me out but guess what I hung in
there I recouped a little hung in there
recouped a little did it again right did
the signing right you guys it was
incredible and you guys was so great to
see you are you kidding it was so great
great to see you it was just
amazing I'm using a pee and lentil pasta
I saw that question come up I'm using a
pee and lentil pasta yeah that's what's
right here there you go and I'm I'm
keeping an eye on it this time I'm just
kind of sticking to this thing right now
because you know what boom once it's
overdone I'm going to have to start over
again because you don't want it so mushy
and so like you know broken you don't
want those pieces broken so you want to
do it right
we were there summer right there whoa we
were there incredible you exceeded our
expectations thank you thank you thank
you I don't even know what to say do a
little curtsy and a bow I can't believe
it let me start getting these potatoes
ready right here these are steamed
potatoes if you take a look now I know
um if you guys are on YouTube right now
or Rumble you can see everything you can
see it all here if you're on IG and Tik
Tok you're probably just seeing like
that right it's just seeing some of it
so I'm going to try to show you here so
these are steamed carrots that's going
to be part of the cheese the cheese
that's going on the Mac uhoh uhoh keep
an eye on this
don't yep keep an eye on these man do
not let these overcook whatever you do I
don't want to start again all right okay
that's cool that's cool
let's keep it
going all right can you guys remind me
please can you remind me again all right
so that's the carrots they're steamed I
just took them out of the steamer now I
got the potatoes for the cheese right
here let me peel these potatoes
now grab a fork you guys I'd love to
talk about the event if you guys are um
okay about talking about it I would love
to there's lots of things we can talk
about because we got some stuff to do
there's we're going to be here for a
little while so you know grab a lemon
balm tea maybe if you have ingredients
try to make this with me okay that would
be incredible too so I'm just peeling
some of these potato skins off because
you don't want your cheese to be brown
because you want the skins off I know
the Skins are so good for you people say
there's no protein in potato actually
there is protein in
potato really easily digestable really
easily
assimilable okay
really easy
protein so there you go because all you
hear is protein protein protein can you
believe you only hear that still out
there so where do you get your protein
where do you get your protein it's like
a sick mind virus right where do you get
your protein it's like a zombie bite
seriously it's like a zombie bite out
there it's like some kind of disease the
protein disease right the brainwashing
is insane I told you guys what they did
they didn't
experiment um they didn't experiment
back in the 50s I think it was the 50s
and a whole bunch of people signed up to
and when you signed up to an experiment
to study in the 50s you couldn't back
out it's not like you can back out or
just drop out so they stuck everybody in
this camp and they were doing a a
protein test a protein test right just
think about how sick this is I got to
tell you guys right now so oh
sh don't even tell me
no you guys didn't
overcook nope you didn't
nice all right all right those you guys
remind
me another minute in
there you
don't
yeah hold on
little Al Dente right a little too much
give another
minute that's that's
good Sherry Fox over there on YouTube it
was such a great event and meeting with
you very briefly at the book signing in
person was really great stage blessings
you did was very powerful oh my God
thank you seriously truly bless
you I can't believe you were there you
guys were there you guys were there
that's amazing I'm going to give this
just one more minute I'm not going to do
anything else right the second I want to
keep an eye on this I don't want to
screw this up cuz I will mess this one
up give it like 30 more
seconds I stay on it
mhm yeah it does cross a blood brain
barrier okay
Brad says so great to see you aw the
protein myth is
exhausting it's
exhausting it's disgustingly exhausting
are you kidding it's unbelievably
bad so what I'm going to do is I'm going
to drain the water out of this I'm not
going to put it in a strainer okay I
know you can't see me over there on Tik
Tok and IG just bear with me I'm just
straining the water out of this
okay there we go instead of dropping it
in a strainer okay okay on IG don't
worry I didn't leave you guys I'm just
draining the water out of the pasta
okay I want to do it that
way and then cuz I want to keep it kind
of
moist I want to keep it kind of
moist we're back to this or what aw in
the kitchen the Antics man the Antics
and I got some stuff to say too I just
want to say it I got some stuff to say
see I'm leaving this kind of a little
bit
moist I don't want it going in there dry
I don't want want it sticking together
like you know in a crazy way all
right I don't want the pasta sticking
together here let's make the cheese
really quick
nice let's get that
Mac all right come on we can pull this
off all right take a look right there
there it is let's get the cheese done
let's get it made move that aside come
on let's do
it BB aaro a
w a w your team did an amazing job at
your event
incredible I just want to tell you guys
thank you so much for being there I I
can't I can't thank you enough did you
guys see how many people came seriously
I mean I rolled in at
6:05 I think I rolled in at 6:05 in the
morning and the line already was crazy
and I was like wait a minute I mean
605 I heard the line started at 11:00
the night
before and from what we've heard
by what it looks like with the numbers
calculated and everything there were way
above 10,000 people there way
above okay so I have some potatoes ready
here I'm just getting the skins off
these are steamed potatoes and they're
freshly steamed just out of the oven
right now and I want to talk about
chronic illness and everything and I
want to get into that a little bit it's
critical to know what's wrong in order
to heal critical it really is just give
me a chance to just do some of this you
guys don't mind yeah thank you for
coming to the event it was very
special it
was it was
Godly Angels were obviously
there it went incredible I knew a lady
that got in line at 2: a.m. so yeah 2 2
in the morning lizie yeah how how
unbelievable that is let's make some
cheese dressing really quick not cheese
dressing let's make the cheese mac and
cheese is happening now let's do
that okay all right I'm just going to
pop this food processor right here you
guys okay with that all right let's do
this first of all let's get some steamed
potatoes in here okay going to break
them up a little
bit all right this is going to be the
cheese you guys can see you were so
humble but I wish everyone could see how
incredibly hard you worked at the book
signing and doing everything you could
to have a special moment with everyone I
really was trying I really was it was
all
inspiring thank you
summer it was really special time would
you guys want to do it again or what
Sandy says it was an awesome experience
for all of us to attend your epic event
your team was amazing as was security
detail as
well yeah when you get death threats and
stuff like that you better believe you
have to have a good security
team yep that's
right and the thing is with me you know
you know how like people you hear it on
social media like I had a death threat
and so you'll hear people and meanwhile
they really
didn't I don't talk about that stuff
it's been years but yeah I've had
plenty all right boom I got this
here let's
see let's get this going I got the
potatoes in here I'm getting ready so
I'm going to do probably about like two
cups of carrots diced carrots but I'm
not going to go too crazy okay get this
the more carrot you put in the darker
your cheese is do you want that cheddar
look do you want that really dark
cheddar look or do you like that that
lighter cheese with your Mac and Cheese
what is it going to be so I'm not going
to overdo the carrot I don't like it
super super like that real dark cheddar
look even though I mean heck I mean
that's a really cool that's cool too if
you like it that way right okay so I got
the elbow pasta that's over there I'm
just making sure I do this I got the
carrots now I just need the onion powder
that is where I'm going it with it right
there I don't want to do more than that
let's get some onion powder in here boom
nice three tablespoons of onion powder
so I'm going to pop the top off of here
get ready whoa whoa and whoa and whoa
whoa nice it's awesome tablespoon of
garlic powder now listen listen if
you're like I don't like garlic powder
then okay you don't have to use it all
right but I'm gonna use it here boom
tablespoon of paprika let's go that's
Cayenne right there I'm not going to do
a tablespoon of cayenne don't do a
tablespoon of cayenne okay I'm telling
you right now don't do a table who whoa
whoa yeah that's serious right there
whoa that was a tablespoon for sure
we're going to do a we're going to do
Cayenne a little touch of cayenne we're
not going to go crazy with the Cayenne
just in case my family wants to eat this
which is what they're going to do and
that everybody loves Cayenne really
really hot let me get some lemon
squeezed in here too okay now on the
lemon these are the smallest lemons I've
seen in the longest time these lemons
are like so small it's crazy let's get
some 1 and 1/2 tablespoons of of lemon
juice in here let's just find a strainer
really quick let's get it going okay now
what I do is I add water into this too
to get it really rolling so I'm going to
do that as well so let me just get these
lemons squeezing here now I have never
I've probably seen a store bought lemon
this small I mean I've grown them and
I've grown them small but these are like
Miniatures
whoa that's a miniature lemon let me do
two hands here to kind of do a little
bit of a little bit of kind of trick
with this you know what I mean so I'm
making the cheese right
now I get a little bit more lemon in
here
yes huh yes please again are you guys do
you guys want to do it again because I
was thinking about doing it again but
make making it even more over the top
crispy perspective oh my God yes please
do it again will you guys be there do
you want to be there for like the light
blast and everything we'll do the light
blasts um Alexandra Sophia do it again
okay okay okay well you guys you guys
are you guys are convincing me
you guys are convincing me big time
seriously I'm Blown Away seriously if
you guys just got on here making baked
mac and cheese I could the oven on this
is going to be so killer you're going to
see this guess what it's cheese free
with no garbage and additives and all
kinds of junk and the fake cheeses it's
not that at all Michelle says absolutely
do it again all right I'm going to have
to we're going to have to we are we are
yes the light blasts were incredible
okay so that's good to know that you
guys are open to that I mean Soulful
healing with Laurence says yes I told
someone yesterday I have a feeling it
won't be long until we're all together
globally again yeah I'm excited about
that I am really excited about that all
right let me just grind this up a little
bit here let's make some cheese Dr Fawn
security Deeds security dudes were like
the Matrix agents they were serious they
were serious security like
serious like it it was and you know they
were there for you guys so what happens
is someone asked me a friend of mine who
came to the uh event just like you guys
right and and he was like he was like
okay this he was like that that's a lot
of security I was like yeah it's for
everybody here that's the whole point we
we have like 100 security guys because I
wanted to make sure everybody was safe
that's the whole point it's security
guys going down the lines with security
guys looking out for people making sure
they were safe making sure nothing would
happen to them cuz that's the whole
point you know like I had a couple guys
for me but I made sure that there was a
lot of guys there for everyone that was
the whole point security was one of the
top requests from the community the
medical me Community were like is there
going to be security is there going to
be security so we brought on dozens and
dozens of security guys they were off
duty cops they were like heavy duty
Marshals and they were there to protect
the medical medium Community I had my
couple of guys but they were there to
protect the community so it was really
really cool really cool all right let's
get this uh going right here hey we're
back to this this is
amazing all
right I'm going to get ready and put a
little water in here too okay I know I'm
going to have to do that
yep Lisa G yes let's do it again you sfc
and your team did an amazing job at the
event okay summer the event was life
changing in a way that I don't think I
will ever be able to explain my daughter
and I will be forever
grateful it was that special I know it
was that special I prayed I prayed that
the Angels would be there I
prayed that it would go as beautiful as
it
did
um I talked to S so to make sure the
light blasts were extremely powerful and
potent like extremely powerful and
potent I made sure
that that you know we were on we're on
target there with the light blasts okay
this is actually looking really really
good I'm just going to give this
another another little blend
here
okay okay now what I'm going to do is
mix this in a huge
Bowl you guys spirit with me right here
okay I want to get the pasta in a big
bowl I want to mix it in here and then
put it back in the
tray there we go I need a really big
bowl for this mixed
job
nice here we go we got the cheese going
as well we're looking good this is the
color of the cheese that I like for my
baked mac and cheese like I said you can
make it darker you can get that really
dark cheddar if you want lra 144 great
number right there 14 144 amazing number
please yes I will be there
awesome I hold you to that I hold you to
that I hope you you'll be there Dino
Rubio so happy to see you again live
live live live live we're
live yep incredible you guys all right
cheese is done okay I'm going to mix
this cheese in here boom okay you guys
just just bear with me a second we're
just playing some G some games here with
this all right let me move
this okay let me get this bowl here I
just want Tik Tok to see this I want you
guys on Tik Tok to see this you know
let's get the cheese mixture in
here all
right all right that's
good okay I just want to scoop some of
this cheese out if you guys are okay
with
this all
right um give me a two seconds we still
got some stuff to talk about if you guys
are up to doing that again we're going
to do it again then okay we are and I
got some really good thoughts about how
we can do it and how incredible it could
be how amazing it's going to be if you
thought this last one was incredible and
Angelic and Powerful can you
imagine all right
lah can the total immune blend from bimy
be used for the time shock therapy for
the time shock therapy okay I just saw
that there I mean I don't use it for
that Colorado where Colorado colonics in
detox center the first class toilets
were
awesome okay can I talk about that a
little bit cuz you know how every now
and then I'll I'll you know talk toilet
talk right but it's usually about bugs
and stuff and things we can catch in
toilets my concern
was okay so I want to show you here I'm
mixing this mac and cheese right now cuz
it's real this is this might be the best
one I've ever made because I mean I'm
looking at it right now and this is epic
right here
epic now on the on the toilet talk so
let me just get this in the oven and I
will'll go into there look at that look
at the strings this is really incredible
do you guys see this am I am I just
seeing it am I am I seeing it you're not
like do you guys see this right this is
the best big macaroni and cheese
I'm like what come on all right I think
we're good I mean come
on
seriously all right let's get this in
the oven but we need this we need the
tray
okay all right let's knock this
in okay and you guys the pasta is not
overcooked it's not how cool is that how
great
all right all
right let's not get this Yep this last
bowl it's intense yeah there we go nice
okay all
right let's get this in here let's Let
It settle in a little
bit in the oven it goes I'm not putting
tin foil on top I'm
not don't put Al aluminum foil on top
you definitely don't put aluminum foil
on top you see this it's going right in
the oven right now just give me a second
you guys can you see this on Rumble in
YouTube right here
or it's in
there woo baked mac and cheese in the
oven right now you guys know how I've
always talked about like toilets and
everything and I talked about great deal
and great length in the brain saver book
about when you use public bathrooms how
to be careful right how how I said put a
little just a sheet on top first of all
flush the toilet a couple of times
before you even sit down on there okay
and then put a sheet of toilet paper on
top of the water so you don't get that
water splashing up inside of you right
all the things that I've talked about
and and a go in detail in brain saer so
if you don't have the book get the book
but check this out right the toilets at
the event let's get into the a little
bit so the reason why they were first
class like
billionaire you know
toilets the reason why there were
toilets that you know like the top
billionaires on the planet probably
would use that an event and then again I
have no idea what they would use like
that if they would the reason why they
were that amazing is because I was
concerned because we're talking about
chronic illness we're talking about the
people in the medical medium community
and do I want the people in the medical
medum community stuffed in those tiny
little cheap pieces
portons do you think I want like the mm
Community stuffed in these little tiny
chemical bound highly toxic
chemical crap like dirty nasty portons
right that everybody uses in all the
events including burning man you think
with Burning Man the amount of money
people pay to go and do that Burning Man
thing you think like to get tickets you
think they would put a better bathroom
in burning man no they have people going
a bathroom in the field in the mud
that's where they're going to bathroom
over there right they're going to the
bathroom in buckets so so basically what
I'm trying to say here is instead of
using those really just those little
portons that are stinky and they're
toxic as hell and I got a lot of people
in the medical meme Community have
nervous system issues that they're
healing from all that
stuff you think I want them you
guys think I want everybody breathing in
highly toxic
chemical soups that are in those tiny
little portons and you're bumping into
the walls and you're banging your head
in there and you're dropping crap in the
seat down into the toilet no didn't want
to do it I wanted to make sure they were
Top Dog
topnotch big time topnotch and so I
wanted to make sure you guys had the
right kind see the right
right toilets all right all right I love
toilet talk but we got to roll the
recipe is in the brain saer protocols by
the way someone was just asking me that
I saw that right there okay it's in here
mac and cheese it's in the oven right
now that's in the oven right now baking
now I'm going to make a salad too we
going to talk about some other stuff as
well
right look long story short I wanted to
make sure that seriously there was like
really high quality top tier bathrooms
for the medical medum community for a
billion reasons because I worry about
the people in the community your health
and wellness I mean how can you do like
something like this and just cram
everybody in the worst bathroom
situation there is no it wasn't going to
happen so I can't say enough about it
but thank you for mentioning it thank
you because I
forgot I'm going to have an announcement
soon make sure you are on the medical
medium
newsletter I repeat going to have an
announcement soon make sure you're on
the medical medium newsletter seriously
because yeah I'm definitely going to be
making an
announcement if you guys were at the
event God bless you seriously I know
many of you were it was really
incredible in so many ways what did you
would tell me you guys were you there
for the light blast did you get hit by
the Light BL bl by S so's light blast
that's what I want to ask you were you
there because that light blast expanded
beyond the park and it went literally
beyond the park ass said it was a very
strong one there were multiple ones they
went beyond the park it hit the lines I
talked to somebody that was in the line
since 7:00 a.m. 7 in the morning okay
and she told me that she was hit by the
Light blast in the line and she wasn't
even in the park she was hit by the
Light blast okay so let me move some
stuff over and make some room here um
you needed to attend next time I hope
you do I really hope you do going to
move these carrots
over okay you guys I got the baked mac
cheese going there and I
am sure that's off let's start making
the salad here look at these leafy
greens I have right here it's a green
leaf lettuce love green leaf lettuce
love the taste of green leaf lettuce I
love the crunch I love it better than
Roma hands down if you can actually
choose if you have a choice if you have
the ability to choose between Romanian
and a green
leaf always go with the green leaf okay
romain's good for you it's a good
lettuce but it doesn't have what green
leaf has it's a stronger lettuce meaning
it's better for you the melage
okay mucilage in that
stem is a lot more medicinal and that's
important too so the medicine is in the
stem right there the base of it right
there's a lot of medicine in there so
it's not just in the greens with all the
vitamins and the
nutrients and the phy chemical compounds
and
everything right here in the green leaf
lettuce is that melage right there okay
and you see it the milk that milk more
more intense more medicinal so I like it
better than the Roma lettuce for that
reason so I just want to share that
there's so many things I can share and I
just never go to chance never get a
chance lightheart mama says I saw Tex
post a video of the
bathrooms I've never seen such nice
bathrooms for an event like that yeah no
they were that that amazing they were
that great Texas did post a scene in the
bathroom I think he did right when he
was sitting in the bathroom and he was
very delighted about the bathrooms as
well as I was and I think we all were
incredible homegrown healers every
detail was top Nach W you guys through
the party of the century thank you and
God bless you God bless you too
homegrown all
right let's get a salad going I think
what I'm going to do is I'm going to
ramble over here here okay IG just hang
on okay I'll try to dangle my hand out a
little bit so you know I'm here ticktock
too
yep when Tex was talking about the
bathroom when he was actually standing
he wasn't
sitting all right onion came in that um
he was actually standing not sitting he
used the garlic here put it there
okay um so I want you to know that
an extremely respectful
way all
right
yep but I did I did my video in the
bathroom too and posted it I
didn't I
didn't all right you guys can I just
check on the baked mac and cheese cuz I
got that sucker going at 400 in the oven
I want to make sure I'm not doing
anything where it's like oo whoa yep yep
that's cooking it is Jessica I was
impressed with the
parking links you sent us so we can find
parking I was worried I was cuz I just
wanted it all good for you guys ingred I
got hit by the Light blast felt it in
the gut
I was standing in the line outside the
park incredible
incredible you know what happened to is
s so made sure the light blast expanded
and was really potent and
Powerful Clans Cafe over there in IG yes
got the late blast and I felt it first
in line outside the park in line for 5
and 1 half hours God bless you it was
the best explanation points got a second
you know I got to tell you something too
um so you guys are totally open to doing
it again then got a second light blast
in the park my lungs felt
better whoa after my lungs felt better
after that is incredible truly all right
all
right move
this okay let's get a salad going so
what I'm going to do is get some lettuce
in here let me break it up
now you can chop it up you can break it
up with your hands I usually chop it I'm
going to break it
up I'm also going to keep an eye on that
mac and cheese in the oven right there
wo aw's bar grill is it open okay just
tearing up some lettuce right
here going to make a really nice salad I
have some Tomatoes here I got some
cucumbers as well I mean you could put
really anything you want in your salad
right you can just be like look all I
have is what I have in the fridge I
can't get to the store so I'm going to
use it that's fine Jennifer L said
Anthony I noticed more of my color
coming back from Vio when I got home I
couldnot wait for the next one I have to
tell you
guys I'm I'm down for the next
one and we're going to make sure we hit
those light blasts real
hard I just want you guys moving forward
I want you moving forward I want you
guys
better seriously though I gotta I gotta
just thank you for being there at that
event it was
insane I mean the amount of people that
were there you guys saw that
right I mean they're
helicopters like Culver City never seen
anything like
that and the and the police department
the fire department never seen anything
like that in Culver City
that was that was just
nuts all right you guys I'm just
chopping up some lettuce breaking it up
there you go making it nice and
fluffy yep and then the mac and cheese
is baking in the oven how toasty do you
want your mac and cheese on top do you
like it when it burns a little you like
it when it's brown and toasty like what
what's the way you like mac and cheese
okay because I like it a little bit more
crunchy on top just a little bit more
you know kind of a little bit more on
the edge of like burnt right like that's
the way I like it comfort food wise nice
Bowl isn't it it's a really nice
Bowl you love the bowl too amazing Cold
Light
spring I I listen I'm happy that you're
happy that we streamed it live Cold
Light spring I'm glad that you're happy
about that seriously that's what we did
we streamed it live right right yeah
because you know that's what we that's
what we wanted to do all right okay that
baked mac and cheese has got a little
bit more time it's got a little bit more
time
there so what I'm going to do is break
up a little bit more lettuce here we
go we streamed it
live if you ever want to catch that you
can catch it on YouTube on my YouTube
channel right you can find it under
video under video and you'll see that
the whole thing was streamed
live like almost every bit of
it okay there we
go I'm just getting the Pieces Just
Right I just didn't want to dice and
chop these and I didn't want to do that
okay here we go there we go I wanted
good siiz pieces I wanted it light and
fluffy
okay there we go there we go just take a
look right there always wash everything
well always wash stuff good I washed the
lemons because they didn't come off the
tree didn't come off of the tree in my
backyard or anything so I I washed the
lemons I washed the lettuce really well
I did I know a lot of people don't do
that okay I washed the dill really well
I washed the tomatoes I wash the
Cucumbers I wash the zucchini really
well radishes I might throw a few of
those in there I even wash the outside
of the mangoes if I'm going to use any
of
that but there's a lot of stuff out
there like this leria going around it's
knocking people's socks off man it is
hitting people hard like there's a leria
outbreak it's just out there it's on
food you got to be careful and it's it's
it's been rough for a lot of people who
get who get actually poisoned by that
stuff so what I like to do is I like to
wash stuff good maybe I'll actually do
do something on just that alone where
we're just sitting there washing I'll
angle the cameras to the sink one day
and I'll just wash the crap out of a ton
of different things that be like this is
how you wash a radish this is how you
wash lettuce this is how you wash kale
this is how you wash parley right I'll
show you guys how to do it and that's
that's that's what we'll you know we'll
do okay um and if you can stand just
seeing me standing at of sink for a
couple of hours on a live then that's
what we'll do let me check the mac and
cheese all right opening here just to
double check yeah coming out nice woo
it's getting Brown and toasty on the top
but I want to give it a little bit more
time all right get some fixings going
you guys okay with some cucumber let me
do a peel here all right okay topic of
today is chronically sick chronic
illness that's the topic of today first
thing I want to say in that topic is if
you don't know what is wrong with you if
you don't know how you got
sick if you don't know
that it's going to be a long road a long
and windy road really long and windy
okay A lot of people are so sick that
even when they find out what's wrong
with them through medical medum
information they still need to take time
to heal because they've been sick for so
long was so
bad it is a long windy road especially
if you don't know how you got sick
what's wrong if you don't know
that man it can be one heck of a long
road if you know what's wrong you're
going to Quicken that healing process
you're going to get there some people
get there real quick if you know what's
going on and and this matters what I'm
saying you know I know there's talk out
there people saying viruses don't exist
viruses every time I hear someone else
say that out there I'm like really
really are you really going to are you
really going to go around saying that
out there and a lot of people say that
viruses don't exist they don't they take
a new age a new age you know view at it
and they're like viruses aren't wild why
people are sick or you or it's somebody
that's not even doing a new age version
of it they're just somebody that's like
it's all about detoxing cleansing and
toxins everybody's sick just because of
toxins toxins toxins there's no viruses
viruses don't
exist if you get tricked into viruses
don't exist if you get brainwashed into
viruses don't exist and you're sick it's
going to be a hard
Road A Hard Road all
right because let me tell you something
they do exist herpy simplex one one
herpes simplex 2 they do exist it is
real it is
real I'm going to make
a zucchini dressing in a bit so I'm just
preparing
this and those aren't the only viruses
stress and emotional turmoil can lower
the immune system allowing viruses to
increase their power increase their
ability to spread and proliferate stress
hardships right emotional
turmoil it can lower the immune system
for viruses to break out viruses to
Surge
okay all right I've always talked about
this for years I've talked about it in
the books and so forth check in the mac
and cheese one more time don't want it
burnt burnt I just want it nice and
toasty Brown on the top and we're almost
there just about ready all right
it's got some tomatoes on the salad you
guys don't mind okay so yeah so what
you'll find you'll find a lot of people
like oh viruses don't exist it's just a
de or or you'll find something like it's
just a DNA strand it's R you know RNA
strand that's all it is it's just a
strand of something and that's what
people say too they'll be like you know
it's not it's not really a virus cell
it's not a virus but it is viruses are
viral cells they like to eat
okay they Thrive they like to thrive in
environments that they can eat toxic
heavy metals they can not only eat toxic
heavy metals but they can eat all kinds
of poisons and different kinds of foods
that viruses like okay viruses are real
they eat they're hungry they want to
live
retroviruses also want to live viruses
technically do not want to kill the
host viruses don't do not viruses would
prefer that you stay viruses would
prefer that you stay relatively healthy
so you can be a super
spreader you
know so you can spread Epstein
bar and spread it far and wide viruses
want you to be strong enough and healthy
enough like a lot of people are out
there as they're spreading the viruses
setala virus hhv6 hhv7 herpes simplex 1
herp Simplex 2 shingles viruses want
people to be healthy enough to just
spread Spread spread because the viruses
want to live live live viruses don't
want to
die they
don't viruses are are lab creat need it
engineered they're
engineered right in the labs and some
are engineered in the labs to kill
people right but even over time when
it's been engineered in the lab to kill
people as the virus goes through enough
people it stops killing
people doesn't kill them as fast even if
they're engineered to kill people the
viruses don't end up killing as many
people ver you know getting to a point
where they don't even kill hardly
anybody because the virus ends up
wanting to live forever Just Like a
person wants to live
forever but you'll see out there there's
like a lot of new age thought and the
new age thought is viruses aren't real
they don't exist it's all these other
reasons why people are sick yeah you
keep on thinking that
that is such a trap that is such a trap
walking along here that's a trap boom
you're
down that's a trap that's a tiger
snare I'd say like I don't know three
more minutes maybe three more minutes on
that I'm going to pop some cucumber on
this okay so I'm not going to do the
whole circles I'm going to do like the
half
Moons okay
and shingles can cause somebody the
worst debilitating pain shingles can
make somebody so miserable they don't
even want to live
anymore epine bar can create a situation
in people where they got Ms multiple
sceris diagnosis or they get a you know
fibro diagnosis an RA
diagnosis okay herpes simplex well that
can do a lot of things can get into the
brain stem it can get into the central
nervous system in so many ways Herby
simplex one two the point is is that
these viruses live in everybody they sit
there they percolate they want to be
spread they want to live and they also
you know keep the person miserable over
time
and so knowing how to heal is knowing
how to pulverize and beat those viruses
to
death that's the key it's not so much
the key as detoxing detoxing detoxing
detoxing you know that that's that's a
that's a word that many people in the
health movement in the last 40 years
said because they didn't know anybody
was sick with viruses they didn't know
anybody was sick with viruses the
hygienic movement is a prime example of
how they had no idea no conception that
viruses were causing any of the illness
I know because I talked about I talk to
Natural hygienist throughout the years
holistic hygienists the movement doctors
and people in the health field for the
last 40 years I've talked to many they
had no clue what caused his illness at
all besides oh the person's toxic the
person's toxic take this rout do this
try this the person's to water fast for
three weeks the person's toxic that'll
fix them you know many people water fast
for 3 weeks came out of that water fast
sicker than ever or came out of that
water fast and just got sick all over
again but worse than they ever did
because the water fast wasn't killing
the viruses it wasn't cleaning up the
viruses all right let's see if I can get
that out right
there all right I'd say we're good it's
brown it's toasty I'm going to grab this
oven thing right
and I'm going to grab this here to all
right hang on you
guys I'm a menace in the kitchen
that's what
happens I think I'm going to put this
right
here I'm going to put this right here
okay so maybe I can even show you too
that's the baked mac and cheese right
there and that's insane okay all
right that's insane I'm going to lower
that down a little bit on IG there you
go YouTube Rumble there you go Tik Tok
there you go twitch there you go
all
right okay all
right we got that right there let's cool
that down let's finish up the
solid okay you guys don't
mind nice you know I'm going to crack
into that right you know you know I'm
going to crack into that put this over
here all right
let's make sure we got everything else
on the salad that we need I think we're
going to do it I could put mango on here
because I have them here but maybe I
won't I let's put some radishes on here
you guys don't mind can I cut a couple
of radishes real quick right I just cut
the root off of the radish of course you
could eat it if you want but I do cut
the little root off right there I mean
you might like chewing on the
root but but your guest might not like
it your guest might be sticking a fork
in that and being like what is this it's
chew
what's going on here so I'm just
preparing a few
radishes I've been in the health scene
for a long
time very long
time not
by a wanting to or that's what I want to
do I was forced into it at a young age
AG starting at 4 years
old with Spirit of
compassion who I argued with many many
many a
time because of it
all and what I have discovered was
nobody knew viruses were behind all the
symptoms conditions neurological
symptoms all the different illnesses
they had no
idea toxins
were the only thing anyone ever said and
that was
it so I'm going to slice up some of
these radishes I'm doing half Boons on
them if you guys are okay there we
go Spirit of compassion told me that the
viruses are a huge part it's not just
toxins and what toxins it's another
thing too back years ago 20 30 years ago
it was just toxins do it water fast cuz
it was just
toxins what
toxins no one knew toxic heavy metals
were giving people all the different
symptoms and conditions that they've
learned about with the medical medium
books today that they poached and you
know go around and even though there's
no studies behind it because it comes
from mm
info but the point I'm trying to say is
I see people still stuck in the mud out
there they're sick they ain't never
going to heal they ain't
and it's sad because they think viruses
don't exist or they think a water fast
is going to fix everything and meanwhile
they're not left with the correct
information after they recover from a
water fast this is just one example or
maybe they think they need a cold plunge
themselves
crazy while they're damaging their
adrenals people want quick fixes man
they want quick fixes but the truth is
they don't know why they're sick
and you have to know why you're sick you
got to know when metals are causing the
problems when it really is Metals that's
right you have to know when it's viruses
and it's really viruses and you have to
know other stuff too Marg says it feels
like everything else has forgotten about
health
history only aw is talking is talking to
us about what trends were out there and
crazy thoughts that's true I don't see
anybody talking about it out there
because a lot of people in Health right
now on social social media they're all
the people on social media they're all
new most of them are new brand new off
the press they got into it six years ago
four years ago three years ago two years
ago last year and they're just shouting
out stuff and you know and the whole bit
but they don't know they don't know the
history they don't know what happened
and then there's bacteria turning into
Super
bugs there's that too all right we got
some
radishes there's strep
right but you know the industry thought
strep only did a certain thing but no
does a lot more causes a lot more
problems all
right how does that look so
far I like this bowl too tiktock you
guys see that IG you guys see that right
there YouTube you guys see that
right deficiencies are a problem as well
they are but deficiencies
don't explain it all on how somebody's
sick and how they have viral
inflammation and bacterial you know
infections low grade and low grade and
high grade and the differences between
low grade and high grade and all of that
right I want to make a dressing if you
guys are okay with
that okay that is cooling down the mac
and cheese you guys just got on
here just want to show you right here
it's cooling down enough for me to take
my hands and actually really put it on
here show you
guys there it is can't wait to crack
into
it all right I'm going to get a blender
over here but I'm going to grab this
first right
here okay three cups raw peeled DIC
zucchini I'm going to peel these
zucchinis right
now really quick
is what I'm going to do boom so all
right and then keep this in mind okay so
it happens all over again you think
you're getting somewhere and you think
you're getting the information out there
you think people are are getting the
information they need and then boom
viruses don't exist anymore oh viruses
don't eat
anything I think one of the most
powerful powerful pieces of information
to actually use to
is knowing that a bug eats something and
then learning what the bug eats so you
can withhold that certain food from the
bug and when you can withhold that food
from the bug like
cheese I've never ripped apart the whole
dairy industry I've never done the whole
radical vegan thing where the vegans
like they get so crazy they burn down
buildings you know right I'm not I'm not
whatever I'm not p on vegans that's not
it it's the reason why s
so went for the
cheese the dairy and said you can't have
that in if you're sick with these bugs
these certain viruses because certain
viruses will feed on that Dairy and feed
on that cheese okay it's not because of
any other reason you can be plant-based
vegan doing medical medium using the
tools in healing I said this so many
times and you could be animal protein
you using medical medium tools and
healing but there's certain things that
are critical if you're sick with chronic
fatigue if you're sick with all the
different conditions and
symptoms it's knowing that cheese will
feed a bug now here's the deal if you
get told well cheese isn't good for you
it's inflammatory maybe because they
learned it's inflammatory from medical
medum information because remember Dairy
wasn't inflammatory all these years
that's mm info Dari was not inflammatory
it it was just it was a vegetarian thing
vegetarians ate Dairy cuz Dairy was
healthy supposedly right healthy nobody
knew nobody knew that Dairy fed bugs
that Dairy feeds viruses that's medical
meme info but when you learn that piece
of powerful information it really keeps
you from eating not eating the dairy in
that moment and then somebody will say
I'm going to go and punish medical
medium out there and talk crap about him
and I'm going to show like a cheese dish
and say I'm not restricted medical
medium restricts everybody from eating
cheese I can eat cheese right here look
sure of course you can but if you got
chronic sickness and illness and you got
MS symptoms and you got neurological
Lyme symptoms and you got every symptom
ALS symptom under the all kinds of Under
the
Sun all
kinds right you're going to want to stay
away from the cheese and when you learn
why you should stay away from the
cheese boom you can move forward it's so
important and then hey you get yourself
better you get rid of the bugs you kill
off those viruses you learn how to do it
through medical medum information you
pulverize and destroy those bugs and
they leave your system yes they detox
out of your system once you kill them
and you want to eat a piece of cheese
because you had your heart set on it
then you eat a piece of cheese
whatever all right I'm going
to pop some zucchinis in here this is
one right
here I'm taking these skins and moving
them
over you saw what this floor looked like
right now everything just went on Amanda
says I never felt right with dairy but
then I got addicted to ice cream chronic
UTI disappeared as soon as I eliminated
the dairy and other no Foods the reason
why is because the dairy was feeding the
strep that creates the UTI that's how it
works but nobody knew that it didn't
exist never existed out there it's mm
info mm published info all right so I'm
going to chop and
dice senini it's going to go in here
okay I'm going to just make sure I do
this a little bit here oh these bikinis
look good they look good let's pop these
in here you guys
okay going to make a really nice
dressing okay now we're looking at three
cups so I think I'm going to go a little
bit more really quick just a little bit
more in this and then we're going to put
some lemon juice in there and a whole
bunch of other stuff I can't wait to dig
into that mac and
cheese that's
right did I tell you it's a pee and
lentil
pasta did I tell you
that Teresa I miss those sessions with
you over there on
YouTube the
resta all
right all right let's hope this Blends
up
okay and let's hope I chop these up
small enough for the
blender yep okay guys
I'm going to take this right here do you
mind I'm going to do this boom boom
boom one soldier went
down right come to
Maine oh
Maine it's a beautiful place people who
are new
right okay um for people that are new
just know that you should get on my
email list when you can my newsletter
list and everything so you know what's
going on and everything that's happening
um all
right let's keep on going right here we
got this in here okay we need three
tablespoons of lemon juice from these
lemons medical.com you can find it there
let's get this lemon juice going
here um I think I'm going to need every
one of these lemons this is crazy but
you know what don't underestimate the
power of these small lemons whatever you
do don't shake a stick at
it okay you guys I leave exclusive
messages on telegram did you know
that exclusive messages on telegram okay
right
t.me slmed
medium all right let's get a little Bowl
here let's squeeze
some lemon in
here check out the medical medum podcast
you might be aware there's been a lot of
plotter stuff on the medical Me podcast
lately
you might be
aware keep in mind if if it's if it's um
something you're not interested in keep
in mind there's a lot of people that
were really badly hurt it's there for
them we have to look out for everybody
in the
community so have some
patience but I also I also see a lot of
people were so happy so happy
to I know everybody wants they wants you
know health information out of me I
totally understand that I also have
health podcasts coming out soon and
there's lots of health podcasts on the
medical me and podcast so check them out
when you get a
chance yep David says podcasts are
amazing thanks
Amber yeah incredible David on
YouTube I know you said plot
cast yep
that's
right Robin says my jaw dropped hearing
about the lies on the plotter podcasts
glad the truth is getting out there to
combat the
lies so am
I I am
too okay I think I'm I'm getting
probably close to enough lemon juice
here and then we should be
good okay there we go
all right Lana says the plotter episodes
are better than Netflix but it's sad
that this is happening I'm just glad
you're you're
listening
okay all right you guys I'm going to
just run this lemon juice right through
here YouTube and Rumble you can watch
them see all the evidence
for the ones that need to see the
evidence listen educating myself said
listen to the cat story educating
myself I read your comments a lot I do
and I even said okay to myself I hope
educating myself listens to the cat
story all
right I kid you not I kid you not
I'm not I'm not just saying that all
right you guys let's get the rest of
this in here and we're good we need some
garlic powder really quick pop that
in French dressing little bit of garlic
powder in there boom we need um some Cho
parsley in there let's pop that in there
okay okay chop parsley got that in there
okay we need some chopped Dill in there
all right one and 1/ half tablespoons
chop
Dill nice got that in there it's
important to know the detail so when
someone out there is spreading lies to
your friends and family you want to know
how to
respond that's in regards to plotter
stuff all right I think I have what I
need in here let's blend it up
I think what I'm going to do
is think I'm going to bring a blender up
over
here you know on on Tik Tok and um IG
you probably only see so much right and
so you don't see all of my different
like stuff where stuff drops dropping on
the floor everywhere you guys on YouTube
and Rumble you're probably watching a
mess happen over here
indeed let's see if this thing can blend
now I'm going to blend this for real
let's do
[Music]
it okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't want it too watery so so I'm
going to have patience here and just
blend am I
yelling
[Music]
nice I did less Chini than the recipe
called for
[Music]
all
right all right
now all right
there we go so it's a little bit more on
the green side this dressing you can
actually add more zucchini and it
lighten it up but I think I'm going to
do that why not I'm actually going to do
that you put this here for a
second give it that
color I have some guests coming over and
the guests I want to try to
impress I can try to impress them so I'm
going to put another zucchini in there
guys I'm over here just just bear with
me I'm
washing a
zucchini as we
speak there we
go
okay all right so I'm going to wash the
zucchini I already did I'm going
to carve out a couple of little things
in here I'm going to carve out the
sticker just going to like carve it off
right
there going to take the butt off and the
head part off looking for any kind of
other stuff here we go now I'm just
going to peel
this this one I'm going to peel really
really down to the
bone and I'm going to add this into the
dressing there we go
all
right so back to the viral talk it's a
big part of why people are sick not the
only reason but a big
part there we go all
right I'll pop this in here as well what
I'm going to
do a little bit more
lemon here we go I want a bigger
dressing cuz I have a feeling that salad
is so
big that I just want a little bit
more
y and
me see
here do is add a little bit more
lemon when you do a salad this big you
might have somebody that like has a lot
of dressing and they're like did you
make enough where's the rest of it now
the the um dill and the parsley you want
to chop up and throw kind of into it
later I blended it in
there we
go
nice all right let's put a lid on it you
guys I can't wait to crack into that mac
and cheese tell you right
now you go
make a little
B there we go
this
one all right just going to clean up a
little bit
all
right you guys I'm going to pour a
little bit of this on the
salad or actually have it on the side is
what I'm going to do get a new bow
here can I put this right here
chop up a little dill and put it on
top sprinkle a little bit on top of
here grab a
spoon okay so here's a dressing now what
happens is when you have guests they may
want the dressing on the side they may
not want it all put on top of your salad
and mixed in so I just did a side one
right here as you can see okay um and
then somebody can put it on their salad
as they wish that's a great way of doing
it I have to do it that way cuz I'm not
sure how everybody's going to want to
have
it versus me just dumping it on like I
like to do okay so just wanted to show
you guys
that okay so that's a salad I'm going to
put a little dressing on there um I
think I'm going to make I think I'm
going to put
that a bowl for
myself a glass
bowl oh here we
go oo
yeah yep all right you guys check this
out okay
all
right okay some mac and cheese I'm going
to put it in this dish right
here okay going to
use here now you can do it in you know
in this
situation oh this is so perfect this is
the
craziest version I've ever made of it
so I'm going to scoop some out and get
it in this dish right
here there we go it's got such such an
unbelievable color to it not just a
great color but it's actually perfect
it's moist inside so it's not dried out
there's nothing worse than mac and
cheese it's so dried
out so I'm going to put it all on one
side here then I'm going to put a salad
over on this side all right so let me
just get more over
here there we
go still hot so it's actually piping
hot I don't know if you guys like mac
and cheese do you woo that baby's hot
underneath there I'm going to do
this you know what
there are people out there that don't
like mac and cheese I
mean there's a lot of people out there
that don't like it all right there we go
and I'm going to put some of this part
here right on top nice and
crispy there we go all
right and then I'm going to put some
salad on the side
too over here
okay going to get some nice green salad
here with the
tomatoes right here just like this
that's incredible I put a lot of mac and
cheese on in there on
purpose looks so
good so I think it's the best one I've
ever
done I don't know how how that happened
but it did but you
know it's amazing
I didn't put onion on there
but
nice love it if you want to
present okay
and you want it to look
good there you
go okay
there we
go well that's what we're talking about
right
there yep best ever
indeed thank you for saying that I can't
believe you think that incredible that
will be your plate Courtney okay yep
lovely presentation I tried my best you
know so that's it right there what do
you guys think on Tik Tok What do you
guys think on YouTube I what do you guys
think right there it is
incredible boom amazing can I try
some are you guys okay if I try
some okay I'm just going to just try a
little bit of it and see what we got
here
insane let say
woo that's amazing
well done guys
incredible all
right I will see you guys next time I'm
going to
tank and have some yummy food hope you
guys are doing good I'm inspired to do
another event at some point so just keep
a lookout make sure you're on my email
list right newsletter and a medical
medium.com check out my telegram I'm
leaving um messages there okay so always
check that out as well did you hear the
cricket one that was really really
special um all right you guys amazing I
will see you next
time and uh I love