I'm so blown away at the brain saver
books
that I'm reading them going through them
and it's just mind-boggling how much
information coming from spiritual
compassion that just blows my mind
greatest books of all time
swear to God
last night
four bed
I was praying to God okay and
was bypassing Spirit of compassion said
you know I just I gotta do some prayers
here and I was saying how grateful I was
because
regardless of how much work it was and
how much work it is and how much
crap I have to face and take from doing
it because no one wants the industries
don't want these books out
that's evident we know that and
it's incredible to think that this
information
came from above and to know people are
getting instant relief from the from the
brain shot therapies instant relief just
like Spirit of compassion told me and
just like instant relief
it's just something that you just can't
even imagine to Be Alive In This Moment
In Time
to make it this far I didn't think I was
going to make it I didn't think I was
going to make it past 12. 12 years old I
just didn't you know hearing Spirit of
compassion and then all the
responsibilities I just didn't think I
would make it and I think I made it this
far
and
with all the gray in my beard and all
the brain my hair hair the things I made
made it this far and to actually be able
to receive that information not lose my
mind doing it
and put in 20-hour days
sacrifice everything I could possibly
sacrifice
I didn't shower for three months I mean
just whatever it's like you just
I just ate and slept in it right slept
two hours and then worked and ate in it
and just whatever the thing I got this
far in being able to somehow survive and
get these unbelievable books the
greatest books of all time in
alternative and conventional medicine
history hands down it will be they are
I'm allowed to say it because it's my
opinion because Spirit of compassion
gave me the information and I could
judge I could judge that information
and
what I'm seeing in these books and what
I'm seeing what's happening with you
guys you're you're taking on these books
and it's incredible to watch this
it's just I mean I I actually was crying
this morning a little bit because I
can't believe with joy joy you know and
everything
and I can't believe like
like
I don't know I don't have words for the
first time what am I gonna say
but the brain shot therapies is just one
one aspect of these incredible books
today I'm talking about supplements that
are bad for the brain and it's in the
brain saver books oh by the way you guys
I don't control the pricing at Amazon
but the books are 40 off on Amazon right
now right now they're 40 off I'm like
blown away and so I got friends that are
buying another set because they ordered
the first set now they're buying another
set
for gifts for presents for for the
holidays for everything and then for
birthdays whatever they're buying more
books it's incredible and 40 off on
Amazon right now it's just what
incredible the book's 29 the brand saver
looks 29 the other book The protocol
book The protocol book is twenty seven
dollars it's like what
um it costs more to print them they're
heavy books it cost a lot of money to
put these books it's full color photos
it's glossy paper it's the whole bit
it's incredible to know this anyway I
just wanted to tell you guys that before
we go into today's topic
I just want to tell you I'm really
grateful I'm grateful that we're in this
lifetime together all of us right here
means the world to me and it means
everything to me and to know we're here
in this moment in time we're the
greatest information the greatest books
the greatest healing books of all time
are released and when I think about that
no no
it just gets me okay let's get into it a
little bit guys we're right now to brain
saver books this is what we're doing to
pop some books over here you guys don't
mind right got a brain in front of me
let's get going we're talking about
supplements good supplements bad
supplements the whole bit a little bit
this is important because what people
don't realize
is that they're on a lot of stuff that's
slowing them down tipping the scale the
wrong way it's tipping the scale the
wrong way and they don't know it and
that's something that happens to people
every day they're trying to heal they're
trying to heal and then they're they're
brainwashed by trendy crap out there and
they become just brainwashed and it's
just like get me in those bad
supplements give me those bad
supplements bad supplements bad
supplements hurting my brain I'm trying
to heal trying to heal bad supplements
give me those bad supplements bad
supplements what no doctor give me bad
supplement friend give me bad
supplements oh online's bad supplements
supplements it's crazy so
yeah I'll tell you
okay
let's get into here a little bit
brain betrayer supplements right there
we're in protocols book today we're in
that big old Bible right there so we're
in here okay let's talk about a little
bit you guys glad you guys are coming on
I'm ready to do it I'm ready let's go
brain betrayer supplements check this
out just hear me out these supplements
fall into four main categories
four main categories
first category
problematic and damaging supplements
problematic
and damaging supplements that's one
category right there
second category mildly problematic
supplements problematic still right to
the brain mildly problematic
third category overrated or over used
supplements
overrated or overused
fourth category quality concerns
supplements where it's especially
important to seek out high quality forms
because they're frequently produced with
low quality ingredients or problematic
additives such as preservatives okay
let's get into a little bit
I'm going to talk about the problematic
and damaging category right now so I'm
going to give you a little bit of a list
about the problematic and damaging
alkaline ionizer water machines
apple cider vinegar
apple cider vinegar supplements taken
internally
Bentonite and other Clays taken
remember this is problematic and
damaging
caffeine-based energy supplements
charcoal taken internally
you'll hear it just go online and post
something I'm taking charcoal I'm taking
charcoal I'm taking charcoal I'm like
you have no idea I'm going to read a
little bit about this stuff just a
little bit
Chlorella chlorella problematic and
damaging
chlorine dioxide
that's sodium chloride
cod liver oil and shark liver oil
remember the shark liver oil thing
there's still some people out there I'm
taking my Shark liver oil capsules right
here my shark live my Straight Mercury
oil I'm taking my Straight Mercury oil
capsules that's what I'm doing right
here
shark liver oil oh I'm gonna take my
Straight Mercury capsules right here
because I I was told it's it's a trend
out there
cod liver oil right
colostrum remember um if you guys just
came on here I'm reading problematic and
damaging supplements I just want you to
know where I'm at brain saver protocols
40 off amazon.com right now 40 off us
amazon.com four the books are both 40
off
29.27 dollars
I mean it kind of hits a sore spot for
me a little bit because it costs so much
more to make that book but I will tell
you I don't care I just want you to have
it I don't control the pricing Amazon
did
God bless them for doing okay
Dear Antler also called deer velvet
antler velvet you're the deer antler
thing remember we're in the problematic
and damaging supplement section of brain
saver okay
diatomaceous earth
how many people just take some
diatomaceous earth that'll fix you
that'll screw you up bad
digestive bitters
yeah digestive bitter so I'm taking my
digestive bitters here taking my
digestive bitters oh good luck tip to
scale the wrong way sorry
just keep tipping the scale the wrong
way
essential oils taken internally
don't get mad at me I know where's my
kick me sign I know I have a kick me
sign on the back of my back
on the back of me everybody's gonna be
freaking out about the essential oils
they're just gonna be freaking out
essential oils taken internally not a
good thing
essential oils taken internally
fat burners
fat burners people don't even know
they're like I'm taking this fat burner
fish oil and krill oil uh-huh uh-huh how
many people are in the fish oil and
krill oil oh my doctor says this Grill
oil is real good this practitioner saw
in line is krill oil I'm Gonna Keep on
taking my krill oil
dioxins poisons Mercury chemical I'm
just going to take my krill oil
gut powder Blends now remember I'm in
the problematic and damaging part of the
supplement section that's what this
Live's all about I am in the books right
here
these books are absolutely incredible
let's just go here okay
where are we where are we gut powder
Blends gut powder Blends gut powder
Blends out there
annihilate the intestinal tract line
it's a man-made concoction of scratchy
crap that they don't even know works or
not go through the intestinal tract and
irritates everything I'll talk about it
a little bit herbal tinctures and
alcohol yes herbal tinctures no I love
herbs love love love herbs
but I'm talking about herbal tinctures
and alcohol we're in the problematic and
damaging section in protocols and I'm
talking venerable tinctures in alcohol
so we're talking we're doing it so let's
get into a little bit see if we got
anything else that's just that section
let's go a little bit more
we're still in that first category
problematic and damaging
so you guys you can get the books at
Barnes Noble too I think they're on sale
there at Barnes and Nobles you can get
them in bookstores you can get at the
book depositories The Book Depository
right
and you can get them at Amazon but I'm
going to tell you right now Amazon us
right now is 40 off I got friends that
are actually buying sets of books for
their family members for everybody
because they're 29 for the brand saver
27 for protocols it's insane in the
memory
okay
HCL
supplements problematic and damaging HCL
supplements I'm bringing right out of
here L-Carnitine and L arginine
mineral oil
mineral oil ready for this one mushroom
coffee with caffeine problematic
problematic no matter what you've been
sold or a bill of goods you've been sold
Focus Point says I can I can drink
turpentine right
number 22.
oyster supplements
number 23 Pearl powder I'm gonna jump
ahead
he said Focus Point said I can drink
turpentine right number 25 in the list
of problematic and damaging supplements
is turpentine
turpentine I hope you don't get mad at
me and say
screw that guy I'm off of here I'm out
of here because I like my turpentine I'm
just I'm just the messenger
a very hated one
a very hated messenger
turpentine oil Pearl powder oyster
supplements I'm doing the problematic
and damaging section oyster supplements
Pearl powder sodium bicarbonate
meaning baking soda when taken
internally in large amounts
sodium bicarbonate bad bad bad
really damages the body
whey protein powder and guess what's
last on the list but in problematic and
damaging zeolites
zeolites zeolite okay so I want to go in
there a little bit now there's so much
information here it can only cover so
much
let's talk about why let's hit the Y's a
little bit
which is going to be fun okay so I'm in
it's one thing to say it it's one thing
to be like that's bad for you that's bad
for you that's bad for you it's another
to have an explanation from above that
blows your mind
that's I mean you know
problematic and damaging supplements
let's talk about alkaline ionizer water
machines it's in that category you ready
metal plates inside these machines
corrode and oxidize over time
slowly leaching oxidized metal byproduct
and metal nanoparticles into the water
regardless of what brand of machine
oxidized metal byproduct and metal
nanoparticles eventually lead to
neurological symptoms
eventually lead to neurological symptoms
alkaline ionizer water machines are not
water purifiers their filtration is
limited water becomes dead water as it's
being deconstructed by the electricity
of these machines the water becomes
foreign to the human body that's number
one on the problematic and damaging
supplements unless they're all bad but
I'm just saying that's number one number
two number three let's move into a
couple of different ones okay
let's go with bentonite clay how many of
you guys been sucked into bentonite clay
that whole thing
bentonite clay these Clays do not remove
toxic heavy metals they are too harsh
and aggressive on the intestinal tract
lining
they act as sandpaper in your intestinal
tract
Clays irritate sensitive nerves that
connect in and around the intestinal
tract so anybody who has any kind of
condition or symptom at all does the
bentonite clay in the Clays they're
going to totally mess their system all
up like their nerves people with
sensitive or inflamed vagus nerves you
guys vagus nerves should not ingest
Clays educating myself how are you page
77 finally the explanation for
spontaneous human combustion
I am at your service
I can't take the credit because it's up
there it comes from and I'm a messenger
and received it Lisa Marie says years
ago you suggested zeolite so no more and
I've I've explained that explanation
over and over again
the only one that I recommended years
ago okay still wasn't the greatest
but it wasn't as problematic now here's
here's the thing we also didn't have
pure sources of dolls at the time or
other things that were available out
there so I was trying to give people
another little option but here's the
thing the industry changed the zeolite
industry changed zeolites that were
inedible were processed in the same
factories as the ones that were edible
the inedible ones tear up your
intestinal lining
boom real bad
so
the world changed I I have my own free
will
but the but what they do they have their
own free will
and they wanna they wanna do what they
want to do the the quality and things
and whatnot and the zeolites that's a
whole nother game I'm just telling you
what happened and so that
cross-contamination was another big part
of it along with other problems too as
everything changed
okay I never said they'd do anything but
help a tiny bit in the intestinal tract
if it's the right one there is no right
one right now
and but zeolites never travel into the
bloodstream and remove Metals out of
your brain they never did it and I never
said they did
okay so let's go a little bit further
here so I want to talk about the Clays a
little bit more get this
Bentonite
The Details Matter by the way
Bentonite Clays can also disrupt
microbiome so anybody taking the claims
and they're worried about their
microbiome they're completely
tearing their microbiome to shreds
Bentonite and other clay suffocate good
bacteria and microorganisms so if you've
got good bacteria in your gut because
it's all about good bacteria in your gut
good bacteria in your guts all you hear
out there well guess what you take the
Bentonite Clays you're gonna
tear up that good bacteria suffocate
them kill them
microorganisms that don't need oxygen
that does that don't mind being
suffocated or the bad stuff so check
this out
Bentonite and other clay suffocate good
bacteria and microorganisms and allow
bad bacteria and microorganisms to
thrive because Clays remove oxygen
inside the intestinal tract get ready
mind-blowing information here it goes
way ahead of research in science way
ahead of any anywhere out there I'm just
going to drop this bomb good bacteria
and microorganisms need higher levels of
oxygen to survive
inside our gut
that oxygen comes from your food
bad bacteria and microorganisms need
lower levels of oxygen to survive Clays
can create a chronic dehydration within
the intestinal tract raising bad
bacteria you take your Clays zeolites of
clay you take your Clays all them and
what happens is you raise your bad
bacteria
I'm not making friends
because it's not about that I have to
have the chronically ill they're back I
have to have their back
I have to look out for them
I noticed that in this world I'm just
going to just tell you right now just
heart to heart for two seconds you guys
would I witness every day and have
is
the people the gurus and all that and
the people in the health movement you
see them out there they're on podcasts
and whatever they're doing all their
thing they're on YouTube doing running
ads or whatever it is all those gurus
they're just about making friends
they'll never go the right direction in
the end because they're all about what
friends they got and what friends they
keep they don't care about the
chronically ill
they don't take risks
they steal and poach when it fits their
they still improach from mm when it fits
their narrative in the moment that they
want to do but they don't care about the
chronic Lil
I'm not about making friends I'm about
making sure you guys have what you need
anything that comes with it whatever
Tara Appleman hey so sad bentonite clay
is one of the first things I tried to
heal my gut needless to say it didn't
help it's it's the first thing that so
many people have tried okay let's go
into another area
I can't read all this there's too much
information in these books you guys 40
off right now at amazon.com 40 off when
I saw it this morning I actually yelped
actually like screamed I was like oh my
God
29 for for brand saver
27 for brain saver protocols both books
you need
okay let's hit another one
there's so many to choose from
let's see let's do a simple one
chlorella everybody chlorella Chlorella
recommended chlorella I saw it online
that's really good for me first of all
it does not bind down to toxic heavy
metals properly
let me make that clear it does not bind
onto toxic heavy metals properly
spreads toxic heavy metals into adjacent
tissue chlorella spreads toxic heavy
metals into adjacent tissue inside the
brain that's what it does
so let's just keep on eating it
chlorella does not have
oh it says something else here
accelerating brain conditions let me add
that in I'm sorry about that spreads
toxic heavy metals into adjacent tissue
accelerating brain conditions
I don't want to take chlorella if it's
going to accelerate a brain condition
chlorella does not have the ability to
remove toxic heavy metals from the body
chlorella is not antibacterial or
anti-viral rather listen to this
ready it often contains bad bacteria
resulting in foodborne illness so okay
let me just buy some chlorella and get
some foodborne illness that's just one
that's a fun one let's try to find
another fun oh Pearl powder
has been like Pearl powder Pearl powder
and this here I think this is why I this
is why so many fake stories and slander
and hits and smear attacks happen
towards me
to the point where there's so much of it
flooded out there you just can't get
away from it there's so much made up
crap about me and this is an example
Pearl powder if you have a bunch of
people invested in Pearl powder
and they they're making it their jam
they're making it their life and then I
come along and I'm like don't do it
Pearl powder because I'm getting the
information from above Pro powder is not
good for you now I have 50 more enemies
online and who knows who they know or
don't and what they spread and what they
do because it's just but like I said you
can go along the way and make friends
and Bank on it too I could come out with
a medical medium Pearl powder and sell
it to all you guys and Bank on a ton of
money and then to all my Pro powder
friends won't be mad at me and they'll
all be happy and everybody will be happy
but that's evil so I don't work for evil
there's good there's evil I don't work
for evil so when it comes down to Pearl
powder
I wrote something about it in here well
I got it from Spirit of compassion and I
wrote down in here you ready an irrits
hint that's abrasive to the intestinal
lining serious like my Pearl powder
meanwhile they're getting scratched up
really bad on their intestinal Linings
and it leads to problems and then
they'll blame their celery juice
it irritant that's abrasive to the
intestinal Linings triggering vagus
nerves Pearl powder is going to trigger
vagus nerves in people creating problems
where they're going to have panic
attacks like one girl out there and guy
out there wants another panic attack
educating myself page 62 too so all
right so you're on YouTube educating
myself all right you're on YouTube so
you sing viral replicate oh replication
yes wow the book is literally heavy with
insights okay so you're on you're on the
you're on the whole thing of viral
um reproduction whoa yeah replicating
itself incredible so it's fine at page
62 I can't help it
oh which book am I in
let's just just find it for a second
and then we'll go back to having some
fun for for a minute here you're page 62
and brain saver there it is viral
replication
yep
I'm probably not allowed to read this
here
but I'm gonna try to read a little
something out of it
um it's all it's all dangerous for
reading on here let's see
uh you know what I'm going to bypass
that you guys 40 off
40 off read page 62.
amazon.com 40 off okay back to Pearl
powder
Pearl powder does not leave the
intestinal tract quickly
it does not leave the intestinal tract
quickly you guys
it accumulates and cakes inside pockets
of the intestinal tract lining so what
it's doing it's caking in the pockets
you've got all these girls and guys out
there
they got all these intestinal tract
conditions they're taking Pearl powder
think it's going to make their skin and
their nails and their hair so great
and they're tearing apart their
intestinal tract
Pearl powder does not leave the
intestinal dry quickly it accumulates
and cakes inside pockets of the
intestinal tract lining you guys need
these books just so you can protect
yourself so you don't get swayed into
some direction avoid if you have any
type of intestinal tract disorder
I don't know but I got like friends
telling me there's a whole bunch of
people using Pro powder out there and
they all got intestinal tract disorders
and they're all complaining it's getting
worse but it's not the pro powder it's
the celery juice right
avoid if you have any type of intestinal
tract problem Pearl powder carries
traces of Mercury
why does Pearl powder carry Mercury do
you guys know
I'm trying to think why would Pearl
pearls contain mercury Spirit of
compassion told me this no one's ever
talked about this ever
and when I heard that so I was like okay
Spirits give me what you got
and he's and basically we're saying was
well it's it's mercury in the pearl
powder and I'm like what do you mean
the accumulation of pearl powder on the
intestinal tract lining can eventually
cause bloating due to the powder not
allowing gas to flow through the
intestinal tract properly so what
happens is
you get pockets of gas that stay into
you in in you too long because of pearl
powder
and the Mercury is going to feed God
knows what inside of somebody's gut
streptococcus viruses and everything
else
there's mercury in there duh
okay so let's see let's see if we can
find another one
and there's so many in here you guys
look we're reading in here good to see
you guys we're talking about the brain
saver books greatest books of all time
hands down
doubt me pick up a book be the judge
yourself
grab a book when you get a chance 40 off
Amazon and be the judge yourself
so Shirley Johnson says asks on Facebook
what removes heavy metals
um there's heavy met seven heavy metal
detox cleanses in these books seven and
you can pick the one that's working for
you
pick the one that's working for you for
sure
okay
I'm not going to say that one there
because I shouldn't say that here
I mean you guys know why I mean there's
things you can't say on here
by the way you guys do you feel like do
you guys feel like making a complaint to
try to get my Tick Tock page back
do you guys feel like do you guys if you
get a chance I know you're really busy
but I've been I've been taking off of
tick tock so um
just for showing the right paper books
so if you guys got a chance can you make
make my case at uh Tick Tock if you get
a chance
that would be incredible
um the night before the book was was
released uh they took down my Tick Tock
page so I couldn't show the books
anymore
I'm sure there was a pearl powder
salesman in the tick tock
engine somewhere or an ionizer a water
machine user who works in there and it's
just like screw that guy I'm gonna try
to destroy his book released and it went
down
all right
okay let's look look a little bit more
let's do some okay fish oil and krill
oil I'm gonna read that one for a moment
because so many people are on krill oil
and it's almost like just they're just
all on krill oil right it's everywhere
and you you see people that are supposed
to be so so like
um really intelligent in the health
world right they got big websites and
they're selling lots of stuff they put
articles out all the time they're
doctors they're practitioners or they're
just big influencers or authors and
they're all into krill oil and you see
them and you're like wait a minute
you're supposed to be really smart I
mean you don't know by now
from medical medium information contains
okay so fish oil and krill oil contains
a homeopathic version of mercury so
krill oil contains a homeopathic version
of mercury the essence of mercury but
get this
left over after Mercury removal from
many fish oils allowing methyl Mercury
to enter the brain easily accelerating
brain diseases most fish oils are
manufactured with unwanted fish
by-product and waste from various
varieties of fish brought to the
processing centers and mixed matched
together during the oil extraction
process one fish oil capsule can be
filled with fish oil that was derived
from dozens of fishes
when a fish dies the okay
ready
you want to hear a mind-blowing line
there's a mind-blowing line in every
line in these two books but you want to
hear a really mind-blowing line that
like it's just crazy when I even think
about it when I even read it
get ready for this
I mean legendary just unique original
information from above
when a fish dies the Mercury and other
toxic heavy metals oxidize and expand
more quickly in the dying fish oil
Who would know that research and science
doesn't
due to gases being produced because the
fish is decomposing
so when the fish dies and it's
decomposing
the Mercury becomes more dangerous in
the fish
this is why it's much safer to eat a
fish than to take a fish oil supplement
you would never eat as much oil eating a
piece of fish as you would concentrated
into a fish oil capsule I mean that's
just incredible right educating myself
again says the whole book is
how much else did you crack me up love
your jokes I try
I try I crack myself up
so my family says there you go you're
cracking yourself up again
you guys might like my jokes but people
that around me too much are like oh no
there's another joke coming out of him
all right you guys I just want to give
you a reminder we're in the brain saver
books we're reading out of brain
damaging you know supplements not good
for your brain the whole bit I'm in so
many areas right here of this there's so
many to choose from I'm just trying to
it's in the problematic and damaging
supplement section I'm just trying to
give you a few
just just for fun
let's do deer antler let's try that one
right there
let's see the deer antler that dare
antler thing oh my God
what a scam that whole thing's been
just just lost a few more friends or not
gained a few ready Dear Antler also
called deer velvet or antler velvet
not helpful for someone living with
chronic illness
uh really
the hormones in Deer Antler disrupt
naturally produced and occurring
hormones in the body so we're all about
hormones right every though everything
every single doctor practitioner every
single person in the world you just
hormones hormones all they do is Big
Pharma all they do is talk about
hormones right hormones are so important
but the hormones in Deer Antler disrupt
naturally produced and occurring
hormones in your body take the air
antler then all your hormones go
dear antlers steroid compounds interfere
with human hormone production hey take
this deer antler that will do it and you
just screwed up all your hormones
throughout your whole body
the larger the dosage of deer antler
supplements the more interference with
the endocrine system occurs so you take
more deer antler supplements more damage
is done and interference to your own
hormones
by the way this is all for free no
courses no nut no pay walls I just want
you guys to have fun with this just you
know me and spirit were here
the larger the dosage of their antler
supplements the more interference with
the endocrine system occurs the higher
the dosage and the longer the dosage is
taken so somebody's like I take a deer
antler for 10 years
the more withdrawal can occur eventually
causing adrenal fatigue and hair loss
then the person loses all their hair
and they get the adrenal fatigue Shauna
says thoughts on multiple sclerosis yes
um there's so many books I mean you can
you can I have multiple sclerosis in
these brain saver books
I also have multiple sclerosis in
the medical medium revised and expanded
right here I was the first to publish
the cause of multiple sclerosis then
Harvard took it seven years later
and I just and I publish it in detail
the true cause of multiple sclerosis and
then Harbor took medical medium
information and published it seven years
later
Maria the light infusion meditation in
day four challenge is incredible still
weeping a little okay well
I knew that was going to be that was it
was it's
I could only describe it as this the
light infusion meditation that's in the
brain saver books right here
if
I can only say this okay
it does more than just heels it's
healing it's soothing it's enlightening
it helps to release
emotions that were trapped inside our
body inside our soul
it helps to release emotions that are
trapped inside organs
it is a rewiring
meditation
it is a spiritual meditation it is a
connecting to The Ether and above
meditation it is one Power House the
light infusion meditation
it's in the books by the way 40 off on
the books I'm trying to remind myself to
tell you because
then
I feel like I didn't do you guys right
if I don't let you know
okay
let's just let's pick one more here
maybe one more we're in the
supplementation Bridget Jones did I miss
the light blast we're not doing the
light blast right now that's the that's
the light infusion meditation that's in
the brain saver books that we were just
talking about
but I'm honored about the light blast
which we will get to for sure
not today but we will
let's do turpentine oil because I know
so many people are on turpentine oil
it's you know Scorch is the intestinal
tract linings
turpentine oil Scorch is the intestinal
tract Linings you know sign up to the
medical medium newsletter if you want to
know about the future light blast that
I'm going to do with everybody sign up
to the newsletter
go to medicalmedium.com or look for the
link
turpentine oil scorches the intestinal
tract Linings killing off more good
bacteria and microorganisms than bad
bacteria and microorganisms
you're killing off the good stuff when
you take the turpentine oil
you're killing the good stuff
when entering the bloodstream when
turpentine oil and enters the
bloodstream
you're raising blood toxicity
not good
which stresses and intoxicates the liver
and brain turpentine oil has a very high
astringency factor that almost brings it
to a solvent level when you're taking
turpentine oil you're actually almost
bringing your blood toxicity to a
solvent level which is not good for the
brain I don't know I do not correct
English do not recommend turpentine oil
maybe we can do another one
there's so many
nay a
please tell me which book would help the
best
okay you ready I'm gonna tell you which
book's gonna help the best you ready
both of them
and I'm not trying to be a smart-ass I
mean it for really both of them for real
foreign
book one
start book one move to book two
or whatever you feel like doing but I
would start book one and then move to
book two but both of them
I'm in a good mood today you guys
I'm in a good mood because
when I think about
how many lives these books are gonna
save it gives you some like it gives you
some crazy feeling I mean the medical
meeting books have saved so many lives
cleanse the heel is an epic book for for
Spirit of compassion epic medical medium
book one Liver Rescue thyroid healing
life-changing foods but the point is is
I I just I feel so good about everybody
getting better Naye says no sorry I
meant between all your books
for a long C
honestly the brain saver books is is
probably where I would start for long C
you've got medical medium new New
Edition revised I was the first to
publish with the cause of long C was
so the pers first the publish and guess
what you guys and then science research
took it after the fact didn't cite me I
can't they come up with their own stuff
and stop taking and stealing and
poaching medical medium information did
you guys hear at the end of the last
podcast did you hear the the bulletin I
have
um after the uh last podcast it was just
published a couple days ago in apple
podcast did you hear at the very end
we gotta wait to the very very end
okay
so I I mean we're having a good time
we're going through these and I'm just
looking through I'm looking for another
one that could be good let's do whey
protein powder how many of you guys
tried whey protein powder it's like I'm
drinking a smoothie and they stuck away
protein powder in it at the smoothie
shop
Sherry says love the brain shots little
brain shots let's talk about it for a
minute too let me just read whey protein
powder we're gonna go into the brain
shot therapy the brain shot therapy
hands down just unbelievable
um quick instant relief
just incredible let's go into the bro
let's go into the whey protein powder
first feeds viruses
whey protein powder feeds viruses bad
bacteria unproductive fungus yeast and
mold so it's like hey I'm drinking my
health smoothie in that smoothie shop I
just that Smoothie Bar I just they put a
whole bunch I got the let's see I got
the rejuvenate and renew smoothie can I
have that please sir okay great thank
you got it awesome it's got a straw in
there I might drinking it
it was really good what's in here it
says whey protein powder whoa this is
great meanwhile that whey protein powder
is feeding unproductive fungus yeast
mold and viruses and bacteria inside
your gut
Miriam says I love the alien podcast now
I just want to forewarn you I know
there's a few people that got really
upset about the alien podcast because it
scared them and that medical meme
information is positive and it has all
this healing information and then here I
come out with this big old alien podcast
episode and I come out with this big old
alien just two-hour podcast episode and
I tell my story of what happened to me
when I was younger and with
the extraterrestrials and you know when
I and I talked about that and then I
talked about things about how things
work or could work or if
and I know a lot of I know a few people
got really upset with the alien podcast
and I could only just say that
um
that alien podcast
is the first of many I'm just not gonna
come out with the next one yet
I am going to come out with another
alien podcast episode I'm just but but I
should have not said anything because
it's not going to be for quite a while
we have a lot of brain episodes I have
to do so
all right
whey protein powder it feeds everything
bad accelerating symptoms and conditions
whey protein powder is inflammatory
because it fuels pathogens that create
inflammation so you go to the doctor and
you're like at the you're at the
functional medicine doctor specialist
and he's like your inflammatory markers
are up we don't know what you got lime
or what or gene mutation we don't know
what's going on but your inflammatory
markers are up we don't know if you have
ra or lupus or whatever you got
make sure you take your whey protein
powder the whey protein powder will up
the inflammation because it's feeding
pathogens that the functional medicine
doctor doesn't even know that exists in
your system whey protein is not a useful
source of protein because it doesn't
break down inside our stomachs in small
intestinal tracts Who would know that
Spirit of compassion
naturally human produced hydrochloric
acid does not dismantle the Whey Protein
sore bodies can't utilize it so when you
put whey protein powder in you guess
what it rots
whey protein rots in your gut your HCL
can't break it down it can't do anything
about it so when you do whey protein
powder just so you know I hope this
doesn't all fall apart on me right here
if you do whey protein powder
your hydrochloric acid your stomach
lands
you're not going to be able to break it
down it can't be utilized or taken apart
let's talk about the brain shot therapy
a little bit you guys
if anybody on here is
breezing through and you see these books
just know
when you read them you'll know they're
the greatest books of all time Natural
Health and any health book you ever go
to that's not MediCal medium but you
ever go to after that will never touch
it
there won't be there isn't a health book
out there they eat better doctors
that put out books
nothing can touch these books I could
say it with confidence maybe I need the
ego shifter maybe my ego got out of
control and my ego's all big now and I
need the ego shifter in the books
but the point is
is that they're that good and I can
judge them because the information comes
from above so I have every right to make
a judgment call myself my judgment call
is they're the greatest books of all
time for for the for chronic illness for
the future of neurological problems and
brain issues all of the above and what
you'll notice is once you're in here you
can't go back to the others like not
MediCal meeting books those you can
always go to cleanse the heel is epic
but the point is and has healed so many
people but the point is is when you go
back to other health books that come out
other diet books or health books and
things like that and you go to that and
then you go to here or you go to here
into that and then you'll know
what you have here you'll know creative
heart says these are the best yet
without a doubt
honored honored honored
Michelle L says I want to buy a million
more copies and I do too
I do too
I do I do
my publisher said Anthony
do you want your free case of books your
case of books I was like I'm gonna buy
them I want to order them
uh I did the anger shifter last night
after being so angry for the day for the
days for no reason just a miracle the
anger left me just melted I'm making
another one right now so that's it
that's somebody that actually posted I
mean posted that comment so you did the
anger shifter
and it works it shifts the anger
it does
I tried the anchor shifter I've tried it
multiple times I have gone through these
shots I have experienced it the shots
are unbelievable the brain shot
therapies now if you guys don't know
what that means and you're on here and
you're like what the heck are you
talking about
cold white spring are you late for class
you got here late today
um so if you're wondering like what is
he talking about I'm in it right here
here they are
the brain shots I can talk about the
brain shots all day long
Ronnie Lee I'm getting rid of all of my
other health books nothing touches these
that's incredible and I gotta tell you
something I don't take that lightly like
I don't say oh good good good Ronnie
good good good Ronnie Lee
I take that I don't take that lightly I
take that as the greatest honor in my
life like the greatest honor in my life
because that's a big deal to me and if I
use my psychic ability and if I use
Spirit of compassion I could try to
somehow connect to you tossing those
books out and try to get to your house
through the abilities that Spirit has
gifted me since I was younger and try to
see you actually throwing them both out
into the garbage and I will be like oh
my God I am blown away and truly truly
honored
wait a minute that's a medical media
book you're throwing out you're actually
throwing out the brain saver stop the
brain saver book's going out just
kidding Valerie says cleanse the heel
really helped me worse ones to heal
where's my cleanse the heel book God for
the breath
for the breath and can't wait to see
those books incredible you guys if you
just got
Frozen up on um
up there sorry about that I don't know
why I did that I just saw a glitch out
having a lot of glitches so I can talk
about medical medium brain shot therapy
all day long the brain shot therapy list
pathogens right exposures pathogens
toxic fragrances negative energy let me
just go to negative energy
so let's go to the negative energy shot
so this is the negative energy exposure
shot right here
can I read this to you guys
I don't want to put you to sleep
okay
this is a helpful shot for those times
when you feel an unexplained sadness
come over you have you ever felt an
unexplained sadness come over you
have you guys ever felt that have you
ever felt that unexplained sadness that
has come over you
incredible time to take the negative
energy exposure shot
you experience how about this one you
experience a confrontation or
misunderstanding with another person
have you ever had a misunderstanding or
confrontation with another person
incredible time to take the negative
energy exposure shot how about this one
unexplained anger arises with you or
even another person so you got this like
unexplained kind of anger just kicking
up like you're just frustrated and
pissed off
get the negative energy exposure shot in
you right away don't let the anger take
over try not to let it take over just
hurry up and get start focusing on
figuring out what you need for the
negative energy exposure shot when that
happens
how about this one you're having a bad
day
aw how you doing today hey W how you
doing today having a really crappy day
just a bad day
ranglin says no way these books saved my
life I have all the series incredible
how about this one take your negative
energy exposure shot ready
things in your life seem to be going
wrong or you're feeling unlucky have you
ever felt unlucky
have you ever felt unlucky right like
I've had that happen worse I'm just
assuming I'm having the worst [__] luck
right now you ever have that get the
negative exposure Energy Shot the
negative energy shot out
okay how about this one
you're fearing something or someone and
you can't shake it you ever have that
thing you can't shake it you've got like
a little fear in you you're fearing
something and you know what it is or you
don't know what it is but you're fearing
something but you can't shake it or
feeling fearing somebody else but you
can't shake it or something boom get the
negative energy exposure shot get that
shot in you
as you can
instant relief
how about this one you're feeling dread
after a bad dream get the negative
energy shot let's do another one here
right you need to stay strong because
you have no choice but to be around
someone such as a friend or co-worker
who you feel has negative energy or
consistent negative attitude
if you're hanging around with Bob and
Bob has just this negative energy and
you're stuck hanging around Bob and that
negative energies are rubbing off and
you can feel that negative energy and
that negative attitude make sure
afterwards you get that negative energy
exposure shot so you're not taking that
negative energy and carrying it on down
how about this one you're spending time
around someone going through mental
health challenges so if you if you need
to be coddling someone or you're helping
someone or you're spending a lot of time
around something with mental health
challenges
that may cause them to be angry or sad
take the negative energy exposure shot
you're around someone who is struggling
to the point of being suicidal I mean a
lot of us have been around and if you've
loved ones people that are just that are
in that state of feeling suicidal
negative energy shot
you can't seem to break depressing bad
thoughts okay that's one right there
that's an important one there's so many
people what's in the shot
got to get the books 40 off amazon.com
us right now
29.27 these are huge books they cost way
more to print
Houston says negative energy shot
question more question mark where do I
find it or is there a recipe you're
looking at it right now I am at your
service that's a negative energy shot
right there it is in the protocols book
Brain saver protocols and it's in the
brain saver book you need both books
you want to be a health expert get the
brain saver books you don't want to be a
health expert still get the brain saver
books
anyway
all right let's look let's look through
these mold exposure shot you think you
got mold exposure of some somehow
EMF and 5G exposure shot
spend a lot of time on computers and
computerized devices do the EMF and 5G
exposure shot live near high voltage
areas do the am EMF in 5G exposure shot
spend time talking about texting
spending time talking on the phone
Rose DeWitt I'm very overwhelmed by all
of your books and I just want to start
with healing what do you recommend
trying to recommend something here
little rescues incredible thyroid
healing's incredible it's the thing is
all the books have incredible street
cred of turning lives around and healing
people like helping them heal and
getting their lives back pulling that
Rising them out of the ashes
and rebirthing all of it right so cleans
the heel is an Incredible Book medical
medium book one is incredible the revise
and expanded brain saver books just do
the brain saver books so what's the
book's name it's medical medium brain
saver and medical medium brain saver
protocols cleanses and recipes
I would probably go with
the brain saver box
and you know what here's the thing too
the books are so cheap
they're so cheap
you're not spending thousands of dollars
on courses in classes
you're not you're not spending thousands
and tens of thousands on on co-payments
over throughout the years and doctor's
appointments you're not you're not
spending like the books are so cheap
and you can always just start with
cleanse the heel it's
16.99 on amazon.com us right now
it costs way more to print and it's a
big book it's a big heavy book you can
you can you can start with the brain
saver books and move on to another book
they're also cheap
it's really amazing the book should be
a trillion dollars a piece
with what like thank God they're not
that would be stupid
okay
so over there on
so Jay Markle says are you in a
different platform right now
FB is horrible
yes I'm on Rumble right now I'm on
telegram right now so if you have
telegram you can go telegram if you have
Rumble you can go to rumble
so you can go to those if you have
YouTube go to YouTube right now I am
Live on YouTube as we speak
live okay
EMF and 5G exposure is really a great
one right there radiation exposure
see
Wendy five eight is saying
over there yeah
sorry Whitley is saying yeah they are
giving it away Whitley 58 yeah they're
giving it away the books for sure toxic
heavy metal exposures big ones so let's
do that let's talk about the toxic heavy
metal exposure shot I haven't done that
yet meaning talking about it
this exposure shot is specifically
geared for recent exposure to toxic
heavy metals helping to stop toxic heavy
metals from settling deep inside the
body this shot can be used in addition
to the heavy metal detox cleanse if you
want
ideal times to use this toxic heavy
metal exposure shot includes when you
have had dental work done such as
getting Mercury amalgams fillings
removed or getting fillings of any kind
including Composites put back in you
having fluoride treatments retainers or
braces great time to use this exposure
shot just got you know sized up for a
new retainer
right
we're live on medical medium.com
actually go to medicalme.com we're live
on my website at medicalmedium.com right
now
forgot to say that
you ate food cooked on a grill or from
another type of cookout so you're at a
cookout you're at a family's cookout and
you're eating food off a grill
they're putting tin foil on the grill
they got a pan on the grill there's just
metal everywhere or they're just cooking
it right on that metal Grill
use the toxic heavy metal exposure shop
because if you consumed restaurant food
or beverages at coffee chains why would
I need a toxic heavy metals exposure
shot after consuming coffee at a coffee
chain
let's see can I buy this at Barnes and
Nobles yes you can of course
so why would I need a toxic heavy metal
exposure shot after drinking coffee from
a coffee chain
because there's toxic heavy metals in
coffee chain water duh
okay breathe in air fresheners
fragrances perfumes cologne sent to
candles to church it's a fabric fabric
softeners just metals and all that when
you're smelling that you're smelling
just metal
in the chemical
take the toxic heavy metal exposure shot
if you smell smoke from something
burning and you do not know the Smoke's
origin or the purity of whatever is even
burning people burn garbage trash
garbage metal Garbage wood with solvents
with metal in them they just burn burn
burn burn
if you get your hair done in a salon I
got my hair done yesterday how do you
like it
does my hair look good today
if you get your hair done in the salon
definitely toxic heavy metal exposure
shot
hair dye CeCe Rodriguez Rodriguez said
hair dye is full of heavy metals you're
on Facebook
the Comets are so tiny and they go up so
fast
and they're far away from me
we are a long ways from the comments
section
if you're exposed to synthetic
fragrances
spend time in or near an area recently
treated with pesticide herbicide and
insecticide spray go to a park anybody
then you need the heavy metal detox
exposure shot
heavy metal exposures
spend time Outdoors during a fireworks
display if you guys the fireworks during
the 4th of July in the US right those
fireworks any kind of fireworks it's all
heavy metals in the air floating
really 58 I just blocked someone posing
as you on tick tock
thank you well right now I have a poser
poser problem right now and it's
happening because of the book released
so I have a opposing imposter that's
what it is not a poser an imposter
problem happening right now the
imposters are doing terrible things like
they're saying things they're doing
things they're making fake consultations
like I'm Anthony William and I and it's
been a problem for the last few years
but it's been really bad lately and
there's people who've been wronged by
The Imposter
and they're spreading information that's
trying to destroy my credibility I mean
they're not probably doing it on purpose
but they're just so they're so hurt by
The Imposter that they're then trying to
warn others that that medical medium
Anthony William guy that Anthony William
Guy is a bad guy
so I didn't do any of that that the
imposters are doing like doing
consultations taking people's money or
saying terrible things to them or
whatever they're doing
I do not do consultation so if anyone is
saying they emailed or anything else
with me it wasn't me it was an imposter
been working really hard because I'm
trying to get a podcast episode done for
you guys and I'm doing all kinds of
stuff and I think I had it five minutes
of sleep last night am I
hang it in there
please let others know about the
Imposter
you know what I love about these lives
it's like this personal connection you
guys like it's like we're really just
Heart to Heart talking about all this
great stuff oh yeah
reviews can you leave some reviews
I mean if you like the books if you like
the brain saver books or you just like
what they look like or you like the
cover or you like the topic brain Savor
you know the protocols whatever it is
leave some reviews on Amazon if you can
or Barnes and Nobles or whatever you got
the book if you can that would be
amazing or if you just bought the book
and you want to go to Amazon and leave a
review
and I want to show you how you can clean
the books one more thing
so
at Amazon when you order a book and it
could be other other
um places too
when you order a book they have conveyor
belts so anytime you place an order your
order goes on a conveyor belt so what
happens is somebody takes a book off the
shelf
they got an order take the book off the
shelf medical medium someone just
ordered the medical mean book throw it
on the conveyor belt
the conveyor belt's got grease on it by
the time the book heads down the
conveyor belt the book can be just
greasy everywhere
you open it up
aw gave me a used book how dare he
why would he do this if your book is
tattered or injured or destroyed
just tell Amazon and get a replacement
the other thing is
if it's just dirty and you want to do
something about you can clean it just
get a little bit of water
right here
put a little bit of dish soap on top too
a little bit of dish soap right here we
go
and then you can give your cover a nice
clean and get that grease off you can
even use a handy wipe let's see if I
have one
I don't think I have one right here but
that's okay you can use a handy wipe
and clean it up
come out nice and clean you'll be so
happy
educating myself says the reviews need
10 stars and they don't have 10 Stars
though
I am honored
Lorena late to the party but I'll catch
up were you always late to school
just kidding
I was
I was always late
and I never went to college I don't have
not college educated
Steph Cohn says stop making so much
sense I'll try I'll try not to make so
much sense I will try to
I'll try to scramble my brain up and try
not to make so much sense
I was always late
medical medium info makes so much sense
but it's not common sense
medical medium information is not common
sense because it's not common it's all
unique original comes from above nobody
ever knew it in the health field of any
health field there ever was it's all
original it's all published original
and it's stolen and pull poached but
medical meme information is not common
sense it makes sense
it makes sense
it's intricate information detailed and
comprehensive and has street cred it's
got street cred you guys
more people healing from the medical
medium books and I'm proud to say the
number one medical meaning the number
one health book series in the world for
eight years running now
I will place my dummy Stomach back in
we can talk about all kinds of stuff
stomachs everything else hopefully it's
gut stay in right there no don't fall
out
I'm just in a good mood to you guys
because the reason why is because this
marks a time in history
and
you know maybe a big part of the world
will never know about it
and that's okay it's not okay because I
want people who are suffering to heal
but
I gotta live with it if however it's
going to be
but I'll tell you this is that this
marks a very special moment in history
and can I just say
authors don't put out two massive books
on the same day
my publisher said uh
uh he might be the first
who's crazy enough to have two
release on the same day
well Spirit has that much information so
there was nothing
we can do we had to do it
you guys
appreciate you to you guys I really do
Jackie B says you're the only one who
makes sense
can you tell Dr Nesbitt that because I
swear he thinks I don't make a lick a
sense and
he said I have to go to school someday I
have to go to college someday he wants
me to go to a university and get college
educated I told him that I'm not a smart
guy
and I'm just a good listener and I hear
the words and I write them down
it's not an easy process but I'm just
glad you guys
got the legendary books I'm calling them
legendary because I know
I know what they are
I know what I read I know what I see and
I know what I feel and when you
experience it you're just gonna be blown
away
if the live stream says trouble loading
and freezing please take a screen
recording and send to me through DM so
if you guys if the live screen that
we're on now
kicks you off and says trouble reloading
or whatever it says you know what I mean
how it kicks everybody off or if it says
video paused
please take a screen video recording of
it
send that screen video recording to my
DM
so I can get technical assistance
right
PK the chicken needs to learn some
respect because I usually see you on
YouTube
your comments
and that goes for any platform by the
way about the screen recording Chris
Owen says blown away oh my God amazing
amazing
who's the real Dr Nesbit Laura says up
there
Andrea Stewart you're smarter than most
phds I've ever met Anthony I am honored
and I am at your service ma'am that's
your service
okay
over here at AWS Bar and Grill we have
all kinds of different things here
girl Mrs Ferguson you're coming
downstairs did you have a good night's
sleep in the hotel today last night
where's Mr Ferguson he's on the toilet
is he constipated again
well at AWS Bar and Grill we got answers
for that
tell Mr Ferguson we will I will be
sending and assisting up there to help
him with this constipation
Mrs Ferguson do you want to take a drink
upstairs
you guys
I hope I'm not losing a few guys like oh
I just I don't know if I want the brain
saver books anymore
cold white spring says Dr Nesbitt
hanging out with the fly you guys I love
you greatly I had a great time
um I'm honored to be in this lifetime
with you guys right now
by the way thank you for listening to
the alien podcast
Uma Kelly did you like the alien podcast
and
just so you know when you open up these
books you'll feel it they're living
they're all live packed with information
but be prepared to have your mind just
blown I promise you that
and
spread the word
tell others who the greatest books of
all time
and when they read them they will not
save to you you're wrong
when they open the book you they will
not say how dare you say they're the
greatest books of all time they will
open the books and be like they are the
greatest books of all time in health
pass the message along I love you guys
greatly and I'm gonna try to do another
live later on tonight
so uh we'll cover some more stuff
all right
Stephanie says love your podcast the
care