facebook live on youtube live live live
live
that's how we do it okay and we don't do
the editing thing where
edit talk for a couple seconds oop let's
edit it on youtube again oop edit again
edit again because so many people have
brain fog i get it they have so much
brain fog that they can't even they
can't
keep a sentence together and they got to
edit edit edit edit edit
and that's okay but over here we're live
we're making
banana lettuce boats we're talking about
epstein barr
we're talking about blood draw why blood
draws
have like a connection to epstein barr
how's that possible getting your blood
drawn getting the blood test at the
doctor you think you're doing a good
thing
they take too much blood they remove
your immune system and then epstein-barr
creeps up i'm gonna read about
epstein-barr in this book michelle l
you're here
hey honored to have you here on this
saturday okay limb bomb love
you're here too what okay so we're gonna
be just doing some
work on that um this is an important
important live right now because
i never really clarified what's
happening with epstein barr
everybody has it it leads to just all
kinds of problems it leads to weight
gain
weight gain you've got millions of
people on the planet
millions and millions of people right
having weight issues
and they're having these weight issues
because they got the low
grade epstein bar year after year
living inside the liver churning and
turning and producing by product
by-product so important to know
and that's what happens the epstein-barr
creates all this byproduct inside the
liver
and then we get in trouble because all
of a sudden the liver gets stagnant and
sluggish
stagnant sluggish glad you guys are
coming on uh
awesome patricia benny came on you guys
are coming on
i had uh brian says i had epstein-barr
virus two years ago healthy eating
i just missed a comment went up but i'm
glad look i'm glad you're here
incredible uh okay you guys so
we're talking about that gonna be
reading about that so
happy to be of service for you guys
today also making banana lettuce
boats i don't know if you guys have the
book the new edition
see the banana lettuce boats right there
so
we're gonna make that and that's the new
edition medical medium there you go
new edition so it's great to be here
all right um
link is in the description for the
podcast episode
so keep that in mind the podcast episode
is about blood draw
and look that might not pertain to you
you think but it gets everybody in the
end and it really does and that's what
happens it just gets them
in the end limbo love says yum love the
banana lettuce boats cool you've had
them
that's so great lorraine ells on here
today kyle wick hey brother what's
happening
thanks for being here awesome so i'm
reading about epstein-barr a little bit
but i'm going to give you guys the
rundown
about epstein-barr a touch because it
plays a role in everybody
catherine elizabeth glad you're here um
awesome you guys so i'm reading about
epstein-barr she's going to read some
comments too i want to be as helpful as
possible but i also want to let you guys
know
how come the blood draw is such a
big one with that epstein barr
epstein-barr
you know as i talked about and it's
published in
medical medium new edition even for the
long
haul right plague that everybody's
dealing with
they get the plague that's going around
or they get the flu that's going around
and now they're kicked down a notch and
kicked down a notch and then something
creeps up
and what creeps up is a good old epson
bar you know sometimes the shingles will
creep up too
but that good old fc mark creeps up now
blood draws
they can knock the socks off of somebody
and really creep up that epstein bar and
hey you're like pepsi bars isn't for me
this isn't the
live i want to watch because i don't
know if i don't have anything to do with
epson bar
but weight gain tingles and numbness
hashimoto's thyroiditis hypothyroidism
hypothyroidism just just that alone
that's epstein-barr
pcos fibroids endometriosis eczema
psoriasis graves okay
uh epstein-barr-up steam epstein-barr
reynolds
epstein-barr even part of depression
part of anxiety epstein-barr
cfs vertigo epstein-barr tinnitus
epstein-barr
burning roving payne epstein barr
simply simple healing awesome you're
here really cool we're going to talk
about epstein-barr a little bit and then
blood draw
how intense that is as far as relating
to it
um yeah the epstein-barr lorraine
sleeping giant it really is it's a
sleeping giant in everybody and then it
gets you
hot flashes heart palpitations
epstein-barr heart palpitations
hot flashes epstein barr really
important now
okay so let's get into it a little bit
so
i'm in the epstein-barr virus chronic
fatigue syndrome and
fibromyalgia right read a little bit of
that you guys ready the epstein-barr
virus has created a secret
epidemic that's the epidemic
that's what it is it's the epstein barr
and that's the secret epidemic and
people don't just
have one epstein bar inside of them they
got two
epstein bars in them mutations
variations different ones they can have
more than two epstein bars
they can have three epstein bars
right it can have three some people can
have three not
three of the same one three
i don't know how to juggle but i'm just
saying
three epstein bars people can have up to
three some people can have more
four they can have five and and that's
how it works with epsilon bar you can
pick them up
through your lifetime talk about that a
little bit everybody's got it and hey
like i said you're thinking i don't got
the epstein-barr virus my doctor says
i'm clear i got nothing going on what
symptoms do you have a little bit of
weight gain
some palpitations maybe a little ectopic
heartbeat got a little hypothyroidism am
i ringing any bells here
any kind of dizziness dizziness in your
life at one point any kind of vertigo
any kind of body pain unexplainable your
knees bother you a little bit but really
there's no real good reason
how about that okay and pcos
like i said and endometriosis
infertility epstein-barr
mystery infertility not like you don't
have a clog
fallopian tube like mystery so that's
important to know okay
so keep that in mind um
let's go a little bit with this so we're
at a place in time where the majority of
the world's population is living
with one or more of many mutations of
the epstein-barr virus
epstein-barr is responsible for symptoms
conditions diseases
disorders and illnesses of every
category
for some people it creates fatigue and
pain that get targeted
tagged as lyme disease or go unnamed
for others epstein-barr symptoms prompts
doctors to prescribe ineffective
treatments such as hormone replacement
a lot of times that i've seen bar you
know everybody's told it's their
hormones
it's their hormones right no that's
those symptoms are your hormones
that fatigue that's your hormones those
aches and pains that's your hormones
right
those migraines that's your hormones
like but we got the
bar instead that's how it works um
so a lot of people are walking around
with ebv and they get misdiagnosed
are you one of them among the reasons
ebv is thriving so little is understood
about it
actually the only thing understood about
epstein-barr out there in research in
science was taken from
medical medium book one
that's right before medical medium book
one epstein-barr was just
mono and mono went away you get mono
you're sick it went away that's it so if
you're
a patient and you're sitting here you
get a call from the doctor's office
you're like hello oh hi
i got mononucleosis that's what i have
that's why i got the swollen glands and
i can't swallow good
and that's why i had the fever and the
listlessness and malaise
so i got mono how do you like that
what after it goes away i'll never see
it again
no problems either and never a symptom
ever in my life
okay well that's what research in
science says now right and that's what
you say there at the doctor's office i'm
never going to see a symptom
mono is just mono is that the
epstein-barr virus
it is and all it does is give you mono
okay and then the publication of the
medical medium book
has determined epstein-barr to be the
culprit of a whole bunch of diseases
symptoms conditions and research and
science plagiarized
and you know what you know it's uncool
because they have to legally
cite where it comes from and because of
discrimination because of my source they
feel like they don't have to but that's
not true they actually have to cite it
and so that's important to know for the
future by the way
um let's talk about this so anyway
among the reasons it's thriving because
very little is
understood medical research and science
are only aware of
one version of epstein-barr okay get
this
right one version of epstein barr
and then medical medium is over 60
varieties of epstein-barr
okay now there's a little
little thing going on with research and
science where they think there might be
two stealing information once again
theresa i'm one week into drinking heavy
metal detox smoothie daily and switch to
vimergy b12
wow what an improvement um
it's important for anybody who needs to
know this stuff i've been saying this
for a long time b12 is not b12
b12 is not b12 it's not okay
there's b12 and then there's b12
and there's a big difference it's make
or break to how to heal
um from what i've experienced with
friends and family
is there's a massive difference with the
vimergy b12
massive difference so if anybody wants
to know that's v's and victor i
am as mary e rgy.com i'm not sponsored
but here's the deal the deal is i want
people better
and i like people getting better and i
care about people getting
better and i notice that with friends
and families and
and you know that i've known personally
in my life and i say no no no that's not
the right b12 switch it to b12 and all
of a sudden they're moving forward it
makes a big difference
these are tools though these are tools
that's what it's about
april says what book is this the new
edition april so it's medical medium new
edition revised and expanded
new edition okay link is in the
description
just so you know there's over 60
varieties and growing
they're mutating i saw lunell she's on
today i saw you chodes
she's on today they're mutating 60
varieties of epstein barr
you guys just came out of making banana
lettuce boats
but we're just talking about a little
epstein-barr for the moment
epstein-barr is behind several of the
debilitating illnesses that stump
doctors that stump doctors
as i said in the introduction it's the
mystery illness of
mystery illnesses it's what epstein-barr
is still is today even though they've
taken medical medium information and now
they
test for epstein-barr every time they
test for lyme disease
i had my lyme disease test and i got my
epstein-barr test
this phone's getting out of control now
okay what
i thought you tested me for lyme disease
you tested me for epstein-barr at the
same time as you tested me for lyme
disease
how come i thought i was looking for
like a lime
test because i thought i had lyme
disease
but you tested for epstein-barr too why
would you do that
because of anthony william and that's
what happens now
the world's changing they're testing for
epstein-barr
and then let's go a little bit more here
into it medical research and science
have no
idea how the virus operates long-term
they just thought it gave you mono
that's all they thought
yeah they didn't know how problematic it
could be the truth is epstein-barr
is the source of numerous health
problems i just talked about that
fibromyalgia chronic fatigue syndrome
ebv is also the cause of some major
maladies that medical communities think
they understand but really
don't including thyroid disease lupus
vertigo tinnitus so that's what we're
doing we're talking about epstein-barr
right here
so um you guys it's so great i'm gonna
make banana lettuce boats in a little
bit
so take it from there
um we're in epstein bar right now
talking about the different sections in
here too
all right
would i've seen bar be responsible for
swollen lymph nodes bumps on one side of
the neck
and i've taught this to doctors for
years okay that's what epstein-barr does
it swells up
lymph nodes that's a big thing
epstein-barr does so it's a lymph node
sweller for sure and that's that's how
ebb works
until the publication is booked those
with ebv would typically be stuck with
it for the rest of their lives doctors
are starting to accept and learn from
the information released here that have
seen bar
is the root cause of problems in the
past they believe the most trouble
epstein-barr caused for a patient was
mild fatigue and malaise that's it
that's it possible fever now some
doctors are in the
infancy stage of recognizing and
addressing the epstein-barr virus due to
the medical meaning
information public published so it's
very interesting there okay
so let's talk about the different stages
i want to give you guys a rundown
first stage epson bar is you contract it
you're in a restaurant
okay so you're in a restaurant
well i just got a nice piece of bread
here with butter on it
in the restaurant here and i didn't know
the chef
a little spittle came out of the chef's
mouth right
he was yelling at the other chef the
sous chef
and he was making the but he was getting
the butter and he was making the bread
and
no one knew that he was yelling at the
guy next to him and spit was flying out
of his mouth while he was back there in
the kitchen
and that spit landed on that bread and
butter and i ate that bread and butter
and now i just contracted epstein-barr
that's as easy as it gets like it's
simple and quick and easy like that
you can catch it like that so easy and
that's how it works
um kissing
it's another one duh right relationships
it's another one
public bathrooms it's another one
sipping off of people's water
yeah i'll take that i'll you just had a
sip i'll take a step too you just had a
sip
i'll take a sip too so it's like that
right double
dipping so i'm just gonna stick my
cheese
my cheese stick in this sauce right here
i'm at a party i'm gonna take a bite put
it back in
double dip boom epstein bar
it's how it's done it's how it always
was done
and epstein bar goes through stages
that's the first stage now you got it
floating around in your body
it's floating around floating around
it's floating around
okay and eventually
it's only floating around a little bit
okay
it could be anywhere in the body
floating around
in the bloodstream but not a lot of it
not a lot of it
not a lot of it at all okay but it's
floating around
and then it eats something it likes so
it's in your bloodstream and it has
something it likes to eat so let's go
into a few things
it likes to eat something so now it's
eating
an egg so you eat your eggs you like
your eggs
i like this hard-boiled egg you know i
like to or i like this one minute boiled
egg right
you eat your egg you enjoy it fried eggs
whatever scrambled eggs
and then when you eat the food the virus
eats the food
that's finding its way into your
bloodstream that's how it works
the virus then all of a sudden does this
okay does this and all of a sudden the
virus goes like that
there's two
right three
and now four then five
then six now you got a bunch of these
swimming around in your body
now your immune system
gets wise and
so your immune system is just doing its
thing floating around in your
bloodstream
and then it comes across one of them
and then the war pursues
and that's coming in to stage two
so that's how the process works i want
to talk about that in a minute
so stage one is it's just floating
around your system
you contracted it it's there's going to
be time and it waits for your immune
system to drop too
so it waits for your immune system to
drop as
it's producing so it's getting stronger
by eating eggs
it's getting stronger by eating cheese
that's what it's doing
it's in our body it's eating food okay
that's stage one
and then stage two is the war
and that's stage two that's stage two is
the war against
the epstein bar and your immune system
but the immune system usually weakens
before
it makes its break and that's how it
works too so you get stressed out maybe
betrayal
broken trust maybe you're totally just
your adrenals are compromised
because you're so jacked up on caffeine
your immune system lowers because of
that
other problems too clones perfumes
concentric candles air fresheners lower
your immune system
but why does it affect some and not
others depends what you got going on
how many toxic heavy metals do you have
in your system how much stress are you
under are you under financial stress are
you
did you go through a divorce everybody
has these different immune system
busting complications are you eating
more
eggs than somebody else what variety of
epstein-barr did you contract
there's over 60 varieties and growing so
which variety of epson bar did you
contract that right there is a big one
too is it a more aggressive one
like the ones going around now which are
much much more aggressive
or is it one of the old-school varieties
they sit in the body for a long time
and you don't hear from them until
you're 49 years old
and then now you got the weight gain and
the fatigue i've been eating whatever i
want my whole life
i've been skinny my whole life my
friends they they're always jealous
because i've been thin my whole life and
then all of a sudden you're 49 years old
it's like why is this weight coming on
why am i getting heart palpitations why
am i getting hot flashes
you might have the old school kind and
now you go to the doctor and they're
saying you're hypothyroid
it's the old school one so what happens
is it's different for each person
stage two is the war and the war is
your immune system with the epstein barr
so that's stage two
so we'll go into that a little bit
at the end of stage one the epstein-barr
virus becomes willing to
challenge your immune system in battle
that's when epstein-barr first makes its
presence known by turning into what
doctors call mononucleosis that's the
war
that's when it's now mono you might not
feel your motto you might not feel
it it might not even be an aggressive
variety
you might not have a lot of stressors in
your life
and somebody else they got more of an
aggressive strain of fc bar and that
mono hits them really hard
really really hard so that's important
there too to know
so and then what happens when that war
happens and you get the mononucleosis
your immune system eventually starts to
win the war and that's when your immune
system starts to beat out that epstein
bar and winning the war and winning the
war
then what's left of that epstein bar
because it knows
it's been defeated it makes a run for
your organs and it ends up making a run
for the liver
spleen and reproductive system
okay a lot of times it might be the
liver
some women it might be the liver and
reproductive system and then it goes in
there and it goes
dormant your doctor says your motto is
over
and now you're free you're free to live
your life
your motto is gone nothing to worry
about it
and that is how it goes so
go into this a little bit it's during
this stage the epstein-barr seeks a
long-term home by making a run for one
or more of your major
organs typically your liver spleen
reproductive system
organs ebv loves being in these organs
because of mercury
dioxins other toxins residues from foods
such as eggs dairy products and gluten
are likely to accumulate here
the virus thrives on these poisons which
could eventually lead to endometriosis
fibroids pcos ovarian cysts prostate
issues
mystery infertility so that's how it
works
um so now the epstein bar is just
camping out
and so it's camping out so then we go
into the next stage
right your immune system drops again
it drops how does it drop
and it could have dropped even from this
before the blood draw
that's how it drops that's a big one
that
leads to more problems i mean this
blood draw okay will drop it at any time
it'll drop it at any time during your
stage
one two three four of epson bar it'll
drop it in all kinds of situations
it can drop it and then you contract it
easier it can drop it and then
you actually go into that mononucleosis
easier i mean but
at this phase especially at this phase
this is when
you're getting routine blood tests you
know you're doing your thing in life
and boom it's it's when it's happening
if you guys haven't listened to the
episode
definitely here you know listen when you
can alright so you can listen medical
mean podcast at apple podcast link is in
the description
it's the blood draw bloodletting um
vampirism episode
okay so that's where the blood draw
problem really sets sets in so let's go
into epstein-barr
stage three once the virus settles into
your liver spleen or reproductive system
organs it nests there
it's nesting so then you live your life
you live your life you're doing your
thing no big deal
life is back to normal all is well it's
nesting in there right
so now the upstairs
guys now the epstein-barr virus is
nesting inside your liver
that's where it is props are getting out
of hand right so much
so the epstein bar is sitting inside the
liver
it's sitting inside the reproductive
system too
whether you're pregnant or not
it's sitting inside the reproductive
system okay
it can sit inside the prostate
in men but the liver is the big one
reproductive system is the second
biggest place
all right it can sit inside the spleen
so
and that's what it does all right
okay so you guys now
as that virus is nesting i gotta make
the banana boats
this is what i gotta do we gotta get
through that
from this point on when a doctor tests
for epstein-barr she or he
will most likely find antibodies and
take these to indicate
a past infection that was in the past
that was in the past okay
well uh oh yeah i'm here
what is it i had epstein barr
so you're saying i had epstein barr you
found antibodies
that showed i had epstein-barr but
that's not the problem
so i don't have epstein-barr now you're
saying
you're saying that epstein-barr is only
the mono i had and i'm showing an
antibody
but that's not why i got this tingles
and numbness on my shoulder
and my my my back and that's not why my
fingers feel like numb and i they turn
purple all the time
and that's not like that's not why i
have any of that it's not what
okay okay okay so i have the antibody
though
they're wrong
this is something that's been messed up
in our system for a very long time
they're completely wrong
and that's the difference medical media
information brought this to the world
that's why people are healing
because you still got the epstein barr
so the doctor finds the antibodies and
take these to indicate a past infection
when epstein-barr was in its mono phase
the doctor will not find the epstein bar
presently active anymore
because that was when it was in its
monophase right so that's what's going
on there
okay important enough the confusion here
is one of the biggest blunders in the
medical hit in medical
history this is how this virus has
slipped through the cracks
because the doctors don't believe you
have epstein-barr
even with the antibody they find and
even then
it doesn't mean they're going to find an
antibody either different varieties of
epstein-barr elude blood tests which is
a whole other thing you guys
okay and so that's another thing unless
you have already followed the measures
outlined in this new edition
in this book to kill the epstein-barr
virus
in fact it's still alive and causing new
symptoms and it eludes the tests that's
because it's living in the liver like i
was showing you guys
it's living there in the liver and
spleen reproductive system and the test
to detect this has not
yet been invented so they have not
invented a test
to know where the virus is we're so
behind with chronic illness like
decades behind i mean a hundred years
from now and people are
a hundred years from now people are
going to read they're going to be
dusting off these medical medium books
i'll be gone all right i'll be gone all
right
and if the world didn't blow up from
nuclear bombs
or anything else they're gonna dust off
these books
and they're gonna be like hey did you
know this guy
hey did you know this guy knew
wait a minute he's saying the virus is
still in us
did we did we come up with a way of
figuring it out that it's still in the
liver
we haven't 100 years later
but wait a minute did you hear about
that new green tea study
they'll be working on the next green tea
study 100 years from now
and not figuring out what's going on all
right
with the virus hiding undetected in your
organs
your body assumes it's won the war and
the invader has been destroyed
your immune system returns to its normal
state your mononucleosis ends
and your doctor tells you that you're
healthy unfortunately the epstein-barr
virus has barely begun its voyage
hence you guys probably know about this
eggs and pains balance issues vertigo
tinnitus
tingles and numbness burning skin pain
in the neck
back legs knee issues plantar fasciitis
right mourns neuroma how about that one
you know all of these pots okay
reynolds lupus cfs eczema
just epstein-barr is involved in there
all the i'm just at pcos
endometriosis did you have anything like
that fibroids
epstein-barr if you have a typical
variety of steam bar could lie dormant
in your organs for years that's why
you'll say
like i read the comment earlier it's
like how come it doesn't happen to these
other people but it happens to
it happens to these other people so
typically it can hide for decades
without you knowing it especially if
your immune system hasn't
been weakened but you keep on getting
the blood draws and here's the problem
you might be somebody that doesn't even
get a blood blood test
i've known people they go 10 years 15
years they don't even get a blood test
right the minute they started getting
sick they're getting the blood drawn
from them all the time that's why you
have to listen to the the
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
the blood draw episode you've got to
listen
you guys i'm just i know some many of
you guys listened
but so many haven't you gotta listen to
that
it's important to know so um
so let's talk about the blood they take
in this situation
so i'm just gonna grab my tomato sauce
jar for a second if you guys don't mind
and i'm gonna do a little blood
extraction right here
okay now they take a lot of blood from
everybody
that's real blood in there no it's not
strained tomatoes right
they take a lot of blood from everybody
is what they do
so important to know
and your immune system could stay strong
and your epstein-barr isn't causing a
problem yet it's dormant
inside the liver okay and you're
you're not challenged either maybe
you're not exposed to enough pesticides
herbicides fungicides
maybe you're somebody that doesn't have
the air fresheners in their home maybe
you're not under stress
maybe you didn't have that divorce maybe
you know
financial problems aren't there whatever
it is
you don't have enough triggers you know
you haven't been triggered enough right
and you got kind of a docile
epstein-barr variety it's not
a real aggressive one so all that's
happening and then
what happens is whether you start
getting your first symptoms to begin
with
happens to everybody maybe they're
getting hormone tested because they got
the hot flashes their heart palpitations
maybe they don't feel good maybe they
just want to check up they're gaining
some weight
and they get all that blood taken so now
they get 70
milliliters of blood 100 milliliters of
blood 140 milliliters of blood taken
from them
and with that taken from them it's
dropping their immune system so they get
all this blood taken for them
from them when they get their blood test
and their white counts in there
their red blood cells are in there and
they're losing this
and then epstein barr is in the organs
okay and creeping up they'll say that
you'll replenish your blood perfectly
fine
perfectly quick perfectly easy it's not
how it works
it takes a long time sometimes three to
six months to get your immune system
back up to par
red blood cells and white white count
cbc your complete blood count
takes time and anybody who's got
symptoms they're already dealing with
the weakened immune system to begin with
so that's important enough
now they take all this blood and they
say they need it you know and this
this is your sum of the blood they'll
take three times that they'll take four
times that
that's the other thing too you'll get
six vial seven vials ten vials and then
if you're sick for a little while you
got to go to the specialist because now
you got to look for another doctor
specialist doesn't care if you had blood
test blood work done two weeks ago
they want another 28 vials and this
happens to a lot of people it may not be
happening to you
but it's totally wasted a lot of people
that's why this is so critical right
all they need to do this is all they
need for blood tests this is it okay
um so let's do a little bit of this
they just need this much so i'm going to
put a little drop on here
they only need that much i don't know if
you can see that
is that too bright
all right this is a very runny
a very runny sauce for some reason it's
not doing what it needs to do
so you see that blood drop right there
they only need that much
that's all they need less than that exac
absolutely less than that just for one
test
two tests three tests you can get three
four
five tests out of that get your
metabolic panel your thyroid panel
you can get um you know your cbc count
you can get your cholesterol done you
can get your a
a anti-nuclear antigen test you can get
your cbc reactive protein test
you can get your deficiency vitamin
mineral deficiency tests right
genus is that really pisses me off
and you got to listen tina did you
listen to the podcast episode
okay link is in the description all
right so
it's the blood draw episode please
listen chrissy said
if they only need a small amount then
why do they take so much
because something's terribly wrong
that's why the system's broken
they don't want to fix it nobody wants
to admit they've been taking too much
it's like you're in it too
deep what do you do right you're in it
too deep
what do you do you got the entire
medical system
robbing and stealing and thefting
people's blood
knocking their immune system down
killing them
if they got diseases like cancer
quickening
uh and quickening their life as far as
their lifespan to a bad
place right deficiencies rampant
creating rampant deficiencies removing
white count all the time your bone
marrow has to go into overload
okay why are they doing it when you're
in it too deep
they're not going to make an
announcement and say
we messed up it's not
good because then everybody's going to
question it everybody every good
scientist is going to question it all of
a sudden like
wait a minute what do you mean you
messed up
like so that's what's going to happen
now so all of a sudden every single
scientist is going to get a phone call
they're like
what what do you need what do you mean
we screwed up
you mean we've been taking everybody's
blood and removing their immune system
people with cancer are dying really
quick because of it because they have no
immune system
left because they're getting their blood
drawn every week
two weeks three weeks um we're taking
blood out of pregnant women
you mean that was affecting babies
because we're taking eight vials of
blood
out of pregnant women wait so all this
is wrong
what are you talking about it's all
wrong what do we do and just you can't
you know you can't how many lawsuits you
know
who's gonna get sued who made the big
mistake
listen to the podcast so link is in the
description
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
that's the place to listen to it that's
the uncensored version
so you only need this much that's it but
they take
exorbitant amount of blood from people
and that's the next thing too so
but where does that lead us to take this
much blood where does it lead us
it leads us in a bad place we lose our
immune systems
so back to the symptoms we'll head there
a little bit
so now the virus okay in stage three
we're talking about
the virus because we get our immune
system lowers we're getting the blood
taken from us we're getting blood draws
it doesn't have to hit us a week after
we get the blood draw but a lot of
people
they're wasted they're wasted a lot of
pregnant women they get their blood
tested they get their blood draw
they're wasted for a week or two they
can't function
after the blood test and you know what
it leads them to
wait a minute there might be a problem
you know it's like all of a sudden now
we got a pregnant woman who's not
functioning good
after the blood test blood draw but they
don't know why they don't know it's the
blood draw that did it
so guess what you better get in here
because you better get into the office
because we need to test you again we
need to get more blood from you
there's so many women that are pregnant
that get they get bloodletted
while they're pregnant with their baby
and they're getting blood draw
every week two weeks eight vials seven
vials
five vials 12 vials and they're doing it
because they don't know why they're not
feeling good there's so many women that
are
caught in this vicious cycle it's an
evil evil vicious cycle right
so as the immune system breaks down and
weakens i'm reading the new edition by
the way if you guys don't have the new
edition
uh you should stress in life okay
um pregnancy can lower the immune system
too
it's just normal 50 of the of a woman's
immune system
protects the baby that's you know also
menstruation
if you're not pregnant immune system
lowers okay i've talked about that a lot
of times
so yeah toby says we're at war
loon says so sad it's it's unbelievable
right
it's just really uncool so what happens
is all of a sudden
the virus makes a break it leaves the
liver
because your immune system has been
lowered
and it heads off to your thyroid so now
the virus
heads to your thyroid and that's where
it goes next
because that's the next phase and
sometimes if the virus was just
in the liver and it didn't settle in
other places it'll start going other
places too
not just not just the thyroid the
thyroid's a common place now you got
hypothyroidism
so now you're a woman or a man that's
got hypothyroidism
or you get a stage of hashimoto's
you get a mild hashimoto's or an
aggressive hashimoto's depending on the
virus
what variety it was that i was talking
about okay and then
now you're somebody that's getting your
thyroid tested
all the time so let's just take more
blood
okay we're gonna need eight more tubes
we're gonna need five more tubes we're
gonna need four more full
tubes and now you're getting more blood
drawn more blood drawn more blood drawn
okay every six weeks sometimes
every three weeks and then now you're
at the doctor's office all the time and
you're getting your blood drawn so it's
a whole other thing too
keep that in mind sometimes every three
months but you're getting those blood
draws
so now you're at the next phase your
immune system is weakening
you've got epstein-barr virus in your
thyroid okay
you're losing your immune system during
draws but you're losing your immune
system anyway because life here
we're always our immune system is always
battling for us it's always up against
colognes perfumes air fresheners
scented candles pesticides herbicides
fungicides toxic heavy metals mercury
aluminum lead arsenic cadmium copper
it's against petroleum products plastics
chemtrails floating out the sky exhaust
fumes
smog pollution polluted water
pharmaceuticals
in our drinking water and our immune
system is already up against all that
and that's just to name a few not
including
asbestos still blowing around ddt still
blowing around so that's what we're up
against
so now we're at stage three of
epstein-barr
and we're getting our blood tested a lot
and losing our immune system
so now all of a sudden we have a
weakened immune system even
past this we're getting more and more
blood draws we're losing our immune
system more and more blood draws more
and more blood straws
we're losing our immune system the virus
then
builds up enough of
other viruses meaning the same type of
virus
it's proliferating you're eating foods
that feed it
because you're told now you got a
thyroid problem you better be eating
these
delicious eggs right here so your doctor
is going to say you need to be on
eggs you need to be on healthy proteins
you need to be on cheese that's a cheese
stick right there
you need to be on your cheese sticks you
need to be on
you should have your hard-boiled eggs
and salads and get your protein
get all that you need that too and now
you're feeding you're feeding the
viruses
it's proliferating you're getting blood
draws your immune system is dropping
and then the virus turns into a real
crap storm
and now it's stage four for neurological
symptoms
okay
all right so you know so the bottom line
is
i talk about the plague today in the
book by the way
very important to know um
so i talk about the plague in this book
you might want to read it if you have
any questions on that
now we're in stage four epstein-barr
neurological symptoms
the virus gets strong er
starts releasing neurotoxins so the
virus gets an appetite
starts to release neurotoxins those
neurotoxins spread throughout the body
and now you're up against your
neurological issues
tingles and numbness aches and pains
right
burning skin pain in the neck pain in
the back
tinnitus vertigo dizziness
fatigue fatigue
so you will be up against that fatigue
and then when you have fatigue
um now you're just at the doctor's
office all the time but
now you're not just at the doctor's
office you're at the specialist they're
going to need 28 vials they're going to
need
18 vials they'll need 14 vials 11 vials
whatever it is they knock your immune
system down more and more now you're at
the lyme doctor too
now lime doctor wants 40 vials happens
all the time right
now the thing is you guys i'm not
against blood work i'm not against blood
tests i want you to get your blood
tested whenever you feel like it
whatever your doctor's asking right
but when you listen to the podcast you
can protect yourself
so you don't get scammed out of your
blood scammed out of your immune system
because that's what it really is it's a
it's a dangerous scam that's hurt a lot
of people and they take
way too much blood they don't need to
take that much blood and you can
be your own boss and learn how to be
like
well there's something i can do to
protect myself and that's what's
important so
i want to make some banana
lettuce boats in a minute too so stage
four i've seen the bar we'll cover that
for one second too
so now we're in stage four epstein barr
let's go in there
stage four of steen bar the ultimate
goal of the epstein-barr virus
is for some of its viral cells to
venture past your thyroid like i was
talking about before i already explained
it
and inflame your central nervous system
so the virus builds up
its numbers it releases uh
um the neurotoxins the neurotoxins land
on your vagus nerve your phrenic nerves
and you get the nerve inflammation so
now you're getting all kinds of
inflammatory markers if you get a lyme
disease test that's an inflammation test
really
you're not getting tested for the
bacteria they say you are but they don't
i know how the lyme labs work okay i
know a lot of different scientists
a lot of different lab technicians
around the world i know a lot of doctors
what happens is they don't find the
borrelia at the lime
at the lab they look for elevations of
inflammation similar to an a a or c
reactive protein test
then they put the bacteria of choice
next to that
inflammation it's really a guessing game
but they plug
the name of the bacteria in they don't
find the bacteria see
you might get an mthfr gene mutation
test positive another inflammatory test
you don't have a gene mutation i can
tell you this right now
when people get rid of their epstein
bars like many have
over the years that i've seen their gene
mutation test
often gets normal wait a minute they say
you can never reverse
an mthfr gene mutation it's impossible
to reverse it because it's a gene
mutation
wrong why does it go away because the
gene mutation test is an inflammatory
marker it's not a gene mutation
they call it that but it's not so that's
another pseudoscience technique they
have so
that's the whole thing i mean there's a
lot of pseudoscience out there and
that's a
that's a big thing to understand so when
you get the tinnitus the anxiety the
tingles and numbness the chronic fatigue
the eye
floaters you're dealing with the
epstein-barr stage four that's all it's
not scary
you know how many people reverse and
heal that with medical medium books
that's why
they're so known people get rid of that
they get rid of the fibro pain the nerve
pain
dino hey why blood draw why blood draw
is are not accurate for diagnosing ebv
so it's talking about how epstein-barr
works they have a difficult time locking
down epstein-barr they find the antibody
but they think
that was when you had mono sometime in
your life so the doctor would be like oh
you had mono a long time ago
and um and ebv hides in organs
it hides in the thyroid now science
took medical medium information recently
and they said they found a link to
epstein-barr to the thyroid now
but they got it from the medical media
book one which was published first
it's actually hilarious right so
that's how it works it hides in organs
hides in the liver hides in the thyroid
it hides in organs very
very very important to know and
monolith mononucleosis when you get mono
at one point that's a full-blown
blood infection of epstein-barr but
that's
not the stages we're talking about now
we're in the stage of stage four
epstein-barr we're talking about that
okay the issues that result from the
this viral inflammation can include
muscle pain joint pain painful
tender points back pain tingles and
numbness hands and feet
jerking and spasms you guys ever
experienced any of that
right migraines
popping sound buzzing humming ringing in
the ears
tinnitus eye floaters insomnia dizziness
fatigue
unrestful sleep night sweats guys
any of that
okay chronic fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia ra
all of which are collections of symptoms
that the medical communities admit they
don't understand
and have no cure in such cases the
patients are given inappropriate
treatments
that don't begin to address the real
culprit because these mystery illnesses
are stage four epstein-barr
so this is the book new edition medical
medium new edition right here this is
revised and expanded make sure you get
one get free
library or amazon.com is on sale and
check out the podcast it's critical to
check out the podcast medical medium
podcasted apple podcast hear the episode
and share it with everybody you know i
know i asked you guys that before but
share it wherever you go medical medium
new edition gonna make some banana boats
let's do that you guys just gotta get my
friend off of here
and clean up a little bit we're good
okay we're gonna do the recipe which is
the banana boat recipe
banana lettuce boat's going to make them
really quick it's so good you guys
it really is yeah amazon has the book
paula the link is in description
okay and the book will not disappoint
um it's a life-saving book and i added
an entire book to it this is the new
edition with an entire book added to it
it's really cool
um so i'm doing the banana boats right
now you guys okay
so let's do that cut some bananas up
recipe's three bananas doing that now
gonna slice these in half first
do you guys like bananas don't be afraid
of bananas whatever you do
such a good food
i talk about bananas in the books mono
eating cleanse and cleanse the heal
about bananas healing all kinds of
digestive system problems
all of that okay so really important
bananas are that important
guys are in the kitchen with me
it's great all right
so i'm going to cut these then i'm going
to get some lettuce in a second
too so i'm going to cut these bananas
so let's do this
and i got some lettuce right here
so these are the banana lettuce boats
okay i'm gonna grab the bigger pieces i
got some great pieces
um that's a nice one right here
i'm gonna do two pieces of lettuce per
banana boat so we'll do that
you guys the thing is with this blood
draw problem right
is i'm making a big deal out of this
but for a reason i can't tell you how
many people were wasted through the
process of their
of their healing journey struggled in
the worst ways because of it
even lost their lives complicated their
illnesses
i've mentioned the blood draw problem on
and off over the years i thought people
would pick up on it
and they didn't and i was like well what
am i gonna do you know
it's like i have to make it president
i have to make it number one right now
until everybody knows you know and
and and has a way to protect themselves
because
and even hearing this or hearing the
podcast episode there's a chance you'll
still be in the doctor's office
or wherever and they're just going to
suck the life out of you with all that
blood knock your immune system down
you're just going to be like oh what
what just happened and
and then things worse and worse and
worse and but if you really focus and
and listen to that episode spend some
time with it
you know it's it's it's just it's really
important so
so i'm making three right here is i'm
gonna do i'm gonna make three
banana boats right here now
three bananas calls for
more than three but that's three so i'm
gonna make that
so i'm going to make a date sauce right
now
i got some dates right here
you got to take the pits out of the
dates if you don't
you can get in trouble
um because you don't want these pits
from a date
i've said this like a ton of times said
this a lot of times i know hundreds of
times but people still leave pits in
them by accident
and they end up like end up getting in
trouble
so what do we do one blood test at a
time
okay if you listen to the podcast i give
you a couple little tips but you got to
hear the episode really okay
it's important um
you have the option of asking for half
tubes filled
so if the doctor was planning on doing
seven full
tubes you go with seven half you just
ask them for seven half tubes
that's what i i tell family and friends
you can do whatever you want you can
listen to your doctor of course they
want seven tubes
that that's you and your doctor i'm just
telling you what i offer friends and
family right
and um and or what i would do if i ever
needed blood work so i made some date
sauce right there
i'm making date sauce i mean so let's
get a little bit of water in here
about a tablespoon of water okay
and i'm gonna add some lemon too
so that's one thing you can do the other
thing is just ask for your doctor to
break up the tests
break them up because that's a good way
of handling it as well it's like
how about if i just do the metabolic
panel on the thyroid panel how about if
i just do
you know an ana and i do this and i'll
come back for the other stuff
and that's another thing you can do
right and you see you're going in there
doing more
meaning meaning more visits and less
blood taken at once right it can make or
break
somebody's healing process it could it
the blood draws
destroy healing processes i've seen it
destroy
healing processes like for real like
that should be good
so um add one more date in here
it's the date sauce right here
and
i mean think about it think about having
lyme disease right
think about having lyme disease okay
and you've been suffering for a long
time been seeing different specialists
and doctors
they're drawing a lot of blood right
and
and you're losing a lot of blood i might
not have put enough water in there
i added a little extra date
um
i like the food processor for this is
what i like
i'm gonna add a little touch more water
because i didn't add much at all
so you can play with this and just make
it right
the recipe is really spot on but i'm
kind of like doing this on the fly a
little bit
there you go
let that kind of go around so you know
you got lyme disease or not lyme disease
you're just suffering with any kind of
chronic fatigue or any kind of illness
and you're just going through a really
hard time
and they're just taking more blood
taking more blood taking more blood
and that's how we get in trouble we lose
our immune systems in the process
add a little bit more water
these dates are definitely really yummy
by the way
are you guys eating dates at all
[Music]
you love dates i saw that
blending up the date sauce
so when you get a chance listen to the
episode
it can really save a life
the thing is is that they get you slow
so you don't know it's happening
see that's the other thing too the
mistake they've made
is so bad the mistake they've made is so
bad
that it sneaks up on you right it's a
slow
slow process
of losing your immune system you just
never know you're in it
it could take years as they deplete you
pull your white count out as
things get better and then you're doing
things as things get worse and then
you're doing things to try to get
yourself better so
that's kind of going against it right so
they're trying to bleed you to death
whether they know it or not right
they're trying to blood let you to death
but it's happening slower because you're
doing also good things well you're
taking these supplements here you're
talking to this other nutritionist here
you're eating a little better you're
drinking more water
maybe you do some juices whatever it is
you're doing that people do out there
you're staying away from fast food
greasy food so you're actually kind of
like
about trying to balance the scale while
they're sucking the life out of you with
the blood work right
see how it works taking all that blood
that they don't need to take
but there comes a time where just
practice it just takes you out
it takes a lot of people out really
really
the way it does okay so i got some date
sauce i'm putting a little date sauce
drizzling a little bit on here on the
banana
so um
a little bit on the banana boat so this
is the date sauce
it's a little bit of lemon with date god
it's so good it's just
it's so crazy good right you can put as
much as you want on here i mean
i i mean look you can make it your
favorite way the one
thing about mackel meat recipes if you
need to adjust it or something
and i'm going to add some raisins i
don't know if you guys are doing raisins
at all
it's an option okay and i'm going to
give you some other options
too i'm going to put some raisins on the
banana
right here couple are just falling on
the lettuce but that's just
the natural process of having fun right
this is great for kids keep in mind
this is great for grandchildren
it's great for children your children
and
so putting a few raisins on here this is
for adults too
i love this and
right so some dates now
i'll tell you what i love about this i'm
going to put a little cinnamon
if that's okay for you guys with you
guys a little bit of cinnamon
but actually cinnamon's optional and
cayenne's optional so i'm probably gonna
put a little cayenne on mine in a minute
so um what i love about this
is that you got the mineral salts from
the lettuce right
you got the mineral salts those are the
trace mineral salts they're critical for
the brain
and strengthen your blood system that's
the whole thing too right
and your bloodstream but here's the
thing too you got the glucose and you
got other electrolytes from here you got
the glucose
from the banana you got the potassium
from the banana potassium's
that's a critical electrolyte mineral so
you got that going on
and then you got the raisins look i know
a lot of people like what foods do i eat
with low iron raisins are high in iron
okay so that's one right there if you're
worried
but they're higher in iron but the point
is raisins are also a medicine that's a
medicinal
grapes are medicinal that's medicine
so this is a really healthy snack and it
tastes incredible and then you got the
lemon with all the calcium in the lemon
so you got that all the calcium and the
lemon that's another thing
jane tedras says just listen to the
blood draw podcast amazing incredible
share it if you can you guys
help save lives protect lives when you
hear the podcast you'll know what i'm
talking about right
it's a perfect snack christy perfect
snack totally
yeah deborah says yummy it's really that
good i mean you guys got to try it
sometime if you get a chance
all right anyway i'm heading off to tick
tock
heading off to instagram and do
instagram live and tick tock
at the same time i'm going to the main
medical medium page
on ig and i'm going to tick-tock so uh
if you get kicked off if you guys follow
with me and you get kicked off ig just
go to tick-tock live watch me from
tick-tock live
i love you guys and i'll see you there
happy