we're live we're live on facebook we're
live on youtube
tick tock we're live on clubhouse okay
making making a cucumber
pickled salad okay for one that's what i
got right here on the table you see
cucumbers see some dough you see some
onions on there you see some lemons
even if you want to help people
sometimes
you can't because they want to destroy
themselves
they want to be healthy they don't want
to be sick
no one wants to be sick people want to
be healthy
but they want to destroy themselves
there's something
in them they're like robots want to
destroy myself
i want to be healthy but destroy myself
let me have some more vinegar i want to
be healthy but destroy myself
oh permission permission permission to
destroy myself
i need validation destroy myself i read
something vinegar is okay for you well
let me do it that's a great idea
we're just we're just robots destroy
ourselves destroy ourselves destroy
ourselves
that's what we are and
i mean really and you know i i could
wake up in the morning and be like
i want to help i want to
help i'm at your service
i'm at your service okay i'll do a
little curtsy and a little
i'm at your service right
and you can't you you can you can do you
can be at people's service
but they don't get the message good to
see you guys we're live on tick tock
we're live on facebook we're live on
youtube we're live on clubhouse
and if you guys just came on here we're
making a cucumber
pickled salad cleansing heel right here
this information about why vinegar is
bad for you
literally if you want to lose your teeth
and bones keep on using vinegar
keep on using it keep on using it go
ahead
keep on using it go ahead keep on using
it
you want to lose your teeth and bones
keep on doing it keep on doing it
good to see you guys good to see you
guys
you can tell people and a month later
they'll be using it they'll be using it
you can't
it's almost like you can try to run
run as fast as you can why somebody's
holding a grenade
and they're about to pull the pin out of
the grenade and you can run as fast as
you can
to go and try to save them to stop that
pin from coming out
and you can even say no don't do it
if you pull the pin out it's gonna blow
up and kill you
and they'll still look at you and go huh
pick
and they'll pull the pin out that's what
they'll do
you guys it's good to see you're off on
tick tock
light within your off vinegar uh for
quite a while now incredible
that's good to hear vinegar is easy to
quit because it tastes
bad light within a saying on tick tock
good to see you guys how are you guys
doing on facebook youtube how are you
you are annoying just to get to the just
get to the points guys skye had you are
annoying just get to the point
so you must be a vinegar person skye you
must be
can i call you really quick is that okay
sky thank you for being here seriously i
really appreciate
scott can i call you
what's your number is it 8675309 like
that song do you remember that song
eight six seven five three oh nine eight
six seven five three 309.
i see sky you there hey skye
hey are you doing vinegar is that what
it is you've been doing it a lot
you like your apple cider vinegar
anything else you're doing
do you need help do you need help do you
need help
to get off the vinegar okay i'm just
glad you're here skye thank you for
being here
we're gonna get to the points guy don't
worry i'm hanging up but please stay
around
sean are you saying raw
apple cider vinegar with the mother
is bad for teeth and bones yes sean
terrible terrible it doesn't matter if
it's got mother in it father in it
sister in it brother in it it doesn't
matter
see just because it's got mother in it
right
meaning living apple cider vinegar
microorganisms
doesn't stop the fact that it's acetic
acid
an acetic acid takes from your teeth and
bones
it does what happens is you're going
going along going along going along
and going along and then your teeth just
start to fall apart
it happens to everybody it's why
everybody has the reckoning at the
dental
chair the reckoning is
at the dental office you guys need to
know this
it is we're trained to be on and vinegar
our whole life our body sees apple cider
vinegar the same way
as it sees regular vinegar
it sees apple cider vinegar okay the
same way
as it sees regular vinegar it sees apple
cider vinegar the same way
as it sees household vinegar
it sees it the same way acetic acid
draws calcium from your teeth and your
bones
and it removes it from your teeth and
your bones
bottom line cry on tick tock how you
doing
cry sd gums also grew back
nice nice nice it pulls calcium from the
bones that's what vinegar
does from the inside
out you might be something like let me
go use a straw
let me go use a straw now because he's
giving me advice but i still want to
kill myself
so he's giving me advice so let me pop a
straw in here
because i'm still going to do everything
i can to destroy myself
because that's how it works too you see
it all the time like he just told us
seven different ways of sunday how
vinegar's bad and what it's going to do
so i'm going to go and think i'm going
to outsmart anthony william
and i'm going to go get a straw and pop
a straw into that
into that apple cider vinegar and and
drink it through a straw so it doesn't
touch my teeth i just outsmarted anthony
williams
it doesn't matter if it touches your
teeth or not
really important to know it doesn't
matter if it touches your teeth
or not kimberly miller
apple cider vinegar destroyed my teeth i
think you said with the comments went up
let me see if i can find it
but you know i think you know the bottom
line is is
it really does that much that damage
austin good to see you
giselle says annoying yeah apple serving
there is
deborah i was always told apple cider
vinegar was great for so many
health benefits yes you were told that
and yes you'll
you'll be continue to be told that
and that's one of the reasons why people
don't get better is because they're told
a lot of hogwash constantly in the
health movement over and over and over
again
you know what has to listen to me you
don't have to listen to me yeah and
you know you can do it you're told to
eat it you go to keep on doing
it keep on doing and you'll get in
trouble you'll get in trouble
you guys couple things two things i want
to tell you first of all there's an
apple cider vinegar podcast episode at
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
listen to the episode to get so much
information right
also full moon the moon meditation time
so check out the moon meditation
at medical medium podcast at apple
podcast please
check that out at apple podcast okay so
the moon meditation
okay moon meditation apple podcast check
it out if you can
all right brenda on tick tock says
listening to you awesome
awesome awesome and what do i get out of
it what do i get out of it i want to
know do i get a prize
do i get a prize what do i get what do i
get for pissing off all the apple cider
vinegar companies
right i just get a hole in my head from
that
right with what do i really get
what am i winning here i don't
understand
like wouldn't michelle l good to see you
over there on tick tock
what am i winning think about that you
just ordered the book
um just so you know i think you're
talking about cleanse the heels before i
go on cleanse the heel
16.99 it's 51 off at amazon.com us you
won't be disappointed
anybody who wants answers and wants to
heal
this is the book to have i'm just
letting you know if it's not on your
radar check it out
if you're really sick and you consume
vinegar on a regular basis
you will not heal
you will not get to the finish line
you won't get to the finish line playing
around
with vinegar is for the not
sick people or
the not so sick
they can play around they can do that
little bad
little good a little bad a little good
that's what they can do they can do a
little bad and a little good
they're not so sick and then
some other purple is gonna be
tricked into it and it's gonna be sad
because they're not gonna get better and
they need to get better we want them
better bad
you don't even realize how much vinegar
you're consuming
another thing right there okay sushi
restaurant food every salad every dish
every soup vinegars and every single
thing
health food not health food doesn't
matter vinegars and everything
vinegars are everywhere ketchups
mustards organic ketchups organic
mustards mayonnaise soy sauce hot sauce
salsa
dressings sauces sauces
salsas whatever
vinegar is for the not sick
yeah eventually they'll lose their teeth
over it
but it's for the not sick it's for the
not
so sick right that's who it's for
if you really want to get better and you
really got something plaguing you or you
got some intimate
or intermittent that plagues you or
whatever it is and you're doing vinegar
you're not going to heal
not all the way not all the way what do
i get into this
what's my reward where's my reward where
is it
you know i could just sit here and be
like yeah do what you want go ahead do
you have to sit there
yeah do whatever do you do what you want
i'll hop on the bandwagon maybe
everybody will like me again
you know maybe they all like me from
years ago
or something i used to say get off
vinegar and they hated me but they
didn't hate me this bad like they do now
now it's everybody's bankrolling on
every single thing out there
every trend they're bankrolling on the
left ends and the vinegar and the fat
and your whatever it is and your
everything they're doing they're banking
on
all the stuff so now everybody hates me
because
i've gone against the industry
right because there's a secret code in
the alternative medicine industry you
guys don't know this
if there's anything to take out of this
take this from from everything okay
there's a secret code in the alternative
medicine industry it's
once you get in there as somebody as an
authority right a health authority
because medical medium information and
the millions of books around the planet
so i'm considered one of those health
authorities right once you get in there
and you're like one of those health
authorities you got the big podcast
got the big books whatever it is right
whoever it is out there
once you're in that realm you're
supposed to shut that
up you're supposed to shut the heck
up when it comes down to no just get
your collagen powder
put your brand on it get your episode in
here put your brand on it
put you get your get your you know
butter and put your brand on it
get your whatever it is put you get your
charcoal put your brand on it get your
chrome put your brand out whatever
you're supposed to do
you're supposed to play in that in the
game of everybody plays the same game
kombucha tea
or whatever it is you're fermented food
you can't you're not supposed to go
outside of that
you have to just be quiet and play in
the game
of bad trends and if you go against all
those bad trends
and you're hurting all those pockets
you're uncool you're really uncool
and that's how it works so what do i get
out of it besides a hole in my head
every time
when all of a sudden someone and some
some
you know big wig and guru in the health
industry says i want to reach out to aw
since he has so much pull in the
industry i want to reach out to him and
tell him he has to chill
you know you get guys i can't even tell
you how much that happens so
gurus in the health field right ones
that have books or their
doctor podcast guys they reach out to
medical medium
and they're like can you chill please
because you're hurting
you're hurting us can you chill can you
back down on the attack on apple cider
vinegar can you back on the attack
back down on the attack on caffeine
please because we sell a chocolate now
and we have a whole bunch of pyramid
scheme influencer selling chocolate now
their own chocolate brands now
can you back down on the chocolate on
the caffeine thing saying how bad it is
and what it does to people
so what happens is they reach out to me
right and they're like
aw we know you got a lot of influence
can you back down yeah can you back down
on letting people know why they
shouldn't have caffeine and matcha tea
and they shouldn't have kombucha tea and
they shouldn't have apple cider vinegar
and they shouldn't have their fermented
foods and they shouldn't have
all these different things can you
totally chill
because you're you're you're uncool
you're out of line
i'm like isn't it about getting the
person better
it's not a it's it's about that it's
about getting the person
better
if you're really sick and you want to
heal
you're not going to make the finish line
tank in the vinegar
bottom line right there i just want you
to know that something that's really
important though
i take texas don't back down that's
pretty funny michelle
l truth has no chill so
vinegar cleans
calcium deposits off your shower
floor
vinegar cleans the calcium deposits
lorraine l good to see you off the
closet
off of the closet just anything you
spray vinegar in the closet you get
mildew out
you get mildew out right
vinegar cleans surfaces
really good it's not intended internally
it's a house cleaner you spray
it on your cabinets you get the dirt off
you spray it in the sinks you get the
calcium deposits out
calcium deposits are the big one vinegar
has
a serious reaction to calcium
serious reaction to calcium cinder c
there's a reaction that occurs you guys
is it possible to do the diet without
celery juice
um look celery juice is an incredible
medical medium healing tool try to do
medical medium tools without it if you
need to
illust lawson says wow you're changing
my whole
life right now thank you thank you for
being here
truly thank you and and look
oh my god that's right patty it's right
right
linda marie says duh right it cleans the
calcium
that's what it does you want to scrub
your sink your shower really good you
want to scrub your shower floor really
good
you get some vinegar you get a cleaner
that has vinegar they put the vinegars
in the cleaners
right you're not supposed to
consume it you're not supposed to
consume it now why is it so important
i just let's talk about that a little
bit why is this so important yes by the
way if you just got on here
making cucumber pickled salad right
pickled salad interesting why is this so
important
because you're going to get vinegar in
it's going to get in your diet
it's going to get in there it's gonna
get in there
you're gonna hold that grenade okay and
you're gonna you're not even gonna know
why you're pulling the pin out of the
grenade you're
like something inside of me just wants
me to pull this pin out of the grenade
it doesn't matter i just want to pull
this pin out of the grenade and hold the
grenade
hold it close to myself and pull the pin
out and i could be running full speed
dive onto you try to stop you from
pulling the pin out
but you're going to pull the pin out
it's not your fault this is not your
fault what about kombucha so we'll go
into that a little bit too we're going
to cover kombucha with fermented foods
just so you know
so here's a question right here on tick
tock is vinegar
apple cider vinegar mixed with water
good
for a toner no terrible doesn't tone
anything
terrible apple cider vinegar surfaces is
good you want to have it in a health
care product it's
on a surface shampoo or something is
fine
calcium and minerals from bones
are removed with vinegar
because the acidic acid is so acidic
it creates a response
in the body and that response in the
body is to dump
calcium dump calcium your bones just
dump calcium dump calcium that's what
your bones do it's like
let's just dump the calcium in you put a
little vinegar i don't care if it's the
best apple cider vinegar you
i don't care if grandma has her own tree
okay and our grandpa has his own treat
and he picked the apples himself
and you made that vinegar out of those
apples
when you do the vinegar you lose your
bones
because the calcium leeches out because
it has to acetic acid
it's a threat to the body the body's
under siege it's under siege
right nikki mickey fox on tick tock says
i regret all the kombucha i ever had
in order for your body to buffer the
acid because it's under siege
you have to dump the calcium in
see you have to dump it in
that's how it works yeah
that's how it works oh my god i never
heard that acadia
yeah so acv is bad i just saw the
question on tick tock it's bad
it's bad it's bad all vinegars are bad
acv
is the best vinegar it's the best
vinegar because it's made out of apples
but it's all bad it's all bad
it really is what happens is that
[Music]
when you put acetic acid into your
bloodstream a crisis occurs you go into
an
actual crisis so the minute the apple
cider vinegar goes in
your body goes into a crisis
and calcium gets dumped out that's it
osteopenia here it comes all great when
you're 25 years old and you're told to
have apple cider vinegar because it's so
healthy
well great i get it when we're young
we feel indestructible when we're young
and we're not so sick or we're not sick
yet
we feel indestructible
we feel indestructible to do a lot of
bad things
because we want to do bad things
here and we want validation for every
bad thing we can do
that's how it works
janine says on there had apple cider
vinegar for 30 years because my
grandma swore by it i felt
good on it but it pulled all the calcium
out of my bones
had bone health problems for years now
and now i know why
thank you aw just feel bad i would tell
people to drink acv all the time it's
not your
fault so much better now with morning
cleanse
it's just convincing all the people now
here's how it works it's not your fault
because you've been handed
misinformation but not your grandmom
by somebody else who told everybody
because that's how it works and right
now there's a huge apple cider vinegar
surge out there because everybody's
desperate for an answer they're
desperate for an answer why am i sick
why am i sick
how am i sick how come i can't get
better how do i get better
check out the apple cider vinegar
podcast episode at medical medium
podcast
apple podcast you guys if you can please
check it out i don't ask much for it
from you guys
check it out so you can learn also check
out the moon meditation apple cider
apple cider vinegar podcast episode and
moon
meditation podcast episode check out
both
check out both if you can right
check out both vinegar's and everything
you guys let's run into that right now
it's in your ketchup that's in your
mustard it's in your ketchup and mustard
right when you have your hot dog but
hey look you might not be eating a hot
dog so that's okay but it's in
everything else
corinne says i'm seeing so many great
testimonials
about how it's helped people in the
comments
but you're only reading the bad ones
okay all right everybody go ahead you
want
bye you want to believe in the
testimonials on how
apple cider vinegar works you know
meaning like works for them and
everything else okay
and go ahead go with it but you have to
remember here's how it works
no one just does apple cider vinegar and
changes nothing else
they get off of processed foods they
bring an apple cider vinegar
getting off the processed foods are
getting them better they're on a bunch
of different supplements
they're getting rid of uh fried foods
they're getting rid of fast foods right
they're going on intermittent fasting
right but they'll say it's the apple
cider vinegar helping them
but just so you know they will all have
bone problems
and they'll all have teeth loss they
will all
have it apple cider vinegar has the
ability as the ability to help the
stomach temporarily and i'm going to
talk about that now let's go into that
right now
don't listen to me don't listen to me
yeah
you know it's the stomach
can improve temporarily for
some that are using apple cider vinegar
so that means like an acid reflux or
something like that okay
not for all but for some so let's go
into that a little bit
and keep in mind keep in mind on this
one okay
i'm actually attacked by the apple cider
vinegar
propagandists i'm not auction i'm
actually watched
by the industries in the alternative
health movement
they watch everything i do they have
scouts go on every live
to see what i'm ripping apart if i'm
ripping apart matcha tea they'll have
scout say how much he's doing so you're
doing so much for them keep that in mind
i'm not saying everyone
but a couple of those are going to slip
in they always do
they're advocating for their paid to
advocate for
all the different stuff that i rip apart
that's how it's done
keep that in mind right there
so let's go into this a little bit
so here's how it works your stomach
has little glands in there
those little glands produce your hcl
right we weaken the glands
throughout the years through caffeine
practices
bad food processed food practices okay
alcohol practices right and vinegar
practices
we weaken those stomach glands
but if you do shots of vinegar
you can spike your
stomach glands into dumping out
a lot of hydrochloric acid
it's temporary temporary it doesn't work
for long
it might work for somebody for a month
it might work for somebody for six
months might work for somebody for a
year and then
you trashed your stomach lambs worse
than ever
before ever
before acv burned my stomach so bad i
wanted to cry
steph grace on tick tock said that
so should i not listen to any of the
the people who have a negative
experience with episode of anger
should i just ignore all those and just
stay focused on the the people that are
popping up saying it helped my stomach
or helped my whatever so let's just
ignore the people that say hey it ruined
my bones hey it ruined my teeth
you know ruined my stomach hurt my
stomach
hurt my intestinal tract should i just
ignore all those
so let's go into this a little bit back
this if you're really sick
and you consume vinegar on a regular
basis you're not gonna heal
you're not you're not going to take it
to the finish line anyway
it's critical to know right there so
it's something you might want to stay
away from
right so we trash our stomach lands
throughout our life we don't do it on
purpose
we do with the fast foods the processed
foods we do with the high fats the high
fats you guys
fat fat fat fat we do vinegars
right margaret hurst says
i fell for it too claiming to cure
arthritis
big joke it really is but there's a
tremendous amount of money invested into
apple cider vinegar right now
tremendous amounts you guys have to see
the signs
and when there's a lot of money invested
in something to have
countless people fighting for it
because they're on the payroll it's just
unbelievable really
casey and there's people that honestly
think it is helping them in the moment
but don't don't realize what it's going
to do to them later on
casey shellman says they used to have
gastroparesis and was told to do apple
cider vinegar
every day and my digestion was still
slow
and burned when i drank it medical
medium information finally helped my
digestion
celery juice is what helped me so much
in following mm protocols
from the books we tear up our stomach
lands they're inside our stomach
okay we tear them up we destroy them we
weaken them
and then we get told to do the apple
cider vinegar and we spike what's left
of them
we drain blood from a stone
because we spike what's left of those
stomach lands in there
what we're spiking is we're causing the
stomach glands to squeeze out every last
little tiny
molecule of hcl to try to give us a
temporary fix and we don't realize it
because someone made a huge mistake
thinking that that stuff was medicine
and then they bankroll on it so no one's
going to break that whole process out
there
just me doing a live about this
always comes with some razor burns
because i'll be hearing it later on
because i'm hurt in the industry's
pocket when it comes down to acv
different if i didn't have as much
influence didn't have
seven new york times uh best-selling
books out there in the world
didn't have books published in almost
every single country in the world wasn't
the number one best-selling author in
health
running six plus years if all that
wasn't happening
then i think they wouldn't care no one
would care
but when you have all that and you start
going into all this stuff and tearing
this stuff because i gotta have your
backs
boy am i going to get the razor burn
later
so what happens is
your hcl gets burnt out finally and
tapped out inside your stomach
so let's go into a couple other things
that occurs when that happens when you
lose your
when you lose um kimberly miller that's
what ac did for me in 2016
i was on my death bed and not digesting
anything my naturopath said to drink
aloe and acv together aloe was a smart
move
and it helped my digestion at the time
and i kept drinking it for years
thinking it was good
my teeth started falling apart at once
a few years ago and it was so scary
that's how it works i got sick again in
in 2018
and my hcl was shot i've been doing your
protocols for two years now
and haven't had any more teeth issues
they actually feel healthier
than ever before i've had teeth issues
since childhood anyways
what happens is especially if you've had
t kimberly if you've had teeth issues
going back then the opposite of fingers
really going to do a number
and that's what happens we go along we
go along we go along we go along
and then all of a sudden they just all
start falling apart from the vinegar
and that's how it's done aloe was a good
recommendation good thing i spent 35
years teaching about aloe so naturopaths
can recommend it
jennifer i lived off of apple cider
vinegar for about a year
i felt awake and well
until i felt and looked like death it's
bad
it's bad it's bad
so what is what does vinegar do to us
besides everything we're talking about
another one healthily
ever after danny
good handle i like that's cool it made
my acid reflux worse
cj and reducing fats was the was the way
and it really is it really is it's good
to see you guys on here
telling your stories your stories are
powerful they matter
truly do kelsey bach kelly kelsey bach
is it 47 symptoms now that you got rid
of
i think it's 47 symptoms i think i read
that in the comments section
on youtube kelsey says i tried for a
week
it killed me right away kelsey you know
what's really cool about you
is you just you you have just um you
have so much passion
to wanting to get the information out
and helping people you really do i mean
you've got rare 47 symptoms
i i mean you're just incredible
absolutely incredible
apple cider vinegar pickles organs
the liver is the organ it likes the
pickle it pickles all
organs it'll pickle the brain get ready
for this you guys
you guys i still have to to create some
food for you guys and i know that so
hang in there for the ride on that
here's how organs get pickled okay
vinegar including apple cider vinegar
sucks the fluid
out of your cells
it doesn't detox the fluid
it leaves behind the toxin
so you can't detox the toxin anymore
vinegar including apple cider vinegar
removes the hydration
in a cell but doesn't remove
the poison in a cell critical to know
get ready for this how do you create a
pickle
do you guys know what's how do you
create a pickle
a lot of salt need a lot of salt
a lot of vinegar a lot of vinegar a
little bit of water
right create a pickle
we have salt in our blood we have
the mineral sodium in our blood
sodium is a mineral we have
in our organs and in our blood
okay when you mix vinegar
and salt you can pickle
anything right
when you add vinegar to your body
through your mouth you drink your
vinegar
okay
you drink your vinegar put it on your
food in your salads
that acetic acid is now interacting with
your
sodium
acetic acid your acv
mixed with sodium creates a chemical
reaction
please remember this that chemical
is pickling
that means sodium inside your
bloodstream
mixed with the vinegar creates a
chemical reaction
and starts to pickle organs
if you did too much vinegar
you'd be in the er the er
you would literally go into pickling
your organs
people though pick pickle pickle their
organs
mildly a little bit on their salad to
skate it by then
a little bit on my apple cider vinegar
shots skated by on that
every day a little bit on here and on
this food a little bit of my mustard
a little bit of my ketchup a little bit
of my my salsa
a little bit here a little bit there a
little bit in my mayo
a little bit here a little bit there and
you skate by
and your body's like whoa how do we
dodge that one whoa how do we dodge that
one boom how do we dodge that one
well i'm just gonna have some sushi i'm
gonna eat healthy tonight i'm gonna have
my sushi
all that vinegar i'm gonna have my sushi
plus mercury let me just have some
mercury
it's like it's like who wants mercury
you guys want markers like i'm gonna
have some sushi i'm gonna have tuna some
can i have a sushi roll please
i just want to kill myself i just want
to have some mercury now
right i mean we're creatures of we don't
want to be sick
i always say that we don't have a fear
of healing and we don't want to be sick
but we do want to destroy ourselves we
have something innately in us that just
wants to kill ourselves
that's how we want to poison ourselves
in moderation
just hey hey yeah i know i'm out here a
sushi bar with a friend nip yep
i just want no give me mercury i want to
kill myself give me mercury
i want to do it slowly in moderation
i want to have vinegar in moderation
laura my whole life
i loved pickles mustard vinegar and
vinegar and everything
now in my 40s my teeth are literally
dissolving that's when it hits
it's what it hits but i've seen it
hitting in in people's 20s too
i've seen it hit in their 20s because
the vinegar i've seen people have
a lot of mineral deficiencies they come
here early with teeth that are already
on the rocky road
they could hit in your 70s though you
can have good mineral
minerals from birth from mom for some
reason
mom had a lot of blackberries and a lot
of raspberries and
he had some decent minerals transferred
over
dad had some blackberries something
happened
you got some minerals transferred over a
little less mercury chris has said
there's a youtube
supplement at right now saying study
shows acetic acid helps carbohydrate
digestion
yeah study shows by acetic acid
companies
that's how it works that's how it's done
they don't know what happens in your
digestion when you dump that stuff in
there
i'm sorry but i'm kind of confused here
i'm scratching my head a little bit um
when you dumb apple cider vinegar in
your stomach you mean they have a
machine
they have a machine that can see where
that apple cider vinegar is going what
it's doing and if it's helping or not
well we have technology that does that
are you kidding me and that's how
the whole thing's a sham and a scam
but the more and more you'll find
that i hurt industries like say apple
cider vinegar anything else the more and
more
a campaign will come on and more and
more another campaign will come on
they'll dump another
five million dollars in in a campaign
and try to get another
bogus study they'll dump another 10
million another 20 million
and like i said the chronically ill will
be sitting there waiting for a bone
they'll be waiting for an answer they'll
be waiting for science research to man
up and actually do something for the
chronically ill
and instead they're just going to be
instead be all busy they're all busy
working on apple cider vinegar let's see
if there's anything else we could
squeeze out
apple cider vinegar it ruined your teeth
too i just saw that
pickling organs is what it does when
it meets your sodium in your bloodstream
that's how it works you guys and
you know i mean should i care
yeah i should care like i should i
should
i should care sometimes it feels like a
battle you can't win ever right
it's a battle you can't win you know you
want to help people
but the industry has oh man they're
tough
they're tough they got it all sewed up
and they got a lot of money invested
and then they need sheep let's talk
about bacteria
balancing bacteria in your gut is a
flawed theory
flawed
flawed theory you're doing your kombucha
tea you're doing your apple cider
vinegar with mother you're doing your
fermented foods and you think
you're balancing your gut bacteria
all the bacteria the microorganisms
that are on fermented food that are in
yogurt
that are in fermented food that are in
kefir
kombucha tea fermented vegetables
fermented pastes whatever it is
in all fermented food that bacteria
doesn't exist in people's guts did you
guys know that
it doesn't it doesn't exist in people's
guts did you guys know that
important to know and what's interesting
is
that bacteria is bacteria that likes to
be on something that
died died
so it likes to be on something that died
when we eat food it comes to life
food comes to life that's what happens
death is something different when
a vegetables dying and ferments the
bacteria and microorganisms on that
vegetable
are on death this concludes the
fermented foods i was talking about
includes vinegar
and all that now vinegar and fermented
foods were a survival food back
thousands of years ago because no one
had a freezer and a refrigerator and no
one had whole foods
trucks driving around going to a whole
foods
every single county every single town a
whole foods
whole foods grocery stores grocery
stores health food health food stores
chain chain stores chain restaurants no
one had access to that
you're in the country in china you died
if you ran
out of food two three hundred years ago
you're in the country in china you just
died you ran out of food
you ate you ate your family members
you ate all the livestock you had you
ate it you eat every single goat
until they're gone and then if that
winter isn't over yet and you're still
hungry
you're gonna then eat grandpa because
that's how it's gonna work you're gonna
keep your children alive
and they're gonna knock grandpa out over
the head and then
and then everybody's gonna be eating
grandpa
okay they did it here too in the u.s do
it anywhere
if you're starving and you have no food
in a way
to preserve food throughout the winter
you would starve to death
that's how it was done so here's how it
works
at the end of the season you take all
your vegetables uh
does everybody get in the last harvest
because it's 20 degrees out now
and we don't have a freezer we don't
have a refrigerator because this is
because it's 20 degrees
doesn't mean that's going to be your
freezer that's not how it works a
freezer has to stay a certain
temperature long term it can't go up
down
up down food just all rots so we don't
have a refrigerator we don't have a
whole foods nearby
we don't have any kind of we don't have
any kind of stores
we're out in the country and it's the
year 1608
and we run out of food by the time it's
december
we're going to be eating our horses
so they took all their food and they
dumped it
in vats they dumped it in vats
and they let it ferment it was a
survival tactic you guys
survival tactics aren't health technique
tactics survival tactics are to keep you
alive
but they're not there to help you when
you get chronic illness
from classified medical research and
science that gave you epstein-barr
they give you hhv-6 they give you
sedimental virus they gave you simplex
one in a
dozen other varieties of simplex one
they gave you simplex two
the classified medical industry who
released
all your epstein bars out in the world
and all the hhv sixes and hhv7s inside
of megaloviruses
all shingles viruses all the different
the chickenpox viruses
all those were released by classified
medical research and science over the
last 100 years
and in 1608 nobody was battling that
so they had to use survival food
survival food was you either eat
something and get some kind of
carbohydrate in you or you die
so put all your vegetables in a vat
that's what they did 2000 years ago you
put in in the east
you put all your vegetables at the end
of the year the end of the last harvest
you put it all in these vats and you let
it ferment
you let it ferment lindsey says makes so
much sense
lindsay napier thank you for being on
here
and you know it's a great name and you
know it's
it's it's interesting
because so what happened was in order to
stay alive
we had to stick it in crock pots without
cooking it we had to stick in these vast
massive ceramic pots you guys
and and that was the pot you go to
when you ran out of food so now it's
january
somewhere or say it's whatever in the
opposite end of the world and it's
whatever
say it's the cold months and now you
ran out of your horse meat
or no you ran out of your goat meat you
ran out of
whatever livestock you think you could
have spared
and now you're going into the crock pot
you're going you're lifting up the
ceramic
smells fermented stinks like heck
it was salt thrown in there too many
times they throw
salt in there there'd be microorganisms
in there it didn't mean those
microorganisms gave you life
they were just microorganisms that
happen to be undead things but the dead
things is what you're trying to eat to
get to survive to get the carbohydrate
so then you're in that slop and that
slop is what you're eating
in order to try to get till march until
that the tundra starts to cool that you
know warm up
and what happens is it was a survival
tactic bottom line
and that's what it was
microorganisms that you think that on
your fermented foods are not naturally
inside your intestinal tract i'm sorry
to say
sorry you guys sorry
and here's another thing too good
bacteria inside your gut that's
naturally in there does not
fight bad bacteria you can't balance out
your gut by putting in fermented stuff
fermented stuff doesn't balance out the
microbiome that's a theory
and you know it but it doesn't balance
it out it doesn't control bad bacteria
you can have all the microorganisms you
want in fermented food but it doesn't
control bad bacteria
it doesn't stop bad bacteria do you know
they don't fight each other you know
they don't go against each other
something that's really important to
know okay
bad microorganisms the bad
microorganisms right you guys
the bad ones they don't care about the
good ones
they don't battle each other they don't
battle each other
that's important to know
and so the idea of balancing your good
microorganisms
isn't even an idea that's valuable
because it's a theory that doesn't work
it cancels out itself
because the most simplest understanding
about our gut
the most simplest understanding about
our gut is that
these two don't play with each other
good bacteria don't go and try to find
bad bacteria and push them out
they don't do anything like that good
bacteria isn't the stuff that's on your
fermented foods
that's not naturally in your gut is your
good bacteria
we're so lost we're so lost
in the world of gut health
i got a doctor calling right now i
actually had an appointment
i got a doctor calling right now because
because this doctor wants me to do
something
dr shallow hey you there
so you want me to do fecal matter
implants right
like so you want to so the new thing is
to make sure that what you're saying is
if you take
someone else's right
and you put that
up my behind right and you plant it in
there
it's going to help me with my bad
microorganisms
but what about the person's poop does
that have any bad
microorganisms in it are you guys
screening that properly
no you're not it's clean poop so you're
using
other people's clean poop you've gave it
a quick scan
but what if you guys aren't looking for
the right stuff with fecal matter in
plants
what if you're not looking for the
shingles viruses
oh you're not you guys have never even
heard of looking for that because you
don't even know what they look like
wait a minute so fecal matter implant
is really antiquated already because you
guys aren't looking for somebody's hv6
that could be in their poop
so here you're just sticking fecal
matter implant material
up somebody else's butt and there could
be like
hsv 1 hsb2 hh v8 hh
so but you want me to do it anyway you
think it's going to help my digestion
it's going to balance my microflora
what's with all you guys with your
microflora
you guys don't even know why anybody's
sick you don't even know why people have
chronic fatigue syndrome
until medical medium published
information about it
but you guys are all experts i i know
i'm not trying to insult you dr shao
i'm not i didn't mean to do that you
want me to try it so you want me to do a
fecal matter implant because you want me
to balance my microflora
all right and but you know that good
bacteria
doesn't fight bad bacteria in the gut
right bad bacteria
stays there in the gut and does its
thing no matter what
so i have a better idea what if we just
learn about killing off our bad bacteria
how about that you guys don't know
anything about that
unless you took medical meme information
all right
i'm gonna hang up okay
microorganisms i'm living things
if you grow your own dill guys i'm gonna
make some pickles
it's a pickled salad not pickles with
pickled salad you grow your
own dill
there's going to be microorganisms on it
you pick it out of your garden you pick
it out a little planter you grew right
on your porch
you grew it on the windowsill you grew a
little planter of dill
you got the microorganisms these are the
elevated biotics
that balance out our microflora no one's
talking about that no one knows they
exist
they're worried about what they can make
in the in in the in the
nutraceutical lab so they can sell you
guys stuff
and scam you on that that's what they're
doing
so scam you on all those probiotics scam
you on all that fermented food talk
scam you on all of that because i'm
making the marinated cucumber pickled
salad coming up by the way so hang
around for that
and but if you grow your own piece of
kale you grow your own parsley grow your
own dill you grow a cucumber someday
if you have anything like that and you
grow something grow your own sprouts on
your kitchen counter right grow your own
sprouts on your kitchen counter okay
marashini good to see you today
dr fond good to see you today darcy lee
womack
it's so surprising how many products
have been occurred have almost everyone
does
elizabeth good to see you
yeah i know elevated probiotics are
small microorganisms that live on living
foods
like your sprouts or your dill you grow
in your garden or something like that
when you pick it and put in your mouth
or you pick a blackberry and put it in
your mouth or you go to a farm where you
can pick your own food
and you pick it and you eat it right
there right you pick a strawberry and
you eat it right off the thing when
you're going to pick some strawberries
even if you do it once a year
the microorganisms on those strawberries
are the ones that go into your gut down
to your ilium and those are the ones
that help you those are the ones that
help you
but guess what even with all that said
those microorganisms
don't battle the bad ones because the
bad ones
never existed in our history until
classified medical research and science
messed around bugs
in the before 1920 around that time
and released the bugs like the spanish
flu
doris whichever book is this information
in this book right here by the way
is just so invaluable the information
that's in it just letting you know get
it free at the library
if you can't you know if you don't want
to partake in the 51
off on amazon.com us this is cleanse the
heal
okay so it's in there right and i have a
cleanse
in july i'm doing the mono eating
challenge you guys in july so i want you
to keep a lookout for that because we're
going to do
so if you have this book at least by
july
so we can all do the mono eating cleanse
together okay
um get through the library i hear people
are getting at the library thank
goodness the library are getting them in
but
amazon's 51 off okay this book has
information in it too about the gut as
well
even when you get the best
microorganisms you ever wanted in your
life you get the best microorganisms you
ever wanted
you pick some kale you pick some kale
out of your garden you pick some deal
out of your garden
and you're getting the best
microorganisms you could ever get and it
goes down into your helium
it's down in your helium okay it's down
there in your helium down here
right these microorganisms they still
don't fight the bad one the classified
medical recent research and science
put into our our world so that we would
be sick
and keep the medical industry running
so all the bugs that give everybody the
brain inflammation
the neurological information your
inflammation
gives them all the tingles numbness
aches and pains biggest nerve problems
all of it it's all those bugs so let's
go get a medium-sized bowl this is a
bowl right here i'm gonna put some um
i'm gonna put some lemon juice in here
so i'm making a dish let's get into this
this is a recipe right here and cleanse
the heal just so you know
check it out this recipe is i think it's
not in here i think it's a recipe i just
have
on the blog is what i think it is so
add some lemon juice so i'm going to
strain the lemon juice let me do that
here
two tablespoons freshly squeezed lemon
juice i'm doubling the recipe you guys
okay
i'm doubling the recipe squeezing some
lemon juice
margaret valentine good to see you
sage there's an audio book available on
amazon
on sale yeah on the cleanse with the
cleanser heel for sure
do uh two tablespoons i'm doubling the
recipe right here
some lemons these are juicy lemons you
guys
love lemon juice in my dressings on tick
tock
amazing
dr fun good to see you moderation and
balance is overrated
it truly is it's for the not sick people
it's for the not sick people you get
sick though
your moderation isn't going gonna take
you to uh the land of healing
lemon doesn't hurt teeth keep that in
mind
does the opposite does the opposite so
we're gonna pop some honey in here
so what we're gonna do
lemon is rich in calcium calcium that's
coming from the soil in the lemon tree
going up the roots of the lemon tree
into the lemon that's where your calcium
is right here you guys love all the
recipes
aw paula thanks on tick-tock amazing
amazing
so i'm gonna do is get a
[Music]
before here so i'm gonna add some honey
right here half a tablespoon of raw
honey
whisk that a little bit years of vinegar
and
and caffeine and high fat diets
pathogens and toxins makes jack a doll
boy
a sick boy
it's jack a sick boy
years of caffeine years of vinegar yeah
just mixing the lemon juice with the
honey right here you see guys just doing
a little whisk
right in this bowl right here
eventually jackets osteoporosis
osteopenia
lots of teeth problems missing teeth
you name it lots of dental work has to
be done
layla says all acidic foods will
dissolve
acidic foods will dissolve enamel rinse
mouth after
not true lemon juice is alkaline
inside the body it's alkaline inside the
body
playlist misinformation you have
right but that's right that's right you
got
you got the grenade in your hand i can't
i can't stop you from pulling the pin
i can't i can't stop anybody from
pulling the pin
right i want to stop people from pulling
the pen
i want to take that 100 yard dash and
just run around and be like no
no don't pull the pin it doesn't matter
how much i can tell you guys
you're going to get misinformations from
some vegan professional doctor
podcast person author or some other
person and
they have it all right
tastes sour doesn't mean it's acidic
inside the body
lemon tastes sour doesn't mean it's
acidic inside the body
it's got fruit acid but that's alkaline
it's alkaline
big difference right there
all right so what else is in here let's
start peeling back a cucumber
so what i'm doing is making
peeling these cucumbers up a little bit
okay this is an english
cucumber put me i'm gonna put these
these are nice thin you see this you
guys nice thin slices here
i can't tell you how many people or say
are new in the medical medium community
and they come here and they hear
what i'm saying and next thing you know
if they're on the internet
half an hour later and oh dr so and so
on this website says
oh apple cider vinegar is good for you
and it's like they're already lost lost
they just don't read the books florence
j
jenkins says why does lemon juice give
me a sore throat
and take the skin off my lips
is it lemon juice fresh from a fresh
lemon
it's a lot of lemon juice
you can buy lemon juice in a little
squeezy bottles containers that's
battery acid
that stuff is battery acid is what that
is
number one um
you know there's like every now and then
there's that person that gets like a
sore throat from lemon
is it lemon juice on its own
if it's straight lemon juice it's pretty
harsh
because it kills off all the bacteria in
your mouth
and when you do a kill off that serious
you might get a reaction when you use
something like that it's medicine
when you're doing lemon juice like like
if i took
if i took this lemon and i squeezed half
this whole lemon straight into my mouth
that would be sharp because that fruit
acid is really sharp
but it's also a bacteria killer if
you're somebody that has a lot of
h pylori don't even know it somebody
that's got all kinds of stuff they got
staffed they got strep in their system
don't even know especially h pylori if
they got e coli in their system
c diff in their system but they have all
that mouth bacteria
they're loaded with mouth bacteria and
don't know it load it with it everywhere
all in their mouth
and you drop that lemon straight in
there boom
yeah my brother's allergic
to the assets in citric sisters fruit
makes him break out so he's never broken
out before
you know be your own detective i love
when i hear that stuff
because so he never broke out never
broke out just living his life
never broke out never even knew what a
breakout is
has citra has an orange and breaks out
but never broke out ever
didn't break not breaking out thinks it
could have been the orange
but it wasn't it was the pizza from last
friday night and it took a little while
for the strep to cause an acne blast
you know we got to kind of like reel it
in a little bit we got to reel it in a
little bit
and just kind of like make sense out of
it so
okay gets breakouts from eating an
orange uh
okay but never had a breakout before
so or is it the breakouts come
constantly they come and go
one week it's a breakout one week it's
not one week it's a breakout one week
it's not had an orange oh it must have
been the orange one week it's a breakout
one week it's not
think about that right having pizza
having gluten having cheese having dairy
having whatever
uh five days later you get a breakout
must have been that lemon
i want you guys to succeed
like i want you guys to succeed
i don't want you to flounder
it's the last thing i want so the last
thing i want is you guys floundering
he says the last thing i want is you
guys floundering
that's a nightmare to me you guys
flatter i need you guys to have the
right info
it's amazing to me when someone's
blaming the healing tools
that are flushing out and getting rid of
the bad stuff inside of us that keeps us
sick amazing
don't point to the pizza my brother had
don't point to the caffeine my brother
had don't point to the chocolate bar my
brother had when he was at whole foods
point to the lemon that's what made the
breakout
wasn't the caffeine in the vinegar
wasn't the tacos with the cheese
wasn't the canola oil and the corn
no it was it was that there was the it
was the lemon
was it the corn wasn't the soy
so you guys i'll show you what this
looks like in a second california poppy
hey where you been california poppy i
haven't seen you in the comments section
that much
in uh in youtube we're brainwashed
to blame the healing tools california
poppy
great quote from california poppy
explain california poppy's really cool
every now and then california poppy will
pop up somewhere
on youtube comments be like this is how
it is you just gotta do the work
sarah elizabeth why is vinegar bad
try to listen to if you can get a chance
uh medical medium podcast
at apple podcast go to apple podcast
right
apple podcast you'll find medical medium
podcasts there
okay that's the uncensored podcast uh
platform of medical medium right listen
to the
apple cider vinegar podcast episode and
by the way
the moon meditation full moon check out
the moon meditation
at medical meeting podcast as well i'm
gonna be doing it tonight
three times is what i'm gonna do so
you'll probably catch me at one time
doing it i won't be live on here doing
it
because i'll be you know in my room
laying on the floor doing the moon
meditation and that's what i'm gonna be
doing it
all right and re listen to this live if
you can
please
marinating some nice
cucumber slices here
marinating don't need vinegar don't eat
vinegar you guys
don't need vinegar right
okay mix this this is marinating
right here so look at that see all the
cucumbers right there you guys on tik
tok
you guys i know in clubhouse you guys
can't see this but still you know i'm
doing it
okay now i'm gonna put a quarter cup of
thinly sliced red onion in there if you
guys
you guys let me i will do it you guys
need to know i'm at your service
bam it's the whole point
it's the whole point i'm at your service
right
i want you guys to have every
opportunity
you can use limes you don't have to do
lemons you can use limes
a lot of people out there that hate
lemon they love lime you know
you say tomato i say tomato but let's
not call the whole thing off
you can use the limes instead of lemons
right
learn to use limes and lemon is a
substitute lemon
if you need to on food you can use limes
on food you can put lime
on all your food substitute vinegar
okay to substitute vinegar all right so
let me get thinly sliced
let me get a real knife
you guys don't mind
so i'm going to thinly slice some red
onion right here
see you guys really thin slice
if you cut too fast you'll just do a
thick slice right you want to do real
just be nice and slow you want them as
thin as you can get right
nice and thin right you guys
there you go
i want you guys of every opportunity
possible
in my heart i want you to have every
opportunity possible okay
all right so i'm just going to cut that
in half like that pop these in
get that in there it's marinating i'm
going to put some dill in here to
put some hot pepper so marinating these
beautiful cucumber
thin cucumber slices this is a pickled
cucumber salad
hold the vinegar hold the vinegar
we live in a world where we there's
something inside of us
so let me get a tablespoon of fresh
chopped
pepper okay i'm gonna go with this one
right here
let me go with these these aren't as hot
these aren't as hot okay
these are these are peppers from uh i've
grown these i got a little tiny pepper
patch
right so right outside my window so i
grow some peppers
using the peppers right here i got super
chilies in here i grow
um there's microorganisms all over this
stuff the kind that actually
does help us help us produce b12 sherry
green dr sherry green good to see you
um your potato waffles are so good
incredible you made some amazing
so these are really hot but this this
pepper right here is just it's
dangerously hot i'm not gonna put it on
this
um that's something i would probably put
in a really good potato salad
but yeah
let's chop up some of these peppers this
one's not
as blazing hot heat units are down a
little bit
this is something i could see inside
this dish right here
so i'm just chopping these up
there we go put these on top of here
boom gonna watch out for the hot peppers
too make sure you don't rub your eye
been doing the moon meditation are you
gonna you uh pugsley bunny you're doing
the moon meditation i gotta mix this up
now
doing it tonight go to medical meeting
podcast you guys at apple podcast do the
moon meditation with me tonight i'll
just be on the floor
doing it i won't be live but i'll be
doing it three times tonight
so the optional deal i like putting in
here you can have the pepper or the dill
you can either either or i'm gonna put
some dill on here because how pretty is
that going to be
it is an option so i am going to do it
put some dill on here
nice
little dill on here too look at that
i'll show you guys guys i always tell
you
don't take the knife this way and pick
up your food and scrape your
your cutting boards with a knife going
with the blade side right
you're just going to scratch all the
wood up well you won't see it you'll be
scratching all the microfibers off the
wood
or the plastic or whatever kind of board
you have or glass you'll just be
scraping
you don't want to scrape you want to
flip your knife around you want to use
the side that's not the blade
and then you want to pick up stuff if
you want to pick it up off your board
like this right
i see people all the time do this where
they have this part of the knife and
they're picking it all up with
the sharp part and they're just they're
just going to be eating wood
and someone's going to complain they got
a tickle in their throat or something
you know
so much detail on the books you guys you
guys got to check it out read the
details they matter
if you don't have cleanse the heel pick
it up while it's on sale i don't know
how
generous amazon's going to be for how
long because they set the pricing
51 off in cleansing heal i'm doing a
mono
cleanse challenge in july
it's the book to have to be involved
with the challenge
if you don't have the book you can try
to fly it blind and go with whatever i'm
going to do but the book is important
letting you know prepare in july we're
doing a mono cleanse
challenge i want you guys to know
let's mix this uh beautiful salad up
so you got the lemon in here you got the
honey in here
and i got the peppers in here
if you guys really are into salt and
it's something you do
and you know and and i'm not into salt
really i think
too much salt is just too much problem
so i've talked about that with people
but
if you guys are going to do a little bit
of a healthy salt or something and you
want it as an
option to put a little touch on here to
taste you can all right
go into ig in a little bit and you can
add this dish this could be a side dish
this is just a beautiful dish check this
out
beautiful dish you guys on tick tock
it's a gorgeous dish
clubhouse i wish you could see it it's
an amazing dish
add this to your you know your salad if
you want you can take some of this put
it on a salad
you can do it that way you can have it
as a dish you could have it as a side
dish
you can mix things up in your life but
this is such an amazing food right here
and it's some medicinal food going to
tick-tock again
gonna have you guys turn back on i'm
gonna be putting
the uh ig instagram on in a little while
it won't take long this time you guys
will be doing instagram pretty soon so
just hang with
you guys coming over elizabeth are you
coming over to to ig
and are we all doing the moon meditation
tonight lorena
looks amazing doesn't it we all doing
the moon meditation tonight you guys
so i'm looking forward to it can't wait
medical meeting podcast is not the
podcast
all right this concludes another youtube
facebook tick tock clubhouse
event going to be turning it right back
on in a little while i hope you guys
join me