um if there's any time to actually do
the moon meditation it is during this
blue moon right here so i'm just letting
you know because i'm gonna be doing it
i'm actually really excited i actually
did it already this morning
i'm gonna do it later on tonight too the
meditation twice myself so
anyway we're live streaming right here
right now okay the medical medium got my
lemon balm tea
i'm actually excited about tonight and
the moon because
what a time like once in a lifetime
we're going to have a moon like we're
going to have once in a lifetime
i mean when i think about that i just
it's mind-blowing to me and then to
actually be able to do the moon
meditation it's that medical medium
podcast at apple podcast that's where
the moon meditation is
and you can just get it for free just
just listen to it for free
man i can't wait to do that because the
gravitational
pull okay the magnetic pull from the
moon the magnetic pull it's a whole
other thing what it does
to pull out hurt and anxiety and
distress
and worry right out of us and when you
do that
moon meditation on a night like this
with the blue moon
i mean how incredible that is on
halloween
oh my god i mean what a time to do the
moon meditation so i just had to like
get on here
tell you guys that i'm so pumped up i
mean i'm really pumped up about this i
can't even tell you i'm glad you guys
are coming on so i'm going to talk about
anxiety a little bit
talk about you know what people go
through how important it is to heal it i
got some foods i'm going to talk about
too
looks like i got a papaya right here
which is really cool too because i want
to talk about papaya
something you guys might want to get a
hold of some days that papaya
so i'm going to talk about that going to
talk about a couple other things too i
even have a couple supplements i take
when the stress gets
out of control and it just gets crazy
anyway
the moon meditation is it at it's at see
the little podcast sign right there
this medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast you guys got to hear the moon
meditation the reason why it's such a
big deal
is because we got the blue moon once in
a lifetime
and the moon meditation is powerful at
any time but
oh my god you do it during
the blue moon forget it on
halloween forget it so i'm just saying
you guys
if you want to extract that anxiety that
hurt
that that betrayal that might happen in
your life
from anything you've gone through any
struggles you've gone through you want
to suck that stuff right out of you you
want that poison to come out of you
you do the medical media moon meditation
and medical medium podcast at apple
podcast i'm just forewarning you guys so
you guys have a chance to really
jump on your healing because whoa what a
time to do it we're live right now
and you guys really i mean seriously
it's a big deal alexandra says
i had a huge release after the moon
meditation last night wait till you do
it tonight
alexandra i woke up with so much energy
this morning that i haven't had in over
a decade
alexandra i mean tonight with the moon
meditation oh my god link is in the
description you guys medical media
podcast at apple podcast link is in the
description
i'm just look i'm excited because i'm
going to do it i already did i did it
last night i did it this morning the
meditation and
and you know someone said to me like
well what do you have to worry about
who does the medical medium have to
worry about like are you kidding
all the censorship i get on me all the
other stuff that happens and everything
i got i'm stressed out absolutely what i
do is that moon meditation
sucks it right out pulls that poison
right out
and if you had anything going on in your
life because i got stuff going on in my
life of course because
i get discriminated against 24 7 by all
everywhere and stuff about it about
being the medical medium and
having this gift since age four and
being able to know advanced medical
information
like in the books cleanse the heel and
all the other books and
advance information about foods that
nobody knows about and what happens is
when you have all that
advanced information you get the crap
kicked out of you
that's what happens i've learned that
through my life that you're not allowed
to heal
people you're not allowed to get people
better did you guys know that you're
allowed to fake
fake it out there and do this and do
that and say hey this try this but
you're not allowed to actually
really provide answers to get people
better through the finish line like
really better and out of debilitating
diseases you're not allowed to do that
that's what i learned in life
anyway anxiety check this out okay
the anxiety podcast make sure you listen
to that one
that's a mind-blowing one right there
and a mind-blowing podcast episode
medically and podcasted apples
at apple podcast okay so the anxiety
episode
it's so packed with information i talk
about foods in that episode too i talk
about foods like papaya
in the anxiety episode did you hear it
did you hear that one did you hear that
part where i talk about the pesticides
and herbicides where people just order
pesticides that come to their lawn and
to come to their uh house and get their
houses sprayed did you hear that little
part where i was like hello
pesticide herbicide pesticide
insecticide company
did you hear that part in there i was
like uh can you come here and spray the
inside of my house in my yard
uh what do you mean my kids that my kids
are gonna be breathing it in is that
safe oh yeah it's safe
sure it's safe yeah okay it's safe to
talk about that you gotta hear that's on
the anxiety episode
anyway um you guys i get the lemon balm
tea this is what i do dude lemon balm
tea i also do like the vimergy lemon
balm right there
can you see it i'm not sure it's a
vimorji lemon bomb b isn't victor i
am e e-r-g-y um that's the one i do i'm
not sponsored by the way
by them um so you guys really important
to know like it's so anna says
is the meditation in the podcast um yeah
the moon meditation is in the podcast
the link is in the description
you don't want to miss this the blue
moon i mean
i mean come on a blue moon and the moon
meditation
a powerful powerful meditation that
already changes lives
just to do it any night any night of the
of the month doesn't matter if it's
quarter moon
half moon a partial moon but this is a
different
story here we're in october we are
we are you know halloween number one but
i mean number three or whatever but
we're in the blue moon
of a lifetime that's when
anything could happen with your healing
process during this meditation this moon
meditation
anything can happen anything just like
alexander was saying how her life
changed last night from doing it well
all i'm saying is get prepared because
it's going to suck the poison right out
of you
so any kind of emotional distress and
you know look
i love the moon meditation hand-in-hand
with the anxiety
episode so link is in the description
check out the anxiety episode i talk
about the tightness in the chest and
how people get crippled by anxiety you
guys
do you know do you know anybody who's
been through that crippled with anxiety
i'm not talking about oh i'm a little
nervous i got a little bit of anxiety
i'm talking about you can't even get out
of your bathroom off your bathroom floor
you can't get into your car and drive
you can't
[Music]
you can't get on the phone and talk to
someone you can't can't call a friend
and be like hey
what's going on because the minute
you're talking to them your anxiety is
creeping up i'm talking about
debilitating crippling anxiety you guys
we're live by the way
live streaming that's how i do it so
listen in this anxiety episode you'll
learn about what fruits and vegetables
to use
whoa you guys doing that
right there okay a bunch of squash
that's really awesome see that's it
right there
it's organic it's an organic one i got
lucky got lucky
so that's a squash right there this is
what it looks like
[Music]
so yeah i got a few foods here right
here so i
want to show you guys too lemon balm tea
like i said but that's a great food for
anxiety for healing
all the glucose that goes through the
brain look at that beautiful color in
there
phytochemical compounds that help
protect you i mean amazing food right
there so
see you guys i just want to go into the
moon meditation a little bit link is in
the description medical me and podcasted
apple podcast you guys subscribe
i don't know when the next episode's
coming out
i don't i don't know what hour or day
subscribe because then you'll know and
and
because it's not just enough to to
subscribe
on you know here on you know whatever
facebook or instagram whatever because
because the fact i'm so censored and so
it's important to actually
um it's important to actually know that
anyway
you can learn about what foods to do for
your anxiety what supplements to take
that are critical for your anxiety like
for anxiety if you don't have b12 going
on
it's gonna be hard to get it better
there's the vimergy b12
remember i'm not sponsored people are
always saying what's going on i'm not
sponsored by all the companies i always
talk about
um you know all the different you know
as far as supplement
companies and stuff this is a free
resource free
resource this podcast i just want to say
this
okay just bear with me for one second
you guys okay
this podcast is not a throwaway
coffee talk thing i know i said that
last time but check this out i just want
to make sure the new people to know this
and this is a docu-series podcast
this is information that can save your
life
save a life save someone else's life
this is
life-changing information that the
nuggets are all
in there this isn't like you bring some
guests on next wrong
cattle call them come on uh let's go up
do you want to come on my show do you
want to call my show okay come on
gone gone it's not that this is
literally a docu-series
that i'm doing for free you don't have
to pay for it i put it in a podcast
like what like what who does that who
does that i mean i'm doing it because
hey
i need you guys to heal i need you guys
to heal um
uh marcellus says just jumped in here
what is lemon balm for
i use it personally for me for like
stress
uh other people use it for anxiety
that's what they use it for
all right that's the vimergy one these
in victor i
m e e r g y that's the best one out
there
it's the cleanest cleanest company that
i've found yet if another one comes
along you'll see them holding their
stuff up that's it that's how it works
with me
um if there's a better wild blueberry
company that comes along you'll see me
holding up another wild blueberry stuff
like company whatever so
you know like i do because wyman's is
the one i like with that one but the
bottom line you guys is
is that it's about healing healing
healing
do you want to get better do you want
things to get
better do you want your life to change
do you want information that's already
saved millions of lives around the
planet the medical medium information
the street cred is in it's already saved
lives for
not only decades but just in the last
six years
in an enormous amount of people i just
want you guys
to know how to heal the moon meditation
if you miss your chance for the moon
meditation
on blue moon night
i i don't know what to say and i had to
get on here to tell you link is in the
description
the moon meditation medical medium
podcast at apple podcast that's the
platform to listen to it and if it's
another platform it's going to be
censored
and even if you hear the episode at
another platform it's still missing
pieces
i share emotional tools in the anxiety
episode
letting you know you know and i talk
about what happens is when you have ocd
ocd depersonalization
bipolar with anxiety so i even talk a
little bit about that when you have
anxiety with bipolar do you know anybody
with that
ocd with bip with not bipolar well you
can have those two together too which
usually they do come
hand in hand sometimes so ocd with
anxiety depersonalization with anxiety
depression
depression with anxiety
i mean the anxiety episode hands down
this thing is unbelievable constance
good to see you
i love you too you know you guys and
look if you have an android phone i just
saw that come up there on the
on the comments if you have an android
phone um
go to medicalmedium.com you'll see in
the menu right there
okay and see podcast in the menu listen
to it there if you have an android and
you don't have an apple device
um and anna says i almost healed my
migraines
with your information i'm so grateful to
you i'm so glad you're working on that
i'm so glad you're working on that are
you guys do you know anybody dealing
with crippling anxiety or even mild
anxiety tightness of the chest
um you're racing thoughts where your
racing thoughts are going in and out
you feel restriction around the throat
you feel like
you're tremoring you feel weird funny
feelings in the gut and the stomach you
feel
all that stuff going on um
uh sunday's in hey good to see you glad
you're glad you're here today
um anxiety podcasts like listening about
my life
so amazing thank you so much for
understanding what we suffer
love your humor makes me laugh i'm so
glad you're okay with the humor
um michelle l michelle do the meditation
over and over thank you for letting
people know michelle
because that's what i'm trying to tell
everybody too it's like it's important
to do them over and over these are not
the normal meditations these actually
come from above they come from above
and it's so important it's so important
to use them to heal it's so important
nadine says which of your books will
help me with anxiety
i got one right here whoa
all right that's cleanse the heel this
is a heavy medical textbook
75 recipes i'll give you guys a quick
rundown on this okay
i know some of you guys have the book
but first of all amazon.com is 51
off it's 16.99 it's unbelievable the
sale for this book
i mean only that kind of sale it's
incredible what's happening right now
and this is a really heavy book and i'll
tell you what's in it okay
it's got 75 recipes there's a recipe
book in here that's just one thing
the other thing is over 200 symptoms and
conditions
where you learn the cause of your
symptom and condition
then you learn what supplements to take
in dosages
and all the information in here i mean
it's packed with information
you can go in here and you can just look
you can find anything bridge riddle
nails just open it up it's like you have
bridge
uh ridge nails boom that's what it is
look i got like it's just it's packed
with information in here depression what
to do
for it um diabetes
okay what you could do for it and it
just keeps on going dry cracked skin
ear infections i mean when you go
through edema eye floaters fibromyalgia
i mean
it's just over 200 symptoms and
conditions in here okay information plus
cleanses
if you're interested i'm just saying in
a book this is a powerhouse right here
it's a medical medium cleanse the heel
book put it right there right here
so in anxiety i talk about what to do
for anxiety in that book too
i mean if i had anxiety i'd have that
book in my hand
i would listen to the anxiety episode
and
look get the book free at the library if
you want if you don't want to get it
like
dirt cheap off of amazon right now get
it free to library but the point is you
guys
is like i just want you to get better
what more can i do
what can i do um i could teach you about
all the foods that heal
i could do that i could teach you about
all the different
herbs that heal and how they heal i
could do that too you know
and that's what i'm doing i can get the
books and information and then the
docu-series podcast
the link is in the description don't
miss out on those episodes the anxiety
episode is something you don't
want to miss out listen to it over and
over again because i can guarantee you
this
i can tell you this i can guarantee this
you're going to miss out on all the bits
and pieces many of them in that episode
because it's too packed with information
there's so much information it's not
insulting to anyone
it's respectful where i'm trying to say
i'm going to give you everything i got
i'm not going to hold anything out let
me just give you everything i got in
this episode
so that i respect you guys you're like
your time and your energy so when you
listen to it
you're only getting nuggets nugget
nugget nugget nugget nugget
i mean really anyway the blue moon
once in a lifetime right the moon
meditation
if you're not doing it tonight come on
you know so that's a really important
thing right there so
you guys so much to learn so much to do
jennifer says i love this book
incredible i'm so glad that you love the
book it's so important
um you guys we can heal we can heal
we can we can all right um
amy bachelor book is amazing amy you're
the best incredible thank you for being
on here today i'm actually blown away
christine says how do we find right site
for tonight
okay well it's medical medium podcast
at apple podcast the link is in the
description
so you can get the moon meditation
that's the whole thing the moon
meditation is for free
the link is in in the description right
here so you can actually get to it and
then
subscribe to the medical meeting podcast
so that you don't
lose the medical meeting podcast and
never get an episode or something again
okay so important um yeah you guys
so let's just quick run down right there
i just saw lorraine's here too
lorraine l so glad just look you guys i
just
i just want you to get better so i want
to make sure i can give you all the
tools right
you guys doing bananas because i never
want you afraid of these right here
that's a really healing food
i've talked about it so many times over
the years i love it for anxiety bananas
are incredible because of the glucose
that goes through the brain
really important right there potassium
is an electrolyte that's an electrolyte
that potassium
that potassium goes to the brain for
emotional stuff that's the whole point
are you guys i'm actually gonna eat this
half a papaya
um probably going to steam this this
baby up right here this this squash
that winter squash i'm just showing you
some tools
i'm going to take a little bit more
lemon balm later look
um get your lemon balm tea do that do
that
look i want you guys to make sure that
you get all the things you need so
the blue moon the meditation the moon
meditation
did not lose out on that right now you
could do it every day of the month
because it heals you
every day but right now is such a prime
time for it
link is in the description i love you
and just hang in there
all that you're going through know that
i care catch the anxiety podcast episode
and uh look out for the new episode
coming out okay because there's a new
episode coming out
tomorrow there's a new episode coming
out tomorrow
yep anyway trisha marie says i love
bananas you're awesome
you're awesome okay you guys bye-bye