we're live right now
live and once again we're doing a sneak
peek into these books right here when
you guys get these books your mind is
going to be blown
mark my words
it's going to be blown i'll tell you why
because
i've been going into these books and
re-reading and i just can't believe what
was put into these books i'm gonna talk
about neurological stuff and a lot of
different symptoms i'm gonna give you a
sneak peek into these books but
seriously guys and they're 40 off right
now which is insane insane they're
hundred dollar books and they're listed
now for 29.26
if you ordered the book at a higher
price it's changed now because when they
do ship the book out you're gonna get
the lowest price so it doesn't even
matter and you won't be charged on your
card until the book is shipped
right
so you know you don't have to worry
there uma kelly yep surprise live so i
just want to tell you guys like when you
have these books in your hands you're
you're not going to see anything out
there in the world like this it doesn't
exist and i said earlier that before the
medical medium books there was just eat
better books
it was just eat better books that's all
it was
that's all there was and then if you had
a symptom like
your
jaw felt crooked your gums hurt your
tongue burned your eyes
flickered your you you had you know
floaters in the eyes you had tingles and
numbness you had fatigue your legs felt
like sandbags there wasn't a single book
or anything in existence before the
medical medium books
if you had bell's palsy
and bad sciatica there wasn't a book out
there if you had hashimoto's
fibromyalgia if you had als if you had
ms you had anything
there wasn't a book out there for any of
these symptoms neurological symptoms and
everything medical medium books they
broke the mold right so people for the
first time ever found out what was wrong
with them but
but get this
and you guys already know the history
with cleanse the heel
how insane this book is and how many
people are healing around the world when
you guys get a hold of these books i
just saw thyroid healing back there too
when i moved the book when you guys get
a hold of these books you i you won't
believe your eyes
it's going to be a mind-blowing
experience
every other sentence and it really is
this is different i mean this is another
level
of medical medium information that's
going to change how health is out there
just like the other books have you know
like neurological lyme they now test
repsting var with lyme why are they
testing for epstein barks medical medium
said i've seen bars behind lyme disease
and now all the lyme doctors are kind of
not caring about the bacteria myth in
theory anymore they're actually all
looking for epstein-barr it's incredible
what the medical union books have done
reserving a book is critical and i know
look
i get it i'm doing it live right now
this is my third live talking about the
brain saver books
blah blah blah
but you got to reserve a book
because
when when the books are released they'll
sell out real quick that's what happens
with the medical media books and then if
you're sick or you have a symptom or you
really need it for a friend or you need
it for a neighbor or a family member or
a loved one you gotta wait and you gotta
wait a long time possibly so reserving a
book is critical you're not gonna get
charged for it
and
it's so inexpensive
and i have people tell me every day a
friend of mine said
i had a i had a friend over right a
practitioner friend over to hang out for
a little bit known for years and he
grabbed on to these and he said this is
incredible
he goes but why are you doing this i'm
like what are you talking about why
don't you chop these up
into like
like books like smaller books or why
don't you and he's sitting here trying
to figure out how i can make money
he says
why don't you make programs out of these
books and just
and just literally everybody has to do
this they have to pay for the program or
whatever i go no
no i i want to make sure everybody has
at their fingers fingertips dirt cheap
in cost at their fingertips they have
answers to all the different
neurological conditions and brain
conditions and mental health issues so
they have answers so they can heal
so many people are in crippling agony
with their anxiety their depression
when you guys read the depression
chapters it's almost like oh my god
i talk about how the soul is intertwined
with the depression
issue and it's intertwined in the brain
and i talk about how that works with
depression
anyway the ocd the bipolar and that's
just a couple little things i'm going to
go into a couple of a bunch of the
symptoms and conditions in here you guys
good to see you guys coming on here
we're obviously live right now we're on
tick tock
telegram youtube rumble
facebook we're all over the place right
now and so anyway you guys we're in the
brain saver books right here
these are them reserving a copy of both
and that's another thing too like making
sure you have both because the book was
this
before we crack into these books do
sneak peek look the book was this i went
to the publisher and i was like
like
you guys there
they opened the door and i went
and they said what the hell is this
what is this and i said this is the book
no press is gonna print that it's just
not gonna happen so we had to break them
apart
two books and they're gonna be two big
books bigger than cleanse the heel right
here so you're gonna get two books just
letting you know
in every line
is informative
mind-blowing
advanced you guys become experts in
neurological health
experts way before anybody else experts
in mental health
have you noticed everybody's going
mental out there
because they are it's crazy what's
happening in the world today people are
suffering
struggling with mental health conditions
that are getting so bad
and so
you're going to be experts at why people
are suffering and struggling with all
the different levels right so this is
the cleanse of heal but i'll show you
the size of the book that's going to be
so here they are right here link is in
the description link is in the bio right
here
okay you won't be disappointed when you
have these in your hand
right
yes so miranda so many mental health
conditions out there it's crazy
what's happening i feel so bad for
people
40 off
amazon us right now okay 35 off amazon
uk
it's incredible so let's let's crack
into a little bit of this do a little
sneak peek right here so i'm excited
about this so we'll start with brain
saver
right
both books are critical they work off
each other so important to know
so what about idiopathic and cranial
hypertension yes i have it in the books
i feel so good to say that because i
just want you better and i want you to
have the answers
and so when i was doing these books over
300 symptoms and conditions
like i knew right
i knew i was going to be asked these
questions right like what about this
what about that
deborah carbone says i can't control my
sweatiness especially around my head and
face and i have it in here
i have here in excessive sweating i have
in these books
you guys this is fun because you know i
feel like i can help
i feel like i can help because i have it
in here
so and it will help so i'm so so happy
about this good to see you guys courtney
good to see you courtney may you guys so
i'm in here right now let me just crack
this baby open right
so all right so
i'm in here right now in one of the
brain saver books okay now when you're
ordering these books you got to order
both of them the links are in the
description link in the bio right there
so you have to order both
it's important okay you don't get
charged until it shipped
and you get the lowest price when it
shipped ring in the ears yep
mary chase i have that in here for sure
definitely the ringing in the ears
okay so i'm in here now so i have a
chapter on anxiety right here hardcore
hard-hitting chapter and anxiety laura
ludwig says what are the best foods for
the brain
packed with info on the foods for the
brain in here
packed
there's a difference with the medical
medium information when there's food for
the brain
in the medical medium books
it means foods for the brain versus
um you know feel better books and eat
better books and all those books out
there that talk about you know food
science and foods and
okay good luck good luck getting better
with that info because it doesn't work
unless you know why you're sick what's
wrong and really what food to use
advanced heavy metal detox in here
cleanses in here 14 cleanses so i mean
here anxiety
this is an anxiety chapter right here
but it's unlike not no other
that i've ever done so it's so packed
with information on not only the causes
of your anxiety like why do you have a
panic attack what happens where is it
stemming from what's the cause what's
your anxiousness you know what's what's
the you know not just a panic attack why
is your chest all tight what's happening
with the vagus nerve all of that in
detail that's just the anxiety chapter
alone right
i have a depression chapter in here okay
that talks about how come someone
suffers with that
that
unexplainable
depression that people have where it's
just you can't explain it you can't it's
just i'm depressed
but what is it someone's feeling you
know how if you've ever been through
that and you had that depression and you
just can't express it to someone or even
tell them because it just doesn't work
it's like meaning like you can't get it
across they just don't understand your
depression like no one can understand
and unless they felt it too unless they
know i talk about why it even happens
what someone's feeling it's so
enlightening when you actually dig into
here
you guys
i mean seriously that incredible okay so
depression chapter is huge because it's
packed
with mind-blowing information the ocd
chapter that's a big one right there
okay
because what the industry's trying to do
and i'll give you this little tidbit
right here yeah what the industry is
trying to do is the industry is trying
to pack
is trying to pack up every single mental
health condition there ever was and
they're eventually gonna funnel it into
an ocd label they're doing that
they're doing that to deceive people
okay
so they're gonna make sure that
everything's that your anxiety is ocd
and what i thought i had anxiety no it's
ocd they're going to make sure that
everybody that has any issue at all
with their their emotional state they're
going to funnel it and create this just
one big
label of ocd
and then they're going to turn against
people who have ocds this is incredible
protective information to protect people
with ocd
protect them help them understand it
empower them
it's like no other what i love about the
ocd chapter i talk about
how it really happens inside the brain
like what happens to create that ocd to
the letter it is unbelievable
if you guys just got here we're talking
about the brain saver books make sure
you get your copies
okay when you get the chance make sure
you get your copies all right
and uh my cover moves around a little
bit you're they're not gonna look like
this these are my manuscripts right here
you guys
but make sure you get a hold of the
brain saver book
both these links are in the description
link in the in the bio right there okay
so bipolar disorder
that's an incredible chapter all in its
own right i talk about how that happens
and when you read it you'll just be like
how's this possible that this
information's here in our hands now
alzheimer's in dementia all right now
some people just be like hey i don't
have alzheimer's i'm not worried about
that i'm never gonna get alzheimer's uh
there's a lot of people now they're 20
years old and 25 years old they're gonna
have alzheimer's
they're gonna have it
alzheimer's is gonna be one of the big
boys down the road dementia and
alzheimer's what people are going to see
is people aren't going to just be dying
they're not going to be dying of cancer
and heart disease
all the time or stuff like that's not
going to be the leading things in the
end when they're 80 years old or
whatever they're going to be
sick and dying of alzheimer's and
dementia at 60 years old 50 years old 40
years old
we're going to go into a place in the
next 10 15 years where
everybody's like not everybody but so
many people are getting alzheimer's or
versions of it and versions of dementia
brain rot and i i talk about that like
this is really
an incredible tractor on its own okay
so i'm just giving you a little sneak
peek into
some of this right
which is really cool
okay
all right
so symptoms and conditions answers to
symptoms and conditions these are like
chapters in here
okay so addiction
right i talk about addiction i talk
about
adhd
right als als is another big one
around the corner for people
no one knew all these different symptoms
were neurological symptoms by the way
years ago the medical medium books
medical medium lectures and information
that i taught out there was putting the
dots together
you can go to a neurologist years ago
and they won't know your symptoms
neurological i can't tell you how many
patients dealt with that like i have
this headache or i have this or i have
this little tingle or i have this and
just didn't even i have fatigue and they
didn't know it was neurological
right
the neurologists of the old day didn't
even know what these people's symptoms
were they'd be like oh you got asthma
they wouldn't know you had neurological
asthma they would just like oh you got
asthma go to a pulmonologist see you
later and go see a psychiatrist when you
can too that's a neuro that's what
neurologists used to do all the time go
see a psychiatrist
and go to a pulmonologist oh you know
look i'll here's here's a guy to see
here you go
meanwhile they're dealing with all these
neurological symptoms right
and anything in mental health that's a
neurological symptom by the way
and people didn't know that years ago
it's medical medium information
so kim culver says lesions with no
explanation absolutely and i have a
lesions explanation in here big time all
the different lesions deborah ann usher
says what about schizophrenia totally i
have schizophrenia in these books
jennifer borderline personality yes all
of that in here that's what's incredible
it is packed you guys
you won't go wrong with these books you
won't go wrong you know like
when i stand behind something you guys
know like i'm passionate about it i
stand behind it and i'm like you know
putting my voice out there saying look
you know it always comes true you know
the books are always that good they save
people they help people
this is a level that i've never done
spirit of compassion
made sure
that this was a level like
getting ready for what's to come what
we're up against all of it right
so
i'm in here right now and i'm just kind
of walking through you walking you guys
through this a little bit anorexia
eating disorders
god i have an eating disorder chapter in
this book that's just mind-blowing
when you guys read it you'll be like oh
my god what this is
just
unreal
so
anorexia anxiety right um anxiousness
arteriosclerosis
auditory processing disorder
right autism okay those palsy balance
issues and dizziness
bipolar yeah i've already said that
earlier brain abscesses
it's a little more rare but people get
them right i wanted it in here i want
everything in here brain fog that's more
common i got it in here with an
explanation of brain fog
right brain inflammation people walk
around with mild encephalitis don't even
know and they're sick they're sick they
have no answers right
brain lesions white spots dark spots
scar tissue and calcifications people
have all these calcifications in their
brain they've got calcium deposits
they've got scar tissue in their brain
they've got dark spots in their brain
they've got white spots
in the gray matter they got brain
lesions
i talk about all of that in detail so
you understand what's going on
which can save a life because when
someone understands they won't get their
brain opened up a lot of people opt for
elective brain surgery because they're
worried about a brain spot right and
then now they have a brain surgeon
cracking open their skull
and playing with their lesion and then
putting it back together and the
person's like never the same again
like this is critical stuff right here
and a lot of people
in the the new mris that are coming out
are gonna be even a little bit more
sensitive and they're gonna pick up more
so many people are gonna have all these
speckles on their brain and it's gonna
bring on this like crazy like
madness of what do we do what do we do
millions of people are going to be
seeing all their brain spots because
people have brain spots they talk about
this in here right so there's that
i mean
it's incredible stuff
right
brain tumors insist breast implant
illness really thorough
thorough
section
in that right there miranda mccollus
speech issues yes definitely in here i
cover that
right
so i mean the
this so so interesting right you guys
john ricciano says what about brain mass
loss definitely my god i cover that in
here for sure i have to that's so
important and i got in here bulimia
burnout the whole brain burnout thing
cerebral atrophy
did you hear what i just said losing
when you said uh losing um brain mass
and i just got to the spot here cerebral
atrophy with a whole bunch of
information in here about that
ken says preventative measures for all
the plastics oh my god anything where do
you do the cleanses augustina speech
delay children yes cover that too
cerebral hypoxia you know people get the
mild strokes and they don't know what
they get the mild strokes
right and other things too and i explain
it all in detail cerebral palsy right
cerebral vascular disease chronic anger
disorder
how many people have anger and they
don't know why and it feels like it's
bursting out of them and they don't want
to they're so tired of it and they know
it hurts others around them and it hurts
them and they feel like it hurts them
and they can't describe it but they get
perturbed so easily and they get thrown
off so easily and they have this
this really it's almost like you can't
it's it's not even stoppable and the
anger is always there right that's tough
one for so many people to trust the
white debilitating migraines yes always
make sure those migraines be in here too
right courtney cohen mental health and
teenagers
definitely all these books are for
teenagers too when moms can and moms and
pediatricians their doctors can work
with these books with the kids cold
white spring may what's going on
explosive anger went away from me with
medical medium information incredible
and that explosive anger is so
so hard on people it's crippling for
people
here's one right here chronic mystery
guilt that's that's one right there
people they just always feel that guilt
always feel that guilt and i talk about
what's happening inside the brain to
make that happen
cushing's syndrome right
hyper cortisol right
cushing's that's it that's one right
there that i wanted to make sure i had
in here was cushions a lot of people
have cushions right
dementia
depersonalization i made sure people
understood that depersonalization you
know so many people have it where they
disconnect it from themselves and they
don't even feel like they exist
but then they come out of it and then
they feel guilt and they feel pain and
depression and then they go back into it
and they just they feel like they're
gone
they're just lost they're numb and don't
feel like they don't feel anything
hannah t good to see you and they they
don't feel like they you know they feel
just lost it's the personalization they
feel like they're missing out on
something all the time they feel a
sadness and they can't explain it they
feel like they can't connect to somebody
else and talk to them they feel like
they don't hear them when someone's
talking to them that they don't they
can't even hear the person talking to
them right hannah says yes that's how it
feels
yeah
um centaur's healing said the
personalization is so hard to go through
so you must have gone through so much
alexander sophia says what about grief
does that happen to the brain exactly
that's what we're talking about all of
that and what happens if you guys just
came on here life-saving books right the
brain saver book here brain saver
protocols both of them are important
40 off amazon.com us right now which is
incredible if you bought it at a higher
price it goes to the lower price
so you don't have to worry when the book
gets shipped when the time the book gets
shipped they give you the lowest price
at the time right
so but reserving the books are critical
you don't get charged on your card
i don't even know what to say like this
is incredible you don't get charged on
your card you can reserve it and not get
charged on your card every time i like i
hear that i'm just like what it's
incredible
so depersonalization so many people are
going through you just order the books
betty amazing i can't wait for you to
get them i can't wait for you to get
them i really can't so i'm going through
some more of these
reserving reserving the books are
critical you guys because it's hard to
get you know things it's hard to get
things fast with what's going on in the
world too it's another thing on its own
depression or dysphoria so many people
get diagnosed with dysphoria right
difficulty coping
how many people have a hard time coping
i mean the information in here is just
it's legendary these books i just know
when i go through these it's just like
oh my god
we're just we're just gonna be doing so
much so much good for the world right
dysautonomia that's in here too dyslexia
how about that
whole thing on dyslexia i've never gone
there before i've never had a chance
it's in this brain book these brain
books
eating disorders
oh my god omg
the eating disorders okay
that's a whole nother game when you read
the eating disorders and learn about
those whoa
whoa
amazing right
so you order both of them
um
cumbernauld
orange incredible
eating disorders encephalopathy so many
people are going to develop that in
these next coming years they're already
developing that you hear that there's
pockets and clusters of people and
they're they're losing their minds right
now
their brains just like getting eaten up
you're gonna see a lot of that you guys
you're gonna see a lot of that happening
where there's clusters and doctors and
small towns are noticing it because in
the cities they don't keep track of that
stuff
they don't right
but they're seeing clusters of it in
small towns around the world in villages
where groups of people they're just
brains are getting eaten eaten up eating
up
and in the big cities and in all that
they keep that all under wraps no one
talks about it doesn't even matter but
they're noticing it in the villages and
the towns around the world
people's brains are basically
dissolving like at 40 years old 50 years
old whatever i mean it's incredible
what's happening
anyway encephalopathy
these books are going to be the key
i don't expect everybody to get a book
i expect you know anybody to find it i
expect hopefully a lot of people find it
but i know that the world is just
there's everybody gets derailed with all
the different trends and things and
but these are life-saving in here for
people when they do come to that
realization that they need this book or
they get led but you know divinely led
steph c says this is literally bringing
me to tears because i finally feel like
i'm not going crazy
it just it hurt i feel for you i truly
do i feel for you
encephalopathy right excessive sweating
hyperhidrosis you know the sweating
where everybody gets they go to try to
get the surgery they cut the sympathetic
nerve and all that and people go through
all that
god
it's brutal i mean when we can fix it in
other ways
we don't have to get like radical
surgeries all the time and we can you
know we can save that for when our heart
valve blows up
when we're 80 right but we it's like
yeah it's sad people are getting
surgeries for excessive sweating i mean
we can fix that without doing a surgery
information is here right
fibromyalgia classic
fibromyalgia right big time you guys
coming on here i'm just doing sneak peek
in both the brain books make sure you
order them if you can if you see this
make sure you order them links are in
the description
make sure you do that i mean look do
what you need to do with your life and
i'm not trying to you know twist your
arm so you can get a book i'm just
saying if you got a symptom or a
condition i'm telling my friends i'm
telling my family i'm telling all of
them to make sure that they
order the book right
focus and concentration issues i got
that in here too neurological is not
just the brain
oh i didn't know that
i'm just being sarcastic okay
neurological is a whole central nervous
system medical medium books are the
first books
to know that neurological isn't just the
brain
okay
no one knew any of the neurological
symptoms neurological fatigue is medical
medium information doctors are using all
the medical medium information now
doctors took
information from this book from seven
years ago and they just released now
that ebv causes multiple sclerosis
and i talk about how it creates multiple
sclerosis and it's not just brain
related nervous system instead
of course
gastroparesis don't you love when it
happens it's like you do all this in the
world and get information out about the
nervous system you're teaching doctors
teaching the world they're taking the
information then someone says you don't
know what you're talking about it isn't
just the brain
but no i appreciate you being here i
know that you're you're a kind-hearted
person you're here thank you
gastroparesis
the neurological gastroparesis
right guillain-barre syndrome which
guess what is happening like man
like popcorn out there every time like
people are just like
getting guilambre syndrome as fast as a
popcorn maker's
popping those kernels i mean it's crazy
out there what's happening
popcorn not a not a great food to eat i
talk about that in the book
headaches
right
hemisphere hems facial neglect jennifer
says cured my gastroparesis thanks to
you
incredible thank you for being here i'm
so proud of you
my god proud of you
huntington's disease
right huntington's okay inflammatory
myopathy myopathy
ran into a doctor the other day
a friend of mine and he's like myopathy
myopathy i'm seeing it everywhere in my
practice i'm like yeah you're gonna see
a lot more than that
coming up
insomnia
inter intracranial hypertension there we
go i found the section in detail of how
it's caused
nobody knows in medical history right
now how it's cost this is the first of
its kind that's going to get out there
so people know why it's cost they don't
know why
you guys i'm just that excited
i just came on here
brain saver right here
brain saver protocols right there it's
two books 40 off amazon.com us make sure
you get it
let's keep on going
right itching and burning
itching and burning
mysteriously everywhere either anywhere
anywhere everywhere
joint muscle pain right man
just in detail about how that works
power compassion i'm excited too i can't
wait for you to get the books
learning disabilities and disorders how
about that
long haul bleep and long-haul flu
long-haul bleep
and long-haul flu
right
incredible
lupus that's one right there lyme
disease that's another one right there
okay
i mean really incredible
chronic fatigue syndrome me chronic
fatigue syndrome in general right
neurological fatigue memory loss and
forgetfulness
okay
i mean i'm just going through some of
these you guys this book is insane
shellyanne doctors are trying to benefit
from the information you gave us years
ago so you know my god shell you know
that's what i thought when i saw a
doctor on tv say ms is caused by ebv
unbelievable
meniere's disease oh by the way they're
taking my information on meniere's
disease i was the only one that said
veneers isn't crystals inside your ear
it's neurological and it's viral
and guess what
all these years
all these years the best medical clinics
there were said that meniere's disease
was just crystals in the air did you
know they just changed it recently
taking it from medical medium published
material
you know what
when we leave this place down down down
the road
yeah
you know you have to deal with that kind
of stuff it's like
you know what i mean no integrity
just completely compassionless doesn't
want anybody to actually have the
answers to heal
man
it's crazy so you know in here i got
migraines in here i already told you
about that earlier
right meningitis
right
let's keep on going a little bit
mitochondria myopathy that's one right
there it's interesting mood changes i go
into depths about mood changes right how
many people the mood changes you guys
okay
i mean multiple sclerosis of course
the first
epstein-barr information and where it
came from right here
multiple motor skills disorder
dyspraxia mylar nerve sheath damage
chronic inflammatory d-myelinitis you
know right mystery fears and worries how
many people have mystery fears and wars
like what are you afraid of
like how many people have mystery fears
and mystery worries
right we have fears that we fear we have
other things but mystery fears and
mystery worries
that's when right there it's gonna be
really helpful for somebody
mystery nausea
and mystery vomiting but mystery nausea
it's a big one narcolepsy that's a big
one there
you guys just
it just goes on and on and on i mean it
just goes on i'm gonna crack into the
protocols uh book a little bit too i
mean there's just so much here i can go
on forever
with all the different symptoms and
conditions and that's just some of the
stuff in here
once you read this book you'll learn a
lot of things and it's it's like endless
you just to get through this book it's
endless the information here it's so
incredible
your info kim miller says your info has
healed my
hypochondria
incredible
so happy about that i am
put this baby back up here so these are
the books right here you guys
two books released at one time first of
its kind no publisher would ever let an
author do it plus authors don't have it
in them from what i heard from my
publisher to do two at the same moment
like this so it's the first of its kind
two books at the same time and the
reason why is i have to make sure you
guys have everything you need to heal
and protect yourself and it's not just
protecting your brains protecting your
body protecting your loved ones
protecting everything that matters to
you in your health in your life
fiona says people are hearing about your
info from other sources absolutely
they are
right
but you know that's just the way things
roll
all right so i got another book right
here i got the protocols book right here
and remember i want to remind you guys
there's 14 cleanses in here there's an
advanced heavy metal detox cleanse
there's seven
levels
of heavy metal detox in this book
seven levels heavy metal detox
there's something
that i put a
like therapy in these books that's
called brain
shot
therapy
so that's that alone is going to help so
many people brain shot therapy okay
yeah
the problem is when people learn medical
mean information from other sources out
there they don't get pointed back to the
original source instead
they get given things that can hurt your
health they'll get told to activate a
charcoal which will literally tear your
guts up
ruin your intestinal tract environment
it could take years to restore your
intestinal tract environment after using
activated charcoal so
that's just one example of so many right
anyway the point is they don't know how
to get back to the original source so
there's so many tidbits floating out
there right
it also you know what's interesting
about medical medium information getting
out there like just say celery juice
people will be drinking celery juice
and the celery juice will be keeping
them level
while they're doing all this bad stuff
and trendy stuff that's hurting their
body but they don't know what the celery
juice is keeping the bad stuff from
harming them so much so they're taking
all this other stuff that's bad for them
like pearl powder a bad collagen a bad
this about that they're hurting their
guts and their body
and then the celery juices actually
keeping them afloat allowing them to
hurt themselves with the other stuff
it's like crazy it's like you go to
practitioners like oh good you're
drinking celery juice oh great i hear
it's good for you yeah yeah you can keep
that going but here keep up the my
collagen keep up my pearl powder keep up
my fulvic minerals keep up my shilajit
keep up my activated charcoal keep up my
bentonite clay keep up my meanwhile
you're tearing your guts apart to shreds
you're actually you're actually worse
than conditions but the celery juice is
keeping you so you kind of don't know it
so it's allowing unfortunately when you
don't know where the source of
information comes from it allows
people to just
sell all their garbage to people and
keep them from getting so sick so fast
celery just keeps kind of hides what the
other stuff is doing to them they won't
notice as much not like the old days
so let's go into the protocols
a little bit
an interesting point right
you fell for the activated charcoal trap
a sling
yeah
it's a nightmare
so i'm in the protocol book right now
you guys came on here
okay
here we are
you guys came on here there we go
protocols that's the one i'm on both
books you want the links in the
description
so i'm in here right now
i'm in medical medium protocols
right
these things are
something else actually kind of wheeled
around
woohoo so excited to read it sofia i am
too sophie
so here we are medical meaning protocols
right here i talk about everyday brain
health and maintenance right
and i got the protocols in here
supplements and dosages right i talk
about how you can apply them in your
life right
i mean supplements and dosages to like
so many different problems it's insane
how many different problems addison's
disease i'm just looking there's just so
many right addiction
right als
supplements and dosages to alzheimer's
so we can bring our loved ones back
you know what i love i love when
i have somebody who has alzheimer's or
dementia and i get them on a protocol
because their family puts them on the
protocol
and they start coming back
and they start getting their life back
and now they're talking and now they're
able to dress themselves
and now they're able to sit at the the
dining room table
and start talking and when you see that
happen with the medical medium
information when you see that happen
it's so nice
shen
777-777 that's a powerful number right
there i was duped by
well air ayurveda
used to always just be like drink goat's
milk
here you are you got you know
you got me cfs you got all these dif
trigeminal neurology you're suffering
with fibromyalgia and the ayurvedic
doctor back in the day would just be
like drink lots of goats milk
like that fixed all that it didn't
it didn't and i'm not trying to try not
trying to rank on air vet i'm just
telling you that's all it was it was
like
it was like ghee and goat's milk it's
like okay we need more answers than that
we need to know why we're sick we need
to know how to heal and you'll see here
vetted now it takes medical medium
information i mean it's sad to say but
they're using bits and pieces of
of mm info now they're talking about
pathogens aromatic medicine didn't
believe in pathogens they didn't think
pathogens existed
but now all of a sudden everybody
believes viruses exist well that's been
35 years of medical media information
it's maddening
so i mean there's there's like
protocols in here for aphasia praxia
arteriosclerosis arrhythmia arrhythmia
protocol
anxiousness protocol anxiety protocol
anorexia protocol
ankylosing spondylitis
protocol so many people have asked me
about that amnesia protocol amnesia
right
anemia protocol aneurysm protocol
okay
i mean how cool is that
so many protocols
afib protocol auditory processing
protocol right
autism protocol autoimmune diseases
protocol that's a big one so many people
if you if you get lost if you ever get
lost it's like wait i got autoimmune
doctor's diagnosing with autoimmune
there's an autoimmune protocol in here
to make things easy
right
arfid right eating disorders okay
avoidant restrictive food intake
disorder right that people get diagnosed
with there's a protocol for that one
look at this one ayahuasc ayahuasca
recovery
i'm looking in here there's ayahuasca
recovery because so many people get
brain damaged from ayahuasca in small
dosages too micro dosing ayahuasca and
their brains get totally burnt fried
and like 10 years later they're like
they're just one big fog
and they're just bumping in the walls
the saddest thing i ever see out there
right
but yet this shaman did it for me and he
was the best shaman in the world and i
get it i'm sure there's some cool
shamans out there and nice people
but dude you just burnt up all your
brain cells
anyway i'm just saying it's really tough
a lot of people need recovery from
ayahuasca so i have it here i'm not
saying don't do it or do or do whatever
you want i'm just saying that
that that recovery protocol is in here
but what's amazing is
there's a thorough information into
like what iowa's good does the brain
like how it works
so when you actually consume it what
happens inside the brain
that is in the micro dosing chapter when
you read the micro dosing chapter you're
just getting like oh my god
this information
there's an alcohol chapter too because
here's the thing we drink alcohol we get
tipsy
we get drunk
but we don't know what happens to the
brain and how it works like why it
happens why the symptoms happen all of
it i go into detail with alcohol and
having effects on the brain
information is just you know anyway
bollow disease
balance issues protocols for that
binge eating disorder i got a protocol
for binge eating disorder right bell's
palsy of course bipolar right blood
clots
people are getting clotted up like crazy
out there
just like oh my god micro clots all of
it
bloating protocol for that
blood draw protocol
you know you go to the doctor you get
your blood test
yeah take another 14 miles whatever or
lose your immune system and you get weak
and then you get sick and then you're
sick and then you go back to the doctor
again and then he takes more blood and
then you get sicker right
blood draw it's one right there
so blood blood draw protocols for a week
before you get your blood work and a
week after you get
your blood work blurred vision body
buzzing and humming protocol
body dis
dysmorphic disorder bdd
protocol
okay
i mean i can go on forever you guys this
is just incredible
brain inflammation so many people have
and they're going to get diagnosed with
it that's the thing
coming up because of mm info so many
people are going to get diagnosed with
that sarah emma spec says aw what about
microdosing
psilocybin or lsd i talk about that in
the chapter you have to read the chapter
my recommendation is just hold off any
do your doctor tells you
but my recommendation to any of my
friends and family
is to hold off on any micro dosing
of anything like lsd or um
psilocybin or anything like that
hold like hold off
until you read the chapter just wait
till you read the chapter on micro
dosing before you do anything like that
that's my recommendation for any family
member or friend or any doctor friend of
mine that wants to do a micro dose of
something like that kind of stuff just
oh no hold off don't do it
hold it off
until you read the chapter
about it
so you can make an educated decision on
what you're doing and what could happen
brain lesions protocol thanks thanks for
asking though i'm glad you're here so
glad you're here i want to help with any
way i can brain tumors and cysts breast
implant illness protocol for breast
implants like a protocol for bulimia
protocol for that burning hot feeling
with no fever how many people feel like
they're running hot but they got no
fever
burning sensations in the mouth what
about that like burning sensations
inside the mouth dr fond md good to see
you burning sensations in the mouth
burning sensations on the skin protocol
kathy
says anything on brain atrophy
absolutely a protocol for brain atrophy
in here in this book
in here
protocol for burnout people get all
their brain they get burned out the
neurotransmitters get burnt out their
electrical impulses get burnt out their
neurons get burnt out how do we restore
them and how do we know what's wrong or
not
bursitis
buzzing in the ears caffeine withdrawal
protocol so many people really want to
get off of that roller coaster ride like
i'm up i'm down i'm up and down i'm up
and down i'm ripped you know all like
jacked up on chocolate checked up on t
jacked up and caught i want to get off
and i'm up and down all over the place
the addiction is fierce and it's real
some people they want to get off that
caffeine ride
and so i got a protocol in here to get
them off that caffeine ride
you guys protocols
for over 300 symptoms and conditions
and that's just part of this book that's
just that's just
this is seven and a half books
is what this is these two books are
seven and a half books of information
seven and a half books is what these are
that's what's in these books seven and a
half books
can i order the books on uk amazon yes
you can april
april taft you can the links in the bio
amazon uk absolutely i was looking at
the amazon uk page the other day to make
sure it was there the link is in the bio
and the link is in the description
carpal tunnel syndrome castleman's
disease celiac disease canker sores
calcifications of the brain which people
don't really know but you know when you
see some weird white spot in the brain
cerebral atrophy whoa cerebral atrophy
right here
protocols for this stuff chemical and
food sensitivities protocol
cerebral vascular disease right whoa
what's this
chocolate and cacao withdrawal protocol
people become chocolate monsters
it's like i'm only going to have a
square i'm only going to have a square
i'm only going to have a square i'm only
going to have one square oh my god i
just had to have a chocolate bar
tyler says pre-order the book cynthia
martinez they don't charge your credit
card until the book is shipped and it's
shipped at the lower price incredible
all right
i'm gonna bring this book back up
right
you guys
the link is in the bio link is in the
description
i'm only scratching the surface
literally just scratching the surface in
these two incredible books
you won't be disappointed
when you receive the books
you'll you'll be so happy what's in here
if you're someone that reads
these books are worth reading okay
know that the emotional brain chapter
there's a chapter called the emotional
brain
the emotional brain chapter
just what you learn about the emotional
center of the brain that nobody knows
this advanced information that came down
i was so blown away it took it took the
toll on me though because i had to learn
it
like i had to learn it understand it i
had to hear it i had to perfect the
writing of it i had to do all of that
and it was intense but the incredible
thing is i've learned so much
i can't wait for you guys to learn
advanced information it's ahead of its
time
and in these books
it
takes it to another level of all of that
so i just want to tell you guys i
overcame my addiction to chocolate
thanks to medical medium information
and dates
isn't that incredible wild lizzie flower
incredible
it really it really helps when you're
off those addictions i swear cold white
spring so much work in so short time
yes it's called burning the candle
at eight ends
anyway
it's a lot of wax everywhere
dunsley said oh i need the caffeine
protocol
whoa
awesome and there's one in here see guys
check it out when you get a chance i'm
going to go off to
instagram i'm going to turn tick tock
back on
i'm going to turn
telegram back on
kathleen crosby says everyone is
different our genetics the way we
process food etc
kathleen medical me kathleen on facebook
medical medium information
are the books that always said everyone
is different in different ways like
they're different because of what's
poisoned them what kind of metals they
have everybody has different viruses
everybody has different chemicals
everybody has different emotional
experiences that's what makes everybody
different
and i talk about that and that's how you
heal when you know why you're different
why you're sick and sickness is
different than someone else's sick in
sickness is different and that's how you
can customize your protocol that you
need to heal because
because medical medium isn't
one-size-fits-all
and aw the medical median books are the
first of its kind for customized
protocols whether your animal protein
are plant-based in the past just eat
better books and you can pick your side
well you can go to the vegan or
plant-based eat better books or you can
go to the animal protein keto animal
protein plant-based i'm sorry animal
protein eat better books and that's all
you had as an option everybody stayed
sick they went to their neurologist
nobody knew why any was sick
and the reason why you see some of the
functional medicine doctors now talking
about mm info
they're like using the info from the
books i love you guys i'm heading off to
ig
it's good to know that so that you know
you can take care of yourself and heal i
love you guys
bless your heart and i'll see you soon
i'm going to go on in a couple minutes
in a few minutes