now
you guys
brain saver books two brain saver books
so here we are and i'm excited about
this i'm really excited about this
because this is going to
not only save lives
but
really help change the way medicine
works out there where people don't have
answers they can't get anything done
they can't get better they try
everything and have done that and
this is an opportunity here
it takes it to another level i can't
even tell you guys how excited i am
about this this is what i've been
working on
i can't tell you how many lost days of
sleep nights of sleep um 20-hour days
24-hour days 22-hour days even up until
this point today
all of that and
the two books are right here so i don't
know if you've seen these yet
but these are the manuscripts just so
you know you're not going to get
the book in a binder you're going to get
the book
in a book right so i just want to say
one thing too many things i'm gonna say
about these two books this is gonna
actually really cool
but
these are not little books
these are not gonna be little books
each book
is bigger than cleanse the heel so it's
bigger than this medical textbook right
here okay
each book is bigger than me so what
happened was
soc kept on giving me information giving
me information
because of how many people are falling
ill right now neurological problems just
overall everything including blood clots
i got everything in these books it's
unbelievable right and
so what happened was
the book got so big and so big and so
big that the publisher reached out to me
and said we can't print the book because
you can't put this book's well over a
thousand pages
this book's 14 100 1500 pages you can't
we can't do it it's not possible the
press can't do it
so we have to divide these into two
powerful life-changing books and that's
what we did
and
over 300 symptoms and conditions
in protocols
check this out you guys you just got to
check this out
well over a hundred brand new recipes
for healing the body and brain over a
hundred brand new recipes and check this
out
you guys i mean i didn't sleep last
night i didn't sleep a wink
at all i'm on no sleep right now i was
too excited okay i was working really
late and then i couldn't fall asleep
because
my mind was racing about everything i
wanted to tell you guys all right
check this out
cleanses
the one thing about the medical medium
information in books is it's not one
size fits all it never was
that's why that's a tactic used against
medical mean because
the colts out there right like the keto
cults and all the other cults and
everything they're all one size fits all
and
the medical medium books are not one
size fits all it's customizable so
everybody has an opportunity to heal
that's why the most people have healed
on medical medium information worldwide
right
it's the leading healing information
worldwide in chronic and on chronic
illness right 14 cleanses
an advanced advanced heavy metal detox
cleanse for what we're up against with
the new barrage of chemicals today
and of course the new garage of medical
things
the new barrage of what we're up against
today
this is a whole new new level i see
we're censored on facebook today
incredible it figures we'd be censored
on facebook today on the book on the
book talking about the book this is this
is this is
amazing
anyway
so it looks like we don't have anybody
in facebook we're actually censored so
you guys
14 new cleanses yeah
an advanced heavy metal detox
because of what we're up against now
right now right
and you know the
the original heavy metal detox is
changing lives and saving lives as we
speak
this is a level
no one's ever heard of see i want to
tell you this
okay
my podcast
when people say oh i heard your stuff on
the podcast yeah it's probably the same
thing in the book no it's not
your blog oh it's probably the same
thing on your blog no it's not
the information in these books i've
never talked about
in detail
like it is we're talking about new
information
volumes of new information
and and while you guys are coming on
i'll actually pause through the books a
little bit these are the manuscripts
these are my manuscripts right here
these are my manuscripts
right there
this isn't the book you're going to be
getting okay
you're watching on facebook that's great
that amazing but but they got they don't
have me censored today there's no
question
these are my manuscripts for each book
right
so i have them in a binder
that's how that's how i do it when i'm
working on these books so you're looking
at my worked manuscripts right here
and
the problem is the book couldn't be one
book because they couldn't print it out
it wasn't possible it's got advanced
information about the brain and central
nervous system that science and research
doesn't even know
no no health authority knows no medical
community knows
out there
it's going to be the leading information
on the brain in the future so people
have a chance to heal
i'm really just excited i can't even
tell you guys how excited i am and i'm
on zero sleep i didn't sleep last night
because
i was working on
trying to figure it out with with my
team and everything on how to get this
thing so we can get this thing out today
so people can order it and everything
and then of course i was too excited so
the two hours i needed to sleep i just
couldn't sleep so here i am
and
uh so i just want to talk about this for
a little bit first of all i just want to
tell everybody and this is an important
piece of information when you order
these books on amazon right now
right when you order both of these books
it's two different books when you order
both of them the price you see
is not going to be the price when the
book comes out
so when the book comes out and amazon is
going to adjust the price
so the price you see is going to be
lower it's not going to be the price you
see now
when the book gets shipped that's number
one number two okay you ordered it chris
amazing christy ordered it incredible
number two here's another important
piece of information to know
all right
so you're not gonna be charged on your
card if you order it right now you won't
be charged on your credit card this is
important people get confused and they
think well if i pre-order the book now
i'm just going to get charged no you're
not you don't get charged for the books
until it's shipped
that's when you get charged for it so
when you pre-order it you're not even
going to get charged on your card so if
you pre-order it now you won't be
charged
and then when it does ship
it'll be at a lower price
because amazon starts to take down the
price on the books on the medical medium
books right
so if you pre-order now
and you pre-ordered it at the price it
is you're not going to be paying that
price
when it comes down to when the book gets
shipped and you're not going to be
charged on your card until the book is
shipped so keep that in mind that's
really an important thing and tell other
people and i just want to tell you guys
okay
you guys have been so good to me and so
supportive
and i can't tell you how i appreciate
you guys you you don't even know like
how much i appreciate you how much i
care about you guys how much i love you
guys for all that you do
i'm getting choked up right now
so i
honestly and in the and you guys been
good to me too with with talking about
the book just now and sharing it with
people and letting them know about these
brain books right now and i can't thank
you enough for that
it means the world because i feel like
we're in it together with helping others
and saving people's lives
and if you guys just want to know how to
order the book the links are in the
description
and on tic tac the link is in the bio if
you want to know how to order the book
but i just want to say from the bottom
of my heart and i know you guys are
coming on because i want to talk about
these books a little bit
i just want to say from the bottom of my
heart seriously you guys for all that
you're doing and spreading the word
and being so good about everything and
you've been what i know you many of you
been waiting for a brain book for a long
time
and
i promise you this
you
will
be so blown away when you get these
books you won't even believe it there's
not going to be a book out there in the
health world as it is that compares to
the medical medium other books right you
guys know that but
this is a level there's no doctor author
there's no health author that could ever
do what happened in these books no
i can confidently say that i can
confidently say this
because
when you open these books up when you
get these books
first of all
the books are bigger than cleanse to
heal each book is bigger than cleanse to
heal when you get the book
be prepared
okay
it's not like oh i can't wait to read
aw's book i'll read it all in one night
it's not going to happen
no one's going to be able to read the
book in one night
it's not going to be possible
every single line in the book has a
powerful piece of information that's
life-changing that science research
doesn't even know yet they'll be taking
the information like they do from the
medical meeting books you know how like
i published that the medical the medical
medium um book one i published how
multiple sclerosis was caused by
epstein-barr and now science seven years
later is acting like they discovered it
which they didn't
but the point is is these books are so
packed with leading forefront
information your mind is going to be
blown like blown and know why i know
that
you guys you know why i know that
because my mind was freaking blown when
i was receiving the information
my mind was so blown
the hard part about putting these books
together was i had to learn the
information
from spirit of compassion
santa is here healing good to see you
good to see you guys coming on i had to
learn the information from spirit of
compassion
and
because it was brand new to me
i thought i already knew enough about
toxic heavy metals i didn't even know
the half of it like
and
so what happened was i thought look i
thought i knew
about so much about all the different
conditions and symptoms right because
that's that being an expert in chronic
illness and and teaching doctors for 35
years i thought i knew so much but once
again i just got basically smacked in
the head
and
spirited compassion said are you ready
for this are you up for this task and
i'm like i don't know
and
when you open up these books and you
read them your mind's gonna be so blown
because mine was because i had to learn
this i still haven't learned it
i took the information as a messenger
and i put it in here
it's god-given life-saving information
and
i got the information down perfectly the
way it needed to be done
but i still have to read these over
and read these over
that's how mind-blowing it is just the
chapter on burnout is a whole thing all
on another level
the chapter on viral brain is a is
unbelievable brenda says you healed my
brain fog anthony forever thankful and i
got brain fog in here
and i talk about brain fog in here too
thank you for brenda for being here
so
yeah noel shepard said thanks for taking
this math for us
bless your heart
so you guys this is a special moment
for the for the sikh community for the
chronically ill community for or or for
the not so sick community that don't
think they're sick but they still have
symptoms
tom jensen says anthony what's the fine
print of the title of your new blueberry
book thank you for asking bless your
heart
let me get that one now and take a look
okay
all right answers
so answers
answers to brain inflammation which is
rampant right now can you see that right
there you guys
answers to brain inflammation mental
health
which so many people are struggling
right now
ocd
which is taking over the world basically
ocd at this point brain fog neurological
symptoms
everybody's got the neurological
symptoms addiction i'm not talking about
addiction to heroin i'm talking about
even the most basic of addictions people
don't know they're wrapped up in anxiety
depression
another level of depression people
didn't realize i have something in here
about depression that came from soc that
blew my mind so much that i needed days
and days to actually understand why
why i wasn't even given that information
yet
about
how it's possible to have that kind of
severe depression
and how it's even possible i have it
literally in detail intricate detail of
depression in these books this book
so if you can put it back on well you
know what i'll put it back on right
there
anxiety depression heavy metals
yeah mind-blowing epstein-barr virus
seizures
lime adhd alzheimer's autoimmune which
covers all autoimmune and eating
disorders which is mind-blowing i'm
going to tell you right now the eating
disorder chapter is is is epic on a
level where i was also on the floor
about that because i was so blown away
now if you think well is that all he's
talking about in brain saver no
no that's a fraction of the symptoms and
conditions and brain saver right there
you guys that's a fraction
of the symptoms and conditions what
you're looking at right there i don't
know if you can see it if i can focus it
let me see if i can get it in into
better focus for you guys
that's a fraction addiction adhd als
als alzheimer's anxiety autism right
balance issues and dizziness bell's
palsy bipolar brain fog right brain
inflammation brain lesions you guys
which people are getting every day now
they're getting them on their mris i go
into detail about that right
okay bipolar i told you better right um
brain tumors insists
breast implant illness
i got a basically a chapter on breast
implant illness in here
it's it's it's so important burnout
chronic anger disorder see how many
people have chronic anger
right cranial nerve issues i'm just
naming a few right there
that's how much is in here i'm just
covering just a few
i think basically what's going to happen
is anybody who gets these books
they're
they're going to know when they crack
them open
they're going to know like how is this
possible
how is this possible
i'm actually emotional about it because
really and
so i just want to say something which is
really interesting and this wasn't
planned
this wasn't planned i have no control
over the release date
i have no control over the day we choose
right now
to actually do this okay it's thrown
upon me
had to be done
and the numbers
of the day
the month and the year
equal a seven
on both today
and both the release day
and
i asked soc about that why because these
actually are for the light
to battle darkness of what we're up
against including darkness in the in the
health field in the alternative health
field there's so much of that in there
it's ridiculous because it's all about
other things it's not about someone
who's chronically ill and really about
getting them better and
i mean
that alone is really mind-blowing
both land on seven
so um
all right so let me just i don't know
crack one open for a second you guys got
a minute i don't want to take your time
i know you guys are busy and you guys
got your life and everything else
but let me crack into the table of
contents a little bit in a couple of
these books right here if you guys just
came on here can i sip some tea you guys
i'm actually i didn't sleep last night
so i'm here i'm probably probably gonna
need a nap later on
for
sure but
i'm excited so let me crack into brain
saver
right
volume one basically
and this is brain saver the other one
i'll show you two in a minute
and you guys check out the link in the
description and if you just came on here
the price you see on amazon is not going
to be the price
when you get the book shipped it's going
to be lower i really believe it's going
to be lower it always is
and
you're not going to be charged on your
card when you pre-order it so just so
you know when you pre-order these books
on amazon right now link is in the
description link link is in the bio you
guys on tick tock you're not going to be
charged
you don't get charged until the book is
shipped to you so eventually when the
book is shipped to you that's when
you get charged so just keep that in
mind which is so awesome so it's like
what you know so great
all right
so i'm gonna brain saver right here okay
so i got a table of contents in front of
me right here
here's a little sticky note right
i always put those things i'm gonna
piles of those eventually
yeah so
all right
so part one is called your brain story
so it's a story about your brain what's
really happening which is really great
about what the brain needs and how if we
don't give what our brain what it needs
how we get in trouble
so
chapter one is called save your brain
but chapter two is static brain
static brain about how the electricity
in the brain gets affected by everything
it's so mind-blowing it's off the charts
like i i don't even know what to say
chapter three is your alloy brain okay
alloy brain means and it's something i
never described to you guys why
everybody's going through so much mental
illnesses because the metals
actually become one and i and i
explained it in there and how that works
that's really incredible
there look there's so many just the
first section has nine huge chapters
right
i got a micro dosing chapter in this
book so people understand stand the
ramifications of micro dosing the wrong
things
so that that alone is actually mind
blowing
there is so much information i can tell
you right now that just this book alone
i'm going all the way
49 chapters
in this book right here so 49 chapters
in this brainsaver book right here
it's just it's unbelievable
unbelievable right i got a chapter on
bacteria and microbes
i got a chap this is just i'm just
naming a couple there's 49 chapters here
i got a sea trail chapter
right about what's really going down
people always ask me about emf they're
always asking me about emf i talk about
if it affects the brain or not i've got
a radiation and emf chapter
right
it's just this is just really
mind-blowing
so
i got
chapters on
right
over a hundred illnesses in this book
talking about in detail what causes that
illness like
more detail than i've ever done on what
causes that illness
i mean the whole bit so i'm gonna keep
on going through a little bit more
ocd chapter of bipolar chapter at
alzheimer's chapter in dementia chapter
right eating disorders chapter which is
off the charts the eating disorder
chapter is just
i think when anybody reads that chapter
they're just going to be like why isn't
this out there why isn't this out there
because this is it's unbelievable
so
i have a chapter in here that's called
what the brain is made out of it's the
most comprehensive books
that i've ever done and you already know
how many lives were saved from cleanse
to heal and are being saved right now
from this book alone
these are the most comprehensive
books i've ever done got a chapter in
here about what your brain is made out
of
what is it made out of
what's going on in there
right
when you read that you're just getting
like
it's incredible
and i i mean
it just goes on
right
not to mention the cleanses and the
therapies in here
so this is just some stuff inside
this book here i just scratched it
scratched it like don't don't think like
i actually covered it and i didn't i
mean
and then
if you look at
the protocols book okay so this is brain
saver protocols cleanses and recipes
all right
and you'll see here for neurological
autoimmune and mental health
now in this book is over 300 symptoms
and conditions
300 symptoms and conditions
right
protocols for them
that are
non-evasive
what happens is people are running
around all over the place trying to heal
right now who don't know about medical
medium books and they're hurting
themselves with evasive treatments
i'm talking about it alternative healthy
basic treatments different mind invasive
treatments and conventional health right
right the invasive treatment so
important to know
so
over
300 symptoms of conditions and protocols
for them
in this book alone now what i love about
this book right here
and it's best to get both of them you
guys it's best to get both of them yeah
they stand alone too but it's best to
get both of them right
what i love about this book right here
it's got new meditations on top of it
that are mind-blowing mind-blowing but
they're not painful like a lot of
meditations are out there in the world
they're easy on the system when you have
neurological problems and mental health
problems and they help to heal so
there's new meditations in this book
right here
which is incredible all on its own and
here's the other thing
there's over a hundred brand new healing
recipes for the brain in this book
you guys i don't even know what to say
there's just so much
there's just that much so let me just
crack open this
cover a little bit too right
and there's a lot of comforting recipes
in here
a lot of comforting recipes in here so
these are my manuscripts you're not
going to get you're going to get a book
like you're going to get a book like a
book for medical medium books when you
do when you do order these and they come
but it's going to be bigger than cleanse
the heel each book is bigger than
cleanse the heel
[Music]
it's two books because the publisher if
you guys just got on here the publisher
they contacted me
and they said aw and i'm like what
happened is everything okay after i
handed in the manuscript
i handed in the manuscript
and they said
we can't print it
authors don't do this
they don't
hand over manuscript because
my publish that's my publisher said we
realize you're in it to get people
better you're in it for chronic illness
you're in it to get people their lives
back but we
authors don't do books like this it's
this big we have to cut it in half we
have to make two books out of it we
can't print it it's gonna be well over a
thousand pages we can't do that
so what i'm doing is i'm just taking a
look at the table of contents right here
see if i can get to it
elena said i can't imagine how long it
took to write
i sacrificed a lot writing it
that's for sure
and
so how do we peggy says how do we
pre-order
the
right the link is in the description
peggy check them out both books are
there keep in mind the price you see on
amazon
isn't the price that it's going to be
when the book is shipped to you it's
going to be less
it's going to be less than that
keep in mind you're not going to be
charged pre-order it and you're not
going to be charged you don't get
charged until it's shipped to you very
important to know so you can totally
pre-order it and it's even going to be
you know like a better price and the
price
that they have it on now is still
incredible because of what these books
are because it's so many books in one
you you it's just yeah
it's still a steal
natalia says i have never seen anyone
write and come out with two books at the
same time
it's the first of its kind yes and and
my publisher made me aware that it was
original and
then nobody does it
it's just that it's like this it's
chronic the chronic illness is rising on
a level no one even imagined in five
years from now people have no idea but
our systems are going to be basically
shutting down out there
meaning the way the world works because
there's too many sick people
if
i don't get this out to the ones that
can find it to to the ones that can find
it because they've been they've been
guided there somehow providentially
through the universe through like
through god and they've been they've
been guided through the angels and they
got to the books
and they got to the books
happy are they
karina says tourette's syndrome info yes
i would never leave tourette's out of
the brain books ever so yeah and it's
it's mind-blowing the information in
there and there's a tourette's protocol
too
so
it's a happy day
alexandra sophia good to see you i
pre-ordered both and will get as gifts
as well bless your heart amazing no
wonder it took so long to write these
they are enormous they are and yes they
took a long time
so i'm in a table of contents right now
of the protocols brain book okay so i'm
in that one here you guys elizabeth says
he must have worked his arse off on this
book
excited for the emf part
i'm excited too i'm actually really
excited too
i really am it's it's books that you're
always going to be coming to it's books
that
there's so much information in there
this line for line
it's
it blows the mind
it really does and you can take it at
the pace you need to take it you can go
read what you need to read you know
divine guidance can help you pick what
you need to pick to read there's
these books are working for us
it's information from above
i'm in a table of contents right here
so
there's
a therapy
in these books
that's
very powerful i'm probably going to talk
about it on another day because it's
really intense
powerful
easy to do the powerful
so that's in here there's the protocols
of over 300 symptoms and conditions
so 300 symptoms and conditions for
protocols
and you pre-ordered it stephanie amazing
pre-ordered both incredible you won't be
charged
until the book gets shipped okay when it
does get shipped down the road then you
will you won't be stretched until then
so you don't have to worry
sassa says pre-ordered both looking
forward to receiving them thank you from
the bottom of my heart to you and soc
you're amazing
you're amazing too
there's a section here on brain betrayer
supplements a lot of people have
questions about things like they have
questions like
does this work why is chlorella bad like
you name it like why is charcoal bad or
whatever you know how people are always
and they're trying so many different
things
i talk about
what happens inside the body with a lot
of these different things and that alone
is is is mind-blowing
so
it's just there's so much information
here you guys
and then there's the heavy metal
cleanses
so there's the heavy metal detox
cleanses which is a whole other level
all on its own
which is really exciting
so and then there's the recipes over a
hundred recipes
no one's ever seen
very incredible for the brain and body
comforting too
many of them really comforting
i'm just scratching but here's the thing
these books the big thing right here
these books
are trouble shooters
they're troubleshooters
we don't have that
to this day i have all these people that
try to contact me and doctors reaching
out saying i don't know what's wrong my
patient they have this symptom that
symptom this symptom and they're just
troubleshooting non-stop and these books
are the trouble shooting guides right
here and that's that's big all on its
own
may these are like the troubleshooting
books
i can promise you this and you guys know
i haven't let you down before in the
medical meeting books you guys know that
but i can promise you this
that when you open these books and
receive these books
you'll say
that guy didn't let me down he was he
he didn't let me down
it is what he said
and more
what's in here is what to look out for
and what could be holding you back
that's empowerment right there even how
long it takes to heal
i
mean seriously you guys
just gonna sip a little tea for a second
alyssa says watching with my sister we
love you aw thank you for changing our
lives
i just scratched the surface you guys i
just scratched the surface on these
okay
they're both important to have it was
one book to start with it had to be
turned into two books they're bigger
than it would be a 12 pound book
if it was in one book it'd be a 10 to 12
pound book that wasn't going to work
when someone has chronic illness because
they can't be carrying around a 12 pound
book
it had to be cut into two books
there's not one line wasted
it's all forefront it's all ahead of
science of research
it is literally what you guys are
witnessing right here is
is
something that's just gonna
change
the way things work in the chronic
illness world and the health communities
i mean the medical media books already
have that's why
it's why alternate medicine the good
parts have changed that have been
created in there and so many people do
get tidbits that come from here but this
is a level that's
you know
i don't even i mean i can't describe you
know i said the spirit of compassion
this morning i said how am i even going
to describe this
you know at the same time my mind is
still blown by all of it and it's hard
to articulate
so i'm going to read some symptoms on
the back of book two let's do that so
this is the other book right here this
is the neurological symptoms protocol
book i mean they're both neurological
symptoms that's the whole point
but i'm gonna
look look back here a little bit try to
not knock these over right okay see adhd
aos alzheimer's anemia everybody's
always asking about anemia all the time
right
anxiety
aphasia
right you guys know about that one
autism autoimmune disorders balanced
issues right bell's palsy bipolar
disorders blood clots a lot of people
worried about blood clots right now
brain fog brain inflammation brain
legions
breast implant illness right caffeine
withdrawal
caffeine withdrawal
canker sores chronic fatigue syndrome
cold sores right concussion recovery i
can't tell you how many people need help
with concussion recovery even long after
they had their concussion their
concussion was a year or two ago
and they still have problems lots of
problems right
restless leg syndrome of course are a
seizure swallowing difficulties tourette
syndrome tremors trigeminal neuralgia
vagus nerve problems vibrating face
neuralgia narcolepsy
multiple sclerosis myocarditis lyme
disease migraines depersonalization
drooping face dysautonomia eating
disorders epilepsy
i've seen bar virus excessive sweating
right
the whole excessive sweating that so
many people deal with hypotrosis right
facial pain food poisoning gastritis
gastroparesis guillain-barre
heart palpitations but you guys this is
just scratching the surface there's 300
symptoms and conditions in here and the
back of the book only has
so many i think there's only like 50 or
something back there we're talking 300
is inside this book these are just 50
thrown on the back there
right
and
that's a special time so what you're
looking at is the brain saver protocols
cleanses and recipes over 100 recipes in
here
that no one's seen before
and then it's for neurological
autoimmune and mental health
but both books
are a powerhouse and
the information in there
is will open not only open your mind but
it it offers an opportunity on a level
so i just wanted to let you guys know
where we are with this
but of course you'll see me again
we'll talk about more about what's in
these books too we eventually get to
there there's just so much to do you
just ordered them amazing
you guys once again if you pre-order it
right now
on amazon with the links that you see
right tick tock the link in the bio and
link in the description here
when you pre-order it you're not going
to be charged for it until it's shipped
to you so your card's not going to get
the charge
that's one number two is the price is
going to drop by the time it gets
shipped to you so it's going to get
shipped to you at a different price a
lower price
keep that in mind
when you pre-order these okay and just
know that you guys i can't thank you
enough for spreading the word telling
people about it being so supportive
right through thick and thin
being supported through thick and thin
right
keep in mind the books sell out
so that
that it happens to all the medical media
books that by the time if you don't get
a pre-order in i'm not doing this to get
you you know like scared oh no what what
it just happens every time so if i don't
say something everybody gets mad at me
because they wish they pre-ordered it
and then when time gets shipped they run
out and then they have to wait for
another printing and that could take
like a couple of months or a few months
so pre-ordering does secure that you get
a copy
it does
so
and
yeah and and it secures that you get a
copy with everything going on too as the
world is changing and everything and
things are happening and things are
harder to get not all that it's just
it's good to know a copy is secure or
copies
but yes two books
launched this is
takes us to book eight in the medical
medium book series clover bowers says i
have never wanted to fast forward time
so much
you and me both
i share that same conviction right there
100 percent
i really do
anyway you guys
i am going to go on instagram
i'm going to turn tick tock back on and
telegram back on and i'm gonna go on ig
in just short time
anyway hannah good to see you
i'm happy to know they're coming too
truth truly am
all right
i love you guys
i'll see you soon just if you want if
you want to come to ig i'm going to turn
tik tok back on and telegram and
we'll we'll talk about it