and medical medium new edition today's
the release
date it's exciting day because i know so
many people are going to be healing
more and more around the world and all
the different countries around in the
world
people are going to be healing and
getting better so i'm really excited
um making a fruit dish right here it's a
recipe
um it's a fruit bowl so i'm excited
about that i got my kiwis right here i
got my blueberries i got my strawberries
good to see you guys i got a papaya i
have
mangoes got more blueberries more
strawberries
i love fruit i hope you guys love fruit
gonna make a fruit bowl
i'm really excited so hey how's everyone
doing so deanna come up there
it's margaret hi how are you doing great
and um
we're going to talk about dental stuff
yeah i'm going to talk about mercury
fillings
removing mercury fillings did you have
mercury fillings in the past and they
were removed
going gonna cover that a little bit i'm
gonna talk about some toxic heavy metal
stuff that's happening out there how
i'm gonna read something out of this
book right here
bettina says i love your new tick tocks
awesome so glad so glad i saw michelle
you were just reading we're
reading this book here incredible and
you got your new book i see everybody
saying got your new book got your copy
um some people are probably still
waiting
amazing so glad you guys have it i'm
excited loving a new book tiffany says
incredible today's the release day it's
really exciting
we're live on youtube right now and live
on facebook
um yeah so fun so fun
awesome um see you guys different things
we can talk about
for sure i'm going to read some uh
excerpts out of this book
st information about mercury and how
it's if it affects us in what way it
affects us kind of where it all
originates going to cover that a little
bit too
and we're going to talk about different
stuff i'm going to start making this
fruit salad real quick
start working on that for the moment
so uh i got my kiwis here i'm going to
start with my papaya going to put that
at the bottom of the bowl
so let's just get going on this a little
bit so
just got braces off need three teeth
see says just got your braces off
um you know i talk about i talk about
was it the plastic braces was it the
metal braces
there's the metal braces right there
right i used these in that funny tik tok
video
where i was brushing um fits and metal
braces
it's good to learn how to get the metals
out medical medium information
i talk about how to get the metals out
so that's the papaya i just opened up
it's a beautiful papaya
i hope you guys can see that if it's the
plastic braces
plastic still has metals in it there are
there's
metals in petroleum products plastics
petroleum product
so keep that in mind so i'm going to
scoop out
these seeds right now so let me do that
i'm going to scoop them into a bowl let
me grab a bowl real quick
you guys great to have you in my kitchen
it's always an honor i'm going to answer
questions try to help you guys out too
today is the book release medical medium
new edition revised and expanded
see how i do this do you guys see this
i mean are you guys buying these
beautiful mirador papayas
what a healing food too so good for the
gut
intestinal tract lining it's soothing
for anybody who's suffering and
struggling with constipation
cramping bloating digestive problems
gastroparesis
right and see how i scooped out the
seeds
like that so isn't it interesting
okay merida papaya here it is right here
sherry i'm currently
so ill doctors can't tell me what's
wrong with me and that you know
it's really that's so hard and and
depending on how many doctors you've
gone to
too that's so difficult i i mean i
understand i've watched this for years
that's
that's a part of what propelled me
to put out the new edition so people can
be their own detective
they can learn how to heal they can
learn how to find out what's wrong with
themselves
why i put the book out there before the
books came out there for 30 years i was
known as the bizarre symptoms guy i was
sent
uh people were sent to me through
doctors
to find out what was going on with their
bizarre symptoms and all that and that's
what my work was all these years and all
these years
and so i put tremendous amount of
information in a new addition you can
always take it to your doctor too
and try to give them a little lead maybe
a little you know
kind of give them a clue to help them
and
what's really annoying is when a doctor
makes a comment somewhere on social
media on one of the platforms whether
it's ig
or tick tock or something and they they
comment
about something they don't like that i'm
doing like putting out information to
help people heal
and they they comment and meanwhile they
don't even know why anybody's sick they
don't know why people are coming to him
every day that are sick they don't know
they don't know you know why someone's
got fatigue they don't know why someone
has eczema
and they're like oh is there any study
behind that okay well that's funny
because
so many people are going doctor to
doctor to doctor to doctor can't find
answers can't figure out what's wrong
with them don't know how to heal
spending thousands of doctors what if
they don't have an insurance
card too what if they don't have
insurance and it's all coming out of
their pocket every bit of it it's so sad
it's good to have answers it's good to
have information
just know that my heart pours out to you
if you're going through that so i got
the
um merida papaya i'm showing you guys
how i do my fruit bowl
i'm showing you how i prepare my fruit a
little bit
doctors there's a lot of different
doctors out there a lot of different
phds there's a lot of different people
but knowing what causes chronic illness
that's an entirely different thing
usually doctors right out of med school
make the comments they come right out of
med school they're hot dogs they come
flying out of med school they don't know
a thing about why people are sick
they don't have any history
into that they have no experience and
they come flying out of med school with
no experience
at all and they're so excited you know
to just hot dog
and get into practice right away and
just you know
start writing out prescriptions when
people come in and start sending it to
medical tests but yet they don't even
know why people are sick or they don't
know how diseases start they don't know
how
foods play a role they don't know about
toxic heavy metals they don't know about
viruses they don't know about pathogens
but
yet you know they're experts instantly
out of med school right off the running
and they come out and those are the ones
that usually don't work either it's it's
amazing right now we have more doctors
that get out of med school that never
work they get out of med school and they
start their social media account
whether it's tick tock or ig or
somewhere and they just want to become
famous
that's what they want to do now doctors
don't want to work anymore all the new
ones that come out of med school not all
of them but
most of them come out of med school and
they're like whoa i have to work
you mean this is a job oh my god i have
to see patients day in and day out well
this is stressful i have to get
insurance i have to get malpractice
insurance this is really
stressful most doctors that come out of
med school they're like can't i go a
different way
and now they become like a food expert
and now they're like
on social media on there you know doing
this and that trying to start up
accounts because they just want to sit
home at their computer they don't want
to go to
go to the doctor they don't want to go
to the office with the other doctors and
work
and that's happening now that's a big
thing going on this is what i do right
here
or they go into cosmetics they go a lot
of doctors go into cosmetics because
they
figure let's put lip filler in you know
women in men's mouth let's do lip filler
and that's
a way to kind of like escape like
all the people coming with problems
medical problems left and right with no
answers because it gets really tiresome
for a doctor when a doctor has to sit
there
while patients are rolling in all day
and they don't have a clue to why
they're sick
that's really hard for doctors they
don't have a clue to why anybody's got
fatigue and rna and
skin disorders and different conditions
they have to scratch your head all day
long
and be like i don't know why people are
sick and because of that no and the
doctors just go well what do i do let me
look at my textbook here
let me look at my my textbook when i
just came out of med school it says
jeans tell them genes
tell them it's a genetic disorder um
ma'am
um that's a genetic disorder we think
it's your genes
uh really you need this i'm your 10th
doctor you just came to
oh no i'm your 15th doctor and that 15
doctors just told you
is your genes too and so what happens is
you know they don't know so they go into
cosmetics it's like let's do
some lip filler and let's do i'm not
saying is anything bad or good about it
if that's what you do or that's what you
want to do i'm not saying that a lot of
men and women do it right
but they go into like lip filler and
jawline filler
and they go into botox you know shove
the needle up in your forehead and
send that boat send that botulism
bacteria in there
and they they go into there because
you know what i mean that's where a lot
of them are heading into now
head into cosmetics because they can't
handle
people pouring in sick with chronic
illness just can't handle they don't
have the skin for it because they don't
have answers
guys i'm making the fruit bowl right
here if you just got on here
um let's see
so nancy says you really bother me why
were you chosen to bring the messages of
healthy food oh that's interesting
i mean i'm sorry i bother you
or maybe that wasn't just maybe that was
just a typo or something but if i do
bother you i'm very very sorry
um i'm doing this i'm cutting this right
here
i do know millions of people have healed
from medical medium information
and have gotten their lives back so what
i do you guys
i take the papaya i got the half right
here and i take a knife
and you just gotta be careful when you
do this you can use
you know a butter knife if you want or
whatever but i'm using a
a knife right and i'm doing this and i'm
trying not to cut through the papaya
into my hand
so we could do if you want to do the
safe way you put the
mirror doll half here and you do it this
way where you're doing it on your
cutting board you see this
right and i'm doing it to show you this
way here so i'm running these lines
right right like that
okay and then i'm running them across
like this
all right and i'm not going to joke
around to pretend i got cut
i wouldn't do that to you guys today all
right so i just i just slice those up
like that
amber gardner says i love you keep
speaking the truth i'm honored
thank you for being here you guys um
so i have that papaya see how that's cut
do you guys see that
right okay
all right so let's put the papaya pieces
down here first
i take the spoon all right and
i cut in here with the spoon and now the
papaya pieces are coming down in there
you see that
okay
jan gordon says started on your program
last week celery juice worked when
nothing else did
got your book today anthony you're such
a blessing thank you i'm
so glad you're doing that i'm so proud
of you that is so
incredible it's beautiful truly is i'm
putting my papaya pieces here at the
bottom of this fruit bowl
there's a lot of juice in this papaya
this is a juicy maridoll papaya i'm very
excited about this
so i'm making the fruit bowl if you guys
are afraid of fruits
if you're afraid of fruit
just know the term fruit fear is out
there because the medical medium so if
you ever hear it on a podcast or you
hear somebody
post it on social media like an
influencer and they don't track it back
or cite it back to medical meaning books
fruit fear started
with the medical medium book it started
with lectures it started with all that
it taught people about fruit fear and
how that works so and it's an incredible
chapter
so i'm putting some papaya pieces here
and
cassandra said downloaded the new book
today what a whirlpool of new
information at it thank you for sharing
this information with us
there's a lot of information in there um
if you
were a reader of the original first
edition the second dish it is
mind-blowing
it the first edition was mind-blowing
that's that's the whole thing i mean it
was
um with no marketing and and money
behind it it went around the world
an organic grassroots movement that
happened with that book that doesn't
happen with books and authors
authors have to pay for all their
traction they have to pay 500
000 to a million dollars for the first
few months to get traction
uh i paid nothing i mean
you know because it actually works
when something works someone tells
somebody else or like hey
hey have you have you tried this book
because it it fixed my cfs it fixed my
ra
it fixed my eczema fixed whatever it
just fixed everything
so that's how it's done
um i've got my papaya here at the bottom
of the bowl
this is my fruit bowl right here susan
said i wish i could afford your books
but i follow you as much as possible did
you go to the library are you
or you know you can go to a library um
in the united states you can go to the
library
overseas the book's free in there i mean
this new book might take a little time
to get into the library
and then get the get the books for free
i always tell people free free free
all right so we got that going let's do
the next one i'm going to throw
strawberries in next and look at these
right here you guys
are you guys with me on this fruit bowl
this is actually look at these
what do you think what do you guys think
i mean are they any good
how do they look look at that one
right wow let's cut these up
i cut them in half okay so watch this
right see
i cut them in half and i cut them
when they're big like this right
see these little slices and then i run
across
boom put them in here
jennifer goldberg you're the only one
that addresses diverticulitis in all of
your books
out there you know i'm honored
i'm honored i want to help people i want
to get people better
it matters um
okay there we go let's just cut this it
matters means a lot to me
okay cutting up some strawberries you
guys while we're doing i'm gonna
read comments whenever i can mc says
great video anthony tell me how come i
never
get a shout out emcee you got a shout
out let's make sure you get some shout
outs i feel like a
non-organic rotten plum tomato
kicked to the side and of a tossed salad
ugh
no way i don't see all the comments and
i feel
bad now well you know what
mc you're getting a shout out that's it
i'm gonna make sure i don't want you
feeling like a a kicked down
rotten tomato i don't want you feeling
like a rotten plum
i don't want to feel feeling like a
rotten grape
right or sour grape
rotten mango all right so i'm gonna look
out for you when i can okay
and i'm thankful you're here truly am
and um so i'm putting some
some um strawberry pieces i still got
some more strawberry pieces going on
you guys i'm making the fruit bowl
dale just said just ordered your new and
revised book really hoping it will give
me
insight as to why i have a salty taste
in my mouth that will not go away
salty taste in your mouth
that's interesting are you getting off
of
eggs are you getting off of some gluten
are you getting off of those things
vinegar is something to get rid of
keep vinegar out of your life for three
months see if that salty flavor's still
there those are things i would do um
you're not on any caffeine right no
caffeine
all these things stress out the nerves
the senses
the senses they burn out the senses
nutritional yeast get that out of msg
burns out the senses
get rid of some of these things try it
out
getting some strawberries in here you
guys putting this together
so um
some strawberries reading some comments
while i'm doing this
then we're going to read out the book a
little bit we're going to talk about
some
kick-ass stuff
ashley kevin i got five birds watching
the live with me
[Music]
you're trying to make me laugh because
that's really funny
i like that so i got some papaya here at
the bottom you see this you guys
i got some strawberries layered here
and i'm working on it i might put a
couple more strawberries oh do i love
strawberries you guys love strawberries
or what
because i love strawberries cindy
anthony your information just makes
sense if you really think about it you
just make sense and i love you for
for that thank you thank you for being
here
i'm honored i try to make sense here's
the funny thing is spirit of compassion
really makes sense
me i try to deliver the information the
best i can
and since i'm human you know i could
mess up delivering the information like
if i'm talking or something i'll
spirit of compassion to say well this is
what you need to say
and so i try to make as much sense as i
can with this information since i was a
little kid
the information has been so intense
there's so much information that comes
from spirit of compassion since i was
young did you guys read that first
chapter
in the medical medium new edition the
origins of a medical medium it talks
about me
growing up what a little bit of what i
went through and all that so this is
really
it's in the book all right so i got the
strawberries pretty much
in here looking good
cynthia love your books you have helped
me heal so many issues that matters like
you healing matters it really does i'm
gonna pop some blueberries in
and then i'm gonna read in a little bit
but you guys i'm making the fruit bowl
as we speak look at that
you got your strawberries you got your
papaya here at the bottom
got your strawberries next let's keep on
going are you guys afraid of fruit
are you
[Music]
i hope not
all right um
so guys i'm talking about
some i'm going to talk about medical
medium new edition right now
let's go into that a little bit when
medical medium new edition
what it has is is a whole bunch more
information
way more than the first book did okay
and the first book to help so many
people with multiple sclerosis chronic
fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia anything epstein-barr
related no one knew was epstein bartlett
related the book
blew the roof off of that for people so
they can heal
know how to heal anti-viral protocols
all this stuff that mattered to get
people better
and the new addition is just a whole
other level
taking it a whole nother level it's so
powerful
i'm going to get some mango in here so
if you guys are you've never read that
book
you're going to be mind blown there's
information on like i said chronic
fatigue fibromyalgia lupus
multiple sclerosis hashimoto's adrenal
fatigue
candida migraine shingles colitis
trigeminal neuralgia neuropathy there's
so much in from information here
symptoms like tingles numbness vertigo
tick spasms anxiety
depression body pain menopause symptoms
autism adhd migraines gut health issues
i mean
the amount of information is just
mind-blowing right and
this brought out the truth about autism
being caused by
mercury being caused by toxic heavy
metals so
and and i've i've been teaching about
that for years for decades and then when
this was published it just blew the roof
off of that
about mercury being such such the cause
and such a difficult situation for so
many people creating
autism and kids and adhd in children and
adults
all for all the mercury all of that
vivian says
you're better than a doctor
penny says i purchased thyroid healing i
have hashimoto's i've suffered from
heartburn for years but since starting
the celery et cetera and avoiding no
foods for three months no more heartburn
thank you
looking forward to healing from thyroid
disease many people have healed from
thyroid disease the medical mean books
this talks about hashimoto's
this talks about hyperthyroidism and
thyroid disease in this book the new
edition
so it's in here you guys i mean look
there are people out there they go to 10
15 doctors they spend
thousands and thousands of dollars i
talk about how
i've seen people that have come to me
years ago after seeing 50 doctors
60 doctors nutritionists different types
of doctors specialists neurologists
right
they spend all this money all this money
and then
when you come to the medical medium book
and you
learn what's wrong it's like that book
was
20 something dollars i just spent a
hundred thousand dollars in all these
years
going to doctor after doctor they didn't
have a clue and this is twenty dollars
and you can get a free at the library
and that's even
more i mean unbelievable really
jen says do you use apple cider vinegar
no i don't that's the teeth destroyer
that's what apple cider vinegar is it's
the teeth destroyer
um there's a podcast episode at medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast
i talk about apple cider vinegar the
teeth dissolver
so stay clear from it whatever you do
because you'll just ruin your teeth you
will
ruin and destroy your teeth with apple
cider vinegar you'll be
getting your teeth drilled you'll be get
you'll be your teeth will be losing it's
enamel
over time you will dissolve your
look teeth this beautiful mango and
that's how trends work in
alternative medicine conventional
medicine
they just hurt people wherever they can
without they're not doing it on purpose
some of it but some of it is
and then no one pays the price when you
lose your teeth no one pays the price
when you age
fast from caffeine and you got
osteopenia and your bones are cracking
and breaking when you're 60 years old
when they shouldn't be
and no one's paying the price after all
those years of telling you all those
good things or when they tell you fish
oil
is so good for you with all that mercury
and i'm about to talk about mercury and
medical medium
new addition and they tell you to do all
that fish oil and all that fish oil does
is rot the brain
causes dementia alzheimer's memory loss
parkinson's all these other conditions
so now you're 60 years old
50 years old you're getting alzheimer's
and they've been telling you do fish oil
all these years this is how the trend
world works
let's get some mango pieces in here
rosanna said i borrowed all your books
from the library then i bought them to
read them
again i l love them can't wait to read
your new book
revise and expand it can you see that
mango
that's the back of the mango okay so
i'm gonna take a knife right here and
just cut some of these mango pieces
off you can use a spoon too
see if you guys can see this i'm making
the salad brandycon a dentist put
four silver caps on my six-year-old and
a fluoride sealant without my approval
is heavy metal detox movies the best way
to help her detox the metals
well here's what happens i tell people
if you haven't if you have any kind of
silver
cap silver fillings and you want to keep
them in you you know when you keep them
in
or however as long as you're proactive
and you're doing like the heavy metal
detox smoothie
you're getting the metals out um
if that was my daughter i would have her
on the heavy metal detox movie
but ask your doctor you know whatever
your doctor
wants to do listen to your doctor but if
it was my daughter
or if it was a you know family and
friends and all i'd be
saying hey heavy metal detox smoothie
just to keep up
so that any kind of any kind of metals
at all are being uh taken up even if
even if the caps are still there or the
fillings are still
there you're being proactive by cleaning
up any metals that escape
and go anywhere that's what i would do
if she was my daughter
um ask your doctor and do it do do what
your doctor says but that
that's what i would do any new
mind-blowing podcast coming up yeah
yep there is
you know how i've been talking about
blood draw lately
well i'm really gonna talk about blood
draw
like no one's ever seen i got a podcast
episode coming out on that
pretty soon and it's worth listening to
you're gonna be blown off your seat
um i've talked about blood draw blood
tests already but this is
this is gonna be the full deal of all of
it so yeah
um look out betty i look so smart
walking in the restaurant with the new
book in my hand
that's awesome that's a major
major compliment i'm proud of you i
really am
um putting some mango on top of here
mango pieces
you guys this mango looks incredible
so i'm making the fruit salad
so yeah it's interesting because like i
said there's a lot of
blood doctors that just don't know what
causes anything out there it's true they
just don't
but they're quick to comment on social
media as if they
know a lot
arlene can i get a shout out too please
i'm waiting for your new book to arrive
and where can i find those beautiful
turquoise bowls love the color it makes
me happy
i'm on day eight of the advanced cleanse
i think i just saw incredible incredible
you get a shout out there's no question
amazing i'm glad i saw that
so let's go put one more mango
in here this is almost done
and then we'll read a little in the
medical medium new edition going to talk
about mercury
i'm going to talk about the mercury
demon
fit and fab can this heal vitiligo
well healing vitiligo determines on
learning about vitiligo right so it's
about
learning about the cause of vitiligo
it's about having the medical medium
books so you can learn about it vitiligo
the cause of it is aluminum
and the epstein-barr virus so what
happens is the epstein-barr virus sits
inside your liver
it feeds off of aluminum that's inside
your liver
and then releases a dermatoxin that
kills
melanin the pigment that's behind
the vitiligo and you end up with your
vitiligo so it's all about
doing an antiviral protocol knowing how
to do it and getting rid of the aluminum
heavy metal detox
smoothie it's all about that if i had
vitiligo i'd be on the heavy metal detox
movie i'd be on the vimergy spirulina
i'd be on the vimergy barley grass
that's what i would be doing and be on
the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie debbie my
girlfriend who is on
keto would say that is way too many
fruits carbohydrates
yeah i bet i bet she would say that i
bet she would say that
definitely guys i'm putting more mango
here
but no one's ever gotten sick from
eating fruit because no one ever ate any
fruit
we've had millions and millions and
millions and hundreds of millions of
sick people around the globe
for decades and decades and decades
hundreds of millions of sick people and
guess what fruit wasn't on their plate
i think some people probably had a half
a grapefruit once in a while with little
sugar on top maybe on a sunday or maybe
somebody had blueberry and blueberry
muffins maybe they had a banana and a
banana split
maybe it had fake strawberries in a in a
milkshake somewhere right
maybe they had that but fruit isn't the
number one food group but guess what
the number one food group is the food
group keto people are on
you know what it is it's caffeine
and guess what keto people they get sick
they get sick a lot i've had sick
celebrities
knock on my door over the years that
were on keto i've had sick
doctors knock on my door that were on
keto some that were making a career out
of keto and had to knock on my door
because they were getting so sick
and i've had i've seen it all out there
keto doesn't mean
you're safe oh i'm not keto i'm safe
i'll never get sick
i'm on keto i'm i'm good i'm not going
to get sick because i'm on keto so
that's never going to happen quite the
contrary because
keto doesn't mean anything plant-based
doesn't even mean anything
if you don't do it right you can be
doing keto and do it wrong
you can be doing plant-based and do it
wrong oh that's right but someone lost
weight doing keto after getting off of
processed foods so maybe they're doing
it right no
and they still are on that vinegar and
that caffeine and other things like that
and they still got toxic heavy metals
and pathogens and guess what they still
get sick
and they still get into the dentist
chair and they still lose they still
need all their veneers
all the keto doctors podcast doctors
they all got veneers i know
i know who they all are and i know they
all got the mirrors
all their teeth are like missing they
got bridges veneers they've got implants
and they're keto guys this stuff you
know all of that stuff so now
keto doesn't mean jack squat when it
comes to
when it comes to anything so and i
totally get it and like you said your
your friend is going to be like no no
way for fruit no way because keto is it
i get it i get it but no fruit is
something people
don't eat they just don't they have a
lunchbox apple
they got a lunchbox banana they just
don't eat it
they don't and so but that's not why
anybody's sick people just don't eat
fruit you know
they just don't and that's what's
interesting
um this book is really
an amazing book and i i gotta tell you
guys like the fruit fear chapter
is really um really incredible chapter
so i'm going to go to it right now
i just want to read a little something
out of there so you know
because that that really reminds me of
so many mistakes that are being made out
there right now
um so many mistakes there really is some
of the fruit for your chapter as we
speak
so ryan can you speak on lectins i'm
hearing more and more recently and it's
freaking me out since most of my diet is
fruits and vegetables
it's just gonna sidetrack you to get you
sicker down the road it's a trick
see before the lectin thing blew up a
few years ago
already millions of people healed around
the world from the medical medium books
okay
so the lectin guys were pretending
nobody got better
they were like in a bubble or something
where they were pretending
no one got better until they actually
took a few people off of some foods with
leptin
what they really did is they just took
them off a processed food so it was
another
kind of hit and miss keto diet is what
they did
they took you off of fruits they took
you off of some different vegetables
they took you off of some
starchy carbs and what they did was they
just
put basically they put you on some meat
and vegetables certain vegetables right
and then if you were somebody that were
on processed foods you'd be like whoa
i'm getting better now i'm losing a
little weight i think i'm feeling a
little better
and it was the lectins and it was
probably the
one of the greatest scams in the last
three four years was the lectin scam
um and you know it's really ridiculous
so
what you're going to be told is don't
eat fruits don't eat you know don't eat
some vegetables don't eat
tomato the big lectin guy was like don't
eat celery don't eat celery and then
the whole thing blew up with the celery
juice movement so big he had to give in
and be like okay you can eat celery
celery's fine well you don't have to
worry about those leptins because
because the whole thing was so many
people were healing it just stomped on
everybody the
celery just moved in just stomped on all
the podcast doctors all the other
authors in health
and so what happened is just the lectin
thing is really
it's so misguided there's so much
misinformation about the lectin stuff
it's ridiculous so people have healed
from these foods these herbs leafy
greens
fruits and wild foods okay and
vegetables and in the way medical medium
has
the medical medium information has laid
out debilitating diseases
eczema psoriasis severe fatigue
fibrosis multiple cirrhosis
als parkinson's debilitating diseases
reversed completely reversed healed 100
percent
tens of thousands of healing stories and
they were eating lectins
they were eating the lectins these
lectin
supplement guys try to sell you so
here's how it works
the lectin movement started with people
trying to sell
supplements that were supposedly
protecting you against lectins
it was a scam that's how it was done
so it was like let's tell you about
lectins so we can sell you a lectin
supplement
and that's that's that's how it started
i'm just just being straight up about
what was going on
lectins are in everything and if you
want to not eat anything
like don't eat any food it's it's
lectins are in everything so don't eat
any food whatsoever and
um you know just just live off of
i don't know dirt and water i don't know
live off of something
try to find something to live off of
okay maybe put some rocks
in a soup in a pot of boiling water
throw some rocks in there and throw a
little mud in there
and then try to like stir it up in hopes
that you you avoid lectins because
there's lectins in everything and
um and there's still lectins in dirt
there's still some lectins in turn
so the point is is like i guess you just
can't eat anything right
so the lectin scam was one of the
greatest scams and it made a lot of
people a lot of money
made a lot of people a lot of money so
you'll just fall for the scam
but um hey look try to give you the best
information i can right
and when it comes down to fruit fear
really important and you know it
information to know it turned out to be
fruit is a dirty word because of the war
on sugar and then fruit got thrown into
there it's like
sugar's bad sugar's bad so
fruit must be bad too fruit must be bad
so i got a fruit fear chapter in here
where fruit is not the problem i talk
about it in here i know you probably
can't see it's getting kind of blasted
out
um let's finish up this and we'll talk
about mercury i want to read a little
bit about mercury
information in there so you guys this is
coming together check this out right
i know evil fruit oh no we got
papaya down here okay we got strawberry
we got blueberries we got mango
bettina says yes i have healed from
hashimoto's thanks to you anthony
and it wasn't avoiding lectins see oh by
the way i forgot to tell you one thing
about the lectin story
just so you know the lectin guys
lectin doctors left in gurus
never knew what causes chronic fatigue
syndrome
r.a lyme disease multiple sclerosis
fibromyalgia
and the rest all the different
conditions excellent psoriasis
it's guessing games out there they never
knew what the cause was medical medium
information was the first to put out
that information
they never knew what it was so they're
doing the guessing games like what is it
lectins
well we can sell those things too we can
sell anti-lectins wait a minute what was
it
it could it be uh wait what could be
what could be causing the problem
is it gluten amanda are autoimmune
diseases caused by
unhealthy diet do you talk about
autoimmune diseases in your books
not only do i talk about autoimmune
diseases in the books
i talk about how your body doesn't
attack itself
and that's what science research says
science science and research will say
amanda that your body is turning on
itself and that's what autoimmune is
they think so their theory from 1950
is that your body's immune system is
destroying itself so if you
were diagnosed with any kind of
autoimmune disease whether it's
hashimoto's or ra or anything
they they say that your body is turning
on itself and destroying your cell your
yourself destroying your organs and all
that so your immune system now that's
misinformation
that's a theory that's misguided and
that's designed to body shame you and
also make you basically hate your body
and feel like you're a failure and
you're never going to heal because your
body's turning against itself
dr fan incredible doctor right here at
md
um you are the man that's all i could
say
you are an incredible guy i'm glad
you're here amazing doctor by the way
so look the bottom line is with
autoimmune your body doesn't destroy
itself
it's not attacking itself and
that's how much autoimmune information
is in my books
it's like there's volumes of it for
autoimmune the true cause
viruses so it's viruses that cause
autoimmune
that's the cause of it and viruses like
epstein-barr
that's the cause of autoimmune but it's
not really
autoimmune it's just the cause of the
symptoms people are getting that are
being
labeled as the body's attacking itself
so
if you got a condition and that virus is
behind it
and i talk about that in the books and
how it works
i'm going to finish up the salad talk
about some mercury
michelle l vitiligo and liver rescue and
cleanse the heal yeah
dove ives i opened my mail as i was
watching and your book yay
incredible incredible okay you guys
gonna put a few kiwis in here at the top
[Music]
robin i knew i'm new to mm living off
australia incredible can't find wild
blueberries is it okay to just use the
powder yes
it's okay to use the wild blueberry
powder the vimergy wild blueberry powder
is the one i use
that's the beverage spirulina right here
um they have the wild blueberries too
the wild blueberry powder
so i'm gonna work on
this right here get some kiwis going
i'm gonna read about mercury glad you
guys are here
so happy so i'm peeling back a kiwi
now you can you can do kiwis in
different ways you cut them in half and
scoop them out
when they're ripe you know i like to
peel them too
like this so we're doing that
peel back a few of them so
can you guys see this this fruit bowl
so i got one kiwi peel let's do another
you got your copy today miss shine
the one thing about fruit people just
don't understand it's not
sugar that's the problem it's fat
everybody's being told to eat fat and
they think that's the answer you just
eat
more fat but then end of you end up
eating sugar anyway and you
end up eating wrong sugar i help
my hospital doctor's cholesterol problem
she is listening
she is so compassionate doctor listening
she is
uh mostly an amazing
okay just peeled another kiwi we'll just
keep on going a little bit we'll get one
more
great to have you guys here blood work
info
truth so needed for the medical
profession excellent
dr sherry green it's honored to have you
here an incredible doctor incredible md
thank you sherry for that i mean isn't
that incredible what happens with with
that with with the whole thing with
blood work
they drain you until you basically die
they'll drain the sicker you are
they'll take more blood and more blood
and more blood
just take it until you're done
until you're done
i've seen people get better by just
taking doctor breaks
doctor breaks with like i'm so sick but
yet i've been to five or seven doctors i
need to take a break i can't go to
another doctor
and and they get this moment of reprieve
and their family's not pushing them to
the doctor in that moment
and they don't know it they start
getting a little better because they're
not getting the blood drawn
and taken out constantly anymore they're
getting a chance to come back
and and survive i mean they'll bleed you
to death
is what they'll do so i'm cutting up
some kiwi
gonna slice this up right here
let's put the kiwi on top
i mean if you guys ever wanted to put
honey on this you can't
you can do that if you ever wanted to
put a little honey on here you can do
that
that's an option
so let's get these kiwi pieces on here
so it's pausing
are you pausing on youtube or just
facebook
both
all right put the kiwis on top
that is the fruit bowl right there so
you got your papaya at the bottom
you got your strawberries on top of that
you got your blueberries you got your
mangoes next i don't know if you can see
those mangoes kind of in there
and then you got your kiwi so that's the
fruit bowl
amy says cleanse the heel check out the
mono eating cleanse it sounds extreme
but it is so
so effective and way easier than it
should be it really is
an incredible cleanse the mono eating
cleanse from cleanse the heel
um gastroparesis i mean it's great for
that it's great for
crohn's colitis you can check out the
mono eating section you can try
different versions of it that are in
here not books
just both these books incredible books i
mean all the medical media books are so
filled with information
that's a fruit salad
i'm in the medical medium new edition as
we speak you guys
and i'm in dirty secret okay so dirty
secret
and that's the mercury demon so i'm
gonna read a little piece of it right
here
so is mercury gone yet no
it's not gone yet right
is the nightmare finally over with
mercury
have we come to our senses and learned
to avoid it at all costs for the sake of
humankind
for the sake of our health and
well-being for the sake of our children
nope we haven't it's just that it's out
of sight
and out of mind there's still plenty of
mercury to be had it's constantly at her
fingertips in ways
that are extremely controversial so i'm
going to give you that right now
extremely controversial think about that
for a little bit
you know what's happening in today's
world this is extremely controversial
right
and there's mercury involved in
today's extremely controversial
stuff happening in the world so that's
important to know
just as a result of modern living over
time your body will accumulate
toxic heavy metals such as mercury your
body will
accumulate that mercury every day it
falls out of the sky
it's in pharmaceuticals it's
everywhere there's still plenty of
mercury out there it accumulates over
time we're continually exposed to this
toxin because it slips through the
cracks
figuratively it slips through the cracks
of our healthcare and industrial systems
literally mercury absorbs into the
cracks of your brain
and all of us have some level of mercury
inside our bodies it's unavoidable
so that's important to know so i'm
reading a little bit on the mercury
okay why should we care why should you
guys care why should i care
because mercury is a top fuel for
viruses
that's a top fuel for why people are
sick this is advanced
information right here so if you guys
are here just letting you know it's
advanced
information in the medical field that's
teaching people's out people people out
there so it's important to know
it's the top fuel for viruses viruses
eat mercury that's the big one there why
are some cases of neurological lyme
really really bad not just from the
antibiotic use that happens
but because viruses behind neurological
lime
feed off of mercury that means they have
a lot of mercury in them bad cases of
fibromyalgia
chronic fatigue syndrome at me
neurological lyme just a lot of
different conditions
you got high mercury and you've got the
tingles and numbness aches and pains of
dizziness and that's just not it you've
got floaters in the eyes
body pain burning pain jaw pain all
these different things people have
that's because there's lots of mercury
for the virus to feed
off of and zeolite doesn't cover it it
doesn't cover it i'm letting you know
anybody says oh you just need the
zeolite no stuff's been around for 20
years
it never worked so i medical media
information how to put out
the right way of getting metals out and
that's what's saving so many people's
lives right now
and so mercury is top fuel for viruses
cancer and bacteria so
cancers caused by viruses
okay for the most part caused by viruses
that's the cancer is caused by
and mercury feeds that
virus it feeds those cancer cells
so that's important to know so mercury
is a toxin so to make
cancer you have to have viruses and you
have to have
toxins so to create cancer you need both
those things you need a virus
and you need toxins well mercury is high
on that toxin list
and so if you got the viruses and you
got the mercury if you don't get
one out and they're both there for a
long time and it happens to be a pretty
annoying virus
then you can end up with some type of
cancer
important to know mercury exposure is a
factor behind inflammation
and it can take people hostage by
causing or contributing to a vast number
of symptoms and conditions
okay so mercury can help take
somebody hostage right i don't have any
mercury to show you guys
because you know maybe i need a mercury
prop i got to figure that out like
where's the mercury prop like what can i
use for
mercury prop right mercury so mercury
exposure is a factor behind inflammation
and can take people hostage
by causing or contributing to a vast
number of symptoms and conditions
all right so including depression
yeah mercury anxiety yeah
mercury adhd mercury
autism mercury bipolar disorder mercury
neurological disorders
pain in the back of the head anxiety
it's neurological
brain fog neurological aches and pains
neurological
fatigue neurological so just think about
that
adhd that's mercury autism
mercury bipolar disorder mercury i said
those already
i'm going to say them again because
people are like wait a minute what did
he say
epilepsy mercury okay
depersonalization where you're like kind
of
just feeling so disconnected from
yourself you just don't know why so now
you're
on the search for like you're on the
search for like
you know ways to convince your mind like
how to master your mind so now
now you're checking out all this this
other podcast or something and you're
looking how to master your mind
because you can't you figure maybe
there's something wrong with how you're
viewing things or something and that's
why you got depersonalization meanwhile
you're dealing with mercury and that's
why it keeps on coming back and keeps on
coming back
parkinson's als mercury
heck yeah ms mercury heck yeah
lyme disease symptoms mercury that's
right
tingles numbness ticks twitches spasms
seizures mercury mercury mercury hot
flashes
mercury heart palpitations hair loss
memory loss confusion insomnia
loss of libido yeah mercury fatigue
migraines and thyroid disorders mercury
that's just a that's just a small list
right
how often are people told they've
they've brought a condition like
depression upon themselves
you know you're depressed it's just it's
got to be you
it's got to be you right it's you need a
psychiatrist
you know you're depressed you're going
to need a therapist psychotherapist like
a
psychoanalyst you're going to need some
kind of some kind of help
yeah it's good to get help but it's end
up it's on you
like it's your fault it's your fault
so the depression is your fault you're
not thinking right you're not thinking
positive your brain
you know you don't know how to control
your thoughts you don't know how to see
things
you must be just faulty you must just be
you know
not so great of a person that's what
happens
and it's all part of the mercury's blame
the victim game because that's how it
works and you got mercury
talking for you creating that
depersonalization that anxiety and that
depression
you got mercury talking for you creating
and you're held hostage by mercury and
nobody knows you'd be at your 50th
doctor you'll be 75 years old now
at your 100th doctor like why am i still
depressed after all these years because
no one's going to tell you it's mercury
those depressive symptoms are the
mercury speaking for a patient without
her consent so here it is you got
something inside of you which is a toxin
and it's mercury and it's speaking for
you without your consent
and that's what's happening so you're
depressed you're not feeling good
emotionally mentally
you got the mercury inside of you and
it's kind of like speaking for you
without your choice
it's actually speaking for you without
your consent that's how mercury works
and that's how the mercury demon people
love it
originally so sometimes mercury moves
past the hostage phase
and takes someone out yeah there's
people out there
got a lot of mercury in their brain and
it pushes them over
the edge over the edge and that's really
sad
you know resulting in death by
alzheimer's parkinson's dementia stroke
it's that serious okay i'm reading out
of new edition medical medium
you guys mercury has injured or killed
well over a billion people mercury
has injured or killed and put
over a billion people in an early
grave right but hey there's no study on
that
but where's your study oh i don't know
why a billion people died
do you have a science study on that why
a billion people died we don't know why
a billion people died because they don't
have a study yet
on alzheimer's we don't know why people
have alzheimer's the best medical
technology
in the world and we still don't know why
is it the body attacking itself
that must be it is it genes it's genes
that's why the person has alzheimer's
it's gene jeans i guess
no one likes alzheimer's it's
frightening terrible disease yet it's
rapidly becoming common
and it's a hundred percent mercury
caused
you heard that here first mercury is 100
responsible for alzheimer's disease
you will never in your lifetime hear the
truth about that anywhere else
unless a podcast doctor steals it from
here and they have
okay there's two podcast doctors out
there
that have stolen the information
straight out of medical medium book one
because there's no science and research
behind it
and it was published here first so they
took it from here and then they talk
about mercury now
because people want to hear about
mercury because millions of books sold
around the planet
and people want to know about mercury
now because of the first book
so then you got a couple of podcast
doctors out there they're acting like
they know something about mercury
it's kind of funny you know they should
cite where it comes from
but they don't that's classic
that's how egos work out there i want it
cited so someone can heal
they don't want to cite it because they
want to look like they know what they're
talking about
um so let's get let's go into this a
little bit more
everyone has a different combination of
toxic heavy metals inside their brains
in alzheimer's aluminum is commonly
present along with mercury
when that's the case aluminum in the
brain will play a role and contribute to
the disease that said
you can also have alzheimer's without
aluminum
whereas you can't have alzheimer's with
aluminum without mercury so here's how
it works
aluminum by itself you guys right
aluminum by itself can't cause
alzheimer's it can't
i mean it can mess you up don't get me
wrong
but you gotta have mercury in there too
with the aluminum to create alzheimer's
you can even have mercury without
aluminum and create the alzheimer's
right
so that's important to know all right
so let's go the medical industry
will never blame mercury for the con
for any condition any condition at all
do you know why
because the medical industry is guilty
guilty
of putin mercury in a ton of drugs
man
you will never ever in your lifetime
ever see the blame
from the industry on mercury you'll
never see the industry blame mercury for
anything the medical industry
is so guilty they got so much blood on
their hands with mercury
it would be a cut a trillion is there
something called it could be is
katrilian real
what's the biggest number you could ever
think of what's the biggest number
is wasn't it something like a trillion
zeros or something is that the biggest
number with like
a nine after it like what's the biggest
number out there because i'm not a
mathematician
but i can tell you this that lawsuit
would be that much money because you got
a billion people dead because of mercury
you got
pharmaceuticals with mercury in them
yeah keep those pharmaceuticals coming
they all got mercury in them to some
extent
[Music]
and so it's never going to get blamed
for anything ever ever
ever it's never going to ever get
the blame instead some cosmetic doctor
will come on the medical media platform
and say
there's no study that determines mercury
has anything to do with alzheimer's
that's what you'll get meanwhile just so
yeah of course there isn't
you're not going to put a study on
something when literally the industry
itself that's going to do the study has
mercury and all their stuff and had
mercury and all their stuff for so long
including quicksilver going all the way
back
which i'll talk about in a second okay
you're not
fingers would be pointed into the
direction of the mercury man
whose true name is unknown
uh illumination tell you anything
if i say the word illumination
is that close to illumination what's the
word
do you guys know the word hey baby paris
you leave comments sometimes give shout
out to you too
because i know i got a shout out for you
guys
um you guys are awesome cindy yeah cindy
bowles good to see you again
yep exactly totally pretty funny
michelle l guillain-barre i saw
guillain-barre there the
epstein barr key limbo so yeah
so anyway the mercury man
all right whose true name is unknown
which
giving you kind of like some hence
illumination
right that basically
is is over everything in the industries
controls the industries right
okay his true name is unknown he's
responsible for the original and very
first good old boy industry it's the
good old boy industry man
mercury is the original good old boy
industry
that's what it is it's killed billions
of people though
worldwide billions of people
um so it wants you
it wants the medical industry to
continue to use mercury in their medical
treatments involving children and adults
what
what did i just say just reading the
book
so okay i've only covered the basics
when it comes to the dirty secret of
mercury that's just the basics that's
just the basics you guys
[Laughter]
pretty funny aj all right medical medium
revised
and expanded new edition
right you guys new addition let's talk
about dental amalgams
so about those let's get into that
okay there's so much to read and talk
about like you guys i could go to town
we can talk like this is
you know we can talk about some killer
stuff right here
all right dental amalgams
dental amalgam fillings are another
common source of exposure to mercury
so many of us have had these silver
fillings in our mouths
i've been blessed to not have to have
those silver fillings
i've been blessed and i have to have you
know fillings because
all this fruit i'm eating should have
rotted out every one of my teeth and i
should have implants like all the
podcast doctors that are all keto and
tell you not to eat fruit
i should have like no teeth left from
all these oranges i sucked down every
single day i must have eaten
thousands and thousands of oranges i
probably ate a hundred oranges last week
um but yeah the podcast doctors who
don't eat any fruit and tell you not to
even touch a lemon they're
just got all the veneers and they got
all the implants 24 7.
all right
this is fun reading the new edition
medical meme new edition talking about
dental work
all right let's go so many of us had
these silver fillings in our mouths and
had
hat and have had them at one point right
it's becoming popular to get all
mercury-based fillings removed at a
holistic dentist office do you know why
because of medical medium 35 years
of teaching about those mercury fillings
going all the way back
to the 80s when everybody thought they
were perfect people got their mouths
filled with it
dentists were on board there was nothing
bad about
it there was no science there's no
science now still
all right this may seem sensible like
the right thing to do
but you have to be very careful about
the process getting
all of your amalgam fillings removed at
the same time can lead to an extremely
high level of mercury exposure
regardless
of the best techniques and protection
available at the dentist office you know
who agrees with me gina and masha
check out the youtube episode medical
meme youtube channel
okay so masha and gina amazing dentists
really good close friends of mine they
came on
the youtube episode with me you guys
should you guys
scroll down on youtube and find that
episode
see dr fon um
so yeah so let's go on this a little bit
more the exposure can put a heavy load
on the immune system and also feed
viruses so when you get your
your mercury fillings out it can feed
viruses all of a sudden boom you got
extra mercury in there and look that can
happen but
it's what the heavy metal detox
smoothies for right you can always ask
your doctor if that's right for you but
it's what i would recommend
recommend my friends and family it's in
the books it's in the book
got the virus that feeds off of mercury
when the mercury escapes and gets out
okay and then when you get all of those
mercury fillings at once then the
bloodstream fills up and then all of a
sudden now if you've got
viral issues it can go into a massive
kill-off
of not the virus but a massive kill-off
of your red blood count
could lose your red blood count in a
shot getting all your mercury fillings
removed
[Music]
so the exposure is a trigger from those
getting all those out it can trigger off
any health conditions whether existing
ones that flare up are new ones that
develop from a dormant virus that was
not
active and then became active and then
that's the re-ignition
that's the re-ignition of epstein-barr
okay
the reigniting of it people are getting
tested for that now because of medical
medium books like this one
anyway so i know people who have had 10
fillings dug out at once and as a result
their blood platelets dropped so low
that they almost died it's best to
remove metal fillings only when an
individual tooth requires it
hear that such as if the filling becomes
unstable or the tooth is damaged
if your teeth and fillings are all in
good order
and you're still anxious to have the
amalgams removed then get
only one taken out at a time schedule at
least a month between each removal
so you so you don't trigger that viral
load and get yourself sick
if you're ready if you already had all
your metal fillings removed then it's
time to do some clean up
baby some clean up protect yourself
and if you get new cavities select the
safest filling option available and make
sure it doesn't contain mercury know
that anything is better than a filling
that contains mercury
so it's information on the mercury man
it's just a little bit there's a lot
more in here which is really cool
i talk about um
so yeah so the medical medium new
edition you guys all have it i'm
assuming you guys all have it
get it from the library for free
eventually if you can't afford it it's
really inexpensive though it's on sale
at amazon.com right now in the us
but dental work of all kinds there's
metals involved with all kinds of dental
work
okay i won't name the brands
plastic braces still got metals
metal braces got metals fluoride
treatment
metals neuroantagonist
aluminum byproduct in your fluoride well
is fluoride that will cause
neurodegenerative damage
you got that okay um
not trying to say throw out your
retainers i'm not trying to say any of
that that's not
it i'm just saying there's metals
everywhere there's metals and all of
this just so you know
so that's important it's metals in all
the dental work
okay um yeah
any but don't fear it's not about fear
it's never about fear with medical
medium information it's about being
armed
with the truth and being empowered to
make choices
armed with the truth be empowered to
that's what it is illumination man
michelle i saw that heavy metal detox
smoothie is what i recommend friends and
family i'm not sponsored
okay and that's the vimergy spirulina
barley grass the dulce the cilantro the
wild blueberries right
the wild blueberries it's a wymans wild
okay so important to know
you guys it's an honor to be here
honored to have you guys with me right
now
that's the fruit bowl i'm heading off to
tiktok and ig
what about metals and false teeth yeah
but see it's about making sure you're
doing the work
and making sure you're taking care of it
that's what it's about you can have
metals you can play with metals you can
touch metals
you can play with metals all day i'm
touching metals absorbing in my
bloodstream as we speak
but i know i'm doing the right things
every day to remove it and that's the
key right there
important to know lowering fats is
important too i talk about that in the
books
guys i'm heading off to tick tock and ig
going tik tok live ig live
probably going to be a little bit more
rowdier there because i don't know
that crowd's not as nice and they always
say where's your science
where's your science where's your study
doesn't matter how many people healed
all right
you guys love you greatly heading off