I'm with Kelly gors my dear friend right
here we're going to talk about the Gaia
heel conference yes which is really
incredible so what are we doing at this
conference it's the first finally live
event we're doing it with Gia at the
Gaia Spirit B to Colorado it's November
9th and 10th so it's only a few weeks
away a few tickets are left so click the
links in our bio to buy some tickets and
be there in the flesh with medical
Medium you're going to want to be there
because I'm going to talk about some
really crazy stuff like for real it's
going to be off the hook I'm letting you
guys know that because it's not the same
thing all right this is different I
don't usually do the lecture circuit so
much cuz I'm busy writing the books busy
doing all kinds of stuff I got them down
you got you got me there so I'm making
sure that that talk is going to blow
people's minds like blow their minds I'm
going to say some things I'm probably
going to regret but that's okay true
medical medium fashion that's what I do
I'm going to talk about life-changing
stuff on a whole different level things
you can do when you can't sleep good
that's going to blow your mind I'm going
to talk about some other different
healing tools but it's going to be
really really enlightening I'm doing a
light blast as well from s so people are
just going to be blown away and they're
going to feel it right down to the crown
of their head down to their bottom of
their feet it's going to be really
mindblowing and you're going to be
talking which is going to be incredible
you got aw there there's other
incredible speakers it's going to be
that powerful and that good yeah who
doesn't want to go to
Colorado who doesn't want to go to
Colorado Okay I want to go to Colorado
so I going to be there it's going to be
amazing make sure you guys are there if
you can be there click the link at the
bio we'll see you there
[Music]