we start our psychosis show psychosis
before we start that special
announcement just want to take a minute
out I launched a podcast episode today
I'm so excited and it's micro doing it's
an incredible episode check it out okay
medical medium at Apple podcast check it
out if you get a chance link is in the
description in the bio so I haven't put
out a podcast episode in a long time
it's been quite a while I know a lot of
you guys rely on the podcast there's so
much powerful health information plus
meditations and so much but I wanted to
start off with the micro doing episode
because you know it's important
important for a lot of people to know
about that information I think you're
going to be blown away mind blown it's
going to be a great episode check it out
when you get a chance that's one
announcement okay hold on second
announcement okay I was on Nicole lapens
podcast Link in the profile Link in the
description I'm excited she's an amazing
person an incredible podcast so check
that out if you get a chance so look
into that link is in the description
link is in the bio all right so I was in
Nicole Lain podcast it's an episode it's
incredible he link said oh my God hi was
just listening to your new podcast
mind-blowing it's crazy I mean it's
really a good one all right the podcast
was still phenomenal you you heard it
too thank you thank thank you thank you
thank you it's all s so though I'm just
trying to deliver trying to deliver the
information I can't take too much credit
Jake Davis said so excited to listen to
the new podcast yeah new podcast episode
come on come on you guys if you're
coming on right now we're doing a show
about psychosis so I'm going into brains
saer I'm going to talk about it because
a lot of people deal with low levels of
psychosis it's really difficult people
struggle mentally emotionally okay so
that's a second announcement third
announcement check out my telegram I've
been putting out really important
details critical information so you
might want to check that out my telegram
okay so go there you know listen if you
get a chance you may be somebody that
was really affected by false information
out there and falsities and me being
framed and it's all lies and everything
else you actually might somebody that's
affected by that so I have to put out
the details and set the record straight
for anybody in the community that had
their head twisted just twist it up with
all the BS and lies and everything so I
wanted to make sure I'm releasing a
little bit of really powerful
information um on telegram so I just
released some yesterday so check it out
when you get a chance if you're somebody
that's been affected and been harmed
because a lot of people in the community
now for four years have been harmed we
know we've gotten the messages we've
gotten the information about how much
they've been harmed it's actually really
scary they've they've stopped working
with their doctors they stopped working
with uh mm info they stopped you know
liking themselves they started hating
them I I've seen it all they were just
so so hurt and so confused by the
falsities and the false stories and the
lies that it has stopped a lot of people
from their healing it's changed the
course of a lot of people's lives in the
community and a lot of people are
documenting it now and they're giving us
that document documented information and
it's frightening absolutely frightening
and so um I'm going to set the record
straight for the community very
important so on telegram that's what
I've been doing if you're interested
that's what I've been doing on telegram
very important um that's the third
announcement before we go into the
psychosis talk out of brainsaver third
announcement just to
rewind first announcement I released a
new podcast episode micro doing check it
out medical medum podcast at Apple
podcast you can go there and see it okay
and it's really cool all right it's it's
about psychedelics and so forth and all
that and then yeah it's about micro
doing that all that stuff and then I was
on Nicole Lapin podcast how incredible
money rehab so it's her money rehab
podcast Nicole laen link is in the
profile link is in the description so
that's a really interesting episode you
have to listen to it and third Telegram
telegram to set the record straight
please check that out unbelievable
what's going on anyway you guys let's
get started all right I'm excited I'm
going to pull my little board over I
might do a little bit of some board work
if you guys are okay with
that all right very important
information I got to tell you guys a lot
of people are struggling with
psychosis and you know they they blame
themselves they think it's their fault
they think it's their they're bad people
they think some something's wrong with
them you know and a lot of people end up
struggling even more because of it
because now they hate themselves now
they think they're causing it now they
think they're the problem Neurosis
psychosis
OCD Mania severe depression anxiety all
of it all boggled up and you know all
kind of added together and bundled up in
one thing so many people deal with that
right mm School mm school I saw that
coming up on IG all right so let's go
into it a little bit psychosis can occur
at many different levels an extreme
situation is when someone becomes
completely disconnected from their
surroundings right an extreme situation
where now they're just like they don't
know who they are they're completely
manic they're they're actually
delusional they're hallucinating you
know that does happen to a lot of people
it's rising right now it's just in the
us alone never mind worldwide psychosis
is rising when it's extreme but we're
going to talk talk about the less
extreme we talk about the mild varieties
and all that but Extreme varieties of
psychosis happening right now in this
country and around the world so much of
that's going on where someone is they
don't even know where they are they
don't know their
surroundings there was a story out there
some guy just ran through naked through
an airport whatever he ended up dying
inside of some kind of jet airplane
engine or something and there's you see
this stuff out there all the time where
they just all of a sudden something like
goes on in the brain and boom they're
just blasting off so and I'm not talking
about like mind altering drugs and stuff
like that and I'm talking about
pharmaceuticals and stuff like that I'm
not talking about I'm talking about
where they're just living their life
everything seems to be going okay and
then pop something goes off like pop
something just happens
internally and they're into a bout of
psychosis now doesn't always happen like
that where you're living your life and
you're going along and everything's fine
and everything's Dandy and then boom
right it doesn't always do that it also
has a slow buildup slow buildup where
someone's struggling a little bit they
got emotional they got emotional
struggles they got the depression they
got the anxiety they're struggling
struggling then with that they got the
bipolar a little bit you know real ups
and downs they've got the anger the
frustration and the anger and the
sadness and all of that and then they're
just then they're hating themselves
they're hating themselves it's like
nobody could ever even understand
because no one understands what they're
feeling no one understands what they
nobody understands what they're going
through and they're seeing their
psychiatrists and seeing their
therapists they're seeing their psychi
analysts and they're seeing their you
right their coaches and they're seeing
all their different health professionals
everywhere and they're like I I'm really
struggling I got so much going on and
then the OCD can kick in and then back
to depression then back to anxiety then
it's up it's down and then they're
struggling then they're level just for a
little bit and then boom a panic attack
comes and then they're just level a
little bit and then they lose a complete
night's sleep and now they don't even
they're not sleeping good they get two
hours a night here 4 hours a night here
they can't get that eight hours of sleep
they can't get that seven hours of sleep
or 10 hours of sleep I noticed on
another note all the influencers right
who don't have to work for a living the
ones that came from money they can sleep
12 hours a night 12 hours a night don't
wake me up okay because I'm going to get
my beauty sleep and sleep a whole 12
hours and wake up whenever I feel like
it in the morning because I got a trust
fund and everything else and it really
doesn't matter and I I'm all set and let
me go now on social media and do
something because I want to do something
on social media whatever not talking
about that I'm talking about people who
are actually getting four hours of sleep
3 hours of sleep 5 hours of sleep people
who have to work for a living people who
have to survive people who have to you
know live life
and they're stuck with this psychosis
they're stuck with
Neurosis they get blamed for being
neurotic they get blamed for being extra
sensitive they get called terrible names
they struggle you guys happens all the
time I see it out there so many
emotional struggles you guys know what
I'm talking about so much is happening
out there okay yeah I got the Whiteboard
let's see if I can make a mess on the
Whiteboard let's see if I can if we're
keeping drugs out of the equation to
explain this whole thing whether they're
prescribed Pharmaceutical right or not
the other explanation is developing
illness inside so I wanted to talk about
a couple of things people are developing
problems inside an illness inside is
developing that's what leads us to so
many emotional struggles it's an illness
developing in the mind the brain in here
okay really in the brain tissue then
from there it transfers to the ghost it
transfers to the ghost so I want to just
do a little bit here all right
so you got your hopefully you can see
this I got new markers okay so you got
your brain right there's your brain your
squiggly
brain all
right so that's your
brain can you see that all right that's
your physical brain and what happens is
we get an illness internally in that
physical brain we get an illness
developing something's wrong with that
brain something's developing in there
okay and as we do that we're now we now
have a physical problem with our brain
it's real we're struggling anxiety
depression OCD
bipolar okay Mania psychosis
Neurosis sadness guilt that's
unexplainable all of it a mental
struggle all of it there's some type of
illness developing in the brain physical
physical okay stop blaming it on
yourself it's physic physical right of
course we can have emotional struggles
of course we can have all kinds of
different problems with emotional
struggles of course we there's so much
abuse that happens in so many people's
lives there's all kinds of psychological
torture Psy psychological warfare on
people in people's lives there's bad
relationships all of this right but that
adds to it right there's trauma there's
struggles that adds to it it's like we
have something physical do in the brain
creating things anxiety the depression
the dementia the Alzheimer's the memory
loss the brain fog the right whatever
the Neurosis The psychosis the Mania the
bipolar the
OCD even the mildest mildest versions of
all that D ADHD all of it something's
brewing in the brain
something is developing physically and
then yeah take an emotional struggle
take a bad relationship take a bad
partner take something that happened to
you take a wrongdoing that happened to
you totally misunderstood totally
betrayed you got a knife in your back
all of it take all that and then it
compels onto also the physical part so
now you're at the therapist now you're
at the the you know the
psychiatrist now you're looking for
help and you got two things going on the
therapist doesn't know the psychiatrist
doesn't know they don't know you
actually also have a physical problem
going on in the brain and then they're
focused on the emotional problem right
they're focused on the emotional stuff
hey you were betrayed you were
misunderstood people didn't understand
you something happened to you you were
abused something went on right you got
that but you also got the physical are
you guys with me on this so get this
right there's a physical and then
there's the
ghost and then there is the ghost
yep here's the
ghost that's the ghost what is that I'm
going to radiate that out a little
bit that's the ghost that lives inside
your
head that's your
soul that is it right
there that's your physical brain and
here is the nonphysical call it
metaphysical call it spiritual
Call It Whatever You Like call it
ghost whatever that is your spirit if
that's what you want to say that is your
soul that is your physical on the
physical side you got things developing
you got problems going on something's
happening inside here we're going to
talk about the different
things
metaphysically you got your ghost right
here okay what happens is these interact
when we have problems emotionally that
are also problems physically there's an
interaction that occurs this is where
the lines are so crossed or blurred or
however you want to say it or see it
this is why people struggle forever for
years they're like they're working on
things they're going they're going here
they're going there they're signing up
to these programs here for their mental
they're doing affirmations they're going
to this therapist they're going to this
coach they're going everywhere because
they think hey it's just it's all
emotional I can tackle this I can fix
this I can turn this around been they're
struggling for 6 months they're a little
better a little better a little better 3
months later they get triggered boom
back into it they're struggling
struggling now to another therapist now
to another psychiatrist now to another
coach now doing another program now
doing another course whatever it is and
then now you're here online here you're
here online there you're finding all
this information you're like I could
beat this I could beat this okay I'm
getting a little better again I'm I'm
changing my life a little bit I'm
starting to spend more time time quality
time with myself I'm doing all this and
boom boom you're down you're down again
you're down again you got triggered o
you got triggered into it all over again
and so what happens is people don't
realize this because something's
happening in here
physically inside the
brain and then we go along and we're
trying to remedy it
here we're trying to fix the ghost we're
trying to fix the soul we're trying to
fix our spirit we're trying to fix our
emotional aspect of us the ghost that
lives in here and they live together see
this right here okay I'm putting the
ghost in here too right guess that's
what happens and something I want to
bring up which is really really
incredible mm information all right when
you go through a trauma or a struggle it
could be small to someone large to you
or you go through some kind of
emotional bad news or you've been
betrayed really bad or maybe some abuse
happened or whatever it is maybe
psychological warfare maybe psychic
attacks whatever it is what happens is
maybe just something occurred like a car
accident maybe it's something like that
where it's black and white in the moment
what happens is your soul exits your
physical brain
it exits your physical brain that's why
you'll hear people say I've talked about
this before where I was looking at
myself why that was happening in that
moment I got that bad news and it was
like I was out of body I was out of my
body yeah because you
were it felt like an out of- body
experience it really did it felt like I
was out of body man I was looking down
at myself I was looking at myself I
didn't even know where I was who I just
saw myself I was knocked out of myself
because what happened while you were
struggling why that struggle happened
why something occurred while you got
that bad news while you were traumatized
where you had that betrayal while
something happened to you I hear it when
people cheat on people when
relationships it's that moment you find
out you've been cheated on it's that
moment you found out you were
betrayed so many people what happens is
instantly in that moment their soul
leaves their physical brain it goes boom
and it's out of body it's over here on
the side it's over here it's over here
it's over here it gets knocked out of
you your soul gets knocked out of you
that's what how how it works bad news
boom Oh out of body there's a reason for
that because what happens right here in
your physical brain is stuff starts to
heat up and burn up the emotional
centers of the brain bra start to get
heated up and burn up see the emotional
centers of the brain right here they
start to get heat up and burn up and the
Soul has to leave so you don't get Soul
damage severe Soul damage and that's
what happens to so many people they get
Soul
injuries but they go out of body to try
to prevent severe Soul injuries right so
their soul the ghost pops right out it
gets knocked right
out you just found out you got cheated
on someone just told a huge lie about
you you were
betrayed someone abused you out of
nowhere maybe it's long-term abuse and
you're so allergic you're so allergic to
the bad people you're so allergic to the
bad situation that literally your soul
lives outside of your body and now you
got
depersonalization that's actually not
necessarily physical anymore you got
that dep personalization your soul is
living outside of your body and most
people are walking around while their
soul is outside of their
body and that's the ghost and it sits
outside of the
body and say you didn't have a really
difficult situation something didn't
really happen that's really grave or bad
didn't get that bad news or that bad
betrayal or whatever it is and you're
struggling because your brain is dirty
it's got junk and garbage in it your
brain has got junk and garbage in it
solvents
petrochemicals toxic heavy metals so
it's got
solvents
chemicals toxic heavy metals in here
right I'm putting little markers
deposits of toxic heavy metals okay some
solvents in here too let's see what we
can do with that maybe we get red for
solvents let's do that solvents are in
here as well we got the red we got the
black right the toxic heavy metals the
red the
solvents
okay what happens is we got something
physical Brewing something physical
wrong we got the anxiety we got the
depression we got the dep
personalization that's physical we got
the bipolar we got the Mania we got the
OCD we got the ADHD With It All We Got
the brain severe brain fog we got the
memory loss we can even move into
dementia whatever we got all that and
then we got the Neurosis then we got the
psychosis then we got the
Mania
yep Lisa that's a really funny comment
um
yeah we got something physically going
on physically wrong in there we do let's
go into it a little deeper
Now problem is that our soul lives
inside our physical brain and so you
have the ghost in here and the ghost
doesn't always live outside of our
physical brain our ghost doesn't always
live outside of our physical brain keep
that in mind
okay it doesn't normally live
outside playing with all my new colors
over
here so what happens is we go to the
psychiatrist we go to the counselor we
go to the psychotherapist we go to the
therapist psychoanalyst we go to try to
find help we look for coaches we're
looking for answers we want to be
coached we want to be taught we want to
be taught tools so we can somehow
navigate with this depression and this
anxiety and all our struggles and
everything but for some reason we just
can't get rid of it all together and
even when we start doing some things for
ourselves like physically we're taking
care of ourselves better we're eating
better and all these things and it's
improving and it's improving all it
takes is one Nast NY thing to occur one
nasty thing to happen and then boom
we're triggered in right back in the
saddle again and now we're doing it all
over
again the goal is to heal our brains
physically and then when something
happens and we're triggered back into it
we start to doubt ourselves we start to
feel like we're faulty we start to lose
Faith and Hope in ourselves we start
thinking that it's us it's our fault
it's your fault
we start thinking that maybe I am a bad
person because everybody else seems to
be living their life look at the person
driving in the car next to me I bet you
they got a good life I bet you they're
okay I bet you they're not struggling
hey look at on television right there
those people seem like they got it all
together hey look at those people they
got it good too I must have something
wrong with me I can't pull it together I
can't get past this I can't get out of
this quick sand and I'm stuck in it and
then you doubt yourself and you judge
yourself and then others tend to judge
you because you're there again you're
back to being sick again you're back to
struggling again but not your
fault it is not your fault it is not
your fault you're not a bad person you
didn't create your emotional struggle
it's not because you want to be
emotional it's not because you want to
have an emotional struggle or a mental
struggle it's not because you're looking
for attention that's not it at all
because that gets thrown on everybody
you're just looking for attention you
just want that attention you just you're
doing this on purpose you have a
pattern and the psychoanalyst
psychotherapist like you got a pattern
this is because you want this to be and
then then you know some of the new age
people will be like you came into this
world it's because a past life you had
your head chopped off Queen Victoria
chopped it off and so you know back in
the back hundreds of years ago and
that's why you're like this and maybe
you know what you know what in 1920 you
were driving your car and you went off a
a bridge and you drowned in your car and
that's why you're like this or you know
you were the chef for the king in
16003 and you know you made a bad meal
and the King you know was mad and they
just off with your head and they you
brought that over to this new place
that's you know right the new age brings
you into that whole
thing or you signed a contract when you
were on the other side I'm signing a
contract to come into this world and to
be all messed up I'm signing a contract
this is what I want to do I'm up I'm up
in The Ether right now I'm up in heaven
right now and I'm going to sign a
contract where I'm going to come around
again yep here's my contract I'm going
to live in a whole bunch of brain fog
and a whole bunch of ADHD and a whole
bunch of mania and a whole bunch of
psychosis and a whole bunch of anxiety
and depression personalization I'm
signing into this one here we go I just
signed my name way up there and way up
there I did the Scrolls I'm up out there
I'm looking at all the records and I'm
going to sign my DOT at line here bo bo
bo going back down now now I'm going to
go down here and have a whole shitty
time boom I get here I wake up woo now
I'm depressed and personalization and
all of a sudden some new age person says
you know you signed that contract you
brought that on yourself you chose to
come into this life to suffer like
this it's not how it works yes the
contracts no disrespect to anybody's
belief system it's not it no dis
disrespect to any of it I have a have
enough Hard Times myself enough Hard
Times everybody's like oh you talk to S
so you know since you were four years
old and everything I get a I get a kick
me sign on my back I'm just saying not
judging anybody for any belief system
but we're told that this is what it is
and why we're struggling we're told we
signed a contract and we came back in
yep Uma says oh man I've heard that so
many times about
contracts but really really I've had
people that came to me 25 years ago
looking for
help and they be like I've Been
Everywhere aw I saw this psychiatrist I
got three psychiatrists I got three
other therapists I've tried everything
under the sun I went to the I went the
new age route right they told me this
and this and this I signed a contract I
came back in there what do you think's
going on here and I'm like well Spirit
of
compassion thinks we got something
physical going on in our
head and you might want to ask the
doctor
this and then they go they go find a
doctor that'll listen to them and the
doctor's like you know
what something could be going on let's
test Spirit of compassion never said
yeah you signed a contract and you came
in here yeah you had your head chopped
off you know 300 years ago yes you were
burned at the Stak because you were a
witch and the 1600s in Salem
Massachusetts yes that's why Spirit of
compassion never ever ever ever said
that to anyone
anywhere about why they're suffering
struggling
emotionally because there's other
reasons there's other things going on
physical things that are going on let's
go into it a little bit St Su says aw
I'm Holding
On by a thread using trauma shock and
lost brain shot my daddy passed from
dementia last night oh my God It's a
cruel
disease it truly is I'm protecting my
brain with mm info the best I can right
now just know that my heart's with you
truly okay my heart is really with you
um I understand the nuances I understand
the details and I think a lot of people
don't know that what happens when you
lose lose a loved one uh from dementia
um Alzheimer's and it's not as simple
and it's not just you know it's not so
cut and clear it's an agonizing process
and there's there's so much to it
there's so much to it um so back to this
physically we got things wrong with the
brain let's go into it a little bit now
okay you guys all
right it usually takes something like
toxic heavy metals but not just toxic
heavy metals in the brain not just
Metals in the brain that can cause
problems with
psychosis it takes also
solvents chemicals and
solvents what happens is a chemical
interaction can happen inside the brain
with toxic heavy metals and a chemical
reaction can happen inside the brain
with lots of different things but metals
react to solvents and other chemicals
and petrochemicals and so what happens
is when we get exposed to something so
say somebody has some metals inside
their brain and they're already
struggling they already have problems
and then they get their carpets
cleaned and the cleaning service comes
in and literally dumps solvents inside
their floors from the machines solvents
that are sitting in the floor in the
carpet underneath the floorboard and
those solvents are in the air they're on
your skin you're breathing them in
they're the carpet cleaning chemicals
that I've seen trigger people for years
and the carpet cleaning chemicals are
solvents that when they get in your
sinuses and find their way into the
bloodstream to your brain they can
interact with the toxic heavy metals
causing a chemical reaction that can
throw somebody from a very mild mild
case of something into boom some kind of
psychosis or really some type of
neurosis that's out of control or
seemingly out of control it's one
example right there on its
own okay um
smoking chemicals in smoking you guys
anything any kind of smoke chemicals in
any kind of smoke the fake logs that
everybody Burns at this time of
year the fake logs that are completely
soaked and saturated with chemicals like
fragrances and petrochemicals and
solvents right there anything that
someone is smoking on top of that along
with breathing in smoke that's burning
in a fire pit a lot of people burn
treated wood in fire pits and the
treated wood has solvents on it it's
saturated solvents you ever see a piece
of trated wood piece of trated wood is
actually has all it actually has green
you know the green color that's on the
wood get a 2x4
2x6 right whatever it is that you're
getting treated wood a lot of people
take treated wood and they burn it in
their backyard they burn it in their
fire pits they burn it in Posh areas
that are really expensive to live where
rich people live and they burn it where
people that don't have resources and
don't have a lot of money live they burn
it there too they burn it everywhere and
that's a massive trigger for a lot of
people where you breathe in that smoke
could be anything something you're
smoking something you're breathing in
big trigger for all kinds of levels of
anxiety and depression but to up it to
up it into yosis eventually Christine
says o says please talk about the
laundry scense they are out of
control I I broke the the news to the
world about the fragrances and the
laundry detergents and the fabric
softeners and the
plugins and all the right all the
different fragrances and the cones and
perfumes and everybody punished me
punished me greatly I mean seriously
like they were trying to cancel me a
while back I mean just like years ago
they're doing everything they could on
social to cancel me because people love
their C candles they love their fake
logs they love their fabric softener
sheets and it'd be crazy because you'd
see on social media all these people
right they would be like you know yo I'm
un social I'm eating better I'm into
Natural Health I'm into all this great
stuff let me burn my scented candles I'm
having my friends over we're going to
have a great dinner they got the fake
logs burn burning they're loaded with
perfume which is all that toxic metal
and everything else and then they're
burning scented candles and then they
got the the worst conventional
detergents petrochemicals and solvents
all in it and they're just one big stink
one big stink bomb getting into sinuses
getting into the
bloodstream yeah and that stuff just
boom just sits inside our liver and it
torments us too which could be a trigger
as well so so going into like say you're
say you're
struggling and you're suffering in some
way depression anxiety dep
personalization deep sadness you can't
explain ups and downs anger and
frustration sadness said it already and
then maybe even something more serious
like you got some manic stuff going on
some Mania you got some serious OCD got
some serious brain fog got the bipolar
diagnosis or something that someone
might have given you and you're doing
all
that and then it can get triggered it's
all you're already struggling you
already have something going on inside
the brain itself and I'm going to go
into something what happens when these
two start to melt together right here
the ghost your soul your spirit whatever
you want to call it and your physical
brain and then you got all these things
going on and then boom you get triggered
by solvents and petrochemicals and yeah
la laundry detergents and plugins and
sented candles and yes and clones and
perfumes and it gets into the
bloodstream fast because these are like
these are solvents they go through the
brain they go through the body into the
organs and then they go and they touch
sensitive brain tissue that's what they
do they touch sensitive brain
tissue okay so you got your
brain right and in your brain are is all
this sensitive tissue when you're sick
and you don't feel
good when you're sick and you don't feel
good
okay you got all this sensitive
tissue gets triggered really easy it
does so much so that you can get
triggered emotionally really easy too
because physically you're struggling
inside because you got physical stuff
happening you got petrochemicals you've
got all the different fragrances in here
you got the MSG in here you got a build
up of the toxic salts if I hear one more
time somebody in help try to recycle the
same old BS and pretend it's new quality
salts you need plenty of fats plenty of
quality salts stay away from this stay
away from that right the good fish oil
do the krill oil don't do the fish if I
hear that one more time that same old
Spiel out there this same old stick
right when people don't even realize why
people are sick or what's going on in
there the reason why you'll see medical
medium
doesn't obsess about salt make sure you
have all the salt in your water make
sure you put salt in your water make
sure you put salt on your food good
salts are good they're supportive for
this they're supportive for that the
reason why you don't hear that the
spirit of compassion says too much salt
builds up in the brain and it
crystallizes it crystallizes inside the
brain because it's got nowhere to go
because you're not peeing it out in time
it's build more salt is coming in and
going out more salt is coming in and
going out you can still get a blood test
and be low on sodium in your bloodstream
and have salt deposits inside the
brain that are
crystallized and no longer are they
liquifying people have MSG deposits they
have salt deposits they have calcium
deposits from being so acidic all the
time then they have toxic heavy metals
then they have all the fragrances and
chemicals they got all of that inside
their brain
and it's making them feel like they're
crazy when they're not it's making them
feel like they're losing their mind when
they're not they're struggling
physically it's not their fault they
didn't cause it they didn't create it
and then they get
triggered
easily but what happens
is Anna says over there on YouTube what
should you do if you have to work in
that
environment well that's what I love
about medical medium information okay go
to the library get a book get a book out
of the library get a medical medium book
okay all right medical medium doesn't
sell anything it's the books you can get
free in the library okay there's no
subscription fees on my website we can't
avoid every we can't avoid everything
we're going to have to live with it
we're going to have to live with
something some fragrance or something or
some colog something's going to happen
in our life something around us we're
going to have to be in work work
environment and that's when we do we
take care of ourselves we get the medals
out we get the chemicals out we learn
how to do it through the information
that s so has given us and we learn how
to get that out and we get our lives
back we take control of our lives so
that when we walk into an area that has
all of that we're strong we walk into an
area we don't get triggered
anymore we move forward and we heal
salt is overdone in Foods it's not that
I don't like salt to some degree I'm not
anti sodium look at the celery juice
I've been screaming celery juice over
and over and over and over again I'm not
anti salt can use a little bit here and
there you just don't want to rely on it
because it's overdone people pile it on
leafy greens have sodium content in it
all the herbs leafy green herbs cilantro
parsley right kale spinach especially
they all have sodium in them right
tomatoes got sodium in them lemons got
sodium in them right but I'm talking
about like restaurant food and packaged
Foods is so overs salted and we get so
used to that salt you've heard that you
get so used to it you're acclimating to
that salt and then what happens is
you're dumping so much salt in you don't
even realize how much Salt's going in
and it never stops because you're so
used to it every day and that builds up
and crystallizes a lot of people need
breakes from Salt so they can also do
some
healing all right the problem
is you're struggling
emotionally because you're struggling
physically your
soul is being challenged in a brain
that's being
challenged you're being challenged visic
in your brain you're being challenged
emotionally in your brain through your
soul cuz that's being challenged and
you're strong struggling you're
struggling and it becomes a vicious
cycle and a vicious circle is what it
becomes and it's hard to break out of it
and it just seems to just get tougher
and tougher and tougher and tougher and
the circle and the cycle doesn't get
broken easy it's back to suffering and
struggling you're feeling a little
better back to it again and no one
realizes we got to get the brain the
physical brain in a better place yes we
need to take care of our soul our spirit
our
what people call our spirit we need to
take care and take care of it we do and
we need to reach out for help and we
need people helping us and we need to
try to understand ourselves but we have
to not beat ourselves up I see it out
there all the time when people are
strugg struggling it's important to know
it's not your fault that your
brain has all this stuff I just talked
about in it and it's not your fault that
we're also up against so much here on
planet Earth where our soul gets knocked
out of us but when our soul is in our
brain and they're both living there and
our brain is struggling we end up
getting we end up getting like OCD more
and allergic more and hypers sensitive
more and we end up struggling more
because we don't understand why aren't
we better why aren't we
better yeah there's so much information
here check out brain saver you guys it's
just making the announcements one more
time real quick okay first things first
I released a new podcast episode micro
doing yep psychedelics so forth micro
doing medical Me podcast at Apple
podcast check it out link is in the
profile link is in the description
another
announcement I was on Nicole Lapin
podcast money rehab it's a great episode
link is in the profile link is in the bi
bio right in the description and then
third and last but not least go to my
telegram if you can if you've been
harmed if you've been harmed by the
false stories for four years now if
you've been harmed by the lies and the
false stories and everything else okay
check out telegram I'm putting out some
information out there that you actually
to whom it may concern it might be
really helpful for you to know because
I'm putting out the truth putting out
the facts and the evidence that's not
hidden
like they're doing check it out when you
get a chance if you're not into that
because you're fine everything's good
you still might want to check it out so
you know what's going on all right and
check out heal withth Amber when you get
a chance on IG heal withth Amber h a l w
t h Amber a m b r she's fighting for the
community all the time always has and
she cares greatly about the community
and the people here in the me community
and their struggles and what they go
through and she's she's working on
setting the record straight out there so
check her out to on IG if you can tell
other people about her um because she's
looking out for everybody anyway you
guys amazing want to give everybody a
rundown on the brain a little bit cover
some of this you know that I care and I
want you guys to Pat yourselves on the
back have compassion for yourself be
easy on yourself and know that you're
good
and it's not your fault if you're
struggling in any way you guys know I
love you much