i'm gonna be making uh bruce get the
toppings so tomatoes
tomatoes and cucumbers that's today
got some basil here got some red onion
that's what we're trying to make right
there
and got some lemons here too look at
these tomatoes huh
you guys are afraid of tomatoes i mean
so many of you are told tomatoes aren't
good
i'd like to talk about that a little bit
on how good for you they are
and how that's misinformation the word
misinformation
no one was using it when it came down to
foods and chronic illness
published it originally in here talked
about misinformation
out there in the medical field
misinformation and alternative medicine
conventional medicine misinformation
about all the trends out there and now
the word is
used against a medical medium
misinformation where's your scientific
study
well how about millions healed around
the world devastating illnesses
and healed how about that anyway medical
medium new edition check it out you guys
um cucumber noodles with bruschetta
topping that's what you
we're going to be making so
link is in the description for the book
it's coming out
it's really coming out soon actually so
hi everybody
michelle l good to see you kathy good to
see you christy good to see you
i'm glad everybody's coming on
so hey
yeah i can't wait for the new book to
come out too can't wait i'm excited you
guys we're youtube live and we're
facebook live
i'm going to start preparing food right
now
and i'm going to answer questions too so
i want to be helpful the best i can
what can you do to help with crohn's
disease when it comes down luanne when
it comes down to crohn's
um you got inflammation okay that's
inflammation inflammation is a mystery
to medical research in science they
don't know what causes it
so being that you know so anything they
label like crohn's
colitis ibs they they don't know what
causes it so that's one of the reasons
why it's so difficult to fix anything so
then everybody's playing guessing games
everybody's out there looking for
answers and they're like well how can i
fix this what can i do and then
and then they'll tell you hey it's your
genes they'll say luanne it's your genes
you just it's your bad genes that's why
you have
crohn's and then they'll come up with a
name like crohn's and
meanwhile they still don't know what the
inflammation is and then what happens is
you get the inflammation um and they get
narrowing of the intestinal tract
you can get it could bellow out you get
pockets you get narrowing and you just
get this chronic inflammatory condition
going on there
and so what i've always done teaching
doctors how to heal crohn's so they can
help their patients what i've always
done is
is the first things first is what foods
can be
trouble like what food can be causing a
problem with crohn's you know
and that's the first thing but the other
thing is
knowing the true cause of crohn's so
that's that's the other thing too so
it's knowing the true cause but
in order to know the true cause you know
that's one thing there you got to know
also like what to avoid
that's actually behind the true cause so
it's kind of like a combination right
and so when it comes down to crohn's
it's
what can we avoid the true cause
pathogens
toxic heavy metals do play a role okay
they do play a role toxic heavy metals
i'm peeling a cucumber right now because
i'm going to make some cucumber noodles
got this little tool right here and
you get a whole bunch of pathogens they
get inside the intestinal tract and they
start to weaken the lining
they start to inflame the lining you can
get streptococcus in there
e coli and they cause a lot of issues
they attach themselves to the lining of
the colon and you start getting little
pockets and little divots and that
happens to a lot of people
then the other thing is viruses too you
know a lot of
viruses create problems in the
intestinal tract lining
um so the combination of both of these
is really
is really contributing and then and then
you know um foods that aren't good that
keep on feeding these pathogens you know
like for instance i got something right
here
like this is not a good food right here
um
we're dealing with crohn's or colitis or
ibs or
digestive issues or intestinal tract
disorders
this is not a great food right here
these beautiful eggs right here aren't
they pretty right
and terrible food for any kind of
condition but i'll talk about those in a
little bit
um the thing is is the intestinal tract
gets so sensitive i hear those eggs
rolling around on the plate right now
tesla track gets so sensitive too
because the nerve endings start to get
sensitive
because you get in that inflammation so
all the nerve endings in the intestinal
tract are really get they really get
sensitive so when you're eating foods
you don't know what's helping or what's
not
and that's something that gets becomes
very difficult um
what i like to do with with crohn's is
um steamed potatoes are really gentle
really easy on the system but they're
also anti-pathogen
so um that's one food right there that i
like to i like to teach doctors to use
for their patients
papaya banana that's a big one right
there so papaya banana do i have any
bananas back here i don't have either or
i thought i
thought i had some bananas back there um
and and also there's protocols in the
medical meeting books you can take to
your doctor and all that
you know and have them have them look at
it right there you guys are making
cucumber noodles
but papayas bananas are really good for
crohn's
that one's very helpful soothing it
helps to
push past some of those narrowings so
that
people with crohn's can can go to
bathroom easy because that's a problem
you get lots of different constipation a
lot of pain
and all that stuff but what to avoid is
a critical thing
milk cheese butter eggs the very eggs i
was just showing you
definitely avoid those eggs and gluten
because all those will feed bugs so what
happens is
if you got the strep bacteria
and you're eating the eggs because now i
got a real egg here in front of me
and you know the strep bacteria is
sitting inside the intestinal tract and
it's
it's camped there there's colonies of it
and that that goes for people with a lot
of digestive tract disorders that aren't
even diagnosed
properly or not where it's mystery it's
like okay what's going on you got
cramping bloating all of that
and what happens is that bacteria just
loves to feed on eggs so we're eating
eggs thinking that's a great food and
then all of a sudden you know that's
that's that's the food it's eating
and then it proliferates two weeks later
conditions are worse but yet the egg
felt
so good it felt so good it went down it
was easy on the system
it didn't rub on any of the lining it
didn't trigger off any of the nerve
endings
the egg was just it was just so easy it
turned just into a glue that goes into
down the patch like a glue that just
sits in the center of the intestinal
tract and works its way down right
and it doesn't trigger any kind of like
pain or any kind of discomfort
so we think the eggs are probably a safe
bet but what the egg does is it keeps on
feeding all the bugs and the bugs create
more inflammation and then we get more
problems and then we're sensitive to
lettuce
meaning in the sense that because you
feel the lettuce going down and then
we're sensitive to other things and
there's a lot of confusion but
that's what happens there um
okay so i'm just get i'm just preparing
some cucumbers here i'm going to turn
them into
noodles in a little bit i'm going to
make the sauce with the brisket on top
of it
um bruschetta you can call it bruschetta
some people call it bruschetta
some people call it bruschetta some
people call it something different
um i'm going to cut these ends off right
here this cucumber
insulin resistance lori insulin
resistance
okay fat equals
insulin resistance right there okay fats
and i mean milk cheese butter eggs
chicken beef i'm not going in i'm not
going against animal protein
nut butters okay nut butters nut milks
all right avocado oils coconut oil
even healthy fats right all fats
lead to insulin resistance so it's about
how much fats in your diet like how much
fat is in your diet you know like are
you guys
like how much fats in your diet are you
guys doing like
a lot of fat in your diet because that
this is insulin resistance right here
i'm showing you insulin resistance
that's what this is okay so here's how
it works okay even somebody
that doesn't have real real high insulin
resistance like it's not off the chart
yet it's always there for everybody no
matter what
so you got all your fats right there you
got your burger and that's a beef burger
okay
that's not a vegan burger that's a beef
burger and
all that fat in there okay what that
does is it blocks
sugar from entering your cells so you
have to basically produce a lot of
insulin but the fat stops the insulin
from taking sugar into cells and then
you got the cheese
more fat right there and cheese has got
sugar in it too which makes it even
worse because you got fat and sugar
combined
right you got more sugar which is the
bun
okay and then you got fried potatoes
fried french fries right
see those fried french fries those are
fried in oil
so when they're fried in oil what do you
have you have insulin resistance because
you got
sugar and fat sugar and fat you see the
burger
the burger is sugar and fat that's what
the burger is
what's the best thing on this plate well
the potato
is one of the best things but the
potatoes been crucified it's been
annihilated i don't know it's been just
it's been
injured because and or sacrificed
whatever it is because it's been fried
in oil so the potatoes been hindered
right and but what's the best thing here
well these pickles well that's that's
vinegar so these pickles aren't that
great you see that because these pickles
are vinegar right
tomatoes the best thing the onion's the
best thing and the lettuce is best thing
in this whole setup right if the
potatoes weren't
fried in oil that would be
one of the best things too so anyway
watch i don't spill this off the this
thing doesn't pop off the plate
i don't want that popping off the plate
and then
um the plate was greasy there's so much
fat in that food
so much that that's from a restaurant
around the corner
there's so much fat in that food that
that like the grease
on the plate it just found its way on
the plate it's all over my hands and i
really don't want grease
on my bruschetta and cucumber noodles
all right let's get going let's talk
about insulin resistance okay how about
we do that
what happens is fat fills up in your
bloodstream
when you have that cheeseburger or the
peanut butter smoothie
because you're putting peanut butter in
your smoothie or peanut butter on your
oatmeal
oatmeal has enough fat in it by itself
naturally right
but that's okay that's all right that's
right but when you
add fat to your oatmeal like all that
peanut butter
you get yourself in trouble because the
sugar in that
oatmeal the sugar the carbohydrate and
that oatmeal can't find its way into
your cells
so your pancreas has to whoo has to
pedal to the metal man that pancreas has
to pedal to the metal
if your pancreas could talk it would say
it would say oh no
why did that person just put all that
fat with that sugar
that carbohydrate because now i'm going
to have to produce
way more insulin and burn my pancreas
out so by the time they're 40 years old
they got type 2 diabetes
by the time they're 45 they got type 2
diabetes
even type 1 diabetes whatever i mean and
so your pancreas just has to spill out
all of that insulin to try to get that
carbohydrate into cells
because guess what we run on sugar news
flash
not to you guys you guys know this stuff
by now because you've been watching
uh you know the medical medium books and
and podcasts and everything else right
but news flash to anybody else all right
your body has to run on sugar you can't
function you can't do nothing i can't do
this
without sugar that's it sugar takes care
of it
and if you don't have sugar which is
hence your blood sugar which
is glucose which runs at your brain it
runs your thoughts
people say you know what he talks so
fast you know
i got friends that say you know what why
don't you talk slower on all your videos
and all your
podcasts and i'm like i have to force
myself to talk slow
i have to force myself and and they're
like well he must be jacked up on tons
of caffeine
no i'm not that's sugar that's glucose
that's natural carbohydrate in a potato
that's sugar from a lemon that's sugar
from a tomato
that's where it comes from but guess
what that sugar is not blocked by fat
so yeah i could have a little avocado i
love avocado
yeah i could have a little bit of tahini
i love tahini
sure you can have that i love hemp seeds
hemp seeds
amazing food but you know i'm cautious
i'm not gonna sit there and and and do
it all day long
i'm not gonna be doing hemp seeds on and
off and then throw some nut butters in
there and then have chicken at night and
then
and then to do a guacamole and then what
happens is you just do too much fat
too much fat too much for that too much
fat and it stops the sugar
from going into your cells because
insulin has to be produced and then the
fat blocks it now you got insulin
resistance
tomatoes really good that's going to
make a great
bruschetta so let's do one more cucumber
here
type 2 diabetes is such an easy fix it's
ridiculous
easiest fix there is so easy
um science and research never knew
still doesn't know how to get rid of
type 2 diabetes so you got all that
money
millions and millions of dollars going
into the medical industry
billions of dollars big pharma and all
all their
paid for studies and they still can't
fix type 2 diabetes
it's such an easy fix it's such an easy
fix
get your liver better lower your fats
get your liver stronger okay
you learn how to eat right okay then you
can heal
that insulin resistance your pancreas
builds up and boom you're out of it you
don't even need insulin anymore
um so
wait let me just get this one going here
because i want to still talk about that
so what happens is when someone stops
sugar okay so check this out you guys
all right
when someone stops sugar okay
and they start to improve
they're only improving because they're
taking
the critical piece away that you need to
get into yourselves but they only
improve
because they took one
of the very things out see it's it's fat
and sugar
combined that causes insulin resistance
but it's fat
that's the troublemaker and that's the
big causer right
but when you remove sugar then you have
all this fat floating around in your
bloodstream
and less insulin is produced because
there's not enough sugar floating around
in your bloodstream
so less insulin is produced so there's
just it's just like okay but that's not
the fix that's not
how to fix it that's not how it works
because guess what your diabetes is
still there and it's not going away
it's never going away because then all
of a sudden you're gonna eat some sugar
wow i've been on this diet for a long
time i'm keeping all my carbohydrates
away
my doctor says my a1c is getting better
it's dropping
but yet i'm just dying for a
carbohydrate i'm dying for a little bit
of sugar
let me eat this candy oh my god my a1c
oh my god my sugar's off the chart
oh my god something's wrong and and what
happens is my type 2 diabetes is back in
full force
i had an orange i had a piece of bread
but what the reality is the truth is if
you take out the fats
you can eat a piece of bread you can eat
an orange you can eat a piece of candy
and guess what you're not going to have
any insulin resistance you're not going
to have any type 2
diabetes it's not even going to be there
that's how it works anyway
lucas thanks for the tip with the high
uh quality spirulina
it made almost all the difference to me
lucas
supplements being the highest quality
or the best for a whole bunch of
different reasons is critical for
healing i've been saying this for years
years ago years ago
there was crap out for supplements crap
right
so it was really hard to get people
better even if spirit of compassion said
this person needs nettle leaf to get a
nettle leaf
product to do its job to take somebody
to the
finish line was hard right same thing
spirit of compassion said this person
needs spirulina to get toxic heavy
metals out right like you're talking
about lucas the spirulina
then it's got to be the right kind and
that's always been the problem out there
you know always
and this is the kind i use you guys know
that the vimorgy
uh v as in victor i am as in mary ergy
dot com spin rg but and i'm not
sponsored but it's
it means everything the higher quality
means everything to getting better
and i that's been the fight all these
years it's been like okay
i can work with foods with people right
but
if they have these these epstein bars
these shingles these the streptococcus
they have these toxic heavy metals
i need more than just just the foods you
know
spirit of compassion told me for years
you need more than that it's like you
have to have the best
quality of of supplementation
and so the vimraj is the best quality
and they have a whole line of stuff
that's incredible i got me and i got it
here
because it's what i take it's a
magnesium i take it's vitamin c i take
the micro state
but anyway it does make a difference
lucas and i'm glad you found that out
rita says i just got out of my third
diabetes
med that i can't afford i want to learn
how to eat
what book can i read
it's a diabetes section in this book
right here
um this is coming out you could look you
can get it right now at amazon.com
um you can go to the library too the
link is in the description
go to the library after the book comes
out and maybe a library will stock it in
time so you can actually
um get a copy for free if you need to
because a lot of people are hurting for
money right now so
i always want people to be able to get
free books um
so that and then cleanse the heal
i talk about diabetes in in here too so
cleansing heal
it's on sale at amazon.com 16.99 it's on
there
and uh so and that's packed with
information which is incredible and i
talk about
i talk about how it works diabetes how
to heal all that
type 2 diabetes i mean more people have
healed of medical medium information
with diabetes than any anywhere on the
planet
it's a beautiful thing it's just it's so
incredible
so anyway i want to talk about i'm going
to get these noodles going so i'm going
to start shaving these noodles down you
guys
i'm going to move the basil over so let
me do that and um
so what i do i have this little
julienner so i'm making some noodles
right here
so
radical fats are are fats that are
see all foods have fats in them all
foods all right
and keep that in mind this cucumber
right here this english cucumber i'm
actually julianne
right it has fat in it every single
thing has fat in it those tomatoes have
fat in it
that basil has fat in it that onion has
fat in it garlic has fat in
so so keep that in mind that's important
to know right and then
there's there's foods that have more fat
they're made of fat mostly and i call
those radical fats
and there's a lot of healthy ones tahini
sesame seeds sunflower seeds right
hemp seeds these are healthy fats
coconut
right coconut oil these are healthy fats
olive oil
yeah healthy fat right so it's not like
i don't know that people
people pretend i don't know that or
something it's actually really funny
he doesn't know he doesn't know about
fats he's against bats he doesn't know
about what everybody's talking about in
the trendy health world about healthy
fats
he's not aware of that oh really because
i got everybody eating avocado
because guess what it was considered to
be poisonous 35 years ago
the health scene was against avocado
you were you were laughed off a lecture
stage
if you said an avocado was healthy fat
did you know that
you were laughed off of a health lecture
stage
and um and so i got avocado really
really out there i mean i spent years
teaching doctors teaching people
teaching everybody about that and so
um and it's a it's a better fat because
all those years ago i was trying to get
people off of the bad fats
i was trying to get people off of this
so i spent a lifetime trying to get
people off of that right there
okay to onto avocado years ago
but here's the thing when you're
chronically ill
when that plate's greasy the plate's
really greasy
when you're chronically ill okay
you need you need a step above that you
need a step
further than just the avocado the
healthy nuts and seeds the almonds the
almond butter right the peanuts the
peanut butter
the hemp seeds the coconut oil you need
to step further than that
if you're really sick you're really
struggling you're really viral lupus
multiple sclerosis um you know chronic
fatigue syndrome me chronic fatigue
syndrome different
trigeminal neurology whatever it is
right there's there's hundreds of
conditions
and you need more more than just
it's not just good enough to be like i'm
going to go keto and still have some
avocado
i'm going to be plant-based keto and
still have my nuts and seeds every day
and my cacao
it's not enough if you want to go to the
finish line
and i've always taught that for 35 plus
years it takes more than that
it takes it takes much more than that
you know and and that's really important
to know
it really is
so
erica what about type one
um when it comes down to type one type
one is
is a is a pancreas injury science
research doesn't know that but
food poisoning um creates a lot of
situations where people go
they become type one they have that
condition because of food poisoning
you could have food poisoning and be
type one a week later
you get out food poisoning and be type
one a year later two years later from
food poisoning right
right and also pathogens you know
viruses get into the pancreas and they
create type 1
and and even with
delayed type 1 where it's like a slow
progression of type one
um late in type one so even with that so
um
and and look there's there's a there's
you always have to keep it in your heart
and soul that there's always hope to
heal
it's just about doing doing enough of
the right things to get there
and that's what it is um i would take i
would take
uh i would take the medical medium books
to
to your doctor healer or whoever is in
charge of your health care and
and read the diabetes section take a
look i offer a lot of things
for type one and type do and you can see
what's right for you with your doctor so
you've got
you've got that forward movement the
most important thing with type one
the most important thing is to
make sure it's not getting worse
okay even improving you can improve type
one you can take
type one a lot get it a lot better and a
lot better and a lot better
and not only that it's also about making
sure type 1 doesn't get worse worse
worse worse
so it's doing the right things to keep
type 1 stable
so your pancreas doesn't get a further
injury so it doesn't um
doesn't become more problematic more
inflamed and
that's the key it's about hey i want my
type 1 to be here for the rest of my
life
and not all of a sudden worse and that's
the key or i want my type 1 not only
here but i want my type 1 a lot better
than what it is and that's the key
too and ask your doctor if you can do 32
ounces of celery juice
ask your doctor if you can do that ask
your doctor
if you can do any of the protocols
medical media protocols
but anyway
so
i'm getting these cucumber noodles over
here
getting them in the bowl so right now
this is what we're doing
so there's my cucumber noodles
still some more work to do still making
some more noodles here you guys
marianna there are people on natural
health group in natural health groups
spreading rumors about you anthony
a friend told me this always oh my god
of course
there always is a lot of hate groups i
think right
um you know there's there's always that
happening
i think i'm an easy target because of
discrimination
and there's a ton of lies and
i mean that's just how it's always been
what happens is
you know you get discriminated against
when you hear a voice
spirit of compassion since age four and
you get discriminated
against when you get too many people
better because a lot of people get
jealous in the health field in the
health industry
they get jealous they're like why does
he have millions and millions of people
following his information you know they
just can't wrap their heads around it a
lot of people they're either jealous or
they're just
psycho about it or something i mean it's
really weird i think
what happens is like why is he the
number one health author
in the world for seven years running why
i mean and just so you know um
the medical medium book series okay is
the number one health series in the
world
right so keep that in mind because it
works not because of promotion or money
or marketing because i didn't use any pr
marketing so
there's a lot of lies i'll give you a
whole rundown of just a few of them
right now
a number one lie he must have serious
money behind his
marketing and pr firms and how else did
he get to where he is
and 100 inaccurate all right
no pr firms no publicists
uh no money into pr and all that okay so
that's number one that's a lie that's
been out there
a simple lie is everybody thought i was
27 years old for the longest time
so every time i said i've been in this
for 30 years everybody would go bananas
and berserk
and they'd be like that's impossible
okay obviously you know
i'm much much older than that and that's
just one all on its own okay
other lies too there's lots of them i
mean it's just the list goes on and on
and on but
but i think what happens is for because
i've talked to
a couple of my friends about this
doctors and stuff they're like look
500 million people in the world know who
you are and
medical medium information has spread
beyond
and around the world because it's the
number one health selling
series and health books there are on the
planet and that's going to lead to
a lot of discrimination especially where
your source is coming from above
since age four so there's gonna be lots
of all that it's just just tons of that
stuff
um
i mean
but you gotta be careful you know with
that and just you know
there's so many lies it's just it's over
it's it's over the chart i mean it's
it's off the chart there's so many so
many lies
so i got my noodles going here i'm gonna
peel one more cucumber
just mixing these you know this likes
it's like spaghetti
i love this i got one more to go let's
do one more
i cut these ends off a little bit here
let me see
so yeah so i'm making the bruschetta and
the cucumber noodles right here so i'm
just peeling this cucumber i'm trying to
pay attention to this so i don't cut my
hand
um marcellus says he is 40
question mark much older
i wish i was 40. that would be so
amazing
wow that would be incredible
that would be incredible it's way older
than that
um but anyway so you know the whole
thing is so what you'll find in a lot of
groups there's a lot of hate groups and
stuff
a lot of rumors were made up and spread
and then of course people try to cancel
me constantly so i'm always trying to be
can't like
always just trying to like cancel
movement cancel culture and cancel
movement against me
that comes up all the time um
you know what happens i just laugh at
all of it i like laughing all the
the stories and the fake stories and the
lies and stuff like that
did you know two women um came to me
back last spring about a year ago and
told me
that an organization was paying
was paying people to spread rumors and
lies
and so both these women were enter
what they were they were approached and
offered money but what they did instead
of taking the money like so many do in
the hate groups
and stuff instead of taking the money
these two women
contacted medical media and
let us know okay let us know
about this thing that was happening
where they were offering money
to write stories claim things
to try to take down the mm so that
everybody stops healing around the world
i'll tell you right now and it was the
people you least
expected that were actually spreading
the lies and stories people that you
would never think that seemed so sincere
and so
oh yeah you know medical medium and
i'm just living my life and you know
with my cute little family and whatever
it is and just spreading the word you
know spreading bad rumors and lies or
people you would never even believe
so it's it's crazy how it works
and they approached a lot of people they
approached it's it's really
it was so sinister and they could still
be doing it
you're not surprised michelle
good good to see you loon
moon you care i don't care all right i'm
gonna start chopping up some tomatoes
right here
but what i'm gonna do is i'm gonna mix
up
katrina says i saw you at upw thank you
for staying strong and not stopping
amazing so glad you're here incredible
i'm honored you're here
i really am i'm gonna chop up some
tomatoes here you guys let me take a
look here
get a bowl going
but what happens with medical medium
information when you apply it right and
you want to lose weight you can lose
weight you get your liver healthy
you lose all this unwanted weight and if
you're
underweight medical medium information
can bring healthy weight back
on when it's done correctly and people
are using it correctly
i'm chopping up some tomatoes right now
i'm gonna read some more comments and
help out the best i can
so um
because i'm gonna get a couple more
things
this is
because
see guys um if you just got on here
making the bruschetta
just some tomatoes got some noodles
right here
got it you know what happens with these
little tomatoes if you're chopping them
you can put them in a food processor and
give it a pulse
you can do that dr font
good to see you on here great md
patricia marie good to see you
and you can you know one of the things
is you could put i wouldn't put these in
a blender
i wouldn't do that i wouldn't put
i wouldn't put um these cherry tomatoes
in a blender
because if you put them in a blender
they're just going to turn into a soup
and you don't want this soup you want
this kind of choppy
and cut in pieces okay that's how you
want it
that's the best way of doing it and
if you do i have a garden yeah i love to
grow stuff
it's not a big garden or anything but i
love to grow stuff whenever i can grow
tomatoes
grow cucumbers love to do it
but yeah you want to
so i'm gonna answer more questions for
you guys
ashley kevin
good to see you
love your videos
these tomatoes are a little extra ripe
which makes them um which makes them
even really nice
they're not over ripe because you know
over ripe tomatoes are the worst you
don't want overripe tomatoes you want to
overripe anything
where it's like it's going bad but um
these tomatoes here are actually
anne says what juicer do i use for
celery juice
i use the mm-900
hds so it's by omega
megajuicers.com omega that's the one i
use
it's an incredible juicer it's my
favorite one um
and uh company's great
i love the juicer it really squeak it
it just saves you so much money and
that's the whole point
um you can cut these in four but these
are so extra ripe i'm cutting them in
twos
because they're so they're so ripe which
is gonna make them really good it's
going to make the sauce really good
because what happens is with tomatoes
you might get some cherry tomatoes that
aren't really fully ripe and
you buy them and they're really hard
then you cut them in fours
and that's what you do i'm cutting these
in twos right now so if you guys
you guys want to know because these are
really nice and soft
but they're juicy as heck which is going
to be really good
why do tomato skins not digest
i see that question don't digest no they
they digest
they do they do your body will it's
tomato skins are fibrous fiber doesn't
digest
but any nutrients around and in the
fiber
digests you just don't know that so when
it comes out the other end and you're
like wait a minute why didn't that
tomato skin digest
how come i see that tomato skin in the
bathroom
right how come i see that tomato skin in
the toilet it's like
well first of all everything that needed
to be extracted from that tomato skin
has been extracted
the rest of that tomato skin which you
can't tell
is actually the the the useless part
well it's just
fiber like i said you always get plenty
of fiber in all your foods
much light in love says love you mmm can
you talk about ocd
yeah definitely run that by you a little
bit so
with ocd okay it's all about metals
but it's all about metal deposits being
rather
larger that's the other thing on top of
neurons so it's metal deposits being
rather larger on top of neurons and
they'll sit inside neurons and that's
and i'll
show you what happens is that um
see these little metal deposits right
here i have on the side of the brain so
these shiny little aluminum pieces here
right
the deposits aren't that big big this is
just a demonstration model right
and so what happens is as aluminum
collects and mercury collects
on top of neurons it's kind of magnetic
the more
aluminum you get in your body the more
aluminum goes to the brain to the very
spots that have the aluminum to begin
with same thing with mercury the more
mercury you have in
deposits on the neurons the more mercury
like if you're eating tuna fish
if you're doing um maybe some
pharmaceuticals have mercury in it
whatever it is you get more mercury
added to
the neurons to those little deposits
right and then it depends on where the
deposits are sitting that creates the
ocd
so deposits are sitting in the emotional
center of the brain
in those neurons that can be really
intense that ocd could be much more
intense versus sitting say somewhere in
the left hemisphere right hemisphere
somewhere else off the cuff somewhere uh
you know
somewhere in the distance depending on
where in the tissue
in the glial cells and so forth but what
happens is
you have an electrical impulse and that
electricity is running so it's running
through the brain right
so you got that all that electricity is
running through that brain
when you think your thoughts okay so
what happens is that's electricity and
guess what that's metal
electricity metal what happens when
electricity meets metal
okay think about that okay when
electricity hits
metal you don't want to during a
lightning storm you don't want to go out
there with like a golf club or something
and stick it up in the air
or you don't want to go out there with
even an umbrella you don't want to go
out there with anything
you don't want you don't want to be out
there with an antenna when there's a
lightning storm
you don't want electricity being drawn
to metal
so what ocd is is electrical impulses
traveling through neurons and it hits a
pocket of metal
and when it hits pressing print said
your kitchen is so inviting i'm honored
hey glad to have you here
um so when that me when that electricity
hits the metal
it then goes back up the neuron the
other direction
while another but while another
electrical impulse
is coming down that same neuron they hit
each other so what happens is
your electrical impulse is hitting the
deposits of metal it's hitting the
aluminum it's hitting the mercury it's
hitting the copper
mostly aluminum and mercury it comes
down to ocd
and then it hits it and then bounces
back
another another electrical impulse is
coming down the same channel
and it's hitting it too it's hitting the
electrical impulse trying to go back up
it's exploding you just got this repeat
we constant repeat it's these electrical
impulses hitting the metal and bouncing
back up hitting the metal
and that's when the obsessive thoughts
come in it's like oh my god
i can't break these thoughts i can't
fall asleep my mind is racing it won't
stop
all this obsessive thoughts just and
then those obsessive thoughts can
actually lead to
taking action you know what i mean like
it makes you jump out of bed you get up
upset you get frustrated now you're
pacing
now you're on a phone with a friend now
you're on the phone with a family member
and you're telling them your obsessive
thoughts and you can't break it
and it gets really difficult and it's
hard to break that
whole frequency um and
it's like it's like i mean i've seen so
many different cases of ocd
and really bad ones terrible ones for so
many years
and one of the worst ones i've seen i've
seen a lot of bad ones over the last 35
years helping people
is this woman who she needed to check
her body to make sure her head was on
her body it was an obsessive thought she
was perfectly sane
she's a great person and um but she had
she's been
she was at the time she went to like 20
psychiatrists
hundred doctors and it was in and she
was
really tortured by it and what happened
was she would have to run into him she'd
have to keep a mirror with her 24
7. she'd have to go somewhere with a
mirror she'd have to go in her car with
the mirror
she'd have to see the mirror because she
had to make sure her head was attached
to her body
and it became an obsessive thought she
knew her head was attached to her body
she knew of course she did she totally
knew perfectly sane
totally new and but that's not how it
works with ocd
you can know your door is locked you can
know you
check the stove i know those are the the
basic versions of it
but you you can know your you check the
stove and drive away
and still have to come back and check it
one more time
and i've seen people couldn't even leave
their house they have to
walk back into the house a hundred times
to check their stove because they're
scared to death it's on right
but that's just those versions this is
another type it's like she had to have a
mirror with her all the time a compact
she had a
everywhere she went she had a mirror and
and then there's people who go through
they go through uh
ocd where they just think something bad
is gonna happen to a loved one something
bad is gonna happen to a friend
something bad is going to happen to
somebody else
something bad is going to happen to them
and they can't shake it and they can't
shake it becomes obsessive it devours
them
right there's so many versions of ocd
that i've had to help people with and
everything and it's it's all about what
kind of metal how much metal where it is
in the brain
how the electrical impulses are hitting
it are they traveling around it are they
hitting it direct are they
bouncing off the other electro
electrical impulses
and that's what ocd is so it's all about
getting the metals out and that's
that's why i've always said you know
it's about the barley grass juice powder
the spirulina
you know the vimergy spirulina of
emergency barley grass juice powder it's
the one i use
it's all about that plus the wild
blueberries and dulce the heavy metal
detox smoothie
about getting those metals out so that
you're free from that
and that's important all right just
going to cut up a few more tomatoes here
this is such a great dish and it's so
easy
to make i'm just taking my time i mean
honestly
could put these in a food processor and
pulse it but i like chopping them
so i see a question by karen i want to
gain weight as well potatoes don't make
me gain
because there's no fat on them are you
eating enough of them
if you want like if you want to gain
weight
um i mean i have athletes
on potatoes they're they don't do any
fats and they're
they're stoking with muscles all of that
are you are you using your muscles
so you can gain weight by building a
little bit of muscle
intraskeletal muscles muscles all around
your body you can gain five pounds of
weight
um using those muscles are you doing
resistance training are you taking walks
are you swimming are you riding a
bicycle
are you keeping your muscles tone are
you building a little muscle
that will put on a little weight just
that alone and potatoes build muscle
so also are you eating enough
uh potatoes are you hungry not hungry
are you only eating one potato two
potato three potato four
like what are you doing and that's one
thing too these are i'm trying to help
you be your own detective
okay are you doing more bananas bring in
some more bananas bring in some more
dates get some more calories and you
might be low calorie
to what you're doing you might be an
active person a really active person
but your calories are low but your
calories are low
you're not eating enough just not a lot
of calories in a potato right
not and it's not like it's not a
chocolate cake
um you know unless it's those french
fries i showed you earlier it's just
french fries you know that's a different
story all that oil right
but plus what happens is when you get
healthy and you start to clean
house and you start you start to clean
up those fats and you start to clean up
the processed foods and
you're doing the low fat what happens is
you're losing all toxic swelling you're
not swelling anymore
a lot of the guys and and women too that
i see out there that even fitness and
everything you can see where they're
swelling
where they're swollen there's a lot of
dudes out there that are you know that
are
stoking some muscles but they're also
they're also got a layer
a layer of fat and swelling a layer of
water
over their muscles so it makes them even
look bigger they got a layer
they got that bulk and it's a lot of
swelling and when that swell lets the
liver not
working good you know when you get rid
of that swelling and you just have the
muscle by itself boom you just lost 15
pounds it's like what happened but
meanwhile you're all muscle
but but but as far as going on i'm just
giving you different examples out there
in case anybody's going through any of
that i'm trying to help everybody
but keep in mind that are you doing
enough calories are you doing enough
potato you might be an active person
and another thing too are you doing
anything to use your muscles to build
some muscle right
um that's that's a whole thing on its
own too so you're using enough muscle to
build your muscle
um little muscles count you can get five
pounds all in its own right there
i know when i work too hard work too
hard work too hard and i can't even ride
my bicycle
and i can't even ride my bike i can't
even take walks because i'm doing 18
hours a day
non-stop and i have to sleep i can't i
can't be
out there doing self-care i can't be out
there riding bicycle i can't take a run
i know that if i'm not running for a
while and i'm not biking for a while and
i'm just working and it goes on for
months and and i know that i'll lose a
few pounds
of of you know lose it like a couple of
pounds and be like hey i think that
couple and then you got hop back on the
bicycle and you do bite the bike
three times a week and all of a sudden
all that muscle comes back and boom
you're all of a sudden five pounds
heavier
you're also five pounds of muscle seven
pounds of muscle and then you go and you
know you do
you do some runs and your leg muscles
are building up but i'm not saying you
gotta run i'm just saying are you active
are you using muscles
are you doing 10 bananas a day you can
do 10 bananas
10 bananas is pretty easy to eat for a
lot of people
you can knock down a few bananas um
are you doing smoothies you can put them
in smoothies you can do banana blueberry
smoothies and do like three of them a
day
do some more potatoes at night you can
do that and actually you know
and actually clean that all up all right
so
and actually get your weight to where
you want to go
um and um
and and also you know it's a personal
preference to where someone wants to be
too
someone might look at you and be like
hey you look really amazing
and you know another person might be
like you need to put on weight it's like
it's really it's it's it's kind of crazy
how things work too on that level
so i'm gonna get some i'm gonna do some
uh tomato here i mean some
some onion i'm gonna chop up some onion
got some red onion it's gonna go in this
tomato bruschetta
so denise says i really need to lose
weight what is your recommendation
first thing i would do is um
checking to make sure i don't have a bad
onion here the first thing i would do
is is get the liver in a better place
and that's about lowering fats what's
your diet like how many fats are you
eating
are you eating too much oils are you
are you eating too much too much avocado
too much oil too much chicken too much
beef too much
you know too much of all that kind of
fat is is that what is that going on
or are you doing something different
guys i'm going to grab another onion
that onion was a little tricky i'll be
right there
so
so i would try to get the liver
healthier take the fats away for a
little while
how about do the medical meeting morning
cleanse have you done the medical medium
morning cleanse
do some lemon water first thing in the
morning flush out that liver
then move on to celery juice a half an
hour later got a nice onion right here
you guys
and take out the radical fats
no fats at least till noon at least
until noon
no nut butters no oils no olives not
that people eat a lot of olives they
don't but they do a lot of olive oil
that's what i would do there is i would
i would at least have the fats out
until noon right i would keep it fats
once a day if you're somebody used to
eating fats like chicken
beef uh fish avocados nuts and seeds
pick the one you want
and make that the only one if it's beef
then you have beef for dinner right if
it's chicken have chicken for dinner if
it's nuts and seeds or nut butters
have it later on in the afternoon or
dinner um if it's avocado have your
guacamole at night for dinner start with
that now
if that doesn't cut it your liver is
definitely stagnant and sluggish
so then i would go days without fats i
would go
just complete days with no radical fats
on any level
take radical fats away i would do maybe
the 369 advanced cleanse
369 advanced cleanse or 369 original
cleanse
and i would repeat it pick the one you
want to do the but you can take it as
far as you want to go there's no reason
why you can't lose weight
everybody and anybody can lose unwanted
weight with the medical medium
information if they actually apply it
i wouldn't do these you're not you're
not going to lose weight easy with these
unless
you've already been eating really bad
processed foods really bad greasy fried
foods or just
chunk of cake or whatever you're eating
and then you go keto and you get rid of
all your processed foods and you're
doing eggs you're like hey
i'm losing weight losing weight but when
you when your liver is too stagnant and
sluggish
you can't get away with just even the
simple keto diet to lose weight it's
like you're doing i know a lot of people
did keto diets and they gained more
weight gained more
weight than back in the gym then they
had to go literally like
like like no calories and just eat a few
eggs a day and it's just
intermittent fast all day long just to
try to lose weight but it always comes
back later the minute you start eating
so i'm going to chop up some onion
which guys what i'm doing is i'm trying
to make this right here
a little chopped onion in there got the
tomato on the
cucumber noodles
almost broke my eggs
if you got any kind of reproductive
system condition endometriosis
fibroids pcos pid even
utis which is you know another situation
all just stay away from eggs
whatever you do stay away from eggs
my eyes are tearing right now from the
onion
let's do a little bit of basil i lost 20
pounds doing the advanced 369 cleanse
elaine i am beyond proud of you i'm
blown away
janice i lost 18 pounds in six weeks on
a 369 advanced
cleanse incredible my god these onions
are
killing my eyes right now i'm crying
ichoda says
that was me i gained weight doing keto
yep
i believe that i really believe that um
my god my eyes are running from that red
onion
that one got me you guys
gotta give me one minute i'm crying
oh my god
[Music]
getting some basil on here chopped up
nice and fine i just got the garlic next
[Music]
i lost 18 pounds doing two rounds in the
original 369 lisa incredible
emma said oh my god you have eggs eggs
over there
all right let's let's finish this up as
far as this recipe
so chopped garlic i got a mincer right
here
i was gonna mince it you can do chopped
or mince
and i love using the mincer too
now two cloves of garlic might be too
much for you
um one clove might be too much for
someone do a half a clove do a quarter
of a clove
maybe you're someone that loves garlic
you can do three cloves if you really
want
eva says dear anthony thank you so much
for your work all my family is healing
because of you
how can i get rid of lipomas sending
lots of love
thank you for my family
lipomas lipomas have a little
tentacle on them so they have a little
um lipomas actually have a little
those onions are really powerful that
onion i brought in here
god that's a really good one
the power those onions have for actually
killing pathogens
it's a powerful herb really is
i'm going to put a little bit of garlic
in here lipomas have a little
um blood vessel
that comes off of it that blood vessel
that blood vessel is its feeding
tube so that blood vessel coming off of
its feeding tube so say this is a lipoma
say this egg is a lipoma right and it's
inside of you
people get lipomas in their arms they
get lipomas in their chest
they get them in their stomach they get
them everywhere i mean they get them in
their legs
they get them on the back of their head
i mean they just get lipomas everywhere
and then there's this little tentacle
that hangs off of light lipoma
and it looks like this okay
so you got a lipoma in you and it's got
a little tentacle
coming off of it right and the tentacle
is a blood vessel
okay angiogenesis right a little blood
vessel
and all of a sudden
you eat a food it really likes like an
egg now that's a lipoma i'm pretending
it's a lipoma okay not an egg all of a
sudden you eat an egg
and that egg material finds its way
through the bloodstream stream all the
hormones in the egg
whether it's organic or not or free
range they find their way in the
bloodstream and the proteins and eggs
find their way and they go up they get
drawn up into that tentacle
and they go right into the lipoma and
the lipoma goes whoa we just
cash we just cashed in some good food we
just got some good food
and that's what they do so then over
time
over time the lipoma grows becomes
bigger and then you can get multiple
but all of a sudden boom you got two
lipomas
next to each other and one is growing
another tentacle off the other one
the other lipomas actually attached the
other one with a blood vessel
now you got two and they're all nice and
happy and they're waiting for gluten
they're waiting for eggs
milk cheese butter they're waiting for
toxic heavy metals
they're waiting for anything
some eggs over there okay let's go with
some lemon
um ask your doctor if you're okay with
higher melatonin higher
higher dosage of melatonin um let me
grab one i think i don't have it right
here actually
all right well i usually have the
vimergy melatonin in my cabinet but i
don't right now
i must have finished it up because it's
it's such a great
great sup incredible quality but anyway
melatonin
ask your doctor if he's okay or she's
okay if you start doing melatonin
or melatonin at a high dosage like ask
your doctor if 20 milligrams of
melatonin
is right for you because or 10
milligrams or
5 milligrams or more and what melatonin
does
is it inhibits lipomas from growing
so it's phytochemical compounds in
melatonin that end up going into the
lipoma
right they go into the lipoma and then
the lipoma can't grow
it doesn't have the ability to grow so
it stays the size because that's the key
i've always told people with lipomas
you want them to stay the size they are
or shrink
and you can you can get lipomas down if
you really keep that diet clean and
you're doing the right
supps and you get metals out of your
lipoma because what happens is when your
lipoma
when your lipomas starts to absorb
things like spirulina
barley grass juice powder the wild
blueberries when it starts to absorb the
heavy metal detox smoothie
and it goes into the lipoma then that
heavy metal detox movie starts to grab
onto metals in that lipoma
and draws them out and so your lipoma
doesn't have metals in it anymore
because metals help life homeless to
grow too what is the 369 cleanse
medical medium cleanse the heal
amazon.com
16.99 it's on sale you can check it out
there's the 369 cleanse in here
369 advanced original
it's a medical medium healing tool
that's at 369
cleanse is so i'm going to do a little
bit of lemon
and teaspoon of raw honey do a little
bit of raw honey here
and i'm going to mix this a little bit
of raw honey
like that and i'm going to do
i'm gonna squeeze some lemon in this
squeeze a little lemon
fat doesn't make you fat it does brianna
it does when your liver says i had
enough
fat will make you fat
that's what happens that's why people
who go keto gain weight
later because their liver had enough i'm
not saying keto is the worst thing to do
it's actually a good
it's a good starting point for a lot of
people because it gets you off processed
food i'm not
ripping into it like it's bad or
something
you can be plant-based in keto okay you
can be plant-based in keto you can be
animal protein in keto and it gets you
at least off of processed foods and
gluten and all that and you can start
even losing some weight for a lot of
people
but it but there's a lot of people that
can't so what happens is that
fat made me fat and kept me fat alison
says yeah
fat makes you fat radical fats make you
fat
it just depends are you young if you're
really young and your liver isn't
toasted yet then you know if you're
burnt out yet you're not going to get
fat eating fat yet but you're gonna get
fat
eating fat eventually no matter what it
gets everybody okay
so if you're 21 years old you're 22
years old and fat hasn't made you fat
yet it's going to make you fat when
you're 45 years old
and doesn't rely doesn't your doesn't
your life matter doesn't your life count
it's going to make you fat when you're
52 years old
it's gonna make you fat when you're 60
years old it's gonna make you fat
someday and it's gonna
somewhere along the line you're gonna
get fat from fat
the question is that everybody always
says which i just saw the question here
doesn't your fat
doesn't your brain need fat um that's
interesting because your brain's not
made out of fat
your brain is made out of glycogen and
the more fat you eat and the less
carbohydrate you eat
and the less fruits and the less and the
less um
potatoes and and sweet potatoes and
winter squash
and the less of those things you eat um
your your brain starts to starve starve
with glycogen
and then your brain shrinks everybody's
brain shrinks
everybody i was talking to a
neurosurgeon last month about this
he says he says he's seen it his whole
life as a neurosurgeon everybody's
brain everybody's brain shrinks
he was asking me why
he was asking me why does everybody's
brain shrink
i said because it's a glucose glycogen
deprivation for too many years and you
get older and your brain starts to
atrophy it's called brain atrophy
and just so you know your brain is not
made out of fat it's made out of sugar
it's made out of storage glycogen which
is sugar okay
that's what your brain's made out of is
there fat in your brain yeah but there's
traces of fat
throughout your entire body everywhere
in your body there's there's a trace of
fat in every part of your body omega-3
and squalene and all that
it's everywhere in the body right but
um then there's traces of fat in every
single food and these cucumber noodles
right here and that basil sitting in
front of me and these tomatoes right
and i'm not against healthy fats if you
want healthy fats but the point is is
your brain
doesn't need fat it needs sugar you run
on sugar your brain
thinks with sugar glucose is how this
runs
it's glucose take your sugar okay
this is funny okay when you go to the
doctor for a checkup
are they checking your blood fat
no they're not if that was so important
i'm scratching my head here
if that was so important wouldn't they
be checking your blood fat
they don't care about that they just
care about your blood sugar
because guess what happens without blood
sugar guess what happens without glucose
to your cells you die
yeah we we as a human race human species
sugar's so critical your brain won't run
it won't even
it won't run it won't even work without
sugar
does your brain need fat no it needs
sugar or you're dead
if your brain doesn't get sugar your
brain can't exist anymore
if your brain doesn't get fat it exists
you can live without radical fat
overt fat whatever you want to call it
you can live without fats your whole
life
because there's fats in everything you
eat anyway and your brain doesn't rely
on fat
you can't live without sugar
in some form shape or some way even if
you eat red meat there's sugar in the
blood of the meat
and it's caramelized when you cook it
it's in there blood sugar animals blood
sugar animals blood inside the meat is
blood sugar
and no matter what your brain has to
have sugar or
you don't exist anymore and that's why
blood sugar is so
critical that's why they've been testing
it checking for it's
all of this so
and everyone's on caffeine which is fake
energy
to keep them energetic while they're on
their high fat diets
it's like stay on your high fat diet
avoid all sugars avoid all fruit avoid
all potatoes
stay on your high fat diet and then use
caffeine for fake energy i mean that's
what people do when really
the brain starts to atrophy caffeine
causes atrophy in everybody's brain it's
like
got all these people all these elders
all these people that are getting older
their brain's atrophying they're
drinking caffeine their whole life
they're not getting enough sugar to
their brain they're getting insulin
resistant so they can't even get sugar
to the brain and they're just wasting
away and you just age fast and
everything else
you know i mean
and a lot of people crave sugar because
they're really craving like
glucose that's what it is their brains
craving glucose and a lot of people
crave salt
because they're craving trace minerals
which is
trace mineral salts
smells so good right here you've got the
garlic in here got the basil
you don't need a lot of basil i mean
basil's anti-pathogen which is
incredible but
it's so good and i'm gonna put this on
top
of the noodles
but you know what you guys you're gonna
get a lot of misinformation out there
and it's painstaking because yeah you
might be somebody that it really doesn't
affect right now but
you can take that misinformation and be
like your brain needs fat let me just go
with that because every single podcast
doctor's saying your brain needs fat
because everybody's saying your brain
needs fat they don't they don't they're
wrong i mean it's not how it works
your brain actually runs on sugar it's
made out of glycogen and it needs sugar
you can't make a thought together put a
thought together
glucose is part of how your electrical
activity even works how
electrical activity in the brain all
that neurotransmitters even work it's
all it's all glucose based
that onion was so strong that onion was
strong um
grabbing a fork here so i'm just going
to mix this up a little bit
so i got the cucumber noodles i got the
tomato bruschetta on top here
okay that's what i have now yeah i mean
look
if you if you're into fat and that's all
you want to eat or something like that i
still want you to make these healthy
meals if you needed to put a little
avocado on it because you're not going
to have it any other way
at least i know you got something really
healthy in in you with that
but i would try to keep a fat free meal
once in a while in your life maybe
in a day or something when you're sick
you'll feel how fat doesn't help you
when you're really sick
that's when the line is is crossed or
that's when you
figure it out it's like it's like why do
you think everybody's intermittent
fasting
they're intermittent fasting because
they they didn't know it
no one knows it not even so-called
intermittent fasting experts whatever
you call that or whoever
it they didn't know that you're taking
fats out of your diet in the morning
that's why but they don't say that
because they think fats mean everything
it's like you need fats
but they but when you take your fats out
in the morning
you just gave your liver a break you
just gave your blood system a break you
just gave everything a break
because the fats in the morning that
actually they kill you
faster and age you faster and and stop
your brain from working what do you
think of res intermittent fasting
they're trying to get their brain
working for
for once in their life and they're
trying to get and then they're jacked up
on caffeine to be
high on adrenaline to get their brain
working it's you know and
so what you do in the morning is you
keep your fats out and you do natural
glucose you do your lemon water in the
morning right
you do that you do lemon water in the
morning that's what you do you do the
celery juice
you do the fruit smoothie you do the
heavy metal detox movie medical meme
heavy duty
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie and you stay away from these
fats in the morning
i mean if you want to have bacons and
bacon and eggs and toast in the morning
and butter on everything i mean that's
that's what takes you down
fast the bad road because you're killing
your liver and over time everything just
falls apart and this stuff
sits in the heart then there's no
glucose getting there's no natural
glucose getting to you to you like from
fruits and everything
anyway guys i just made the meal i'm
heading off to
well first you guys medical mean podcast
at apple podcast i'm going to be coming
out with episodes pretty soon but check
out the ones that are there
the meditations so medical medium
podcast apple podcast
check it out it's docuseries style
podcast
packed with information a caffeine
episode apple cider vinegar episode v12
episode
potato episode neurological symptoms
episode anxiety episode egg episode list
goes on
check it out when you can um go to apple
podcast that's the un
censored version and um you guys
i love you much and i'm gonna go to
instagram and tick tock at the same time
and i'm gonna let it fly i love you guys
take care