the medical medium how is everybody out
there I have Elizabeth Schaaf Roth right
here with me she's an old friend and we
didn't originally start out that way you
came to me 10 years ago but liz is an
amazing person she's here to tell her
story about Lyme disease about how she
struggled and suffered as a young woman
because it's just it's really hard when
it's when it's at that age especially
and we're here she's a dear dear friend
I'm really really lucky that I got her
here right now with everything and and
she's here she's gonna help out so many
people because it's important to know
about Lyme disease it's important to
know about the truth about it about what
people go through
she has history that is it's priceless
this history because you know it's
different when you're diagnosed with
Lyme disease today a lot different than
it was 10 years ago 11 years ago 12
years ago and I mean it's the dark ages
now with Lyme disease it was the dark
ages 10 12 years ago for real like even
more so because there wasn't any any
kind of I mean it wasn't even any kind
of hope because science research didn't
know laughs anyway have Elizabeth here
I'm so happy thank you for coming on I'm
so grateful you Anthony
saved my life Anthony is unique from my
personal experience I mean he shows
unconditional love to people which I
find was very hard to find in my
experience with professionals and
practitioners and he actually really
cares about the person each individual
each person and that is what compelled
me to Anthony and from the first time I
spoke to him on the on the phone I knew
that he was someone that actually cared
and didn't just you know just wasn't in
it just was following a book or
following a set of rules no Anthony has
and he has the research to back it up
and so I just want to thank Anthony for
coming into my life I never you know I
never saw it happening I just one day
stumbled upon Anthony and he has changed
my life think was a health food store -
and it was like 2010 probably right
right around that time so we're coming
on ten years I think so that's what
we're doing and but it's it's great to
see you the vibrant and here and alive
and well and safe and you know and I
always I mean I think what were you 23
when you came when you came to me
originally so I was around 21 when I
began having symptoms I was in college
it was my third year of college and I
woke up one day and I felt like a
different person I was not the person
that I was I had no energy no physical
energy Coffee stopped working
look I would have coffee every day and
it would cut me up and make me feel
great and it didn't happen - that
happens at people when they're starting
to get sick coffee's not cutting it or
they need their coffee no matter what
because they have something underlying
and they just don't nobody knows about
it yet and years could be where they
have to have their coffee to function I
want to talk about it later too because
people like it's like why do you need
your coffee to function I mean that
means something's going on you know but
you so the coffee just didn't cut it
anymore
I was so unwell that I just had no
energy I had no physical energy I no
mental energy and I had no idea what was
going on with me and I had to I couldn't
go to class I stopped attending classes
I had no energy I couldn't I I had no
idea what was going on so you're in
college I'm in college you're not able
to attend classes is that a big deal
like that's a big deal right for a young
woman you can't attend classes I can't
and I'm not I'm feeling horrible I'm not
feeling good I'm feeling really really
bad I don't have energy I don't feel
like myself I I'm like just it's so hard
to get through the day and unfortunately
I had to leave school in my third year
and you know leave all my friends and
leave everything and I went back to New
York City which I'm originally from and
that's when I started going to doctors
to 40 doctors over the course of like so
six years so it's like so it's like
here's here's instead of just instead of
college and friends and and planning on
career and future and all this other
stuff well you you we have to leave
friends you have to leave college you're
21 years old and you have to now make
your life about doctor's appointments
and this is this is the whole you know
when you came to me ten years ago you
know I knew that was happening in
people's lives but nobody talked about
it they still don't talk about it I just
did a recent podcast recently and I'm
just sitting there talking about this
stuff and people they look like deer in
headlights like you know young women are
really struggling with these conditions
no one talks about that like okay life
stops
I mean how serious is that I mean for
you was it like okay why is my life
doctors appointments now how come
there's no you know I had no other
choice like so I just this is my life I
have to go to doctors appointments I
can't go to class I can't study I have
to know I have to get better I had no
other choice but to get better and
doctors did not know no one knew what
was going on with me I tried everything
I tried every pill every treatment
everything that I could find in regular
conventional medicine and nothing helped
me nothing with the doctors that you
know I was going to and then one day a
friend said why don't you go to a Lyme
specialist a Lyme disease specialist and
so I went to a Lyme disease specialist
and they diagnosed me with Lyme disease
and they said I had neuropsychiatric
Lyme disease and which is when what
which is when Lyme disease they believe
is affecting your mood or your life or
your your attitude your anxiety I was
having brain fog you haven't the brain
fog I was like brain fog is you know
when you're just if you feel kind of
spaced out and you don't know why you
just you feel spaced out you don't
really feel like yourself and rain
brain fog is debilitating brain fog can
literally stop people from functioning
getting sentences out or being able to
articulate be able to converse with
people brain fog is brutal except people
from working but I mean here you are 21
years old you're dealing with severe
brain fog and you're you're highly
intelligent you're a highly intelligent
person you're extremely sharp I've known
you for 10 years your brilliant mind a
brilliant person and and actually have
to deal with that brain fog like that is
brutal so so they diagnosed you with
psychiatric Lyme aspects can don't quote
me on it but a scan of my brain they
said I had global brain inflammation and
then I started the antibiotics and I
started intravenous antibiotics I had a
PICC line in my arm I was being you know
everyday infused with antibiotics and it
wasn't doing much of anything and I just
believed in it I said it so it's got to
get better I know it's the Lyme disease
and then this was like years later so by
now I'm in my mid to late 20s and I'm
still struggling and I was one night I
was in in a restaurant in New York City
called Angelica's kitchen and I was
leaving the restaurant and I see this
magazine this health magazine and I'm
skimming through it and I see Anthony
and I'm like I felt an urge to call him
I can't even describe what I felt that
night out of nowhere I needed to call
Anthony and I haven't know I had to call
you like it was so weird like I don't go
around calling people in health
magazines it's not it's not my day today
so I mean I go to these I go to some
doctors but anyway the it was amazing so
I called him and I was I remember it was
11 p.m. at night I was standing in bet
Best Buy in New York City and Anthony
called me back immediately and I told
him what was going on which is something
that doesn't happen that's another thing
I have to wait months and months and
months
waiting list to get to see a line
specialist for a year why so you can for
what and you know and even me it was
hard to get back to people fast I mean
our office got back to people as quick
as we could like immediately and I
worked I worked day and night I mean I
got four hours of sleep at night for
seven days a week for a member like six
or eight years straight without a half
day off or a holiday but I remember when
I got a hold of you you were surprised
you were like what what's going on it's
just funny and he basically said to me
he said to me that you don't have Lyme
disease I said what do you mean I don't
have Lyme disease yes I do I thought I
did he goes no and I believed him I was
like you're right I don't have Lyme
disease that's false yeah because I mean
you didn't get bit by a tick no I warned
I didn't have any recollection of a tick
bite which is unbelievable some people
do but even then you know still not Lyme
because you guys are learning about Lyme
now what's happening and everything
anybody who doesn't know about the
medical medium information Lyme disease
has now moved out of the category of
bacterial now so medical medium
information allowed that to happen
actually prompted and pushed the medical
industry to change it they changed it
because of the millions of books that
got the truth out about Lyme disease
Lyme disease is not bacterial if you're
still stuck in that bacterium minded
world of Lyme disease you're gonna be
held back from getting better and it's
gonna hold you back for a lifetime if
you're not careful because it's not
bacteria and the Lyme labs
they've been bankrolling off of this
because this is what they built their
empires on they know to so what's
happening is is is the world's changing
now it's put in autoimmune so Lyme
disease the medical industry took Lyme
disease and they put it in autoimmune
now which means they think the body is
attacking itself and it wasn't bacteria
so just so you know and with her when
she came to me with all these symptoms
and everything else and and all of that
it wasn't Lyme disease it just wasn't
you can call it that you can call it
Lyme disease you can name it anything
you want but it wasn't what was really
happening and you know and I and I new
to with you that you weren't bit by a
tick
and even when you're bit by a tick it
doesn't mean that's Lyme disease and
I got it you know the whole thing I
remember we talked about it and
everything I mean did you have a relief
like a feeling of relief though oh I had
a huge sense of relief because someone
was actually you know I believed him
completely and he said that it was
something else
Anthony told me that it was heavy metals
and it was viral and that I had
inflammation going on and that we had to
address those factors and no one really
would ever address what was actually
going on with with the underlying you
know the issue and I didn't know what it
was yeah because for brain fog to happen
you got to have mercury got to have
toxic heavy metals like mercury
everybody's got mercury in in them and
if you guys don't think you have mercury
in you it's not true you have mercury in
you and and our ancestors do forefathers
down the line all had mercury in them
and mercury you know and what's
happening now is young women are getting
more sensitive to toxic heavy metals
than ever before in our history and it's
a cumulative effect to that's happening
yeah and aluminum are not good obviously
and they're you know they're neurotoxin
and you know if you get enough mercury
in enough aluminum and your body is
sensitive force whatever Prieta
predisposition you may have it's gonna
trigger something and it's gonna set off
a stream of things that that is not you
and you need to start looking at what
actually is going on what's causing you
know you got to start getting those
heavy metal metals out of you and slowly
obviously and you talk about that so
what happened we had the PICC line you
were getting me antibiotics were you
getting better no so the antibiotics
weren't getting him better and that's a
thing with Lyme disease because so you
weren't you were you feeling sicker from
the antibiotics
I actually was feeling I was feeling a
little bit yeah I was feeling sicker but
I was feeling no different at all and
you know I think that if I stayed I
stayed on them and many much longer it
could have been to the point where I
could get I could have gone very sick
yeah why did you stop them like what was
it because we talked to her you just
knew your
it wasn't working and no because I spoke
to you and you explained it in a
different way I think I probably
probably told you and I can't remember
but I probably told you if you stand the
antibiotics you're gonna go down the
path when I watch 30 years of people
diagnosed with Lyme disease getting
bombarded with antibiotics and losing
their lives and I know you were young
and you just started them and I was like
in this situation you're you're just
gonna end up like the rest we can't let
that happen I think I was probably you
know really really charged about it
because it was like wait a minute
you know how old are you I just don't
want to see you go through this now
because that's what happens because we
had thousands of people contact us women
that were already down that the dark
place of tons of antibiotics and their
lives were shattered because of it
because they weren't properly diagnosed
about they weren't properly diagnosed
about the viral issue they had the
epstein-barr they had or anything else
and they and they weren't properly
diagnosed with the toxic heavy metals
and their lives were shattered by this
phantom bacterial thing which here's the
thing Lyme bacteria is not a super bug
it kills off easy from from from
antibiotics it's not it's not MRSA
people actually heal from Mercer with
antibiotics and Merces antibiotic
resistant and people recover I've seen
people go in the hospital tumors to come
out of hospital they recover because
Merce is a super bug but it has a higher
healing rate than Borrelia Babesia it's
unbelievable then Bartonella it's
unbelievable so what happens is my bar
people with tremendous amounts of
antibiotics it's not even about bacteria
viruses don't get stopped from an
antibiotic antibiotics make viruses
worse that's why the Lyme community has
suffered decade after decade have gotten
worse and worse and it was like no Liz
you know and at that point I didn't know
you like you know like a best friend now
but at that point I was like Liz no you
can't go through this I can't watch you
go through this but you were relieved to
know that it wasn't
there was I was relieved when I got the
Lyme diagnosis I was hugely relieved I
was like finally someone knows what's
going on with me but when Anthony told
me it wasn't Lyme there was no
resistance for some reason I wasn't in
there wasn't a need for me to hang on to
it because I really understood what he
was like everything he was saying made
sense in a way that I that I don't
doesn't make sense with other people
that I've seen it's completely his
knowledge is has research to back it up
and he's dedicates his life to
understanding underlying root causes of
issues of illness well the research
comes later what I when I when I told
the world Hashimoto's thyroiditis many
years ago and even published it and said
that the Hashimoto's thyroiditis is
caused by epstein-barr virus and
fibromyalgia is caused by epstein-barr
virus it came out later that they found
a link with epstein-barr so the research
comes later and that's what's always
happy to work sure the research shows up
and people say oh he must have got it
from the research know the research
guided for me that's the irony and it's
so crazy how that works and the same
thing with Lyme disease I've been saying
it's viral all these years now they took
it and put an autoimmune category now
they're trying to phase out the
bacterial energy about it all and
doctors are swimming like they're
swimming in a sea of confusion now
doctors are like wait a minute I thought
we were treating bacteria and then you
get the old dogs left that are still
treating bacteria but the new doctors
now that are getting all the medical
medium books all the new doctors that
have them in their offices and
everything they're treating it like
viral now they're starting to because
neurological Lyme is in the autoimmune
category so it's really it's really
amazing how millions of these medical
medium books have been infiltrated
doctor's office offices have gone into
people's hands and it's changed what
happened them the big mistake the Lyme
mistake and I know a lot of the Lyme
groups online don't understand this yet
many of them do many of them I know that
Medical meaning books were a dirty
secret for a lot of people because they
would get they would get like you know
you know hassled if they got off the the
road of it being bacterial but this is
saving lives it's safe so many countless
lives that when you're a girl
you're 21 years old you're you know
young woman you can't finish college or
you're trying to struggle to do college
and you're visiting 23 I mean how many
doctors did you see like five doctors
five doctors is a lot of doctors five
doctors is a lot of doctors at least
over the course of six years probably
around 25 at least that's incredible I
went I had I had no other option though
because I was I was I was in unable to
function so if I didn't for myself there
would be no one because no one
understood what was going on no one
around me social media social media
wasn't born you know what happens is
like a lot of you guys you guys tell
your stories you show your stories you
show like your skin problems you show
you talk about your chronic illness your
neurological problems now you know young
women are allowed to actually they're on
social media even though it's still
swept in the carpet even though it's
still not taken seriously out there but
it's still a platform this is like two
thousand eight nine ten this was a
really dark period for young women with
with this kind of problem I mean it's
you're you're a fighter that's how I see
it you know you're a fighter and you're
like okay yet you you you saw 25 doctors
and you just I mean it's it's amazing
yeah I just think about the people out
there who don't you know are getting
misdiagnosed I think that's the problem
it's not just about Lyme it's kind of
like you're being you're being diagnosed
maybe it's the right diagnose but
there's no there's no long-term like
understanding of what's going on
underneath of just giving someone a pill
and Taotao and maybe the pill is a
little bit helpful and that's good maybe
you have to take the pill that's okay
that's no problem if you have to take
the pill but it's it's that there's no
regard for anything else because they
don't understand they don't they don't
know what is going on yeah no it I
totally I totally get it but I didn't I
only lived it on on by seeing you know
like your your struggle okay
I lived it that way seeing others
struggle over the years but I'm a I
haven't lived it physically you know I
haven't lived it on that level so I
can't put myself in your shoes because I
haven't lived that I haven't had you
know where I was struggling like that
you know physically with a lime
diagnosis or anything else but I can't
imagine what that's like when you're
young when you're older it's hard oh my
god women and 30s women are the forties
women and the fifties it's it's it's
hard but I can't imagine though I mean
your life should not be disturbed
it should not be kind of like
roadblocked because you know you've got
this diagnosis that the science of
research has nothing no knows nothing
about and that's the hard part for me
it's like when you're healthy and you
feel undestructible and nothing seems
wrong science research seems to have all
the answers but it kills me when I know
that they don't have the answers but
we're pretending they do and then your
life stops because of it but what about
all the other young women out there
their lives stopped because of it
because science research doesn't have
that answer and so you know visiting
doctors and and I mean you find out who
your friends are and if you realize you
can't keep up with what you you know and
all of it it just it becomes difficult
and yeah that's why I say you're a
survivor of this and you're a survivor
of it but you're still really young of
course but you're a survivor of during
that that dark period that was coming
out of 2008 2009 2010 no social media
kind of platform the lime groups weren't
there for support there wasn't you know
he whether they have the right
information or not there wasn't any of
that and you know you were in it alone
is what I'm saying and yeah you found me
but you were in it alone
there's millions millions of other
people out there going through this who
are suffering and and there has to be
more than just a surface topical
solution to what's going on I feel that
people need to realize if you're young
out there and you're going through
something and you don't know what it is
and you you know the people around you
are looking at you like what's wrong
with her
she's maybe she just doesn't want to do
this maybe she's lazy you know just know
that they're you there's nothing wrong
with you and you just have a physical
problem and it's not your your fault
yeah and and it's not your body
attacking itself because that's what the
industry that's what science and
research wants she didn't know they want
you to know that your body is attacking
itself that's what they really want you
to they want you to believe I'm sorry
that your body's destroying itself your
immune system is destroying itself
that's why they moved lime into
autoimmune to is because not only was it
a complete mystery and it's not
bacterial but it's there because it
falls into the category now of because
Lyme people they have the Hashimoto's
and they have the thyroid problems and
they have skin problems they have all
these other problems in the they're
realizing they never even knew it Lyme
was to begin with so they so they just
now they're lumping it in to the
autoimmune category they want women they
want young women to know that their body
is faulty and just and and it's
destroying them and our genes are faulty
their body's attacking itself they want
them to know that now why do they want
them to know that I don't have any idea
the only thing I can come up with is
science researchers likes to protect
itself when it doesn't have the answer
so if it doesn't have the answers it's
going to protect itself over people but
but the bottom line is it's like so
you're in this position in your life
you're a young woman you're going
through this there's there's really
you're in it alone that's how I see it
because you're walking out of doctors
offices you don't have an answer you're
really sick I mean when I met you you
were like you were you told me when I
talked with you that you can't even get
out of the house there was there was
there was no exercising you weren't
gonna be able to exercise you weren't
gonna be able to hop on a treadmill you
weren't gonna be able to do you know
that you weren't allowed you weren't
gonna be able to do Pilates or weren't
gonna be able to do things yoga things
that young women I was I was a high I
ran track in high school and I couldn't
God I didn't even know that but I I was
a sprinter in high school but I could
even get to the gym like I couldn't get
out of the house and it wasn't you know
I mean so it doesn't matter if you you
know whatever it's well when when you're
young woman your your running track in
high school you know that exercise
because exercise is also a release
it's like release it's a great release
it can it can you know when you're
stressed out that's how you can battle
stress as a young person you're actually
even an older person whatever you can
you can you know you use exercise as a
tool how they tool and stuff so here you
can't exercise you have a history of
running track that's that's a big deal
and so and when I met you it's like I
remember you on a you know you're on the
phone and you were like Anthony I can't
even I mean I can't even I can't the
brain Fox so bad the fatigue is so bad I
remember you telling me your weight was
really really low like really low you
could barely eat because you mean
because you had no energy I mean it
takes energy to get food to make food to
eat food I mean all of it you were like
you were like and and you know you you
bore it really well I gotta say because
when I was on the phone you were like
you were just like what do I need to do
that's it you're like what do I need to
do and I get I get choked up about this
because it broke my heart to see you in
this condition
and because I know I know who you really
worry the one thing about how it works
with my source and how I hear the voice
I hear and the gift I have and
everything is I know who you are as a
person and and to know that you were
suffering and struggling like this it
just I broke my heart and I was like
look you know we're gonna get you better
and I mean and we were you were talking
a lot we were you know connecting a lot
to make sure you you were you at least
knew your body wasn't your body you that
you did have something going on it
wasn't Lyme and we had to now go we had
to go after the true problem and I
remember then the spirulina came I think
I consumed so much spirulina in that
amount of time
remember I have some right in here my
heavy-metal detox movie but I remember
coming home one day and there was
spirulina all over my kitchen my cat had
knocked down a glass bottle maybe the
whole thing had exploded everywhere and
I took me like weeks to clean it up I
just had so much spirulina during that
time and I was you know in cilantro
I remembered juice I was juicing I was
juicing all the time
and it was so helpful for the brain fog
especially huh oh my god the juicing
yeah because you know what Happel I had
somebody recently tell me like oh you
just started this the other day your
heavy metal detox movie are you kidding
this is going all the way back 2010-2011
and you're doing the spirulina and
cilantro
yeah because spirit always had this
information going all the way back and
that's a thing because it's that it's
that I watched it help so much so the
cilantro the spirulina those two alone
were helping you and and I think I try
to get you on the wild blueberries I
think that was happening I think a lot
of fruits because it was anti fruit then
to fruit every few every hour I had to
have a piece of fruit yeah and yeah but
you were you were like you were like
what do I need to do and I was like you
got to do fruit because fruit kills
pathogens and that information still
isn't out there you can even surf surf
around you YouTube and find all these
professionals that are on there talking
they're not they're not Pro fruit they
don't think fruit does anything and it
literally saves lives and that's the sad
part about you know if your first time
watching this learn this now and put
your belief system aside and and
actually learn but it's it's the fruit
and I remember telling you know you got
to do all this fruit and you were just
like you're like you're just tough
you're just like okay what do I got to
do
and you remember I remember and and it
wasn't and you weren't afraid and I have
to say that I understand when people are
afraid I I understand that but but and
and people are afraid when they're
trying something
isn't so popular like right now the
world hates fruit so much for no reason
and back then 2010 they hated it but it
was a little easier to also do because
it was like it wasn't so bad with so
many professionals you know harping on
fruit like they do now but it's like but
you still did it and it was odd you were
like you know meaning was odd that I
would recommend that kind of fruit nice
every hour you had to have it because
your nervous system and this is the
thing when you have a nervous system and
it's a viral load causing the problem so
with you was the up steam bar which
everybody has if you don't think you
have Epstein bar you're wrong it sits
inside all of us and it'll waits for an
opportunity whatever that might be you
may accidentally get more heavy metals
through some Avenue that that you know
we research and we know where mercury is
or other metals and lumina manned copper
but we all have epstein-barr and young
or old we all have it and it awaits to
want to come out one day and wreak a lot
of havoc and so you had the epstein-barr
you had the mercury and the aluminum the
epstein-barr feeds off the mercury in
aluminum you get the brain fog you get
the brains the brain inflammation you
get the nerve inflammation and then
that's that's where you were and and the
fruit was so important because you
needed you need a glucose for the nerves
and the nervous system the nervous
system runs on sugar
another great mistake now you guys is
everything's Kido Kido Kido I'm not
making fun and Kido Kido has it has a
some offers a lot of great stuff because
it gets you off of processed foods and
all this other junk and garbage so it's
really good on that level but when
you're really sick and you got real
issues going on that's don't they they
starve your nervous system they don't
feed it so if you're somebody if you're
a young woman dealing with Lyme in your
neurological Lyme and all of that the
last thing you want is to beat your fats
to be threw off the chart and the high
fat diet just because it's popular and
you don't want that you want to make
sure there's lots of sugar in your diet
healthy natural sugar like steamed
potatoes and and and I think I had you
on steamed potato so I'm pretty sure at
one point
and fruits like the bananas and the
blueberries and all this because it's
sugars that revive and revitalize your
nervous system when you're going through
this inflammation in this neurological
Lyme and if your first time seeing this
just don't pooh-pooh it you take this
advice she did and I mean did it save
your life I mean so what I became just I
was having a lot of digestive issues but
severe constipation and things going on
and the gut was the first thing to heal
my gut my gut was the first thing to
heal in a matter of weeks I was coming
back to normal like it was unbelievable
so you're on the phone with me and
you're like and I remember that - you're
like my stomach's getting better and and
and now was huge for you because then
you're like wait a minute I'm getting
better yeah I couldn't believe that I
was getting like I was feeling better
like you know with my stomach and then I
was slowly getting the you know anxiety
was getting better the brain fog was
getting better you know I still to this
day have some some issues with with my
energy levels residual issues because I
I found Anthony later on unfortunately
though oh yes I'm you but it's very you
know it's very manageable like I'm hot
you know it's nothing you got your you
got global she has her global strays
foundation because I want you to get a
chance to talk about that for a minute
cuz that's important because this is
this is this is a big deal to me right
here is here you are you recovered from
something so that was so difficult and
and you were suffering and because of
recovering from that you're saving
animals
you're saving dogs which I have a love
for dogs that's why I talk about it in
the first book I have you know the
storage story with August and and
everything and and and dogs me in the
world to me and they just do animals
didn't mean the world to me - of course
and so what happened is you're you're
now doing this powerful work globally on
saving dogs and it's called global
strays and I want everybody to check
that out its global straight
and look into that if donate to it or
whatever I don't know how its set up but
you you know that's yeah you can make
donations and so forth she can help out
animals but she's she's running that
that's and and but yeah so also when I
got better I was able to go back to
school I always wanted to study
photography and I was able to become a
photojournalist for a few years and then
in New York City which I absolutely
loved I loved I loved photojournalism
and I still do love it and but I was
gravitated towards helping animals and
the people that were rescuing animals in
parts of the world were there is very
little help for animal welfare issues so
I travel to parts of the world Central
America and I saw there was an
overpopulation crisis of animals
everywhere horses dogs cats everywhere
and it was astounding to me that nothing
was being done to control the population
to help these animals and I started
meeting with animal rescuers who were
doing incredible work but they had no
help
they had no outside donations so that's
how I began global streams began to
develop it was the need to help people
who had no help and they wanted to help
animals and we're helping horses we're
helping dogs were helping cats in a
different and not just in in rescuing
one one animal at a time we help
families with veterinary care who cannot
afford veterinarian care for their pets
incredible so when we do say neutering
and educational program so people can
understand more about the love of the
love for animals and why animals are
important animals have also changed they
have the animals help me they support me
emotionally I mean my dogs are there my
therapy now my therapy with everything
going on and you know it's it's such a
critical part of my life so I know it's
part of you know cats and dogs and
horses and they're a part of everybody's
life so many people out there so while
she's doing incredible work me and and
she she healed to do that so you feel
like you feel like you know you're it's
manageable now like
you can you can work you even went back
to school and it's manageable completely
manageable I'm living wonderful life and
I mean there's no obviously there's days
that sometimes it comes a little bit of
it comes back and I have to take more
supplements and I have to you know and
you can't you know but I'm unable to do
what I what I couldn't do without that's
incredible that's incredible what were
some of the other supplements that I had
you on the zinc e 12 b12 because the b12
is critical and if you don't just get
any b12 the best b12 is the benarjee
calm I gave some way in a giveaway I
purchased some and gave someone a
giveaway recently so it's of energy v as
in Victor I am ERG why energy outcomes
so they're b12 is key and because it's a
special blend it's a quality and
everything but b12 is imperative for
your nervous system and what happens is
with people when they have neurological
Lyme or any kind of nervous system
diagnosis whether it's fibromyalgia
whether it's any anything
and whether it's CFS you know mecfs
whatever it might be that you got a
diagnosis of what happens is that your
b12 might be high at the doctor's office
and they don't know you still need it
that you can't go by that reading on
your bloodwork that your b12 is high and
you don't need any b12 it's a great
mistake great mistake at the doctor's
office it's not the doctors fault for
not knowing these things they're not
gonna have a source of then they're not
gonna have a source that can provide
them the information like I do they're
just not so what happens is the b12
critical for your recovery and you know
and and and zinc's another one to zinc
is critical for recovery because of the
viral issue so when you have
neurological Lyme or any kind of Lyme
disease diagnosis whatever it is you
need zinc because it's your defense
that's your defense against the viral
issues that created and and the people
with with Lyme disease they'll have the
heavy metals too toxic heavy metals
whether they know it or not and they'll
have the pathogen the epstein-barr
epstein-barr and shingles they'll have
either both of those yours was
epstein-barr and and so it's important
to know that but you you say you still
it's good you still take your
supplements though it's still because
you have
- and you still eat pretty good right
yes definitely I when I eat gluten is if
I ever return to gluten that's when I
noticed my symptoms start to come back
so I have to stay gluten free that's
been one of the most helpful things with
the gut especially yeah I just felt
right away better when I took you
personally when I took luta now
everyone's different but that was you're
gonna be sensitive to the things that
were that we're causing trouble at the
beginning meaning like you had the viral
issue you had the heavy metals and then
anything that that like gluten and dairy
products if you do too many of those you
can get sensitive again because because
they get in the way of the body's
healing mechanisms they get in the way
of the body healing and everything so
I'm really proud of you for for doing
that and we got some celery juice in
front of us but hopefully doesn't spill
it's a it's a gentle anti-inflammatory
it's really amazing it's antiviral it's
it's so it's it's a great one I love
tumeric - I mean vitamin C when the
vitamin C gotta have vitamin C if you're
dealing with Lyme disease vitamin C's
critical and you you want to be generous
with your vitamin C you want to make
sure you're doing an ester see that's
number one
the Vemma G ester C is the best the
medical medium vitamin C shock therapy
is incredible for people dealing with
Lyme disease dealing with any kind of
diagnosis that's confusing autoimmune
diagnosis of any kind because autoimmune
any autoimmune diagnosis is viral you
just need to know that's the only way
you're gonna learn and if you've heard
that before out there it comes
originally from the medical medium
information and books so just know where
it originates from so doctor toll tells
you it's viral that autoimmune that
originates from medical medium
information know where the source comes
from but but I'm just proud of you
because I'm honestly you've always
you've always taken care of yourself
since then - you didn't just get better
and throw it
you know you didn't get better and just
throw it all away I've gotten people a
lot of people have gotten better and
pulled them out of a dark space and they
just kind of they forget what got them
there meaning like doing all the good
things and stuff so you always have
these tools here and you're always using
them and know better and it's amazing
you know and I'm really proud of you for
that it's incredible
so overall like she say you know you
learned how to heal you learned what the
answer was it was a great relief to know
you you actually had something else that
you can pinpoint that was wrong like a
real the real cause do you think that's
gonna help out a lot of other people out
there when they know that there's these
other real causes other other things
that could be going on yeah yeah it's
important if you get if you got a lot if
you get locked into a certain belief you
got to be careful like if you're being
told one thing is the one thing I notice
is is that with the medical medium
information is always controversial
because it goes against all of the
trendy money-making things like Lyme is
a is a moneymaker it's stood out there
so what it is if you go against what
they're trying to do then you know you
look like you don't have the answer but
they all have the answer be cautious on
all those very things because that's how
it works we get sucked into these trendy
trendy protocols diagnoses and all the
stuff out there these trendy ways of
that things are handled or created we
got to look out for that stuff because
it can block you what happens is you
know you get diagnosed with Lyme disease
you get told it's bacterial you get
thrown on antibiotics and you just you
feel like that's just the way it's gotta
be but it doesn't have to be that way
there's answers what I mean is you have
to be open you something inside of you
were like no this is I mean is that is
that angelic intervention I don't know
you just knew and just knew at the time
meaning like you know you were just like
you just knew you had to call me because
that's funny because so
people when they say that they'll be
like I don't know how it happened but it
just it just did and I'm just blown away
that you know I'm just blown away become
friends we've become close friends all
these years and I didn't think I back
when I met you in 2010 okay
I didn't think we'd be sitting here
right here and doing this this is this
just blows me away
I never thought that ever like if you
told me that then what do you talk about
we're gonna be sitting you know what I
mean we you know but it's incredible um
and so overall every day your energy
still feels pretty good you're still
feeling like you know obviously not do
you run into people do you know anybody
that's dealing with Lyme do you ever run
into people over the years do you know
anybody that's dealing with other
conditions so I encourage them to to
read your books
yeah actually alternative perspective
yeah so every book I started with your
first book yeah and that really goes
pretty much yeah yeah has the Lyme story
right there exactly and you can learn
about Lyme and the truth about Lyme and
everything um please know that I don't
do consultations if you're if you're
you're you're trying to reach me for
that I actually did the books purposely
the waiting lists of people were in the
millions by the time I published his
first book but the answers are here to
heal you don't have to see me in water
to heal the the answers are like what
we're giving now we're here while we're
doing this this is the whole point
[Music]
and changing the diet and really giving
it a chance with the diet change yeah
and I know it's really really hard it's
not easy though it's not easy but but
what's what's harder what's that's
harder yeah hardest thing sick I love
that and you know because it's true I
mean it's like I don't know but look I
wasn't sick like you in the sense with
the neurological I'm I haven't suffered
in that level
I suffer from from just the the the
hearing spirit that's not fun and not
being able to do live a normal life
because of it you know throughout my
life but that's you know my story in
here but the point is is that I haven't
been in that trench myself personally
and I just I all I know is I can't
imagine what you went through and you
know I am NOT going to pretend I can
because I've never felt that kind of
fatigue and that brain fog and I never
had to go to 50 doctors for some people
and 25 doctors ten doctors five doctors
is too much and I've never had to do
anything like that so I can't imagine
but all I can tell you is that I I feel
you and I believe you know what you've
been through I was there at that time
with you and and you were crying on the
phone and you know and just know that
hey I'm it's a it's wonderful that
you're here I want people to know you
can get the answers you don't have to be
on the phone with me you don't you could
get the answers in the books and you can
get the answers on like with with this
here at the YouTube law I've make sure
you subscribe make sure you hit the
notification bell so you can see these
lives and thank you for coming on and
hey I'm gonna click the button and
everybody take care