foreign
[Music]
day three
of the medical medium Brady shot therapy
challenge
try holding your breath that long
[Music]
I held my breath for like three minutes
I don't know what it was you guys
brain shot therapy challenge day three
we're here I'm pumped up obsessive
thought shifter
I got obsessed in thoughts right now
if we're gonna have some fun I'm gonna
successively thinking about fun it's
gonna be incredible you guys I'm excited
so here we are
[Music]
um
incredible you guys are you trying this
you trying the shots we're on day three
I see people out there they're doing the
shots they're drinking the shots sending
them down incredible so hey let's get
into it a little bit
all right so we're going into the book
right now
so we're doing the obsessive thought
shifter today and I want to give you a
little bit of a forewarning
because it works
it works
I'm saying that because I don't want you
caught off guard
it works
how why how is it possible
can a human being
figure out the combination
to stop obsessive thoughts
how is that possible no human being
can't
there's no doctor
there's no lawyer
there's no scientist there's no lab
technician there's no food science
person there's no podcast person there's
no person in health that can do it not
even me I can't do it or figure out how
it works it came from above
it came from above and that's how it
works right there because it can't be
done by a human they won't know it's not
possible there's no science a thousand
years from now that can say if you put
this much radish and this much celery
and this much sage and this much apple
together that you can literally start
changing and rewiring thought patterns
in here the electricity so that OCD or
obsessive thoughts starts to calm down
and starts to go away that can't be done
in science today
there's no
there's no Harvard grad there's no Ivy
League school grad there's no University
there's nowhere there's no scientist no
one can figure out that when you put
Apple
celery in the right amounts
radish design amounts and Sage of the
right amounts that something happens
some kind of chemistry happens
synergistically the combination does
something no one ever knew and what I
was taking down that information from
above
from Spirit of compassion and I was
writing it down I was like this is what
people need this is it right here I was
so excited because I knew it would work
because guess what
this is out of all the books they all
have helped people heal the heavy metal
detox Smoothie has saved lives this 32
ounces of celery juice to save lives
around the world the protocols all the
different customizable protocols so of
course they would work but I said the
spirit of compassion
what's gonna happen with these
and I got the answer of fast relief
quick rewiring
quick rewiring and fast Relief really
incredible you guys were day three so
pumped up people are having incredible
results
did you see some of the stories with the
OCD did you see the one with the washing
hands the child that was suffering with
washing their hands so much so much
washing his hands and it's it's coming
down so many benefits are happening for
people out there it's what I pray every
night about I want people to get relief
I want people to have an opportunity and
it's my greatest greatest dream come
true when you see a child get some
relief when you see life-changing
results happen from these brain shot
therapies and that's the whole point
when I was getting the information
this word of compassion was telling me
when people have these in their hand
they're going to have a powerful tool to
turn their lives around and that's what
it's about it really is
so let's get into it a little bit so
exciting you guys so I'm gonna get to
another little section here I got all my
little notes going on here medical
medium brain shot therapy if you just
rolled in you're like what is he even
talking about because this is not a
closed channel right here this is open
to anybody who can find their way here
so you might be brand new you're popping
on you're like what is this guy doing
what's going on we're doing the medical
medium brain shot therapy right there
medical medium brain shot therapy we're
in the brain saver books so
remember you can get the brain saver
books anytime okay well right now
they're 40 off amazon.com us which is
unbelievable there are two massive books
over 600 pages each 12 books combined
and anyway we're doing the brain shot
therapies right here now you can be
somebody that doesn't even believe in it
but you try it and you will have a
change happen
you don't even have to like me you can
dislike me you could be a non-believer
with it you cannot even care but when
you run those ingredients together in
that Precision like in those
combinations and in that amount
you're going to get a result even if you
don't believe this is not a juice this
is not just a juice oh he's juicing
that's what this is no it's not
and this is information from above
putting specific combinations together
creating a medicinal shot for specific
reasons no one would ever know no one on
this planet including me would never
know in a million years
that if you put this group together of
ingredients you see
that OCD and obsessive thoughts
start to calm down and dissipate and
disappear
and that's from one shot you do them
regularly for severe cases and
improvements happen improvements happen
and but nobody on the planet would ever
know this it would not even be possible
which actually goes to show us along
with the other medical medium books that
the information works and that's why
they're the most popular book health
book series in the world for health
there's a reason because it works but
the brain shot therapy is incredible
medical medium brain shot therapies
offer instant relief
your brain and body have a quick
response to medicinals in liquid form
going directly to the brain and what
these do is they absorb quickly remember
yesterday on day two you guys on day two
I did the shot the trail and broken
trust stabilizer
and when I did it I felt how it went
into the mouth you'll feel that with
these you will actually feel the
difference when you do the brain shot
therapy you will feel the quick
absorption happen in your mouth you'll
feel it go into the cells of your mouth
it'll hit your blood vessels quick
Apples by themselves won't do that Apple
Juice by itself won't do that it won't
absorb that quick it's the combination
of the sage the Apple the radish the
celery it's the combination that makes
quick absorption happen
and it drives into the blood vessels and
it gets to the brain fast
Kristen says I have done brain shot
therapy so I have done brain therapy
shots two days now and notice how deeply
I am sleeping
not sure if it if it's related but makes
sense to me
well it's okay if you're not sure or not
but it's working and you're sleeping
deeply and that's okay you can be
somebody that's like wow let me try this
and see what it does here's what's
incredible
it could be a day later
and the incredible results start kicking
in it can be instant means it's
happening for you in the moment you may
see things within seconds you may see
things within hours then it may carry on
and give you results the next day
or the day after but then if you do it
again and keep on doing it again it
builds on itself you guys it builds upon
itself making more profound effects
happening with symptoms conditions and
issues and problems and emotional stuff
going on and mental stuff and mental
health all of it it's life-changing and
you guys are experiencing it
these shots are designed to be highly
absorbable in the mouth that's one of
the big things right there the valuable
healing components of all of these gets
driven into the brain quick
the brain gets them fast
big part of it and then it's the
combination the specific combination
synergistically combined that gets to
the brain really quick it does its thing
once it gets to the brain that's a whole
other thing now these are special
configurations synergistically combined
just to crack the code
of how
these Godly ingredients right these
Earth Mother Earth Earthly mother
ingredients can get to our brain
this shot was so delicious and helped me
to follow sleep for real fall asleep for
real
I'm for real I did it yesterday evening
amazing
incredible so you guys
we're just going to read a little bit
more
while Creative Juice concoctions out
there offer their benefits right because
their juices
it isn't what this is so if you take a
whole bunch of stuff I'm gonna juice I'm
gonna get into juice I'm gonna put
apples I'm gonna put carrots in here I'm
gonna put all this stuff and I'm gonna
juice whatever it's not the same thing
entirely different
that's the key
the healing shots of the medical medium
brain shot therapy are tools that come
from above I can't say it enough but
it's important to know and it's
important to know why they work
you can't give me I I can't get the
credit when it's from above
because I would never know how to put
that together it's not even possible
nobody no scientist no one can
the healing shots of medical medium
brain shot therapy are tools that come
from above these brain shots are
composed of specific combinations of
ingredients that work together
systematically for reasons Precision
reasons only a source above can know
Rhonda said I was having a really rough
morning the other day and tried the
obsessive thought shifter which we're
doing today and it changed my entire day
I noticed it changed quickly I had such
a beautiful calm come over me
Kimberly says my little girl has had her
life debilitated by OCD since she was a
toddler oh my God probably earlier she
knows all about Anthony and SOC we
started the OCD shot yesterday she calls
it her angel juice
because she knows there is no doctor
that knows how to help her we still pray
to the unknown angels as well incredible
oh my God that's just the most amazing
amazing story I'm so proud of her
you guys I really seriously
um all right well I gotta tell you
something
I did the obsessive thoughts shifter
last week
when I was like I was working I was
working I was working
and I was trying to get something done
and it was like this thing where I was
like I gotta get this done I have to get
this done
and you know it's like in reality sure I
had this deadline but I I I could have
somehow just backed down and not I could
have somehow and then I said you know
what I have to finish it it was real it
was like two in the morning
and I said you know what I gotta go to
bed
I'm just gonna do the obsessive thought
shifter right here I sent that down I
made it real quick and sent it down
and all of a sudden instead of like I
gotta finish that deadline I gotta
finish that deadline I was like you know
what let me get ready for bed
I'm actually just gonna go to bed and it
was like amazing what happened it really
was incredible so we're doing that one
today
and very excited about it very happy
about it too so you guys have you been
doing the different shots this is a
10-day brain shot therapy challenge
right it's 10 days we're on day three
hope you guys stick with us all the way
to the end to the 10 days now this is
like the entry level brain shot therapy
cleanse that's what we're doing right
here
so it's important to know so let me just
move through here a little bit we'll
talk about sign up
to get your free grocery shopping list
the free pdf that you can actually
download so sign up for it make sure if
you're here so you have the free grocery
list so you know what you're doing all
of that go to medicalmedium.com sign up
so you're in here it's okay if it's day
three and you're starting now if it's
day three start now if it's day five
start then we're in the and get your
brand saver books you have to always
have your brain saver books too Lorraine
says I literally felt this one hit my
brain and love the taste too
I'm like addicted to this obsessive
thoughts shifter now just so you know
we're in the shifters now we did a
stabilizer yesterday we're in the
shifters today Tara says I have a really
sensitive stomach and I'm amazed at
these combos how they don't cause me any
nausea incredible and I'm finding that
too as far as the gentle nature of them
as I'm doing them
they're so gentle at the same time
potent and Powerful life-changing but
gentle that's what's incredible about it
make sure you have your brain saver
books
that's critical too so order them when
you can if you can't even though they're
on on sale like this killer sale on
these
if you still can't get them to 26.29
it's six books in each book if you still
can't get them go to the library
and get them out for free
so I don't care I want you to have them
it doesn't matter to me plus they're so
pre I don't control the pricing the
prices are so low on the books it costs
triple quadruple to print them to what
the price they're selling them at so it
doesn't even matter anymore to me like
it just doesn't
so if you get them on sale incredible
right if you get them for free at the
library it's actually all the same now
so it doesn't matter anyway all right
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanses
that's what we're in so
um let's take a look here all right you
guys got a minute I'm gonna do a little
reading out of the brain saver book
right here
so
emotional injury
really interesting section inside the
brain saver book emotional injury
when we say we've had emotional wounds
and Scar scars in life
this description is more accurate than
we know so when we say like I'm I've
been emotionally hurt
I have an emotional wound
when we say that it's real
a lot of people don't give the person
validation for an emotional wound
like if you've been emotionally hurt
it's real
you're emotionally hurt I know that a
lot of people want to shake it off they
don't want to believe it's real a lot of
people won't give anybody the validation
about emotional hurt right but when
someone says hey I've been emotionally
hurt
it's actually more real than anybody
knows so when we say we've had emotional
wounds like I've had an emotional wound
in my life I got an emotional scar in my
life
somebody like what what is that it's
actually true
the description is more accurate when we
say I've been burned before have you
ever said that I've been burned before
I've said that in my life man I've been
burned
I've been burned bad on that one do you
ever say that in your life like I've
been burned
we really mean it
it's real
we really mean it that's because when we
go through
upsetting and traumatizing experiences
we can experience physical injury in the
emotional centers of the brain so in the
emotional centers of the brain you guys
we can experience real physical injuries
now why am I even talking about this
because obsessive thought shifter is
healing
these injuries
a lot of times OCD or obsessive thoughts
occur from an injury your boyfriend
breaks up with you or your boyfriend
cheats on you and you can't stop
thinking about it your girlfriend cheats
on you and you can't stop thinking about
it and you're laying up all night long
wrecked by it
because the obsessive thoughts it
becomes obsessive
I I better drive by my girlfriend's
house I better drive by my boyfriend's
house I better drive by my partner's
house
because you're obsessed you've been hurt
I better check my boyfriend's phone I
better check my girlfriend's phone
because are they cheating on me that's
happened so many times to people and
what happens is that obsessive thought
really cranks up because there's an
injury that occurs
we actually get injured
that's just one example of hundreds of
examples of how people get emotionally
injured right that's just one
we can ex we can experience physical
injuries in the emotional center of the
brain from any kind of hurt or any kind
of upset anything traumatizing losses
anything struggles
anything that we go through in life
we can get injured but nobody talks
about this real injuries happen inside
the emotional centers of the brain real
injuries occur what I'm saying is even
if it's on the mildest injury the
mildest form the most gentle mildest
form of injury we can still get the
obsessive thoughts
we can still get the OCD we can still
get these things now you can get OCD
without an emotional blow I want to make
that clear
because
serious cases of OCD
come from the toxic heavy metals but
what I love about the obsessive thought
shifter it rewires the brain so we can
move around those Metals we can move the
electricity around those Metals so when
we have OCD and we're suffering from OCD
like repetitive thoughts that you have
to act on that you feel compelled to act
on right those are toxic heavy metals
creating that variety of OCD
the reason why the obsessive thought
shifter works is because a spirit of
compassion knew what to put together to
give somebody that instant relief to
re-route that electricity inside the
brain
so that someone can get relief until
they can do like get the medals out
until they can do other medical medium
tools
so the obsessive thought shifter is
geared for somebody struggling with
obsessive thoughts whether they have a
severe case of OCD where they're at they
have to be compelled to act
on what their repetitive thoughts are
because that's serious heavy metal heavy
metal toxicity
so the obsessive thought shifter
what that does is it rewires electricity
so that it can drive down to different
neurons
and get away from that spot for the
moment to break the obsessive thoughts
that's how critical this is that's how
important this is really
so
when it comes down to it
keep this in mind you may have you may
not have toxic heavy metals but you have
obsessive thoughts in general you've
been hurt emotionally
so that happens to a lot of people
where they have some kind of emotional
trauma to break up a relationship a
divorce or some kind of struggle or an
emotional confrontation or something has
happened to them or something like you
know a fire broke out or something
happened where they were traumatized
whatever it is anything we go through
on the smallest level to largest level
emotional injuries occur in blood
vessels and neurons inside the brain
and with the obsessive thought shifter
does is it's there
to actually heal blood vessels to an
emotional Center centers of the brain
help them heal and then reroute
electricity too so more healing can
happen which is even incredible
rise of Melton says I had a few of the
OCD shots the past few days and I
noticed I was able to stop the OCD
thoughts
that's how powerful it is so proud of
you by the way Bernadette says my
dizziness got instantly better
and went almost away after just a few
shots it's unbelievable and by the way
these shots they're healing what I what
what is said that Spirit of compassion
said in the books what I wrote down in
the books they're healing
but they they do heal other things too
with it that are connected which is
which is really incredible
Judy says my face always tingles after
the shots and so does mine
so does mine some people their face
doesn't tingle after the shots my face
might I get tingles when I do the brain
shot Therapies
so um
here with Marie said I think she had a
comment there too I'll read so so many
things are happening when we do the the
brain shot therapies so many things that
are healing so let me read on a little
bit
Patricia says hello I'm so happy I did
last night with my husband you say he
did a brain shot he does not believe but
he felt a big change he doesn't have to
believe
in the shifters
right and the exposure shots and the
stabilizer shots he doesn't have to
believe in medical medium he doesn't
have to believe in me
doesn't have to have any any faith in me
or believe that I have anything to offer
but when
he does the shots he's gonna feel it
when you do the shots you'll feel it
see here's a question here a comment we
already tried this shot and it is so
delicious and it works I felt then much
better much more energy than ever
and what's incredible is if you like the
taste of the shot it's it's a plus
remember with Spirit of compassion I
said it's Spirit compassion No One's
Gonna like the taste of these shots
I remember writing them down I was
sitting at my desk I was like
I was like sfc No One's Gonna like the
taste or flavors of these shots these
are not put together for fun these are
not put together for taste
Spirit of compassion said they're not
supposed to be for fun and taste if you
have fun doing them if you have fun
drinking them then that's an added Plus
they're to work that means someone might
not like the flavor someone might think
it's okay someone might think it's me
oat mediocre someone might think it's
absolutely disgusting and someone might
think it tastes great
but it's not there for the delicious
thing about it the delicious part about
it like the concoctions are made to be
flavorable and fun right that's not what
it is this is about medicine from above
medicinals from above fixing and
rewiring actual brain problems real
problems with the brain and nervous
system
and that's what it was about so it's not
about how good they taste but if they
taste good to you for I'm going to just
be straight out here some of them I just
don't like the flavor
but I like what it does
but I don't like the flavor like I
I did a couple of them and I was like
but yeah I like what it's doing for me
does the mm obsessive shot help with
obsessive actions as well
yes it does
it does and stories are coming through
about that all over the place for sure
it's really incredible
so let me read a little bit about what's
happening in here so this is so
important
when we go through an upsetting or
traumatizing experience we can
experience physical injuries in the
emotional centers of the brain from the
intense heat generated that's the thing
something happens he is generating brain
heat our heat our brain starts to burn
up
it does
when we're showing emotions on the
outside or not you don't even have to be
reacting you could be so pissed off or
upset and internally you feel it and
your brain is heating up and that's the
thing that burning and heating confuse
brain tissue right that's what happens
and then we get in trouble we have all
kinds of different emotional symptoms
and other symptoms
these brain wounds can then influence
how we think feel and behave and that's
another thing when we get injured
emotionally then these wounds in the
brain can actually alter how we think
behave and feel this I'm reading you
guys right out of the brain saver books
I hope you have one get one as soon as
you can
here's a section right here scorched
brain tissue scorched brain tissue
for example when you're lying in bed
fixated on something hurtful someone
said or some misjustice that occurred
that was out of your control or a hurt
you experience from betrayal in a
relationship and the hurt feels
impossible to resolve so it takes over
your mind and dominates your thoughts
so if there's been some kind of
misjustice it could be small in your
life but it could dominate your thoughts
and take over and then the brain heat
happens
Kendra says my body craves these juices
shot shots but I don't have an intense
reaction like other people report am I
doing something wrong I feel more so
than I am getting slightly better long
term with each shot and my appetite has
decreased but I do not have a strong or
immediate relief thank you so much for
all you do
so Kendra so what you're doing is you
are experiencing some some symptom
relief or you're experiencing
improvements so that's what's happening
right there you said you feel you feel
more as you're getting slightly better
long term with the shots and that's
incredible but that's what you needed
and that's what was happening in your
body for you to have but keep in mind
they surprise you so you can be in the
the trajectory of actually just getting
better like you're doing or you've got
this longer term getting better each
shot so every time you have a shot
you're getting better and your appetite
has decreased so you're getting better
in all these ways appetite decreasing is
a good one so as you're doing that all
of a sudden a surprise comes
when you do another shot and then you
start feeling it in different ways so
things are going to happen along the way
in different on different levels plus
which shot are you using it's the same
shot all the time are you trying some
different shots too so keep up the good
work keep on doing that healing keep on
moving forward that's incredible
so
let's go into a little bit more about
how this works the electrical patterns
in your brain don't just swirl around
your entire brain and circulate
part of your brain's electrical patterns
can actually lose circulation because
the hurt that occurred has become such a
singular Focus that it is driven in
pinpointed electricity into a specific
area this is the most one of the most
profound things the information in the
brain saver books is just mind-blowing
so listen to what this was
when you have some kind of experience
your electricity doesn't just FL free
flow everywhere in your brain
when you're having some type of
emotional upheaval or experience the
electricity gets pinpointed to a
specific area in the emotional center of
the brain and it keeps on hitting there
because your neurons where you've been
hurt is where that electricity is being
driven this is Advanced original medical
medium information this isn't from some
Neuroscience crap or some telomere crap
or something out there because there is
nothing out there that is like this the
information of these books is new to the
world unique and extremely Advanced it's
decades and decades ahead of time it
could be a hundred years or more ahead
of science research
Rhonda says it's a relief to know there
is a reason for my difficulties
and that I am not just broken it gives
me hope you're not broken
you're not broken
no way
no there's real reasons why we go
through what we go through There's real
reasons to what happens in our brain
real problems that happen in here
physically
so here's what goes on if you have any
kind of emotional hardship on any level
you get burnt tissue because electricity
is pinpointing to that area where the
neurons are in that emotional section
so if you had really bad relationships
there's a certain area of the brain
where that is located hurt from
relationships is in a certain area of
the emotional center of the brain that
means electricity in that area
only circulated in that area really
pinpointing and driving into that area
because it hurt was so bad from that
emotional hurt
and so there we get the injury
and it needs to be healed
part of your brain's electrical patterns
can actually lose circulation because
the hurt that occurred has become a
singular Focus directly pinpointing one
area of the emotional center of the
brain
it can feel impossible to keep your mind
distracted with other thoughts in this
situation you've been hurt it's
impossible to break the thought pattern
if you went to the store and the cashier
made a mistake an honest mistake and
they
you know typed in a few extra dollars
for something that wasn't in your
grocery bag or something like that and
you figured it out and was like oh my
god
um there's 20 extra dollars that I
didn't get in here that I had to pay for
but where are my apples and where I'm or
whatever you're gonna actually focus on
it it's gonna then keep on circulating
to that area of the brain and it's going
to pinpoint that section it's going to
become obsessive
you guys are not saying neurosciences is
crap out there I'm just letting you know
okay I know a lot of you guys are like
you come here and you're like wait a
minute I've always said neurosurgeons
which I know an incredible neurosurgeon
I always said that brain surgeons are
needed there's a lot of incredible
doctors out there there's a lot of
incredible scientists but what happens
is that if you've been sick long enough
you know the answers aren't there
I'm just being honest about that I can't
lie and say the answers are there
I can't lie to you and say that your
20th neurologist is going to have an
answer for your OCD
or for your bipolar or for your
depersonalization or depression or
anxiety
I can't say that Neuroscience figured
out why someone has depression because
they haven't I can't lie and make up and
stick up for neuroscience
I can't stand here and lie to your faces
and pretend that Neuroscience figured
out why people have Alzheimer's when
they didn't
and I can't lie to your faces and sit
here and tell you that Neuroscience has
all the answers
to why someone's suffering from
schizophrenia from Mania from psychosis
from Neurosis to depersonalization to
like crippling anxiety to all kinds I
can't I can't lie to you what am I am I
supposed to am I supposed to stick up
for Neuroscience when they don't have
the answers all the clinics don't have
the answers but guess what's crazy
is that Neuroscience takes information
from these books and then they take it
that's what's crazy medical medium was
the only place that said Alzheimer's is
caused by toxic heavy metals and now
Neuroscience is starting to kind of talk
about that a little but they have no
papers or research to Showcase they got
it from published material
science has taken the multiple sclerosis
information from me that I published
years ago about Epstein-Barr the point
is is that what am I supposed to do I
know that somebody got upset about the
Neuroscience comment but am I supposed
to sit here and pretend Neuroscience has
all the answers and lie to you that's
insane that's actually demented
I published in great details out there
about what happened with MS and
Epstein-Barr and great details about
Alzheimer's and toxic heavy metals and
science doesn't have any of that to
offer out there but it's here and it
gets poached and you guys know that but
I know that somebody got upset about the
Neuroscience thing and it breaks my
heart because I'm
I know that when someone's really sick
and they and they're going to
neurologists and they're getting their
50th MRI on their brain and they're on
all these antidepressants and they're
suffering that there's no answers out
there and a telomere a telomere theory
is not going to fix them
schizophrenia Mania depression anxiety
OCD Eating Disorders they're all in the
brain saver books right here with
detailed information so that you know
what to do but the painful thing is am I
supposed to just lie and so you guys
Neuroscience has it all sewed up they
have all the answers out there go to
your best clinic and they'll have all
the answers are you kidding I can't do
that I can't lie to your faces like that
so I have to be honest and if it and
that Honesty hurts you
I don't know what to do I I don't know
what to do I would take one of these
brain shots if the honesty hurts you I'd
go and take one of these brain shots
you'll see there's 30 shots
Robin said Robinson said no the truth is
important and it's true they don't have
the answers
they don't and you know what I noticed
is even the theorists all the you know
the people that are theorizing about
Neuroscience beliefs where they're just
like talking about all this grandioso
ideas about neuroscience and people's
thought patterns and stuff where does
that get anybody when
does that get anybody
when your child's suffering went from
crippling OCD or a mom is suffering from
crippling depression where does that get
anybody I I don't understand we need
answers we need things we need answers
now and it's critical
Bree says do I follow yes they do my I
follow my father regularly to the
neurologist for his Parkinson's and he
can never give my father an answer
well the thing is they don't have
answers for Parkinson's but Parkinson's
answers are in the brand saver books and
we have to do something now we have to
change lives we have to get people
better so I'm sorry I'm sorry you guys
anybody out there that got hurt if I say
Neuroscience is crap I get it it
probably sounds I get it I sound
probably I don't know sarcastic and and
too you know I sound like ridiculous
saying it that way and and the irony is
I know really good brain surgeon can
really help with somebody's aneurysm and
and it depending on where it is in the
brain they could only do so much brain
surgeons they can only touch upon the
outside of the brain a little bit they
can't do too much but the point is it
saves lives like good brain surgeon save
lives car injuries and stuff like that
all kinds of stuff car accidents but I'm
talking about all the mystery stuff
and I'm talking about all the millions
and millions of people actually the
billions on this planet that can't even
function because of their brain fog's
really bad and the depression anxiety is
so bad
and
I get it I would probably not have the
right to say that Neuroscience is crap
if people didn't heal already from all
the amazing books from from above the
medical lean books so I want to read a
little bit more if you guys got a second
so
so here's an important point right here
all on its own it can feel impossible to
keep your mind distracted when our
thoughts are just taking over right to
Simply change your brain's electrical
patterns back to normal circulation
because the emotional injury has been so
shocking so it's hard to switch gears
right it's like I got this emotional
blow I'm going to try to go outside and
walk it off my boyfriend broke up with
me and I'm going to try to get on the
treadmill and do a really good workout
my you know girlfriend broke up with me
so I'm gonna go to the gym with the boys
and just try to push some weights you
know my whatever my doctor told me this
something ridiculous I feel hopeless so
I'm gonna go and buy an ice cream
somewhere and try to break my thoughts
like whatever happens like all of us do
different things right whatever happens
it's hard to break those thought
patterns when we're hurt in some way
so that hurtful experience can become an
obsessive cycle that can replay over and
over and over again in your mind
and then cauterization occurs from the
intense heat generated in one area
and that's why we get in trouble this
intense heat generates in one area and
then we're stuck and then we got the
obsessive thoughts and then we got the
emotional hurt
and then we're in a difficult situation
we can have a little bit of depression
we can have depersonalization we can
have it all and then we can have that
emotional injury that no one understands
that no doctor understands and no
scientist understands and no drug
company understands and we just don't
know what to do and we're stuck but
we're getting out of that Inky says yes
they fixed my aneurysm but mm fixed my
crippling anxiety because the experts
had no answers incredible I'm so glad
you're here and that's so true because
and I'm so glad that that you're getting
answers and I'm so glad that yes
conventional exactly fixture your
aneurysm and I know brain surgeons like
I said one particular that actually does
a good job with that let's see my
neurologist didn't have any answers all
they did was put me on meds when I said
how do I get off these meds they said
try try taking you off and see if you
think the comment went up see if you get
better
um and if not we'll up your dose that's
what the answer is the comment so that's
incredible I've heard that so many times
where they don't have an answer to why
you're suffering or struggling and then
they say Hey you know take these meds
okay we can lower the dosage and see and
then up the dosage and say
I tried weaning myself off meds without
my doctor's permission symptoms didn't
change until I started implementing
medical meaning protocols have been off
pills for one and a half years
symptom-free incredible
absolutely incredible and the amazing
thing is I don't see that other places
I don't I don't see that out there I see
top five things you can do for your
brain health top five things you can do
for this it's like but there's no
answers
and that's we need to change that and we
did intermission a little bit
who wants to do the robot with me
come on enough of this nonsense
enough of this BS let's go
[Music]
I'm getting ready to make this brain
shot
[Music]
what is going on
all right
try that holding your breath the whole
time
okay guys I'm excited all right
so we're gonna start doing it let's keep
on going
so I'm going to 5 20 Page 520.
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanses that's where we are
all right you guys
these cleanses are imperative to what's
happening right now in the world we're
getting exposures we're getting all
kinds of chemical warfare upon us in our
schools our homes institutions Society
society today it's getting the
pesticides
right insecticides fungicides said to
candles air fresheners all the stuff we
get
when you embark on these cleanse options
you're using your free will and
intention to heal see I can't make you
do a brain shot I can't say do that
brain shot
I can't make you do it
I can't say
fix the problem take the brain shot
therapy it takes your free will
someone can stand there because I've had
this happen I've told like a friend of a
friend to be like make sure you do this
make sure you do this brain shot therapy
make sure you do this one and they're
like what
what
I don't know
I don't know if I want to do that brain
shot
it's your free will it's your intention
to want to heal that's a big part of it
all
because it's you it's you using your
free will and your intention to project
anything out of your brain that
shouldn't be there to rewire your brain
as well so it's your intentions your
free will to rewire the brain that's
critical that matters right and here's
the incredible thing your brain Harbors
Knowledge from the past your brain
that's incredible your brain Harbors
Knowledge from the present Knowledge
from the past your brain will Harbor
Knowledge from the future too and you
you tap into your intuitive psychic
telepathic Clairvoyant skills and I've
been saying that over and over again for
a reason the brain shot Therapies
help you tap into that making that
stronger so you make good decisions in
your life so you use your free will and
your intentions to make better decisions
in your life do you ever have that
situation you're like why did I do that
why did I make that decision what was I
thinking about
what was I thinking why did I do that
did you ever have that happen right
ever like that happens to a lot of
people it's like why did I do that oh my
God what was I thinking
well you know what happens here like I
don't know if that was a good decision I
don't know what what happens is when
you're doing the brain shot therapy
cleanses
you're tapping into your intuitive
you're psychic your telepathic your
Clairvoyant powers that everybody has
deep inside you're igniting that and
you're projecting the crap out of your
brain that shouldn't be there and you're
rewiring the electricity how incredible
is this and it matters
so
let's go what are we doing here we're
doing the obsessive thought shifter
show you which one
and we're going this page four
72 right here because we're in the
shifter shot so here's how it works
there's exposure shot stabilizer shots
and shifter shots we are in the shifters
what I love about the shifters is they
got a power to them that's different
than than say the exposures when you do
an exposure shot you feel the immediate
relief but it's something different that
happens inside our brain so the reason
why they're classified Spirit of
compassion told me originally they do
different instant relief fixes they do
different it's a different way the brain
heals so we're in the shifters obsessive
thoughts shifter so that's an entirely
different classification to help our
brain heal
we were doing a stabilizer yesterday
betrayal and broken trust stabilizer
so you have the exposures the 10
exposures that Spirit of compassion gave
me the 10 stabilizers and the 10
shifters
so but I find that the shifters have
their own way of working just like the
stabilizers have their own way of
working and just like the exposures have
their own way of working
the world is getting so complicated in
so many ways and we're being pushed in
so many different directions do you guys
agree
is that is that just Spirit of
compassions
like thought on that or do you guys
agree I I mean you guys don't have to
agree but the world is getting so
complicated in so many ways and we're
being pushed in so many different
directions it's easy to get confused or
stuck in a pattern that is not helpful
to the healing process and that's easy
right now this world is a brain screw
right now and it can throw us into
getting stuck into a pattern because
this world is such a brain screw
and I'm not trying to pull that like
thing where you got that really really
old guy that's like
back in my day when I was young I had to
walk through the snow barefooted five
miles to get to the school when I got
there the school teacher could stick a
dunce hat on my head and smacked my
wrist with a ruler and made me skip my
lunch
and then I had to walk five miles back
barefooted and all the ice
and that's what I used to have to do
right I'm not saying that you know
it's just it but the world has
definitely changed for real it's got
complicated so we get pushed in so many
different directions it's easy to get
stuck in a pattern this is how people
get stuck into so many patterns
okay so it's easy to get confused right
these brain shots are designed to help
shift
it's a shifter these brain shots are
designed to help shift our Direction so
our body can shift and heal and our
emotional frame of mind can break a
pattern
of confinement
so here's how it works you got OCD you
got obsessive thoughts you have anything
like that when you do this obsessive
thought shifter it's breaking a pattern
and it will reduce triggers so if you're
somebody with OCD you'll get triggered
less into an OCD pattern you see how it
works you actually get triggered less
into an OCD pattern
how powerful is that
that's that's just it's mind-blowing
really
so we're doing the obsessive thought
shifter that's where we are right now
so let's get into it a little bit
you guys when you think about it
when you think about it
if we have the ability if we have a
if we have an ability
to break a pattern that we've been stuck
with
it's it's a miracle so what I call these
brain shot therapy cleanses I call them
Miracles I call these brain shots
miracles
and that's a big part of like all of it
when you think about it like whoa It's
like a miracle just happened how is this
possible it's possible because it's
information from above now with the
obsessive thought shifter there's a few
words in here before we get started
we're about to make it
try this shot when you're trying to
break repeated painful thought patterns
resulting from a difficult situation or
hardship you had some type of
Confrontation some kind of difficult
situation
something's creeping up from the past
that's bothering you something you feel
like you know you you're stuck with
thinking and you're thinking about and
thinking over and over again you can
definitely use a Shot For This
here's another one too you experience
chronic OCD or you're going through a
relapse or heightening of OCD symptoms
so if you're somebody and you're having
a relapse or a heightened sense of OCD
where your OCD got triggered again and
now you're you're really struggling with
that OCD it's time to use this brain
shot
this brain shot covers all forms and
varieties of OCD how about this one I
know that this one is not a big deal and
I get it because I was saying this the
other day and it's not that big of a
deal if you're stuck with a song playing
in your head but let me tell you guys
something I heard a song the other day
that drove me bat crazy right it
was in my head it was a song that I
liked like 20 years ago I liked it for
five seconds and then it got stuck in my
head and I was trying to get work done
Spirit of compassion was talking to me
and I was like I had the song playing in
my head while I was trying to work
and I don't know about you but the song
playing in my head thing that's I I just
took out I took out the juicer I just
said that's it I took out the mm 1500
and I was just like I'm making this
obsessive thoughts
so repetitive thoughts that are
disturbing you continue to play
repetitive thoughts that disturb you in
any way that continue to repeat and
replay
or repetitive thoughts that are causing
you to make repetitive decisions and
actions so it's like whoa this
repetitive thought is making me actually
do an action
here's one right here you're hearing
voices in your head or experiencing
thoughts that are upsetting
unproductive so you're trying to fall
asleep and you're just healing you're
hearing yourself even yourself talk
and you just want to just go to sleep
and you just want to not be involved
and then there's a memory of a past
experience keeps Rising it could be an
experience that happened last week
that's a past experience it could be an
experience that happened a month ago
experience that happened a year ago 20
years ago and now it's creeping up and
what happens is a lot of us we have
experiences that happen in our life and
they creep up years later and how do you
break it now you're seeing counselors
and therapists
a memory of a past experience keeps
arising in your mind and it's not
helpful to keep thinking about it you
got to get the obsessive thought shifter
out and slam them down
Krista says and the songs never stop
every word triggers a new song it's hard
to think I'm serious that happens to me
like I was in the car
with a friend and they turned on the
radio and I was like don't turn on the
radio right now just they turned it on
and this really dumb song came on
and it was like that was it I was like
thanks I really appreciate it I told my
friend thank you very much because now
I'm going to be dealing with that song
Until I do these success thought shifter
so here we are let's get into this a
little bit
you guys I'm gonna get the mm 1500 out
here
so you guys the mn1500 is on sale just
so you know it's my favorite because
it's 20 it's 20 off but it's my favorite
because of what it does so it's
extraction method is just remarkable I
don't think anything touches it out
there so it saves me money when I juice
so it squeezes out everything and what
the deal is when you get it when you
have a juicer and you can use any juicer
for this but when you have a juicer that
squeezes everything out
you're getting all the phytochemical
compounds that make the shot like that
make it work really strong and that's
another thing too
if someone's like you know well I did it
but I'm not really getting the best
results did they use a blender what did
they do all of it and you guys know I
work with
Omega on the mm 1500 900 but the reason
why I work with them is because of what
it does it's got that celery end cap on
here it's got the compression and so it
saves me money because I'm always buying
less produce and I'm doing these shots
I'm buying less produce I do my celery
juice every day I buy less celery
because it's squeezing so much out that
you're not throwing away that juice
extraction you're not throwing it away
so that's where you know why I really
love it it's quiet there's like a bunch
of reasons it doesn't have the metal
gears rubbing all that stuff I just love
the machine it saves others money it
saves families money and all that it's
like incredible because it does what it
does and it's 20 off right now mm 1500
just so you know if that's if you're
looking for a juicer if you've got a
juicer use a juicer you're you have
all right I'm excited about this
actually
let's go one radish
we got the radish right here
what I'm gonna do is cut that radish in
a couple of pieces and send it down
you guys making it with me right now
radish is first
I got my radish right there
now if you got a small radish use a
small radish I think this radish was
actually a pretty decent size
seeing bigger radishes but
get the radish in there the other one's
eighth cup Loosely packed fresh Sage
eighth of a cup
of loosely packed fresh Sage
so I'm gonna get some Sage leaves off of
here
eighth of a cup
crunching them down in my hands because
I got a measuring cup in my hand that's
how I do it there we go
all right send it down in here
next one is a half of Apple of course
you can do one apple it depends on the
size of your Apple tip you got a really
large Apple
do a half of Apple if you got a small
apple that's a small one there
you can just do a small apple
so let's go this is a small apple right
there
so half of Apple
you'll do one apple if you want
I'm gonna do like three quarters of this
apple it's a little bigger it's not that
small of an apple
there we go
and then one stalk of celery
[Applause]
try to do them in order if you can to
the ingredient list in the book
foreign
there's my shot
[Music]
if you've been doing these lately you
know the feeling you get before you do
them right
it's a feeling that you know something
good is gonna happen
because you know they work
and if you've tried them and you know
they were you can feel
what's in your hand the energy
the light
The Light Within the books The Light
Within the ingredients The Light Within
the shot when they're mixed is that
information comes from above to how this
works it's about it being
synergistically combined just right
science could never figure that out
because they wouldn't know it comes from
above that's the whole point it's not
man-made anymore and when it comes down
to Healing we need help we need extra
help because you see what's happening
down here on Earth
you really do and if we don't get extra
help how are people going to get better
[Music]
to get the tingles
a little bit of tingles I'm one of those
right because some of you guys get that
too
[Applause]
oh it just hit
it took the second sip do you feel that
[Music]
it took the second sip
foreign
[Music]
bartender
give me another
I'm telling you do you guys feel that
and it only happens when these four are
put together just like this in the right
way in the right order
ing says yes hickey like that too on the
second sip it hit me
it's incredible
you guys have you tried this brain shot
what did you feel please share your
experiences okay tag at Medical medium
medical medium and when you talk about
the brain shots put medical medium in
front of the medical medium brain shot
therapy medical medium obsessive thought
shifter medical medium betrayal and
broken trust stabilizers so that people
know where to find their way back so
they can get the real shot with the real
ingredients and everything if you can
and one more thing to you guys can you
sign up to my Dr Nesbit account please
can you sign up to Dr Nesbit account
because on tick tock on tick tock that
would be great if you sign up to Dr
Nesbitt account on tick tock
if you sign up there because you guys
know like
you know what it is is I want to go live
on Dr nesbitt's Tick Tock account but I
can't until I get enough people to sign
up and Dr Nesbit actually gave me
permission to use his Tick Tock account
so I can go live once again on Tick Tock
is that right Dr Nesbitt says that he
had the obsessive thought shifter after
he did surgery on a patient he says he
wished he did the obsessive thought
shifter before he worked on the patient
really he said he had a bad song playing
in his head when he did surgery on a
patient and he wished he used it before
he thinks it did not help
you guys I'm actually updating my
website constantly I'm making it an
incredible place to be with information
like you can't believe in recipes and
everything else like you name it I'm
doing it on the medical medium.com
website look out and we're going to be
doing those light blasts all of that
stuff is going to be coming so you want
to be signed on to the medical medium
email list right so you can sign up to
the newsletter get the newsletters all
of that
you guys check out the mm1500 when you
get a chance
um an incredible juicer for the shots if
you're looking for a juicer but listen
just know this though that I I can't
believe how I feel when I take the
obsessive thoughts shifter it hit me on
the second Sip and it did like did you
guys feel that Lorraine said it hit her
on the second sip too wasn't that crazy
Lorraine right it was just crazy how it
hits you it hits you on the seconds it
hit me on the second sip absolutely
amazing I can't even express how it
feels to be using medicine like this oh
my God it's just absolutely incredible
tomorrow is day four of the medical
medium brain shot therapy cleanse day
four and guess what we're doing
the EMF and 5G exposure shot
EMF and 5G exposure shot
we're doing that tomorrow on day four
can you believe it it's going to be
incredible you don't know 5G and EMF
could be bothering you maybe it's not
we'll find out we're doing the EMF in 5G
brain shot therapy tomorrow day four oh
my God and by the way one last thing a
couple last things you guys I'm doing
exclusive telegram messages
I've been doing a lot of them and we're
going to be consistently doing a lot of
those close heart-to-heart messages you
know I I um it's a certain time I do
them when I'm in a certain frame of mind
after I'm taking a break in work for a
little bit for that moment and then I go
and I I grab the phone and I'm like you
know what I got to do a telegram message
so sign up to my telegram when you can
please get on there because I want you
to hear those messages
um and so yeah it's exciting but
tomorrow's EMF and 5G exposure shot
we're hitting the exposures tomorrow is
what we're hitting and that's incredible
I feel that shot it's really amazing
hey you guys want to do the robot with
me let's go
[Music]
the robot foreign
what am I doing
this is shots
[Music]
you guys
I bet you guys are getting really good
on the robot
it's incredible I'll see you guys
can't