we're live right now day three medical
medium anti-bug cleanse challenge
have you guys done level five cause i
know so many of you guys are on level
five we're live on tick tock we're live
on telegram
i love the private messages i'm doing on
telegram that's so cool we're live on
youtube
we're live on rumble
how do you like that incredible you guys
i think we're live on facebook too
making the potato and herb stuffed
peppers okay
so this is what it looks like so
everybody knows
there it is potato herb stuffed peppers
right out of cleanse the heel you guys
see on telegram okay
there we go you guys on rumble
so i'm in cleanse the heel right here
life saving book do you guys have the
book have you read the book more than
once because what happens is when people
read the book once they miss so many
incredible pieces of information
and then they have to actually then read
it again and like whoa where was that
how was that there's over 200 symptoms
and conditions and the causes of those
conditions because when you're looking
for help it's like why am i sick
like
what's wrong with me why do i have fibro
why do i have autoimmune how come my ana
is up like why am i getting an
autoimmune diagnosis whatever that
autoimmune diagnosis is right why do i
have crippling anxiety why do i have
depression answers they're priceless
they're priceless because that's the
whole point all those years of people
going to doctors but not getting an
answer
we need doctors we need doctors and they
do a lot of great things but we also
have this chronic mystery illness out
there
and it encompasses like autoimmune in
every aspect of that hundreds of
diagnoses and symptoms to that
autoimmune that diagnosis right so
whether it's a thyroid problem or
anything else so we need to also have
answers and answers are critical because
we could see doctors for 10 years we
could see doctors for 15 years we could
see we can we can just be on that
treadmill of doctors and that's fine
that's fine of course we've got to see
doctors right
but
critical information is in here right
protecting you and giving you answers so
you could bring them to your doctors be
like hey you know i think i have an
answer to why i'm sick because i know
you don't have an answer
here at the doctor's office so since you
don't know why i have lupus and you
don't know why i have crippling anxiety
and you don't know why i have eczema i
actually found the answers and guess
what people are getting their lives back
by following protocols in medical medium
cleanse the heal so it's not an insult
to the doctors it's like hey by the way
um
um doctor so and so uh uh i found an
answer from my eczema and no one else
has that answer so i think i'm gonna
start working on this is this okay and
you know that's what's incredible about
the book anyway 51 off at 16.99
amazon.com right us
pick up the book when you can right it's
a medical textbook it costs more to
print it i know i say that i know i
sound like a broken record it costs more
print it costs more to print it
it costs more print but it does
make sure you get one or get one free at
the library right get a copy free of the
library and that's perfectly fine we're
day three of the anti-bug cleanse you
guys are making the potato and herb
stuffed peppers boom
i'm making those i hope i make them
right that's all i can say
yuna says uda says you were the only one
who give give me gave me the answers
it counts so much you guys i got a quick
announcement
okay so i'm going to be talking about
essential oils
later today 6 15 eastern 3 15 pacific on
rumble
only so i'll be on rumble only just so
you know it's gonna be part two talking
about essential oils i'm gonna answer a
lot of questions that that cropped up
is does an essential oil evaporate right
does it have these terpenes in them like
how does that work okay why are you
talking about mold and essential oils
and how come you're mentioning things
like that and i left a private message i
want you guys any anybody on facebook or
anybody
anywhere else you guys ticktock or
whatever
go to
the telegram page right and listen to my
private message today so it's t dot m e
forward slash medical medium that's me
on telegram listen to the private
message
so you can hear what i was talking about
because i i left a private message on
telegram
talking about what i was a little bit
about what i'm talking about tonight at
6 15 eastern 315 pacific gonna talk
about the essential oils what's
happening with that so it's really an
important important small episode don't
miss it later today
and i would i would um subscribe to
rumble.com go to rubble.com forward
slash medical medium so this is all
important information right
uh jamie says get ready to rumble
right so anyway
make sure you have a book because the
anti-bug cleanses in here and we're
doing this recipe
so i think what i'll do is i'll start
making the recipe and we'll start
talking about the cleanse let's have a
little fun
right
let's do that i got my spicy hot apple
juice or spiced
hot apple juice right it's really really
good and
i've been getting into it
i'm excited about that so i got about
roughly about two pounds or more
potatoes right here so these are steamed
potatoes i cut them in half
but they're steamed potatoes so i'm
going to be stuffing the peppers i want
to get them in the oven so we can get
down to business
that's what i want to do
so
i'm removing some of the skins not
because you're supposed to
you can keep them on
they're good for you more than good for
you i'm just pulling some of the skins
off because
of the look right
it's the look i'm going for in this
recipe of course you can keep them on
and i'll keep a lot of the skins on
right
i'll do that but i'm just taking some of
the skins back so i'm looking for a
special kind of like stuffing look in
the middle of the pepper so i'm just
taking some of the skins back a little
bit i'm not taking them all off right
so i'm going through these these are
steamed potatoes right here
you know i was talking about on the
telegram message
how
i don't know why
i have to be the only one
to release
never before heard information
that's life-saving life protecting
remember the blood draw problem
everybody getting too much blood taken i
was the first to bring that information
out there reactivated epstein-barr
first to bring that information out
there so people can know what's wrong
with them so they could actually start
getting help right
long haul covet
right
uh being reactivated epstein-barr i was
the first to put that information out
there okay
i was the first to put the information
out there that you're not creating your
illness with your thoughts meaning that
that's not why you're sick like you're
not just somebody who somehow is
imagining your condition and your
symptoms because medical medical
research and science and both
alternative medicine conventional
medicine doesn't know why anybody's sick
so they came up with a lot of theories
and one theory was you're creating it
with your mind
so you just need to rewire
so you're sick with your hashimoto's and
your lupus and your multiple sclerosis
because you're creating it
it's all in your head right the you know
alternative medicine
all the spiritual medicine right so i
was the first to break the news that
that's not correct
right
first to break the news about all the
air fresheners
all the air fresheners poisoning
everybody
first to break the news about
staying the hell away from dental
amalgams that have mercury in them
i remember in the in the early 1980s i
was shouting it out in the mid-1980s i
was shouting at it everywhere and people
were just livid
angry as
bees like you just hit a beehive so when
i started out getting out there and
lecturing and going on the circuit
saying no you can't put the amalgams the
mercury amalgams in you can't do that
anymore people thought i was like an
alien from another planet with 10 heads
and i took a lot of for that man
that was a tough one
so i don't know why i have to be the one
to do all this
but i guess that's just my
curse or burden i could keep it going
all day on that why do i have to be the
one to let everybody know that
chickenpox is not the shingles they're
two separate viruses
you still see tv commercials if you had
the chickenpox you also have the
shingles they're the same virus
make sure you get the shingles
medication from our pharmaceutical
company
if you had the chickenpox you are going
to have the shingles first of all
they're two separate viruses and people
have both of them
they're two separate viruses but why do
i have to be the one to to break that to
the whole world
the best medical clinics the best
doctors don't know it
i have to be the one to break that out
because i'm confused about that when i'm
scratching my head about that one
all right so i'm just peeling some of
these skins back because i'm going to
mash these potatoes
i could make it a whole episode on how
i'm the first to put this out
i could make it a whole episode but i
don't want to
the point is is the essential oil thing
has gotten a little out of control so
on rumble
i'm going to talk about why and get down
to the nitty-gritty in the details about
it i want to answer questions i want
people to know
more information about it so they
understand okay and
so um
we're going to just bust all that out
later it's going to be 6 15 eastern 3 15
pacific make sure you subscribe to
rumble 2. i'm not censored on rubble
rumble i'm censored on facebook
that's why with my 3.6 million followers
there's only like 400 people on facebook
watching
when there used to be 6 000 7 000
when i would went back four years ago
[Laughter]
so um
yeah so just just so you know but i'm
not i'm not
censored
on uh rumble i'm not censored on
telegram
i'm censored on tick-tock
censored on tick-tock
but anyway i'm not censored on me we so
it's me we rumble and telegram
incredible platforms
incredible to be uncensored there and my
podcast on believe it or not medical
media podcast at apple podcast isn't
centered
okay that's not
although
some things i want to say about that
anyway
so anyway look telegram which is you
look look subscribe to me on telegram
which is t dot m e forward slash medical
medium
right
so i just peeled back some of these
skins we're making the potato and herb
stuffed peppers were day three of the
anti-bug cleanse if you just got on here
we're making this
just to kind of get you in the loop
right we're in the anti-bug cleanse
with cleanse the heel i hope you have
the book i really do so if you're
somebody that doesn't have the book
consider it
because when you get the book it's there
as that protective measure you can read
you can learn you can know why you're
sick i mean there's 75 recipes in here
that's just a couple of tidbits there's
so much in that book i couldn't even
cover it right now so
anyway i got some potatoes i'm gonna
mash them up
so let me get my little masher
right
that's what we're gonna do
get my little masher so
and i'm gonna do this
right
now i'm gonna add
some paprika in here into the
mixture paprika
put a little bit of that in here right
okay
look if you want to put a little bit
more then then then what's in the recipe
put a little bit more than what's in the
recipe there's some
onion powder right
a little bit of onion powder in here
and i'm gonna put a little bit of garlic
powder in here too
a little bit of garlic powder in there
right
that's good
i'm gonna mash it up a little bit
i'm gonna chop up some chives and throw
a little bit in there it's also to put
on top later
while they're in the oven
i'm just going to mash these up
so i'm glad everybody's here what level
have you guys decided to try on the
anti-bug cleanse did you do level one
are you staying away from eggs milk
cheese butter are you staying away from
dairy products are you staying away from
corn
are you on level two
are you staying away from soy and corn
and then all processed oils okay are you
on level three
right
where you're staying away from lamb
so which i mean i know a lot of people
don't eat lamb but you'd be surprised
it's the strangest thing they eat more
lamb than they do spinach
right all that misinformation
out there about oxilic oxalates and stay
away from
spinach that's misinformation out there
it's funny no one eats spinach they eat
lamb more than they eat spinach
it's like okay when's the last time you
had spinach two years ago when's the
last time you had lamb last night
what did you hear out there
so
check out the rumble
video
i did yesterday on essential oils okay
i'm gonna be doing a new one tonight
answering all the questions in a whole
bit let's keep that in mind
so what i have right here is
a mixture that i have of potatoes i'm
gonna stuff the peppers but let me get
some chives in here if you guys don't
mind i'm gonna chop up a little bit of
this
i have an oxalate video i just got
a little
tidbit of info i can it's popping up
i got an oxalate video
on rumble check out the oxalate video on
rumble that's an important one also to
look at i know a lot of people are in
oxalate fear
what happens is when someone says hey i
want to do a cleanse i want to do say
the anti-bug cleanse i want to get my
life back and all of a sudden they run
into all these walls and be like wait a
minute wait a minute wait a minute wait
a minute i can eat fruit oh no i have
fruit fear
oh wait um i can't eat that food uh
oxalates oh wait a minute i can't eat
that food on lectins how am i going to
do the cleanse if i can't eat anything
i'm like dude
those aren't these rolls
that's just a bunch of made up theory
stuff keep you from healing
you know why people don't heal
from all that kind of stuff all that
kind of misinformation there's tons of
it
out there
that's why people don't heal all the way
right they don't heal over wet
and the people that usually shout out
hey you should do this you should do
that they never got sick yet when they
get sick and they realize oh crap
whatever i've been telling everybody
ain't gonna get them better because i
finally got sick in my life and now i'm
doing what i've been telling people to
do and i'm getting sicker
so i just put some chives in here
so i'm mixing up the mixture
and now i'm gonna
cut up the peppers
there we go
so this is a mashed potato mixture with
paprika if you just got on here
garlic
onion powder right
that's what this is and i'm just getting
ready to stuff the pepper so that's the
mixture
boom we got it those are steamed
potatoes by the way
steamed potatoes
so what pepper do i want to pick in this
batch
i know a lot of you guys
are afraid of peppers right
that's an interesting pepper right there
a lot of you guys are afraid of peppers
okay
so i'm taking out the center of the
pepper
and then i'm cutting the pepper in half
all right and i'm going to stuff them
this way
that's how i'm going to stuff them like
that
but you can do another option too
you can just take the whole pepper and
you can stuff it
in the center if you wanted to that's an
option right there
okay
so
you can also do it this way too on this
recipe you can cut it in half
like that
right
you can scoop out
center
and now you got a nice boat
i like that i like that way
do you do it the way you feel like doing
though you know you could be really a
creative person really creative person
right
and you want to do it the way you want
to do it so i showed you a couple
different ways that's one way right
there you can fill these that way here's
another way where it's kind of like more
of a boat
all right
so let's do it that way let me grab
another pepper this is a nice big one
right here i'm gonna cut it down this
way
scoop these out you guys i'm stuffing
peppers
i got the oven on at 400.
so i'm excited we're live on tick tock
facebook youtube telegram
all right i'm gonna do a yellow pepper
you guys okay with that
and we're live on rumble
which i'm pumped up about
live on rumble
so i just took out the centers of these
peppers i made these nice pepper boats
let's start stuffing them
let's start doing that now so i'm going
to take the mixture
right
i'm going to start putting it into these
peppers like this i want to show you
guys
so i'm doing it like that
so
getting this mixture in here there's
chives in here there's some garlic
powder onion
powder i'm going to top them off too i'm
just
you know evenly doing this
so this is great
look do it the way
you want to do it too you can look at
the recipe like look i could do it this
way that's perfectly fine
this is where
you should be like your creative self
you know just like you are in so many
other
parts of your life of course always
being creative
that's good right there it's one pepper
that's two peppers let's pop another one
here
filling these up
look you guys if you're doing level one
you do level one if you're doing level
two you do level two in the anti-bug
cleanse if you're doing level three you
do level three every level
is great
every level is great now you're on day
three so you gotta remember bugs are
dying bugs are starting to fall apart
bugs are exploding bugs are imploding
from the inside out because they were so
used to eating whatever it was you were
feeding them
okay
they're so used to it
so i'm topping these off
because i i got some extra
so this is great
a friend of mine was making these and
said reminds me of stuffed clams
i was like really
yeah when i go to a fancy restaurant and
i order stuffed clams i'm like i don't
know if you should be ordering stuffed
clams in any restaurant
i don't know if that's a good thing to
do to eat
food poisoning anybody stuffed clams all
right
yeah it's all fine and dandy until you
get the worst food poisoning ever
okay so i'm gonna pop these on the sheet
just give me a second here
so you got a clean sheet over here
right let me bring this out
to you guys okay
so i'm going to lay these down
okay
[Music]
you can cook for 20 to 25 minutes you
might want to cook longer if you want to
brown them it depends on your oven
everybody's oven is different you might
have an oven that man that that oven's
crack just for some reason it just cooks
things quicker than somebody else's it
happens all the time i got it to 400
degrees i got the pepper stuffed are you
guys making it with me some of you
i'm over here by the oven i don't know
if you guys could see me rumble you can
probably see me right
kind of
popping these in
bam
boom
love it
incredible
all right
you got four categories
take notes if you want four categories
one category is bug fuel you're removing
bug fuel
you're removing the food that feeds the
bugs you're removing the fuel for the
bugs
what bugs pathogens viruses
even the flu virus loves to eat eat eat
eat eat eat
loves to eat the plague virus loves to
eat eat eat eat eat
these these these viruses explode inside
people's bodies because there's so much
food to eat
okay
but epstein bars that cause your thyroid
disorders your hypothyroidism your
hypothyroidism right your tinnitus
ringing the ear you're popping your
fluttering in your ears those are
popping fluttering that shouldn't be
happening your floater's in your eyes
all that the epstein bar right or your
jaw pain
your jaw pain your neck pain your
shingles virus your simplex one virus
your clenching teething your teeth
clenching jaw your you're grinding your
teeth at night when you're sleeping
you're supposed to be sleeping
instead you're like
grinding your teeth
okay shingles causing colitis how about
that sciatic pain bell's palsy if you
ever had that you're like people got
bugs in them they're loaded with bugs so
what you're doing is you're removing bug
fuel fuel that feeds the bugs you're
removing it so the bugs love to eat and
you're actually removing that food right
so
what you're doing
is if you're doing this you're removing
that food so there you go
you're moving those fried eggs how come
those eggs don't slide off the pan
you're removing those eggs that's a fuel
right there for the bugs what's in my
hand the bug right there
so we're doing this this is the first
this is like the first category there's
four categories you're removing fuel
from the bugs how awesome is that okay
so it's a great thing
all right
second category
you're removing blood thickeners
thickeners we're heading into a land of
blood clots out there in the world
uh-huh gonna build a lot of blood clots
i'm serious
micro blood clots
macro blood blood clots one seeable by
the doctors and some not so seeable by
the doctors blood clots blood clots
blood clots that's where the land is
going and heading so blood thickeners
we're removing blood thickeners that's a
part of the category of the anti-bug
cleanse i mean how incredible it is if
you guys just came on you've got to get
the book someday 51 off amazon.com us
you got to get the book get it free the
library if you want
all right so but incredible price okay
dehydrators now when i say dehydrators i
bet you some of you
are thinking food dehydrators food
dehydrators i make crackers i make my
raw crackers i got to get rid of my food
dehydrators no
no keep your food dehydrators if that's
what you got or want
right
no i'm talking about dehydrators to the
body we're getting rid of one of the
categories dehydrators to the body the
caffeine we're getting rid of that we're
getting rid of caffeine we're getting
rid of vinegars we're getting rid of
excess salt we're getting rid of the
body dehydrators the high fats which
dehydrate the blood right we're getting
rid of the dehydrators
that's important what the dehydrators do
is they stop you from getting nutrients
to your brain glucose to your brain
neurotransmitter chemicals you need to
your brain complete electrolytes full
electrolytes
then we're getting rid of the category
toxin contributors because now your diet
is not a toxin contributor think about
that your diet's not a contributor to
bringing toxins into your body
right
you're keeping the caffeine out which is
still a toxin too you're keeping that
one out you're keeping other things out
too so it's really important you're
keeping your chocolate out as well when
you're doing this thing you're taking a
a chocolate break right
a chocolate break
that's important like kathy
you guys know
there's a limitation
right there's a message that hits you
when you're on your third chocolate bar
right
if you're on your third chocolate bar
you're like oh
i pushed it too far
wait a minute here and then it's like
whoa
okay let me just do a couple of squares
i got this dark chocolate bar i got from
the health food store it's supposed to
be healthy it's got nothing bad in it
let me just do a couple of squares a day
and then a couple more squares a couple
more squares and you just you just know
you know
right
you know you gotta chill
abby says there's no sound
so
anyway
bottom line is
you got to look out for the caffeine you
got to look out for the the other stuff
i'm talking about
so rumble check out rumble if you can so
anybody who's got no sound go to rumble
rumble.com or go to youtube
go to youtube you'll get sound on there
okay
because i know that uh yeah and telegram
you go to telegram i know that facebook
is knocking out my sound
to censor me and i know that ig's
knocking out my sound essentially
individuals in there
anyway viruses love to eat foods they
love when you get toxins in your body
they love what you get dehydrated they
love when your blood gets thick they
love when you're yeah doing all these
things and when you're doing the
anti-bug cleanse you're taking these
away
and you're working on your healing
process it's like a miracle it's
incredible really
so i'm going to check on
those peppers real quick so they're
still cooking in here looking good
give it a little time
did you guys have your celery juice at
all
today
so what i'm gonna do is just
crank out a little celery juice
knock some of that out
so yeah they what they do is they
individually
knock out the sound on many people
[Music]
yeah just keep in mind
sign up to my newsletter so you know
where i am
medicalmedium.com go to my newsletter
sign up
so you can learn where i'm gonna be when
i'm gonna be
when the book is coming out the new book
and
[Applause]
that new book is going to blow some
minds
but spirit of cat the spirit of
compassion is giving me the
information
my mind was blown
i was i was like
i was learning it
[Music]
because
my teacher spirit of compassion so the
information comes through
and that's how i learn
that's my school
my schooling is getting advanced medical
information nobody has
and my job
is to
translate it
in a way for spirit of compassion
and put it in the books and that's what
this is
that's what this is
it's information from above
it's not man-made
guys i'm running a little celery through
[Music]
a little late in the day for celery but
it's okay you can have it anytime if you
really want to why don't we say that
the cleanse basics for the anti-bug
plans is 16 ounces of celery juice
or 32 ounces
of celery juice
you can do that
right
keep the troublemaker foods out check
out the troublemaker foods chapter when
you get a chance drink at least 32
ounces of lemon water or up to a liter
right
on every level any level it's the it's
this is for this is the basics for any
level one through five
sip some coconut water if you desire
make sure it's not pink or red
and
you can sip some hot
spiced apple juice that has the recipe
of
some
cinnamon
nutmeg
and cloves
trying to read some comments on tik tok
there too you guys
i just had my liver rescue smoothie day
5 of the 369 that's incredible
the 369 cleanse has brought so many
people back
to life after being going through so
much hell with sickness and chronic
illness
guys anybody who doesn't have this you
should have this book
get it free of the library if you don't
want to get it on sale on amazon
so i'm doing is i'm juicing
some celery
if you're interested in the juicer wait
for the sale
it's gonna be a sale coming up
because i know i get asked that i just
saw one question come up on that
[Music]
[Applause]
we're day three of the medical medium
anti-bug plans challenge
i want to make a quick announcement for
all the new people that just came on
here
at 6 15 eastern i'm gonna be on rumble
exclusively so i'm gonna be on rumble
it's free
when i say exclusive it doesn't mean i
have some like thing going where you got
to go and pay something
or when i say exclusive i don't want you
confused thinking oh what's he selling
there that you know is just for people
exclusively no it's for free it's an
exclusive talk today's topic is going to
be about essential oils
rumble.com forward slash medical medium
315 pacific 6 15 eastern
kimberley all good said the juicer is
awesome
i love it
especially with food prices rising this
is the greatest thing i never thought
like
because this this cuts um
celery costs in half and anything else
you put it in here cuts it in half
because it squeezes over the last drop i
never thought i mean
with the food cost rising how great it
would be
it's just so great
but it's only this model it's the mm-900
hds all right
here we go
ran some celery through here gonna put
this down you guys
don't add anything to your celery juice
the reason why i like to juice celery
in front of you guys is it kind of gives
you a little window into
how to treat your celery juice don't add
apple
don't add lemon
always strain it don't add water don't
add ice
very important tips if you want this
complete electrolyte to go to the brain
and actually work if you want this to
kill off pathogens because this is not
only anti-bug but this actually helps
and destroys destroy bugs in in and out
of the body right
all through the body very important to
know so it destroys pathogens viruses
bacteria so viruses
and bacteria
have a membrane okay
peppers are coming out good
they have a membrane around them
that membrane
around bacteria and viruses is what
protects the virus and the bacteria
right makes it hard
for your immune system to kill
it makes it hard to die
so one of the things you're doing with
the anti-bug cleanse is you're starving
the bacteria you're starving the virus
right so your herpes simplex cold sore
fever blister virus that stays in you
forever you're starving it now
all the different bugs we have that
cause autoimmune we're starving them
right
then
what's cool about the anti-bug cleanse
and you guys are doing this anyway a lot
of celery juice
when you're bringing in the celery juice
which i'm gonna strain when you're
bringing in the celery juice
you're
breaking down the membrane
of the bacteria the streptococcus you're
of the virus
so now you're breaking you're stripping
the membrane down
so the virus is weakened
so your immune system can kill it easier
see how it works so celery juice is
antiviral antibacterial
so you're using it as a weapon
debbie says since i've been on the
celery juice i no longer need my daily
metamucil whoa whoa
that's incredible okay
that i'm happy about
because
it's no fun if you gotta be it it's no
fun if you've got to be on your daily
metamucil
i don't know that's not a fun thing it's
not like i'm having fun on my metamucil
this is the funnest thing ever
no it's it's far from fun right
okay so
you want to strain your celery juice
keep that in mind
it's a mistake often made simple mistake
people make it they don't strain it
that's all
simple mistake
got your celery juice right there
there we go
incredible
so what the celery juice does
is it starts to break down the membrane
membrane of the bugs so this is the
anti-bug cleanse that's an anti-bug
drink
so what's incredible about the mm-900
it's dry in here
it's like dust
it's dry and this is dry
so that's why the food costs go down
with that juicer it's the mm-900 hgs i'm
mentioning it because i hear people are
freaking out about food costs
and they've been asking lately
so it's it's really nice but just wait
for it to be on sale so let's go
let's move along let's take a look
we are pretty much there i'm gonna take
them out
so i'm gonna do that now
i'm just gonna look for an oven mitt
real quick
because i think that would be a good
thing
i think an oven mitt would be good
man let me just do this
here by holding you guys i gotta move
piggy
and i gotta move donkey
and i gotta move this arm right here
okay you guys
all right there we go
this thing's coming out blazing hot
and i don't think donkey and piggy would
appreciate
so i'm gonna just hold it over here for
a second here
i'm going to put it right there for a
second these are them
these babies
are awesome i'm going to not let this
slide off so bear with me here
nice
let that cool down for a second
so what i'm going to do is chop up a
little parsley because i'm going to
garnish it with a little bit of parsley
and some more chives
so
got some parsley right here
any of you guys making this right now
i'm not look i like putting a little bit
more parsley on there but i'm not going
to put a ton of it on there just a
little bit
any of you guys making this dish have
you tried this dish that's what i wanted
to ask you guys have you tried this dish
yum i'm going to make it today amy
i made them last night
debbie says i'm really glad i ate before
watching this
monique says mini hammer
says she's making them
monique i read your um comment on
telegram too i think you left a comment
on telegram
all right so i got some parsley chopped
up
so what i'm going to do is grab one of
these peppers
and bring it on over okay
so what i'll do is i'll grab this yellow
one like this
i will grab
this red one too
so i have them here
if you guys can see that and i'm gonna
drop a little bit of parsley on there
just like this i'm gonna put a little
bit of chive on there too
just cut up a little bit of chive
there you go
i wanted to show you and then i'm gonna
plate it okay
so
i'm putting these two here i'm going to
plate the rest right now if you guys are
okay with this
this is like one of my favorite dishes
okay
now i know a lot of people have
nightshade fear but
there's no
oil
in here
there's no dairy
that's what causes a nightshade problem
it's not the nightshade causing the
problem it's the dairy the cream the
milk the butter that's what causes that
so it's very important to know
pathogens cause your symptoms
okay
peppers are antiviral
antibacterial
viruses and pathogens and
bacteria cause your symptoms so you're
somebody that's sick and you go and you
talk to somebody like maybe you should
stay away from nightshades you just got
handed
a one-way ticket down south to sick land
okay
this is a one-way ticket
up
to healing land okay when someone says
stay away from those night shades don't
eat the potato
they they're just not educated as a
health professional to know
the potatoes bad from being fried in oil
grease
like people eat them and doused in
butter cream milk
and that's why the potatoes bad oh i
forgot
cheese
lots of cheese on potatoes now
what the health professional doesn't
know
is that it's the cheese the milk the
butter so you're really kind of screwed
think about it you're out of health
professionals
in office you're trying to get help
and so you're relying on them to be
smart and like stay away from potato
stay away from the red bell pepper like
okay all right
because they're bad they're a nightshade
no
it's the milk cheese butter oil
it's that the cream
it's that
that's giving them their problems
i've done your 369 cleanse and read your
cleanse the heel book
it helped me tremendously eliminated my
anxiety and eczema and i loved many
recipes in the book asparagus soup is
delicious asparagus soup is amazing
i'm gonna pop on a few more chives
because i only i really just put on
parsley so let me just put a few more
chives on top
because that's the way i like them
so the nightshade problem out there was
a guess it was just another guessing
game because nobody knows why anybody's
sick it's just another guessing game
maybe it's the nightshade sounds so
spooky nightshades ooh
maybe that's why you're sick you can put
a little lemon on here if you want too
i'm gonna add a little bit lemon a
little bit of lemon right on the top
that's what i'm gonna do
fresh lemon to give it that nice flavor
that's what i'm gonna do there
okay and then i might even try to take a
bite of one of these but this thing is
gonna be hot let me get rid of the
pathogens
okay
now you can you can cut these in half
again like cut them in half and have
smaller wedges
you can take a bite right
so if i do this i can go this way too
i'm just showing you all the different
ways of eating it okay
that's insanely good
that's just insane
you can cut it in a wedge like this
okay
i just cut in a wedge
all right that's that's good
yep
wait i got a phone call coming through
i forgot i hadn't a friend calling
hello
hey you're calling on time
what do you mean i broke my cleanse
i didn't break my cleanse
yeah i'm on the cleanse
you're watching me right now where
rumble
you're on rumble
what's the problem
how can i be on a cleanse if i'm eating
something like this
you've never heard of anybody being able
to cleanse while eating this incredible
food
you know that this is
fat free there's no cheese milk butter
there's no dairy on here
yeah you're freaking me out man
i didn't break the cleanse i'm on the
anti-bug cleanse
you've never seen a cleanse where you
can actually eat this much
any incredible food like this and still
heal
whose cleanses are you talking about out
there
they don't even know why anybody's sick
out there
yeah you can actually eat look at this
do you see it
are you watching
you think i broke the cleanse because i
these aren't stuffed clams with cheese
on top
no what are you you're acting like this
is b what
it just looks that good
god
you know why does some of my friends
just don't know they just don't get it
they don't know anything but you just
gotta love them
um this doesn't feed the bugs just so
you know yeah i'm still on the cleanse
yeah it's incredible
are you now upset because i'm about to
have some hot spicy apple juice too
mm-hmm
it's amazing
well just
dude get over it
i'm still on the cleanse yeah maybe you
should go on it too
what are you doing you're swallowing
olive oil
what cleanse are you doing
you're doing somebody else's cleanse
you're swallowing olive oil
maple syrup cayenne pepper
eight tablespoons of olive oil what are
you doing are you trying to kill
yourself you're going to end up in a
hospital with a gallbladder attack like
so many people have doing that
yeah that's the disaster cleanse
what's it called a master disaster
cleanser what's it called disaster
cleanse
you know many people ended up in the
hospital because it because they got a
log jam and they're they're ducked and
they had to get emergency service
surgery yeah and they
they also need yeah
they also need to contact health
services afterwards
for like care as they were home and
couldn't even move for two months
yeah
yeah how about pancreatitis you know how
many people got pancreatitis from doing
that cleanse
yeah i watched people come through my
office said the worst case of
pancreatitis they could they were sick
for months they almost lost their
pancreas
nope
that's not a cleanse all that does is
put your system in shock
and you can't cleanse with all that
olive oil
man
i wouldn't do that cleanse
be smart about it
debbie says
i feel like this only resonates with
people who have been really sick for
quite a while seasoned
that's why medical medium is hated by a
lot of not so sick people out there
they're doing all kinds of different
fancy belief systems out there and they
just hate the medical medium because
they've never been sick
someday if they get sick they they'll
get a chance to heal
if they can somehow
you know
get past all the the misinformation out
there to swamp out their misinformation
you guys this is incredible
so we're day three
of the medical medium anti-bug cleanse
make sure you have cleanse the heel
you guys i don't know how long
amazon is gonna keep the book that low
in price
like
they may be even spying and be like okay
we're gonna
bring it up now so your people can't get
the help they need so just keep that in
mind that this is like an angelic
intervention is what i think
and it's 51 off it's a medical textbook
costs more to print it check it out or
get it free at the library go to the
library i don't care if everybody goes
to the library tomorrow
it just says can i take the book out
please all right
so
amazing
listen
6 15
eastern 3 15
pacific i'll be on rumble only
subscribe gonna talk about essential
oils all right
the cleansing heel book isn't just the
anti-bug cleanse it's 200 symptoms and
conditions what causes them protocols
supplements how to take them dosages
zinc shock therapy so you can further
your healing it talks about you know the
369 cleanses the mono cleanse right the
heavy metal detox cleanses so just make
sure you know that this thing's packed
75 recipes okay
morning cleanse whoa
it's incredible are you guys i'm gonna
be back on so telegram i'm turning you
guys back on in a little while right
tic toc turning you guys back on okay
and i'm going to turn on instagram and
hopefully you guys have sound on
instagram
here's the thing if you guys go to
and you're getting kicked off go to
telegram
go to telegram all right
so that's t
right dot
m e forward slash
medical medium all right and rumble.com
forward slash medical medium all right
if you like this video on youtube give
me a thumbs up
hopefully you like it maybe you like the
if you're afraid of nightshades
and you're upset right now give me a
thumbs up
on youtube
if you're somebody that
thinks i'm wrong about anything give me
a thumbs up
all right
hey what and don't
hit the thumbs up twice
don't give me a double thumbs up because
it un does it
and then you have to do it again
all right someone left a comment and
told me that
i love you guys i'll see you soon