hello I'm Anthony William and you're
listening to the medical medium radio
show where each week I talk about the
most advanced healing information and
secrets about health much of which is
not found anywhere else and is decades
ahead of what's out there now as I've
always said who has 10 or 20 30 years to
wait for answers to their illnesses life
is precious and there's no time to spare
do you have 10 years to find out what's
causing your
inflammation or 10 years to find out
what's be behind your thyroid condition
or 10 years to be find out what's behind
your psoriasis and eczema no we don't
every day is precious here everyday
matters and if you've waited this long
and if you waited for a long time to
find out why your injuries are not
healing to find out what's going on how
come something's not moving forward if
you've waited a long time we're not
going to wait much longer cuz we're
going to get down to it we're going to
figure it out and we're going to move
forward that's what it's all about at
the show and that's what the show is
about it's it's about getting that
information it's about finding those
answers and providing those answers so
that you move forward that's what it's
about so let's start the healing now
Today's Show is about recovering from
physical injuries if you've ever
suffered with a physical injury you'll
know how painful and inconvenient and
reoccurring this can be fortunately
there's more that can be done to reduce
inflammation and assist in recovery from
injuries and I'll be covering that in
this episode
so hang in there for this episode check
out my lifechanging Foods book the
medical medium life-changing Foods book
that's the book coming out soon after
the summer um try to get an order in if
you can I'm only saying that because I
just don't think they're going to stay
in stock um the last book had a hard
time staying in stuck and I think this
is going to be a lot more difficult so I
want everybody to be able to get a copy
frustration occurs if someone can't get
it when they want to and they need it
for their health and so forth and then
we're waiting so um maybe you know
getting one getting one now and having
it on pre-order and hold is really
helpful so life-changing foods and
what's really cool about this book and
really special is it's really unique
because it's information about what we
can really do with food for the first
time ever it's not just a a regular
recipe book or or you know a a book that
just sits on the coffee table but you
don't read it it it's
literally it's like changing and and
like the subtitle says it's save
yourself and the ones you love what I
mean by that is there's information in
there to keep us healthy for the Long
Haul uh for our families for our
children to come and uh and their
children and so there's there's
information in here um that's so
critical and so important about what
food really does what illnesses what
diseases autoimmune diseases and
illnesses and conditions to everything
from cancers you name it um which food
helps with which illness and condition
first time ever um this is out there
because it's coming from Spirit and the
information is going to be there for
everybody and um and not only is there
information about foods and what foods
do uh for the illnesses there's ways of
taking all the different foods in there
matching it up to your illness and
really knowing how to conquer what's
happening in your life I mean it's it's
really geared for this person who needs
to get better who's looking for answers
but not only that to protect yourself
and your family and moving forward in
life it's specific it has details about
it it's not just oh this is good for
this and that's it so that's a big part
of it plus there's a lot more
information in there that's critical for
health and moving forward in life so
make sure you locks lock that down if
you can um we're here we're talking
about
injuries um I'm excited today because of
this because injuries are so confused
using they really are um you think they
wouldn't be it's kind of you think they
would be clearcut you bang your knee and
it hurts and uh you go to the doctor and
you know and the doctor says you either
have an injury or you have a you know or
you have an ACL issue a t an ACL or
whatever it is and it's straightforward
it's not really that straightforward um
some injuries are and you know and and
and many aren't and we're going to we're
going to go into this a lot deeper um
first of all it's easy to get an injury
it can happen to anyone at any time and
just when you're thinking it can't
happen it can happen I remember years
ago you know I was just walking outside
and there was there was some Icy boards
and I was trying to step over these icy
boards and I slipped right on my
butt and it hurt and it hurt for weeks
and weeks and weeks because it was one
hard fall on my butt and so so you know
and that was it okay it healed fine but
what about the person you know that
slips and they injure their back they
injure their butt they injure they
injure a leg and it's just not going
away and it's sticking around and
sticking around and I'm not even just
talking about breaks I'm not talking
about broken legs I'm not talking about
broken bones and that too we're going to
cover too you know making sure that we
you know we help every aspect of
injuries and you know when we get an
injury and it doesn't want to budge and
it doesn't want to go away it can be
devastating I mean it's it's no joke I
mean people can suffer and then if you
have a chronic illness around it or
chronic illness happening you know in
your life or something going on or other
symptoms and you have an injury that
doesn't want to budge that it just
really weighs heavy really weighs heavy
I mean is H does that happen to you at
all or do you know anybody that has an
injury plus you got these other problems
going on you know plus you got diabetes
plus you have some other symptoms plus
you have severe fatigue then you also
have an injury or you have an ankle
injury and if that's happened to you
then you you know you understand you
know how how harsh it can be how hard
how complicated you know and it makes
life really difficult it's one thing to
be fatigued it's another to you know
have a lot of brain fog it's another to
have you know other issues neurological
issues but then they have an injury on
top of it you know it's just too much
it's too much for a lot of people out
there and I've seen people suffer and
I've seen people go through so much it
breaks my heart and it really does um I
mean it it it's it's i' I've had some
people literally with injuries occurring
consistently you know when they were
sick so I've had people come to me and
say look Anthony you know I've I've had
chronic fatigue syndrome I've had
fibromyalgia okay and now every time I
might even do anything I Ste the wrong
way I got a bad ankle um I walk too much
and my hip hurts um you know I can't I
you know I hurt my sprained my
wrist just opening up you know a opening
up a jar of something a jar of peanut
butter or whatever and you know and
spraying my wrist and then now I have my
wrist wrapped up you know it I've seen
it all and I has that ever happened to
you because it it does happen to a lot
of people so the injury thing is a is a
serious deal and then of course there's
injuries there's car accidents get into
a fender bender you get into a car
accident um you know we're going to
cover that too there's people that get
into a small fender bender they're not
even injured and then 3 days later they
their whole body's hurting head to toe
and hurts for about 2 years and then
they go to the doctors the doctors don't
even know what it is because they have
no physical injury you know there's
those kinds of injuries that mysterious
injuries we're going to try to cover
what we can there's a lot so that's
another example right there um getting
you know knocked around not having
anything physically you know showing or
physical physically tangible at the
doctor's office or you know at the
emergency room but yet you're injured
and this happens to a lot of people and
then there's some people they get
injured they just heal from it real
quick and that's it no big deal they had
a small injury they get better they had
a big injury well they healed and all
set done move forward you know they put
it past in their lives and that confuses
a lot of people too that confuses a lot
of people that have ongoing injuries
ongoing trauma and they don't know why
it's not going away and they don't know
why it's not healing and they see
someone else break their leg menend
their leg and they're off the running
and now they're playing basketball again
or something or whatever they're doing
they're you know playing a sport or
they're you riding their bike no problem
um you you know and I've seen people
I've seen people you know uh you know
break their shoulder you know get a
break in the shoulder um doctor says
well it's clear it's clear and
straightforward should men no problem
should be you know should be no big deal
and it everything looks great it's
healed it's looks great on the scan but
then they have leftover pain that's
running up into their jaw running down
their arm and it's now troubleshooting
it's now troubleshooting and it's like
going to doctor to doctor neurologist
neurologist like what is this so our
injuries come with also um these
leftover residuals these leftover issues
that occur and if you're a practitioner
you've probably seen this if you're
someone suffering with it you probably
felt it so you know this this happens so
what let's talk about like the
difference between these so you get
somebody who you know they injure
themselves they break they break a a leg
they break an arm or whatever and it
gets casted and they come out of the
cast they do a little rehab a little
physical therapy they're off and running
and then they put it past them and it's
all good and then what about the person
who gets a break or not even a break
sprains something it's inflamed it's
swollen you know I've seen people with
knees that are just barely injured and
they're swelling and they're swelling
for months and months and there's not
even a tear it's not even a there's not
even ACL tear it's not even anything
else going on and I've seen that happen
too so what's what's the difference
between these two like what's what's
going on in here is it just what they're
eating is that a piece of it it's not
exactly um a lot has to do with other
things happening in the body like viral
conditions especially Epstein bar I mean
that one for sure has a lot to do with
injuries if you're on if you have an
Epstein bar um viral load inside of you
and it's percolating and it's going on
and then you get into a fender bender in
a car and the adrenaline's pumping and
flooding all through your system so tons
of adrenaline is pumping all through
your system saturating your body and
adrenaline is it weakens the immune
system that's what it does it drops the
immune system down to like half its
value when you have that kind of
adrenaline Surge and then if you have a
viral condition that's peaking about to
Peak that comes out next thing you know
it you got an epine bar situation on
your hands and you're feeling
fibromyalgia from a small fender bender
small car accident for the next year or
two or if you don't know how to address
it and have the answers like I put in
the medical medium book or I put on
social media or the answers I put in my
members groups or whatever it is if you
don't have the answers to how to move
forward these you're stuck with this for
10 years or 15 years who knows I've seen
this happen with people so much and so
that's one of the aspects is viral
conditions that are underlying they have
a huge impact on knee surgeries that's
another thing standard knee surgeries
knee replacements okay or or just you
know knee knee fix itss or whatever um
standard knee surgeries okay where
people get a knee replacement all right
should be no big deal clearcut great
surgeon incredible surgeon job gets done
great uh state-of-the-art um uh knee
replacement okay parts state-of-the-art
parts and you know basically should be
up and walking um in in in a in a couple
of weeks in a week or two and doing
rehab and then next thing you know it
the KNE swelling up swelling up not
doing good swelling up you're back at
the surgeon's office back getting an MRI
and you know not sure what's going on
and everything's inflamed not responding
good this is rampant out there this is
rampant and then you get someone who has
a knee replacement boom they're they're
walking they're walking in one day
they're walking in one day yeah well
maybe that's not the right thing to do
but they do it anyway they were walking
in one one day so what I'm trying to say
is that you know this is going on and
when when when that does occur and it's
mysterious troubleshooting like knee
issue that's lasting and everything
that's a viral condition underneath it
that's something very important to
understand the one virus that tends to
work with that mostly is the Epstein bar
that's the infamous one that actually
keeps the knee swollen keeps it going
same if someone bangs their knee or gets
an injury underneath it keeps it swollen
it keeps it inflamed could keep it
inflamed for 6 months keep it inflamed
for a year I've seen it do it for 5
years for people whatever and so that's
that's a big part of the injury World
another big part is the shingles virus
um I've seen people you know people that
work in packaging where they're you know
they're carrying packages and they're
doing things with packages and they're
lifting they're lifting things every day
nothing really that heavy 15 lb 10 lb 5B
packages 20 lb pack 20 lb packages 25
maybe 40 sometimes is you know light
packages for a lot of strong people I've
seen strong people doing this doing this
work and all of a sudden one day
something kind of feels weird in their
back and in their shoulders it's
unexplainable they go to the
doctor um doctor doesn't know what it is
it's just now it's an inflammation
that's developing doctor thinks it's a
tear um you know next thing you know
you're at the surgeon's office surgeon
well you know you get the MRI get the
CAT scans doesn't look like a tear and
all this confusion happens and lo and
behold it's a shingle virus and it
literally stops people from using their
arms they take Frozen shoulders I talk
about it in my medical medium book about
the Frozen shoulders that
occurs so you get you know that can
happen out of nowhere the whole shoulder
freezes up people get disabled they lose
their jobs they got to go on you know
they got to go on
disability and then the injuries last
for 10 years 5 years 3 years until
something's done about it they go to
doctor to doctor said this is an
example um and maybe that's happened to
you something similar has happened to
you same thing with neck neck and
shoulder a lot of that's shingles you
don't need a rash in order to Showcase
that I talk about that in the medical
medium book if you haven't gotten the
medical medium book yet what are you
waiting for you just got to get it you
got to order it you have to get it you
have to look at this stuff it's so
important it's important because you
might run into someone else that needs
it that needs the information um and and
my goal is to get the information out
there that's basically what my goal is
that's the number one goal uh that's why
we provide tons and tons of info cuz I
just need people to get well in my
lifetime it matters to me spirit Spirit
wants people better Spirit has has
instilled in me the same fight to want
want to get people better um so if you
haven't gotten the book get the medical
meeting book um and learn about how
shingles work so that gets in the neck
it gets in the shoulder someone can
literally just be fine one day and they
turn turn around they pick something off
the ground and their neck goes
completely mysteriously their neck goes
okay they're getting massaged they're at
the chiropractor's office they're
they're getting
um they're at the doctor's office either
way you know and they're getting it
looked at and there's no tear there's no
no break or anything like that and they
got they got a neck that doesn't work
good or you know they get a shoulder
that doesn't work good these are viral
injuries that's what they are they're
viruses that are kind of percing
percolating they've been you know kind
of nesting and they come out and they
inflame things they inflame nerves and
muscles and this is one part of injuries
that this is the big part of injuries
that's being overlooked so people walk
around with injuries they walk around
with problems they go to doctor to
doctor they can't get the answers they
need unless there's a physical thing
wrong that's really there and even when
that gets fixed they still have
inflammation they still have injuries
and look if you're someone who escaped
all that just had one little injury or
had a break and mended you moved forward
you didn't have the viral inflammation
thank God you know for you you because
you know then you know you get to you
get to experience some freedom and then
when we don't have that we lose some
freedom and it's difficult so that's
what today is about like that's what
we're talking about today we got to get
that freedom back I got to get that
freedom back for the person who's
dealing with that kind of inflammation
that's occurring post injury so it's
like post injury
inflammation very important um you know
when I'm in a crowd or around crowd
which I try not to do too often I try to
just save that energy for events so I
can do the life blast and I could do the
things you know to to be there and
sustain um when I'm around crowds you
know I see back problems everywhere so I
see back issues and um even if I'm even
if it's not at an event even if I'm
somewhere else and I happen to be around
a lot of people or I'm on the plane and
um and spirit's giving me information
about what's happening with anybody
behind me in front of me on the side of
me left of me right of me and I often
look at
backs and um I like to see the
conditions people's backs are in and um
and a lot of times people have the
messiest backs they have their discs are
all out of place they have old injuries
they have soft tissue injury they have
connective tissue injury they have
vertebrae injuries um they have um um
you know degenerative discs they have uh
um anything spondylosis they have all
kinds of different things going on with
their backs scoliosis you name it and
it's amazing how so many people don't
even feel it don't even feel it at all
don't even feel it when they have discs
bulging don't even feel it walking
around disc bulging discs bulging for um
30 20 years don't even feel it
and then there's someone who has
something equal and they feel it or
there's someone who has something
less and feels it or or there's someone
that doesn't have anything wrong with
their back and feels it like you know
the back looks fine the discs are lined
up okay there's no nerves being impeded
um nothing fishy going on and they're
inflamed and they're inflamed okay and
then there's these routine there's
routine back surgeries like you know
routine laser back surgeries or there's
some really good surgeons out there
amazing surgeons are doing really good
back surgeries back surgeries are not
like they used to be back in the 80s
they were just you know they were pretty
gruesome um and because of technology
and our surgeons we're actually getting
a lot better with like back surgeries
there's some good clinics that do it and
so forth and you know a lot of people
that get a back surgery because they
have an impeded nerve or an issue they
get it they they get they get a um they
get some some um Scar Tissue shaved off
or or they get uh a nerve repair it's
slightly repaired or they get they get
some work done or they get a you know a
type of fusion whenever they're getting
done you know they walk out of there
okay there's some back surgeries where
you same day you're walking out you're
sore you're on a pain med but you're
walking out and then it
recovers then there's someone that said
you know there's someone that goes
through a routine back surgery they're
told it'll be fine they'll be you know
walking around in a week they'll be
recovering and it doesn't happen they
have the same pain they did before they
went in and even
worse and the Mystery of that that's the
troubleshooting mystery that's
that's what I'm talking about that has
everything to do with the viral
inflammation that we have one person
might have a little bit more of a
shingles virus maybe an Epstein bar one
person might have both and those are the
two viruses that mostly stand behind the
post injuries that keep them lasting
longer it's a big piece of it and if
you're eating the wrong Foods you're
feeding the viral situation so you're
getting more viral
inflammation and then that that's
occurring and so so it's a vicious cycle
so that's why foods are important so
we'll cover some of that too let's let's
um so let's talk about a couple of
different things let's go with the backs
because I like the backs because most
people have the back issues am I right I
mean do you have a back issue at all or
did you have a back issue at all maybe
you had one in the past maybe it creeps
up some people say well my back goes out
every fall it goes out every fall not
every time you fall but every fall every
October every November whatever every
late September so some people you know
that's what happens in their lives their
back the back goes out on them like once
a year or every 6 months or 3 months
maybe that's happening with you so we
we'll cover some good stuff with that so
if that's happening and then your back
gets better now that's a good sign if
it's not getting better well you got a
little bit of viral inflammation fine
and that could be dealt with but either
way one thing regardless of where you
stand with your your back you have to
learn how to cold pack your back you
know it sounds simple cold packing like
an ice pack like cold pack um sounds
simple but you'd be surprised how Nobody
Does
It Nobody Does it it's one or does it
enough if you get a back injury or just
start getting a back injury you have to
jump on it right away you have to get a
cold pack on that back that's critical
you don't have to burn the skin you
don't have to have ice pressing against
your skin but you have to get a cold
pack on it that's for first and foremost
that's how you can completely you know
elude or you can completely get around
it getting worse and worse and worse and
the inflammation getting worse um if
your back gets tweaked and it starts to
get inflamed there's more than the
tweaking the mild injury or the mild
movement you did that was off that's
causing this this is definitely caused
by a little bit of inflammation caused
by a viral
situation so you want to jump on it with
ice that's the first thing you want to
do um 30 minutes twice a day that's
important that's a really good amount
right there you want to do it in the
afternoon you want to do it at night if
you can do it in the morning um but you
want to do it every day the key for this
and why you have to do this is you have
to train your nerves to get DEF flamed
even though defamed is probably not a
word you want to you want to train that
nerve to calm down push that nerve back
okay because you that's a critical piece
to it especially if you're chronic if
you're chronic with back issues chronic
with back injuries you want to train the
nerves back you want to train them down
if you don't they're going to get
inflamed they're going to start to crack
they're going to start to harden they're
going to start to dry up and you can't
train them down as easy okay so that's
that's number one if you've been doing
this a long time meaning in pain with
your back going through struggles with
it for a long time time then you still
you have to learn how to cold pack it it
still matters um another thing is you
want heat on your back early in the
morning or in the morning you want heat
in the morning and then ice from there
on or cold packs from there on
throughout the day this is really
critical very important um the heat will
loosen up the muscles in the morning
because the cold packs in the ice does
tighten up muscles and tense up muscles
but it's doing that at the at the same
time it's training the nerve to calm
down it's pushing the nerves back you
want the nerve to be allowed to be
pushed back and trained back so um so
what you do is you do heat in the
morning okay and heat swells up the
nerve a little bit but it but it loosens
up all the muscles and that's what we
want and then later on during the day in
the evening it's the cold packs you want
the cold packs there you want to train
those nerves down that's a great way for
a chronic back problem to heal over time
I've seen some people with some slip
discs that doctors were like no has to
be surgery can't go with that it has to
be surgery there's no way around it and
you know I've seen the people suffering
with this and then once you do some of
these techniques and you and you work on
it just right you literally can heal
from it move on and not have back
surgery um I've helped people many times
over that so this is something to to be
thinking about um we're going to go over
supplements for all this stuff a little
bit later too go over supplements and
some
foods um as well so the back issues are
big because so many people go through
them um people have problems and then
you get the sciatic nerve sciatic the
sciatic nerve that's a big deal you get
the paraph foris you get the nerves in
the paraph foris nerves in the GL the
glutalor nerve all these different
nerves that run through S nerve
especially and what happens is with
people with with um back injuries and
viral inflammation they'll get pain on
their toe but not on their back they'll
get pain on their foot pain on their
calf like unexplained debilitating pain
on their calf that's so bad you can't
even stand you can't stand you can't
move you can't walk they go to the
doctors they get mized they get cat
skins everything checks out fine nothing
wrong um but they have pain that's could
be in their thigh it could be on their
calf it could be literally down by their
toes it could be on the top of their
foot and the pain is so vicious where
there's nothing that can really treat it
except for heavy drugs heavy medications
you know um lots of that kind of thing
and and so this is this is a sciatic
problem mostly you know tibial nerve and
sciatic problem caused by a viral
inflammation this is this is viral it
gets into the lower spine lower back it
can't be seen you can't see on MRIs you
can't see it on CAT scans and and the
the nerve sends a signal down to the
foot sends a signal down to the calf now
if you're one of those um yeah you're
you're dealing with it you know what I'm
talking about so that's another viral
inflammatory situation mostly from the
shingles virus the sciatic nerve mostly
from the shingles virus um and so that's
a big deal something to know about so
you got the heat in the morning like I
said before you got cold and cold packs
in the
afternoon um and in the evening very
important and then with injuries it's
important to move it's important to walk
now it's a catch 22 if you got somebody
with really bad fibromyalgia they got a
really bad Epstein bar issue they're
inflamed in all their
nerves if they don't move it gets worse
if they move too much it gets worse so
there's this vicious cycle I mean right
have you ever known anybody like that or
have you gone through that and um so
when that happens it's really really um
really debilitating but but it kind of
breaks the spirit because you don't
you're really not allowed to exercise
obviously you know because you feel like
if you push it too much you're going to
be all flared up everything's going to
hurt including your back including your
arms including your legs neck whatever
maybe fatigue will take over too but if
you don't move it can get worse as well
everything can get worse so there's
there's we have to find a comfortable
like place for you we're in movement you
know if you're that kind of person we
have to find that comfortable spot so
you know you got to move a little bit
you got to walk a little bit same thing
with a lower back problem in sciatic in
a sciatic nerve issue whether it's viral
or not whether it's the shingles or it's
a it's a you know an injury where your
disc is collapsing whatever it is we
have to move a little it's very
important for Recovery to actually move
walking sticks are important for
injuries don't have so much pride that
you can't get a walking stick and that's
that's that's not that's not you know
it's not debatable it's not a it's not
an issue that you know you're too young
or something in your life to have a
walking stick or whatever walking sticks
are really good for recoveries you have
a knee issue you have a knee problem um
don't be afraid to use a walking stick
for a little while you got a back issue
don't be afraid to take pressure off by
using a walking stick for a little while
there's some really good ones out there
there's these fiberglass ones they're
adjustable they have different handles
on them I love that for people with
injuries people with chronic illness
people with chronic
injuries and it can actually help you
walk a little bit more and heal a little
bit faster until you don't need it
anymore you don't need the crutch
anymore so that's how it works there um
back braces back supports try a few
different ones I think they're fantastic
you know Bower find is my favorite
company for people I've gotten better
results by offering back supports and
knee supports and elbow supports and
wrist supports and and uh ankle supports
from Bower find I think it's like B
Aur um and then um what's it find f i n
d or something but do a search the
spelling isn't correct on all thing but
it's bow find um so what you want to do
is you want to check out their their
supports now they have compression
supports if you have a knee issue
wearing a compressive sleeve compression
sleeve is ideal incredibly ideal and
then taking it off throughout the day
and putting cold packs on your knees um
getting the inflammation the swelling
down I've seen some bad knee injuries
heal with no surgeries without needing
surgeries and I've seen ones that people
went through surgery that wouldn't heal
heal from doing the right things um some
people say well I don't want to you know
weaken the muscles in my leg by using a
sleeve or a compression support for my
knee and or a back brace for my brace
for a back support I don't want to kind
of you know people say well I don't want
to kind of do that but that's that's
actually not correct information um the
support is critical and it's important
and you're still using your muscles with
the support or not even with using the
support you're still using your muscles
you're still using everything you know
that you're using you're still using
your body the only difference is is
actually you're taking a little less
pressure off the injury and the
inflammation or the viral inflammation
and injury you're taking a little less
pressure off and you're able to walk a
little bit more and you're able to get
stronger and protected at the same time
so compressive compression sleeves are
really good uh knee braces are really
good not knee braces but knee sleeves I
really like those so these are some of
the things to do including the walking
sticks these are important um and you
know understand that that with injury
injuries um
frustration we have to deal with
frustration in a different way there's
nothing more frustrating than an injury
because if it happens for a silly reason
you trip off the front porch you slip on
some ice um you know you hurt yourself
doing something we have to we have to
emotionally get grounded about it all we
really do because there's nothing more
frustrating nothing more agitating than
having an injury feeling like you could
have avoided it or some maybe something
could have been different that day maybe
you shouldn't you should have walked on
the ice differently whatever it is sure
we could learn from our mistakes but we
make these mistakes and we get injured
it's it's a normal process of Life quite
honestly I have never yet seen a single
person not sustain you know not sustain
one injury and in their life no matter
what some many some less some really bad
ones some not so bad ones regardless it
happens frustration levels we have to
kind of
calm down we have to calm down about it
we can't beat ourselves up we can't
punish ourselves for our injuries that's
something that's very important I know
people that you know they get injuries
literally by the week because they're
struggling with a chronic illness
they're trying to move around they get
small injuries while they're doing it
they slip they fall all kinds of things
are happening and we have to keep a
sense of humor the best we can as bad as
it is and it is you know it's a struggle
we got to keep a sense of humor we have
to stay lighthearted the best we can
with these injuries and the pain we go
through with injuries so that's
something to keep in mind I know you're
probably saying hey Anthony easier said
than done I've been through a lot in my
life and it's easier said than done and
you know it's hard to put a smile on my
face when I'm dealing with injuries and
dealing with pain dealing with the
suffering I've been through and I I
understand I totally understand just
that the frustration tightens up all the
muscles anger tightens up the muscles
tightens up the nerves puts more
pressure on the
injuries so we have to find a way to
kind of you know relax and and stay as
calm as we can around it and that's why
I'm proud of you guys because I know you
guys do that already and I know whoever
I know who you know meaning like well
your loved ones and your friends and you
guys are doing that already and I'm
proud of you exactly exactly you're
probably you know you probably don't
need to hear that information CU you're
already working on it I get it so but I
can't help it I can't help but talk
about it so you know want to talk about
ankle injuries when someone gets an
ankle injury um the idea is to stay off
of it right away sprained ankle you know
um ankle injury bruised ankle um but
there's a fine line between that you
have to use that ankle a little bit
that's why supports are good when you
get an angel ankle injury an angel an
ankle injury well you need angels too
when it comes down injuries we're going
to cover that in a few minutes as well
we're going to bring in the angel for
injuries they do help and um so when you
get that kind of ankle issue and you you
definitely need need the support really
important you need to do things like
cold packs like I said on the back you
have to still do that for knees you
still have to do that for ankles
remember that that's important um but
you have to use the ankle you may not
have to use it on the first day or the
second day but you have to start using
it with the injury and you could talk to
your doctor about that you could talk to
your practitioner physical therapist or
or or you know or your healer or your
natural practitioner or whatever you can
and but it's important to move a little
bit you know putting a little weight on
it putting a little pressure on it when
when it starts to come around a little
bit because if you don't the injury can
sustain longer it could stay longer it
can get worse it's there's this Catch 22
fine line in between there don't overuse
it okay because we can get in trouble
that way too but you got to use it a
little bit the reason why I'm saying
this I know people have injured their
their
ankles and stopped using their foot and
they've done too much rest on it and
very little movement where it's just
just very little and it slowed down the
healing process it you have to walk on
it a little bit I'm not taking take I'm
not saying take a one mile walk with it
saying just maybe just a little bit more
around the house maybe a little bit more
around the kitchen and then rest it rest
it and kind of gauge it this one way to
help heal the ankles ankles actually
need that movement um and so that's one
tip I could give you that's really
important I'm offering that tip because
so many people ask me about it too they
they're like look I twisted my ankle and
it's not healing or I twisted it thought
it was healed and then I took a hike and
now I'm worse than I was before so
there's this gradual thing of movement
healing moving
forward and you move forward now if you
had fibromyalgia which is Epstein bar
with the nervous system inflaming nerves
so if you've had fibro or you have
fibromyalgia and you twist your ankle
you could be dealing with a little bit
more of a longer injury a longer
inflammation process that I talked about
before and you know that that requires
yeah Tender Loving Care Plus like I said
before it's about knocking down the
Epstein bar you know get a copy of the
book so you learn about Epstein bar so
you know what you're doing there um so
that's a big piece of it and so I want
to talk about nerve damage so nerve
damage with injuries anybody out there
dealing with like nerve damage or
they're told they have nerve damage um
because that's what happens some people
have these nerve they they have these
injuries these physical injuries the
injury goes away and they might have had
some surgery with these physical
injuries might have been in a car
accident whatever it is that's happened
fallen off of a horse um and the doctor
says well you have nerve damage now you
you that's what's going on here and your
nerves are damaged and that's why you're
feeling this pain it could be like this
for the rest of your life there is ways
of recovering the nerves there are ways
of healing the
nerves and it can be done so um and
we're going to cover that with some of
the supplements we're going to talk
about uh that's important so don't feel
you can't heal your injuries try to you
know let that go I was talking to
someone the other day and they were like
Anthony I there's no way I can heal and
I said well that that doesn't sound
right cuz I don't believe that number
one because you can heal there's no
question you can and tell me why you
can't heal that's what I said to the
person they said well I just it's been a
long time and I got this nerve damage
and I got this you know I have this
injury and I got another injury and it's
just not healing it's been going on 15
years the doctor says I'm always going
to have this
and it seems like it's getting worse and
then when the weather comes in and the
rain comes in and the you know the the
low pressure storms come in or low
pressure or high pressure I feel it my
whole body hurts it's not getting better
you feel the barometric change you feel
the weather you know that's that's what
this person was telling me and yeah I
understand because when weather changes
and weather comes in and the damp
weather comes in and the low pressure
storms come in we feel it because
there's pressure it puts pressure on our
nerves and I said well look first of all
we have to get rid of the thought that
you can't heal that that has to go away
we have to throw that away that has to
be thrown in the garbage so let's
crumple that up like a you know a piece
of bad paper and let's just you know
let's just shoot it into the wastepaper
basket because that's where that has to
go right now and so well the person said
well it's really hard for me to let that
go because I just I've been convinced
there's just no way this is healing I'm
convinced and and I said
look number one okay your body responds
to your thoughts bottom line it does it
responds to your thoughts it needs that
tender love and care you have to give
your body a chance and the person said
well I gave my body a chance I was all
excited I was all enthusiastic at the
beginning of my injury and you know I
thought I can heal and you know I went
to a lot of different practitioners and
I thought I can heal and it didn't
happen and I said look we're dealing
with a few different things we're
dealing with a lot of lot of different
information we're going to be giving you
spirit and I number one new information
that's key and critical uh that's why I
do the radio show anyway too and we're
going to give you that new information
it's number one and number two you're
going to click on that healing process
in your body you're going to click it on
right now you're going to tell your body
you know you can heal you're going to
have to do it I don't care if you don't
even believe it you're going to have to
tell your body you're going to have to
start with that and I told this person I
said you you got to start with that
three times a day I said three times a
day I want you telling your body that it
can heal that it's going to heal and
it's healing three times a day I said I
don't even care if you believe it at
this point so you don't have to believe
it I just want you to tell your body
that so the person did that three times
a day told her body you're going to heal
if there's you know there's no doubt
about it okay um Anthony says you're
going to heal I'm saying you're going to
heal yes so this person told their body
of course the person didn't believe it
meaning didn't believe they were going
to heal but I told that person that
doesn't matter just don't worry about
that right now just tell your body and
it was three times a day for 2 weeks and
in two weeks less pain was occurring in
the body a little bit less pain and then
belief started kind of getting stronger
and then all with that we started
working on different foods and then we
started working on supplements like the
B12 Dino silk of alamin I'm always put
putting everybody into because that one
right there is literally lifechanging
for people with nerve issues
neurological problems you know nervous
system problems from viral issues
injuries you name it getting on the B12
and it started coming together for the
first time in 15 years and then the
belief got stronger and the faith got
stronger and then when this person said
to their body I know you're healing they
actually had this feeling like of Joy
like this flutter in their in their
tummy this flutter this little kind of
this light feeling that went through
them kind of like Goosebumps and and
like almost air rushed through them that
they actually were healing and they
believed it and the faith was building
and if you bend through an injury for a
long time and you just don't think he
could move forward we're going to we're
going to switch that around we have to
switch that around and we're going to
move forward chances are you've had
viral inflammation the whole time you
you you may have nerve problems but
maybe not really nerve damage okay so
that's another thing too so back to the
nerve damage thing I took you guys off
course took you guys off course a little
bit because I wanted to tell you that
story um but back to the nerve damage
thing nerves can heal Miracle they have
the ability we have the ability to grow
new cells in our nerves new tissue in
our nerves and new nerve sheets and and
we can heal and we can move forward and
so if you've been you dealing with an
injury and suffering for many years with
an injury you can move forward so we
covered a lot of different things we
talked about the back we talk about back
injuries talked about icing it heating
it in the morning we got all that down
okay we talked about the viral
inflammation so we have to go over
supplements some healing supplements
let's start talking about
that supplements so the B12 that's Prime
that's the one that matters not the most
but it's one of the ones that matters
the most it's one of them so the B12 the
Adeno Sil kabalam and you guys know it
many of you guys are knowing it now I
got people telling me hey which I've
never talked to before and I talked to
them they're like hey I'm on that adino
silk ofam in that B12 and it's getting
me to feel better um I was helping
somebody out that was there about I
think they're 92 or 93 years old and the
doctor told them that you know they're
getting old okay they're 92 they're
getting old and that they're just going
to have to live with the pain so by bot
line could do a little Physical Therapy
but you're just going to have to live
with the pain you're just going to have
to deal with it you know your your
injuries that you've had over the years
and the pain that you're in and just it
you're getting old and you know what
this person this person refused refus to
take that information and and digest it
I said you know what I'm not seeing that
I'm not seeing my age as being getting
old and person came to me and was
telling me this whole story and said you
know what you just need a little bit of
the dino silk bamin the B12 and the mix
the the methyl and the uh adinos cell
and you need a few more things and they
were taking it and the pain wall went
away and 92 93 years old and still fine
so you it wasn't about getting old it's
another thing too I got people in their
50s are like well I'm getting old this
is this is how it is I got pain no we
can't we can't do that we can't do that
we can't go there so um let's talk about
some supplements we got the B12 the
vitamin C very important for injuries
vitamin C is a miracle for injuries you
know oh yeah but I'm on vitamin C I've
had people tell me I'm on vitamin C I'm
like how much vitamin C are on I'm on uh
200 milligrams of Vitamin C like that's
not enough that's not enough that's
that's good it's good that you're on
that let's get you on 3 4,000 milligrams
go to your naturopath tell your
naturopath you want to take you know
6,000 milligrams you want to take 7,000
milligrams see what your tolerance is
and you start you can start slow and
work your way up you can start with
2,000 milligram to three and then four
cuz vitamin C can make you go to the
bathroom it can kind of flush your
system out so you want to see your
tolerance is and you want to kind of
rise up and then you can really help
injuries including nerve inflammation
viral inflammation from fibromyalgia
which is abstein bar you guys know that
now you guys know that now you know that
secret okay so you know that um silica
living silica is a good one I like
Organo o r g n o G5 silip plant so
that's a great one for injuries healing
injuries silica matter silica is better
than calcium better than calcium for
tissue connective tissue for
bones um everything it actually is
better so that's a great one glucosamine
is pretty good I say it's pretty good
the funny thing is is that people people
really like their glucosamine I'm not
going to take it away from them I've
seen it help some people I don't see it
help everybody but it's one of those
things where you'll know if it's helping
you you try it you see how it works and
then you you know you can you cannot use
it but I've seen glucosamine help some
people so that's one to try um MSM MSM
is really really uh helpful um nettle
Leaf that's one right there it's really
incredible so nettle Leaf is important n
leaf tea n Leaf cap capsules nle Leaf
tinctures
plantbased megas Omega-3s so plant-based
omegas that's a great one so you want
that um natural Cal that's a good one
magnesium magnesium glycinate or natural
Cal using both of them are incredible
for injuries spirulina that's amazing
for injuries as well spirulina is
incredible for injuries because it
provides so many micronutrients to
Injured areas the body really has the
ability to move forward so these are
some of the great St supps to use Foods
Top Foods leafy greens kale kale spinach
lettuce arugula um mesculin mix these
are amazing for injuries oranges never
underestimate oranges they help heal
injuries if you eat an orange once a
month you're not going to get your
injuries getting better you know on in
life-changing Foods the book um I really
lay it out to what fruit what vegetable
really does help what condition what
illness and if you increase that one
food and then you find another food in
the book that also can heal that same
illness and you increase that food
things start to change and it's really
detailed in the book so make sure you
remember to get that and get one
broccoli incredible for injuries wild
blueberries nothing compares to wild
blueberries for injuries two cups a day
every single day that's amazing
strawberries raspberries blackberries
cherries sweet potatoes and winter
squash can't go wrong with those
incredible
Tomatoes Tomatoes oh yeah but they're
night shades that's what people say oh
yeah but they're night shades night
shade I can't eat a night shade no you
eat a fresh Ripe Tomato try to get an
heirloom tomato if you want I need a
fresh heirloom tomato Ripe Tomato it's
incredible for injuries very important
inflammation viral inflammation so um
asparagus supers Sonic for injuries sea
vegetables like dolls kelp nor
sasame seeds tahini can have some tahini
in your hummus you can have make a
tahini dressing apples grapes grapes
grapes don't worry about the whole grape
thing where people are like oh there's
are too sweet there's too much sugar
grapes are incredible for Recovery
incredible phytochemicals antioxidants
for connective tissue soft tissue for
ligaments to you know everything bones
you name it organs incredible for
injuries incredible for
bruises uh anemia you know low iron all
of that grapes are amazing so keep that
in mind um zinc very important to take
your zinc when you're dealing with all
the injuries because viral inflammation
is behind so many different injuries as
I was talking about before making the
injuries last long just remember about
the zinc and keep that in there and even
some cat's claw sometimes that's a good
idea as well lemon bomb that's a good
idea is your antivirals olive leaf is a
good idea for injuries because it's an
antiviral very
important so we're at the end of our
talk so we just closing up on a few more
things know that I love you know that I
care about you if you're dealing with
these injuries hang in there for me we
can get better we can move forward one
step at a time sometimes it doesn't take
much but just a little a little bit to
move us forward it's not your fault
you're a good person I love you dearly
thank you for hanging in there for the
show Blessings by and I'll see you next
week love
you