anyway i'm here the medical medium
number one new york times best-selling
author of the medical medium book series
many of you guys know that
and um books are all over the world
helping people heal
around the globe powerful information
got my celery juice right here
and i'm ready to do a youtube i want to
talk all about this you guys know the
books there's the medical medium book
one
there's a life-changing foods that
brought some books along why not right
for anybody who doesn't know about them
thyroid healing medical medium
thyroid healing right there and then
liver rescue one of the latest books
right there getting your liver
healthier so powerful and the celery
juice book
which i mean it's epic it has
information in there really powerful
stuff to heal
the medical medium book series is about
advanced
medical information they're medical
books and they're around the world right
now millions around the globe
and many of you probably already know
you're using the information so you can
heal and move past your illnesses but
today we're talking about
why eggs make us sick and if you don't
know they make you sick you're going to
learn all about it right here today
this is a powerful topic and listen this
this is a topic i'm here talking about
this is a critical topic to start the
youtube live series with and that's what
i'm doing so
i want you to know about the eggs and
what's happening so many of you have
symptoms
conditions i mean everything from acne
to eczema and all kinds of different
conditions
and staying away from eggs is critical
it's critical so that's why i'm here
talking about this topic today alone
but in this in it actually really soon
i'm going to have guests come on people
that heal from medical medium
information i'm going to have doctors
come on
can have dentists come on special
friends special guests
scientists lab technicians people i know
people have known for years that are
actually fighting the battle out there
helping people heal from chronic illness
spreading the medical medium information
which is the most
advanced healing information that exists
today
so many know it doctors know it so many
other people know and i want you guys to
learn about it too so today it's all
about eggs
and why they're not working for us and
why we're getting
sicker without realizing it and we don't
blame the egg
nobody blames the egg you'll blame a
piece of fruit
somebody will blame something else way
before they'll blame all the eggs they
eat all those years
even if it was an egg once a year once a
week once a month
or once a day they won't blame the egg
so i'm going to go into it
so we're going to we're going to cover
it so the medical industry
is involved with why eggs are bad not
because they're out there talking about
eggs being bad but what happened is they
were using eggs
back years and years ago to raise bugs
so bugs are why we're sick and we're
going to go into this this is going to
be really intense it's going to be
really interesting
and so much information i got to cover
see basically what happened is viruses
pathogens bacteria were raised in labs
a long time ago back in the 1920s back
in the 1930s back in the 1940s
and so on and these bugs were raised in
labs these are the bugs
that got into people now that are into
you if you have acne
that's streptococcus i'm going to go
into streptococcus all the different
groups and stuff like that a little bit
later
but if you have acne that means you have
strep in your system
that strep is in your system because
that strep left a lab back in the 1920s
1930s
i don't know how mysteriously left the
labs
probably on purpose obviously so we can
stay sick so we can be a sick society a
sick culture
250 million americans alone are sick
right now with symptoms and conditions
and if you don't think you got a chronic
illness if you have one symptom
that comes and goes intermittently or if
it just comes and goes periodically or
you can't get rid of it or it's there
all the time or you got two symptoms or
three symptoms
that's a chronic problem that's a
chronic illness so
do you suffer from autoimmune do you
suffer from maxima psoriasis vitiligo
lupus lyme disease endometriosis pcos
fibroids breast cancer tingles numbness
aches pains
burning feelings sensations heart
palpitations ringing in the ears vertigo
dizziness tick spasms
acne ibs crohn's bloating colitis
fibromyalgia
hundreds of more conditions they're
caused by pathogens
so you can get your best medical
information out there alternative
medicine or your best healer or your
best advisor in in medical health
and they won't tell you which bugs or
bugs that are responsible for this
responsible for all your illnesses and
how eggs
feed these bugs so this is critical
information it's really important
so in order for pathogens to stay alive
they need
food and everybody has pathogens in
their body
every other pathogens in their system
that's how it works if you've had
fibromyalgia if you've had a hashimoto's
problem if you had a thyroid issue
there's pathogens involved so we'll
cover some of that too along the way
so eczema psoriasis that's a virus
inside the liver along with
abundant amounts of copper a toxin that
sits in the liver so i'll explain about
that too so
here's how it works viruses
stay alive by feeding off of food inside
of our body
pathogens stay alive by feeding off of
food inside our body so that's how it
works i got some eggs right here
of course you have to have the eggs
right here right so
when you're eating the eggs every day
you're just
bringing yourself closer to sickness now
you could throw up a blind eye at this
you can just throw your hands at it and
be like okay what does he know
what's going on here or whatever but
because you're feeling good you might be
young you might be indestructible at the
moment
you might be working out in the gym
every single day you're 20 years old
you're 25 years old you're 22 years old
whatever and you're like no i have eggs
on my salad
i'm told it's a protein source i'm going
to cover all that stuff but in the end
you will get symptoms everybody does
whether they get it at age 38 whether
they start getting reproductive problems
at age 35
whether they get something at age 42
they get it
see that's the whole thing no one's
going to escape that unless they
really know what to do for themselves
what do you actually do
what to use for the health and and how
to avoid things they shouldn't be eating
because in the end everybody gets
symptoms
bottom line i've been doing this for 35
plus years
been involved with it i've talked to
thousands of health professionals
over the years i know how it works
everybody gets symptoms if you don't
think you're getting them now
you're going to get them later so why
not avoid them why not actually
do something about it this is one of the
most powerful ways to handle it is
getting rid of these babies right here
and so get them out of your diet no
matter what and so look
i'm not in the food wars okay we know
that i'm not all about the food world
meaning like you guys may not know if
you're brand new to this it's the first
time you're watching this
with me or anything like that but people
who know medical medium information
know that i'm not involved with that
whole food war thing where it's the
vegans against the paleo's the paleo's
against the vegans whether it's whatever
diets that you know anybody subscribed
to where animal protein against the
non-animal protein people
and how it goes and the flip-flopping
that happens all in it where people
leave the vegan world and they go back
to animal proteins
meanwhile they got sick to begin with
off the animal proteins people leave the
animal proteins they go back to vegan
world they're all going back and forth
and what's happening is everybody's
guessing and everybody's still dealing
and fighting with their symptoms
as they go along the way or they get rid
of symptoms for a little while and then
they come back
so not about just subscribing to one
side of it or one hey
veganism is the way to go or hey
paleoism is the way to go it's not how
i've ever been
i'm about real answers real truth
they're in the medical medium series
books
so you can actually be armed and be able
to take care of yourself and help
yourself heal and get better
that's what it's about it's about making
sure that mom who can't get out of bed
to take care of her kids gets real
answers for the first time after she's
already been to five neurologists after
she's already been to five other doctors
or a dermatologist or
however because of her excellent
psoriasis or some other condition i'm
all about making sure
you get your information so you can heal
and be empowered
and rise above all the nonsense and the
noise that's out there including the
noise that's on youtube
including the food war noise including
everybody thinking they got their handle
on a diet or whatever
when in the end no one knows what causes
illnesses
they don't know the epstein-barr causes
actual sickness like all the different
conditions i mentioned earlier
some of them many of them and they don't
know about all the different shingles
varieties the epstein-barr varieties the
over 60 varieties so we're going into
this stuff in depth
um gonna have to actually drink a little
celery juice keep me going here
so let's go into a little bit more of
this
the basics let's just start out with the
basics right here
viruses and pathogens that are
responsible for autoimmune
and other illnesses if you've been
diagnosed with an autoimmune condition
of any kind and your doctor finally said
hey it's autoimmune or you went online
and looked and it's autoimmune
whatever that is what that means without
anybody telling you
is that you have a condition where you
have a pathogen inside the body
causing problems creating neurotoxins
creating dermatoxins like if it's eczema
psoriasis
that's a pathogen creating a toxin that
floats to the skin this is advanced
information now if you eat eggs
if you're eating them or you ate them in
the past you're feeding
that pathogen you're feeding that virus
and that's what's keeping you sick and
that's what what's going to keep you
sick so this is really important to
understand
so that's just a basic rundown of that
so food is medicine you guys heard that
everybody's heard that food is medicine
food is medicine right
what food that be that medicine all of
it and you know you know the whole thing
with that
is food is medicine what's
medicine with food if you don't know
what causes illness
how can you know what's good or bad for
you how can you know as a health
professional what's really good or bad
for you
how can you know as an influencer how
can you know if somebody actually giving
advice out there when you don't know
what causes illness
if you don't know what causes all the
different symptoms and conditions
how do you know what food is good or bad
why do you think people are still eating
eggs
and that's how it works if people knew
what was really wrong with them and what
was causing illness and sickness out
there
eggs would actually get a bad rap like a
really bad rap
see that's the whole point so
everybody's saying hey food is medicine
but sure there are some good things in
eggs
but there's bad things in eggs too
there's bad things that actually
feed bugs and that's really important
understand
just because there's a nutrient in eggs
or like omega-3 or something like that
that you're being told is in an egg
just because you know some omega-3s in
here there's some protein in here
something that you think is actually
good for you or some nutrients and stuff
like that just because that's in here
doesn't mean there's something else that
isn't in here
that's causing trouble look the
industries
use this in labs as a food
source for all the bugs that are keeping
everybody down
disempowering women and men actually
hurting people
keeping them sick hurting children
keeping them sick
that's what they did they did that
without your permission no town hall
meeting
no vote no anything this was done
without your decisions involved so eggs
were actually
ruined because of this okay and before
all this yeah eggs will probably find
food to eat why not
why not so let's go into uh something
called
autoimmune i want to cover that a little
bit why i want to talk about
that when it comes down to eggs
autoimmune and eggs and and kind of
link that together so that's really
important to talk about because so many
of you with autoimmune conditions of any
kind
or symptoms that may not have been
diagnosed as autoimmune or anything
so many of you are actually eating eggs
or
go back to eating eggs or maybe come off
of them and go back to them you know
it's one of those things where
it's a staple in all the diets maybe if
you're not a vegan sure
but you know what it's a lot of people
they're not vegan long
you know they're vegan for a very short
time they're vegan for like five years
yeah that's a short time that's a really
short time
or they're vegan for one year and
they're back on eggs what do they do
when vegans usually leave
that whole thing plant-based people they
go right back to eggs
they do a little fish or they stay with
eggs they bring on cheese or something
or butter they usually start there but
so i want to talk about how most
everybody has been either been on eggs
when they're younger or they're on
eggs later or they're just on eggs every
day
so let's talk about this think about
technology back in the 1950s late 1940s
right think about technology think about
the phones go watch an
old movie i know i say this a lot watch
an old movie
and look at technology back in 1950 all
right you'll be in shock
because we're so used to tech now we're
so used to life now we're so used to
what's happening now okay
and so go back and look at that and when
you look at that
you'll see the old phones you'll see the
old cars cars as big as
as big as boats you'll see all of that
you know
and what happens is when you realize
technology was where it was at then you
have to realize
medicine was where technology was at
back then too
it was in the dark ages okay that was
the dark ages of medicine
that was where theories were born just
like now theories are here now
we're still you know in the dark ages in
many ways because you know hey they
still don't even know what causes
chronic illness and autoimmune but think
about as far as back in the late 1940s
early 1950s well that's when the
autoimmune theory was
birthed that's when it was born okay so
if you're someone who's young right now
if you're someone that's already been to
a couple doctors you've got a little bit
of eczema and you're realizing it's
autoimmune or you've got some swelling
on the body or you got something that's
you're getting a diagnosis of lupus or
you just got
symptoms that are actually being
classified as autoimmune are you dealing
with a little fibromyalgia or chronic
fatigue syndrome or whatever it is
that's all in the autoimmune family or
lyme disease now pushed in autoimmune
i'm going to go into that more detail it
whatever you're dealing with
okay autoimmune is a theory still
the word is a theory the concept is a
theory your sickness is
real your symptoms are real they are
very real way more real than the
industry
lets you feel or know because that's how
it is
by saying it's autoimmune they're saying
your body's attacking itself they're
saying your body's destroying itself so
that's what they're doing so think about
that for a minute
here you are you go to a doctor it's not
the doctor's fault doctors work for the
industry it's not doctors are amazing
it's not about the doctor
but you go to the doctor and the
doctor's gonna be like yeah you have an
autoimmune condition that's what you
have
so now you're you're making your protein
shakes now you're making your smoothies
now you're having your hard-boiled eggs
on salads now you're doing all this
because you're trying to eat healthy go
to a good functional medicine doctor and
they'll like get off a gluten get off of
this get off of that
but they still think you have an
autoimmune condition they're still
following that 1950s
theory where your body's attacking
itself
see autoimmune means your body's immune
system is attacking the glands and
organs
that's what it means that's a theory
that occurred
back in the technology of that you know
old school of the 1940s and the 1950s
that was a theory that came up because
science of research had to protect
itself
because millions of patients were coming
in
with new symptoms for the first time in
history
so please know that and there's no
science proven autoimmune yet the
autoimmune theory
there's no science or research that can
actually prove the autoimmune
theory okay that's how it works you can
look all you want
they'll still say your body's attacking
itself and they'll talk about an auto
antibody
but they could never find that auto
causing harm it's not possible it's
still
a complete and total theory a farce
actually
it's basically a ruse played on you and
i'll tell you why
it's to train you that you have a faulty
body that your sickness is your fault
it's not a pathogen it's not the
epstein-barr virus
it's not this it's not that the industry
doesn't want you knowing these truths
the industry doesn't want you knowing
any of that the industry wants to keep
you sick that's how the money machine
works you've heard of that right
well it's like that with autoimmune the
theory so this is how it works
in the 1950s they didn't know why all
these people were sick
they were pouring in and pouring in
symptoms they'd never seen before i've
even talked to old
doctors back in the day when they were
already 90 years old after practicing
way back then
and i've and i've talked to them and
they've told me how it all worked and
what was happening
and the autoimmune theory was just a way
to confuse people to protect science and
research because these signs of research
has to protect itself
and it uses you and women kind to do so
not in all fields i'm talking about
chronic illness so just know this not in
all fields
you know when i talk to scientists
they'll say the same thing they'll say
it doesn't it doesn't protect itself all
the time in
other areas and but it does in chronic
illness and
women suffering and struggling so when
women come in with all their different
symptoms or heart palpitations oh it's
their hormones
or all it's you know or their fatigue
their severe fatigue oh it's their body
attacking itself or it's in their head
and they're creating it
or it's genes these are techniques used
for the industry to protect itself so
first of all the industry
used eggs to raise all of these
pathogens
that make us sick then when everybody
got sick
and is getting sick now and pouring into
their offices and still today like never
before in history we have an epidemic
right now right
now that people are pouring in sick they
use the old theory that came out the
protected research and science the
grandfather law theory which is the
body's attacking itself how do you like
them
apples huh exactly so so
you're going to be say 22 years old 21
years old maybe 40 years old maybe 45
years old with your first diagnosis you
got a thyroid problem oh wait a minute i
got hashimoto's thyroiditis so i got
hyperthyroidism
and you're going to find out that's your
body attacking itself there's no answers
out there so there's no answers out
there
whether you like it or not about me
telling you this truth whether you're
somebody that's like ah that's not true
there's answers no no no i trust my
doctor no no i trust research in science
i trust all the different non-gluten
diets i trust everything
but you know what there's there's
something i call bullshitting yourself
and that's what people do every day and
they actually themselves to
still eat eggs that i've learned i'm
going to talk about that a little bit
here's here's how it works it's
important to know what causes sickness
so you can actually help others move
forward
rise out of this it's important to know
that pathogens
cause sickness heavy metals cause
sickness
mercury aluminum you know lead arsenic
uh nickel you know cadmium copper cause
illness and heavy metals like mercury
okay
with foods like eggs feed bugs
that keep us sick that keep us down that
keep us hurting
that keep us fatigued that keeper keep
give us thyroid problems and so forth
you have to break out of that whole
thing
where you actually think that your body
is attacking itself
or that you that you cause the problem
or its genes
or it's even the wrong foods you're
eating
people will be like well it's fruit
that's causing my hashimoto's that's
actually not even
possible fruit cannot feed pathogens
like viruses
they can't feed that they're actually
blueberries
help you get rid of pathogens they help
you get rid of viruses
they help you heal that's the whole
point and so you need to know there's
certain foods that
are medicine and there's foods that
aren't
medicine that's why it's so important
here that's why i'm talking about this
so many people are sick because they're
eating the wrong foods
and they think it's medicine they think
the wrong food is healing
and that's how it works they're also
told their body's attacking itself so
they're given no
answers it's why there are so many
people healing with medical medium
information the reason why there's so
many people healing with medical medium
information
globally out there because of the
millions of books that got out there
all in the world is because they have
the truth
and they and they know better not to
just yes themselves they know it they
know what they've been through they've
been to 10 doctors
they've been to 15 doctors they've seen
how hard it is they've been to four
neurologists
they've been through hell and back they
bend down on their hands and knees
suffering
and they paid tons of money and they put
so much money out in so many different
ways
and they've suffered and they've
struggled okay and they know
this and so what happens is those people
that have healed through the medical
medium information know not to eat eggs
but hey
but this might be the first time you've
ever seen a video of me
first time you ever heard about my books
so we're gonna go into more of this so
just back to the autoimmune theory
it's not your body attacking itself
that's not how it works
and that's just a complete and total
fraudulent
theory that was created to protect
science because there were no answers
and so every single illness now is
classified practically every single you
have to understand
it's not just 10 illnesses 20 illnesses
or a hundred we're in hundreds of
different
conditions now are classified in the
autoimmune category
because they have no answers
and then you're supposed to believe your
body caused it
and then when you sit there with that
autoimmune diagnosis you're eating your
eggs
because you're told by some dietitian i
mean i love dietitians there's some
really great ones
out there that know about medical medium
information and or more decent
information in general
but you'll be told by some dietitian and
keep on doing the eggs you'll be told by
a nutritionist keep on eating your eggs
because it's high in protein
and then what happens is if you've even
started recovering because you got rid
of certain foods like you got rid of
gluten and you got rid of fried foods
and you've been eating healthy and
you're exercising a little and you're
starting to do some recovery and you're
seeing a good functional medicine doctor
and you're taking good supplements
you're starting to just come out of it a
little bit you're still going to be
eating eggs
and then boom years later you get a new
problem boom you get or you get a
relapse
or you just you're back to where you
were before see
they don't know what causes illnesses
that's how it works
you go to practitioners they don't know
not all practitioners know the ones that
actually know about medical medium
information
they know what's going on they know
what's causing diseases
they know that epstein-barr one of the
60 varieties of epstein-barr which i'll
talk about in a little bit
what that is about they know that that
virus causes more than a little bit of
tiredness
it causes aches and pains it causes
fibromyalgia it causes
rheumatoid arthritis it causes eczema
and psoriasis
it causes hashimoto's thyroiditis it
causes multiple sclerosis it causes
aches and pains tingles and numbness
ringing the ears vertigo that's just the
touch of what it causes
okay and that's not even pcos because it
causes pcos too and some reproductive
problems and conditions
so that's what epstein-barr causes
you're not going to get that you're not
going to get that clear
information instead you'll be told to
keep on eating your eggs and that
yeah you have autoimmune and you need to
do maybe an aip
diet or some other kind of diet and so
forth and it's not that i'm against any
diets that's not it
it's just that it can't subscribe to a
belief system what happens is people
they fall into a belief system they have
no choice they fall into a belief system
and that's what they do i can't do that
that's why i'm not in the food wars
that's why i'm not like you know i'm not
throwing stones at the vegans i'm not
throwing stones at the paleo
you know people they can eat animal
protein i'm just gonna teach you
what foods actually feed the real
problems why people are really sick
how to do something about that and
that's what the youtube subs live series
is going to be about like i'm going to
be bringing on the guests i'm going to
be bringing on other people
in the future episodes what we're going
to be doing but i'm going to make sure
you have the answers you need so let's
talk about lyme disease a little bit
i want to cover that lyme disease
everybody thought it was all sewed up
they all thought it was bacteria it was
bacterial you got the bartonella
you got the babesia got the borrelia and
that's what they thought it all was in
the past okay
that was the whole thing now you just
need to know something because of the
medical medium information
and the millions of books that got out
there in the world and the amount of
doctors using the medical medium
information
at this point now in time the lyme
disease information has changed out
there because of medical medium books
it is actually altered so which is
actually a good thing
but it's what happened out there the
industry is sneaky though
they don't like when this information
gets out there they don't like when the
truth gets out there because they know
it threatens them in so many ways it
threatens them from making money it
threatens them in different ways from
taking control
they don't want women kind taking
control over their lives over their
health
and they want to make sure they sell as
many antibiotics as they possibly can so
the lyme disease movement is all about
selling
as many antibiotics as possible the
industry wants to do it they've made
trillion dollars on antibiotics in the
last 35 years still a lot of money no
one wants to lose that
so but what happened with the medical
medium information the truth got out
there
thousands and thousands of doctors just
in this country alone and globally
know that lyme disease is viral that
bacteria can't
cause a neurotoxic response
like all of the neurological lyme
patients go through
i actually broke that information out
there in the world through through my
source that you guys learn about if
you've never heard about that it's all
in the books
and so that information is changing the
world but what the industry did to try
to kind of like catch up to itself a
little bit they took
lyme disease they removed it from
bacteria
category even though the lyme labs still
test for bacteria and all that they took
it from this category of just bacteria
bacterial and they placed it in the
autoimmune category
they now say lyme disease is in the
now it can't be in the autoimmune
category if it's bacterial related
but you see how that works they just
took lyme disease after 35 years
out from underneath everybody no one's
even realizing it
and they placed it in the autoimmune
category
which means they're telling you that
your lyme disease and lyme symptoms are
now your body attacking itself wait a
minute wasn't it bacteria for 35 years
didn't they literally bomb the hell out
of people with antibiotics
decade after decade and tortured women
kind and tortured people
literally i mean people have suffered
you wouldn't believe if you don't know
about this you wouldn't believe with
lyme people lyme patients have gone
through in the hell they've been through
it's so heartbreaking you just can't
even imagine
you can't even imagine see they placed
it in the autoimmune category
for a reason because we've altered the
information out there
because people are healing when they
realize it's viral
see look babesia bartonella borrelia
they're not superbugs they can't harm
you like people really believe so
see that's how it works they can't
produce a neurotoxin
because they can't produce a neurotoxin
like viruses like epstein-barr
hhv-6 shingles varieties and other
viruses hhv-7 simplexes and so forth
they can't produce a neurotoxin
neurotoxins is why people suffer with
neurological lyme symptoms
that's how it works and the industry
they got kind of wise to what was
happening and what was shifting so they
took the actual
diagnosis of lyme disease that condition
and they placed it in autoimmune
now they're teaching people that's your
body attacking itself that's what it is
they're leaving the bacteria
aspect of it out of it because the
bacteria was never the problem
mrsa has a higher healing response rate
of recovery with antibiotics
than bartonella babisia okay because
and borrelia there's a reason for that
because
mrsa is a real superbug but yet has a
higher response rate in recovery the
reason why people with lyme
suffered all these years with
antibiotics and they've been they've
been bombarded with antibiotics in their
system and haven't had good recoveries
and they've even gotten worse so many of
them is because
they were viral when you use antibiotics
for viral conditions you suffer worse
that's how it works and that's what
happens
see if the bacteria borrelia and the and
the hybrid babesia
and the bartonella were the true causes
of lyme disease antibiotics would kill
them off so simply and easily
because they're not superbugs like even
mrsa and mrsa has a higher kill off in a
response rate of recovery
my god i've known so many people that
have you know had mrsa and recovered and
that's like the superbug one of the
superbugs
and that's how it works see lime lyme
people people that have dealt with lyme
disease and everything else and they're
dealing with the symptoms neurological
lyme and all that lyme disease patients
would be freed up in a heartbeat from an
antibiotic
and a heartbeat and and it would never
come back
and so but the reason why they don't and
they end up getting sick again or they
end up suffering either way
the reason why it's always been viral
that's why antibiotics are being phased
out of lyme disease protocols
doctors now lyme doctors are using half
the amount a quarter of the amount
now they're bringing it down to a
fraction because they know better
they've seen the wake of the hell that
has happened and they've seen what
people have gone through
and what do they do though everybody
just tells everybody to eat eggs just
everybody just eat eggs i mean that's
how it works just lots of eggs
and so and those eggs feed the viruses
behind lyme disease
so the medical medium information was to
bring out the truth that it's viral
that it's viral neurotoxins produced by
viruses causing neurological lyme
the industry got wise they placed it in
the autoimmune category now
okay that's how it is and now the
autoimmune category means your body's
attacking itself wait a minute what lyme
wasn't bacteria i'm confused now the
body's attacking itself what is it down
they're slipping in there and they're
kind of like
and all the big doctors now and all the
big protocols they're backing down on
the antibiotics you see and then they're
using more natural things they're using
more natural stuff they're using the
diets and people are recovering but the
reason why they're starting to recover
is because they're viral and that when
you clean up your diet and your diet
gets better especially with the medical
medium information of what foods to
eliminate when you clean up your diet
and everything starts to go down you
start
getting rid of all the bad foods
including the eggs
that's right your symptoms start to back
down and they start to back down and you
start to recover
and so that's just a whole example of
lyme disease autoimmune
how things work how the system out there
works the trickery of what's happening
the aspect of it all
so it's so important to know this so
just to recap real quick before we move
on because we're moving on to some cool
stuff
without a doubt so a little recap on
things okay
and i love the comments coming up it's
incredible so
um i'm gonna answer questions if if the
eggs are organic is that a good thing so
we'll cover that in a little bit
um the whole bit so there's because
there's important things to know about
how eggs work so i'll check out the
comments too
um let's go into food as medicine
so what food is medicine okay is it egg
medicine is it egg medicinal no it's not
it's not a medicine it's not medicinal
this is so important to understand it's
critical okay
spinach is a medicine so just know the
difference
get the reference you know like like
know what we're talking about
like all of us are talking about right
just like
spinach is medicine yeah of course it is
you know that i mean
of course you know it's medicine i mean
a pile of spinach in front of you
you know that's medicinal you know
that's medicine okay
eggs no they're not medicine and there's
a spark in us that knows that why do you
think eggs in moderation
you've heard that oh eat eggs in
moderation why could you probably get a
heart attack and die they're worried
about like yeah
that's one of the things like why eat
eggs in moderation
you've heard that one spinach in
moderation
i don't think so you can eat spinach all
you want the whole bit
i mean but eggs in moderation that
phrase came around because of high
cholesterol
because of because of plaque in the
arteries
because of your blood clots because of
all kinds of other issues high blood
pressure
so that's so that's where eggs in
moderation was a concern
because it's not a medicine it's not
it's actually a food that's you know
constantly promoted by backers of the
industry
for a reason so we'll go into that a
little bit celery juice
is this medicine or is this not medicine
it's medicine
spinach medicine wild blueberries
medicine
blueberries medicine potato even a
potato
medicine so you know potato without
cream without butter
without you know without any of that yes
in important you know potatoes without
cream butter
cheese all of that so i want to talk
about potato for a second somebody
like out there you guys might be vibing
us the
feeling well potato is not medicine
potatoes terrible for you i'm on this
certain diet potatoes bad for me oh i'm
just
i'm gonna just completely all this
information doesn't mean anything to me
now because i've learned potatoes are
bad out there from some kind of diet
so if you're somebody that's getting
that that feeling of like why is he
talking about potato there's something
called
lysine lysine is inside potato
people are suffering out there with the
epstein-barr viruses the shingles riot
do you know anybody that has jaw pain
neck pain that they're it's
unexplainable
they got trigeminal neuralgia they got
migraines they got headaches that's the
shingles virus that can cause
all of that chronic sciatic nerves
sciatica problems if you know a relative
or a friend that has a back problem that
just doesn't want to back down
surgery or no surgery or whatever it is
shingles variety see shingles there's
over 30 varieties of undiscovered
shingles varieties i mean that's the
whole thing see epstein-barr
there's over 60 varieties only one they
have discovered out there
they don't have the over 60 price of
mutations and strains
so let's go into this a little bit um
we're talking about foods as foods as
medicine we're talking about the
potatoes the lysine lysine
actually harms viruses so that's how it
works so just pretend
you know just pretend that look this is
a virus i got the little critter in my
hand right here i've done this before
say that's the virus the pathogen the
invader lysine when you eat a potato
starts to hurt the invader starts to
take down the invader starts to take
down the pathogen that's how it works so
potato has something in it that is
medicine
to stop conditions that lyme suffers
fibromyalgia
chronic fatigue syndrome you know me
chronic fatigue syndrome all the
different conditions
just regular fatigue all of it people
that suffer with
what happens is potato actually helps
you heal it is one of the foods is
medicine but it shows you how the
industries don't know this
and they'll just be like oh it's a carb
toss it or whatever but that's a prime
example of how the industries and how
people in the diet fads and trends don't
know what causes your symptoms or
conditions or illnesses
that's how it works celery juice is a
medicine
helps to actually destroy and kill off
bugs
so it actually helps to kill off viruses
and that's what's important
so i'm going into stuff like that no one
eats potatoes by itself so caught a bad
wraps everybody eats potatoes with sour
cream they protect you know the potatoes
cheese on it with butter on it so yeah
it is it it actually is bad for you at
that point it's not going to help you
with all of that on there
and they put oil on it all of that
doesn't help so yeah
it catches a bad wrap and rightfully so
if you're going to do all that to it it
doesn't work
so let's go into another thing too
everybody is guessing out there so that
leads me into this next part
everybody's guessing that's how it works
so everybody in the industry is they're
guessing
to what food is right to what can heal
you to what is good it's all
guessing games that's how it works much
of it built off of theories
it's a prime example how everyone is
guessing and no one knows how to heal
and you can watch this on people's
youtube channels you can see you can see
what they were doing two years ago on
the youtube channel you can see all of a
sudden they're doing this and they're
changing it up and they're starting to
get a little better and they start
getting a little worse again
and they're confused and they're
shifting their diet or you can see it on
the youtube or
you know different episodes of people
where it goes back a few years ago or a
couple years ago you can watch the
progression now
of people getting sicker too you can
watch that too you can see it when
they're younger and then three years
later they're starting to get excellent
for the first time in their life
they're starting to get something for
the first time in your life and you can
actually witness this
and they're trying different diets and
different trends and they're working out
and you can see
where everybody really still doesn't
know what they're doing everybody is
guessing including the big diet people
out there
being the people that back the trends
the people that actually start the big
diet trends out there
they don't know what actually heals
somebody or doesn't heal somebody
because
once again how can you actually know
what heals someone when you don't know
what
causes their illness so critical to know
so
if you're suffering with any chronic
illness say just
you think about that for two seconds how
does anybody know
which you know how to heal someone if
they don't know what's causing
the problem you have to know the cause
in order to heal you have to know the
cause
you have to know what's causing your
illness so then you can know
not to eat this when you have pcos when
you have endometriosis
when you have you know chronic utis when
you have all kinds of different
conditions or reproductive conditions
you no one's going to know hey you can't
eat that
because that's going to feed a virus
that's responsible for your condition
or breast cancer same thing with breast
cancer no one's going to know
hey you know that's the thing when
people get breast cancer they're told to
eat more eggs
when people get pcos they're told to eat
more eggs and people get endometriosis
they're told to eat more eggs they're so
no eat eggs eat this and they'll say
sure eat salads and
and some vegetables and eat your
vegetables and maybe have a few berries
you'll hear all that stuff out there but
they'll leave the eggs in there 100
which will make pcos worse and worse
and worse and so that's an example so
how is it possible
that everybody knows what they're
talking about there out there about what
can heal and what can help
when they don't even know the cause of
the pcos
they don't know the cause of the
endometriosis they don't know the
constant cause of chronic utis
they don't know the cause of your eczema
psoriasis they don't know the cause of
your fibromyalgia your multiple
sclerosis your aches and pains your
tingles and numbness your chronic
vertigo your balance issues your brain
fog
if they are the cause of your brain fog
then how do they know what's going to
heal it
and so the medical mean information is
all about getting those answers
it's like that with breast cancer they
don't know the cause of breast cancer
because they still don't know the cause
they're just starting to link up steam
bar virus because that is
the true cause just starting to link
that finally
with all the medical medium information
that's gotten out there for all these
years and it just finally the length of
that it's just fine
i talked to scientists and lab
technicians that are pro medical medium
information out there
i'm going to interview some of them
along the way and they'll talk about how
yeah i mean
this is the information this is the way
to go look
chronic illness isn't about laying in a
bed dying
and and and believe me there's plenty of
people out there doing that it's the
saddest thing out there
it's a saddest thing it's heartbreaking
it's disturbing in so many ways
it's it's heart crushing but chronic
illness
is any symptom condition that you got
or you're developing or going to develop
10 years from now
are going to develop it's easy when
you're 20 years old and just really you
don't have much going on
and then all of a sudden you start
getting that brain fog while you're 27
years old
and that brain fog is getting in the way
of your career getting in the way of
things and then all of a sudden you find
your thyroid count is off your
if your thyroid numbers are off and all
of a sudden you find other things are
going on and it's happening to everyone
no one's escaping it's happening but you
can stop it you can learn how to heal it
you can figure out how to you can figure
out what the cause is
all of that's possible that's the whole
point so
it's so critical to know so a chronic
symptom and condition
chronic illness is any symptom you're
battling with or struggling with that
isn't
helping you that is hurting you in some
way
or lowering the quality of your life or
reducing you know
your your positive nature your outlook
on life because you're just bummed out
because you got these symptoms and
whatever it is the symptom is
they actually those symptoms keep us
down
and they keep us down and that's that's
chronic illness chronic illness isn't
the person that's in a bed dying and
there's like i said so many are in that
condition
and it's so sad but chronic illness is
all kinds of stuff
it's all kinds of symptoms that you're
dealing with so let's talk about the
protein and eggs
um so yeah so it's great comments coming
up thanks guys
really appreciate it i love doing this
live
not edited or anything it's like youtube
live it's just so fun to do
the protein and eggs let's go into that
a little bit okay
is it good for us hey you should eat
your eggs because of protein so maybe we
should have
eggs because the protein look at all
this protein here so you'll hear it over
and over and over again it's like a
brainwashing out there
and but what no one understands or
nobody knows
or no one realizes is protein
was one of the food sources that was
given to bugs to keep them alive
it's one of the sources so it's protein
inside eggs
that kept bugs alive in the labs they
learn to feed off of the sticky protein
that's in eggs
so that's what happened so when you're
eating egg proteins
they're slowly feeding things because
everybody has things in them
and they will get something eventually
they'll pick it up they'll pick it up in
different ways pick it up from
a new relationship people in new
relationships pass the bugs along
say somebody has acne okay and they've
taken antibiotics for
their acne over and over again that
streptococcus that they have
which causes their cystic acne because
that's the true cause of acne
that strep actually gets stronger and
stronger with antibiotics then you get
into a new relationship that strep gets
passed to another person and that person
has that streptococcus
and so we we tend to pass all of these
bugs around and then bugs continue to
get stronger as the years go on we pass
along the epstein bars we which is mono
nucleosis we pass along all the
different h pylori
we pass along these things we get them
from restaurant food we get them from
restaurant glasses we get them from
all kinds of different things we get
them from people not washing their hands
and working in places we get them from
public bathrooms we just get
bugs and we're going to get them along
the way in our life one way or another
because we're going to sit on a plane
somewhere and we're going to
pick up a bug somewhere and we're going
to be in a on a plane bathroom
and we're just going to get bugs in her
life if we're not careful we're not
cautious but we're going to get him
that's how life works
with those bugs they just they incubate
over time i'm just being straight out
i'm just telling it like it is because
if i if i keep the truth from you and i
act like you know and i just
talk silly stuff out there like you
should have some butter in your coffee
or something or if i talk silly
stuff out there like you should be doing
this that and not have the answers to
heal
it's not enough we need more i want to
protect you it's about protecting
yourself it's about making sure you have
the answer so you can protect yourself
so we actually pass around these bugs
and then we eat eggs and we feed the
bugs we may not see a problem in a while
sometimes we go through a lot of stress
we go through some emotional heartaches
some heartbreaks things like that trust
gets broken next thing you know what our
immune system gets knocked down a little
bit and then the bugs that we have
floating around in us
get left lots of ample food we have some
eggs and then we get in trouble with
that i haven't covered the emotional
aspect about eggs and why we're so
attached to them and how i understand
i want to do that too i don't want to
forget about that the other thing that's
in
eggs are hormones let's cover that now
some of you out there might be like well
he's talking about hormones and eggs but
i eat organic eggs they free-range eggs
i eat my own eggs no no no i'm talking
about
the hormones that are in those those
eggs
these these are organic eggs right here
and there's hormones in these
they're just not added but there's
hormones naturally occurring to grow
that baby chicken that's how important
it is to understand this stuff and so
these hormones were another food used in
labs to raise
all of the bugs that keep us sick sick
let's just cover the bugs for two
seconds first okay
so there's over 60 varieties of
epstein-barr mutated strains and so
forth
over 30 varieties of shingles
undiscovered by research and science
that plague people left and right out
there
they give them a neuropathy they give
them all kinds of aches and pains
trigeminal neuralgia
they give them bell's palsy everything
so there's all these different kinds of
shingles varieties out there non-rashing
and rashing
there's hhv-6s there's hhv-7s out there
too
there's simplex 1 simplex 2 and all the
different mutations and varieties that
are being passed around all over the
place
and then there's cytomegalovirus there's
that one as well
then there's the undiscovered hhv 10s
11s 12's 13s through 16
that scientific research doesn't even
have their finger or pulse on on any
level
so you got all these different viruses
then you have the different varieties of
streptococcus over 50 groups of strep
now are developing over 50 groups and
multiple strains per
group you can't even the alphabet won't
even cover it now you speak group a
group b
strap group c uh um you know d
h whatever and you know the whole bit e
so what happens is that
i probably got it backwards right there
but the groups have different strains
and multiple mutations
these are all the bugs i'm talking about
that are keeping everybody sick
you can arm yourself you can knock them
down you can clean up your illnesses you
can be like other people medical medium
information in the books that actually
understand this stuff
and actually realize that doctors don't
know that most doctors don't even have
an idea
or or know about this it's not their
fault all doctors are good because they
want people to heal they're in it their
hearts in it i know lots of doctors work
with them
there's doctors on the front of these
books that that have written
forwards on the front of these books and
there's amazing physicians out there
done incredible work out there but when
it comes down to eggs you're just going
to feed the bugs so much as this this is
so important to know about
so it doesn't matter if it's organic
doesn't matter if it's free range
doesn't matter if you grew it yourself
it's going to have hormones in it that
feed
the viruses it's going to have a protein
that feeds viruses and bacteria
and keep us sick that's the bottom line
so all of this is important to know
about let's keep on going a little bit
further and all this so
a lot of people ask the question and
this is a good one a lot of people ask
the question
um is raw egg okay
so that's what they'll do is raw egg
okay the whole bit now
raw egg is definitely better than cooked
egg but still with raw egg you got to
worry about other problems
one being the main problem it'll feed
your pathogens it'll still
feed everything viruses will will eat
raw egg
they'll be cooked egg pathogens will eat
raw egg cooked egg that's just what they
do
and then when you cook an egg you
denature what's even good in it that
people think is good in it so the
omega-3 everybody says is good in eggs
you
cook it you destroy it so you're not
even using the omega-3
so anybody who says well hey look
there's omega-3 in eggs
yeah good luck getting it if you're
cooking it because you're destroying the
omega-3 you can't cook omega-3
it won't work in your body it just it
just it can't be used
same thing with proteins they become
denatured you can't cook proteins
they become denatured you cook an egg
protein it's denatured
so if you eat a raw egg you'll get the
omega-3 you'll get the protein
but you'll feed the bugs all the same
and maybe even get yourself salmonella
or a food-borne
illness if you eat rags too so you got
to be careful it's a whole nother thing
here's the thing i have nothing against
eggs
okay if anything and i got nothing to
gain doing this
all i get is is flack from actually
telling the truth that's all i get
that's how it works out there in the
world
you tell the truth you go against the
industry you actually let the truth out
to get people to heal
all you do is get crap for it that's the
bottom line okay
but the only thing i have to gain is you
healing and that that's true i have that
to gain because i know that i could
sleep at night knowing that you have
answers
while i'm in this lifetime now that you
have the answers so you can work on
healing
that's critical to me okay but other
than that there's nothing to gain with
this
it's not like i have anything against
eggs it actually tastes really good i
mean
i mean eggs people love them they taste
great it's emotional connection
our moms made eggs or dads made eggs or
grandparents made eggs there's so many
people all that through the
the family line you know we went to
diners right did you guys all go to
diners and have eggs in your lifetime
you know maybe somebody got drunk and
went to a diner after a college party or
something whatever it is
just just you know had eggs there's all
these emotional connections
people have with eggs down to the family
line
goes back in history i mean i mean down
to
the food that's made to egg salad that's
made by you know a family recipe
a potato salad with eggs mayonnaise
whatever it's just whatever it is
mayonnaise and eggs and all this stuff
there's so much going on there
and there's so you know with omelets and
fried eggs and scrambled eggs and
all the way people like them you know
and i get that and i completely
understand
and i know that connection is deep in
people
but see you know what happens is the
industry
they don't care about your family they
don't care about you and your health
they want you to think your body's
attacking itself they want you on eggs
they want you sick and they want you
playing guessing games
and they want you throwing stones at
each other and throwing fake science at
each other you know like the vegans and
the paleos do and everybody else
everybody's throwing all this stuff at
each other
and the iep and everybody's just
throwing all the stuff because everybody
thinks they have the answers when they
don't even know what causes
anything that's the whole thing i don't
even know what causes anything
and so the industries want everybody
guessing they want everybody confused
and they want everybody to stay sick
that's just the bottom line okay i have
to be the one deliberate well that's the
way it works you know
i want to tell you read this new york
times bestselling book deliver rescue
learn about protein the whole bit
protein myth
critical critical to understand so you
can protect yourselves so that's a good
book you can actually uh get into
if you're new to my books so let's move
on down the line a little bit more i'm
gonna sip a little bit of celery juice
here
okay so if you can't afford a book can't
get a book go to the library
get a book for free i don't care if
everybody goes to the library
back to hormones and eggs i don't care
if the eggs organic free range you still
have hormones that feed pathogens that
keep you sick so your excellence rises
are going to come and go it's going to
keep on coming
that's how it works doesn't matter if
it's you know it's free range like i
said the whole bit it still has hormones
in it it's like a ball of hormones
that's what it is naturally occurring
and the hormones and eggs confuse the
our endocrine endocrine glands our
endocrine system so it's really
important to understand
and they also get stored up in her liver
so the protein and eggs get stored up in
our liver
the the hormones from eggs get stored up
in our liver and then we get sick
because of
pathogens sit inside the liver i talk
about all the different viruses and
pathogens that sit inside the liver
and they feed off of a storage bin of
old egg
by-product that's sitting inside your
liver so it's really important to
understand
eggs are not blood sugar balancers let's
cover that a little bit everybody's like
oh eggs will balance my blood sugar
eggs will actually keep my blood sugar
balance they keep me level first of all
eggs have sugar in them
so it's not just this protein food
non-carb food that's not at all eggs
actually have a lot of sugar in them
there's a reason for that without sugar
glucose a baby chicken can't form
get muscles can't break out of the shell
there has to be sugar
inside of an egg or a baby chick
can't develop and break out of the shell
can't have the strength to break out of
the shell
so there has to be sugar in there
i mean there is but if you take the
the sugar naturally didn't have any if
the egg didn't have naturally any sugar
in it a baby chicken couldn't break out
of the shell
so that's how it works so when you have
sugar and fat combined
you have now you destable you're
actually you disable your blood sugar
that's how you create insulin resistance
so just know this this is actually
something is really important so
eggs are toted as blood sugar imbalances
they're good for diabetics they're good
for people with diabetes and all that
not true
worst thing for diabetics the worst
thing to keep you with diabetes you
continue to stay with diet
being a diabetic or a pre-diabetic or
your a1c
is going to constantly be unstable and
you're going to have to need medications
and the reason why is because this is
sugar
and protein this is sugar and fat
combined inside of an egg
it causes instant insulin resistance so
it's not a blood sugar balancer
because when you put fat and sugar
together
the sugar can't find its way into cells
because fats blocking it so insulin has
to be produced to try to somehow get
that sugar to bypass the fat and enter
into cells so you can actually have
strength
and that's how it works so these are bad
for diabetics but yeah
diabetics are told to eat them
everybody's told to eat them that's the
whole point we're all told to eat them
so the fat clogs up the blood
keeps the insulin from attaching to the
sugar and then the
sugar the glucose entering your cells
that's how it works
so when people are eating carbs if
you're eating carbs with some type of
fat
the same thing occurs that's how it
works so
like for instance if you're eating
french fries with oil
french fries with oil is fat and a carb
right
see so that's insulin resistance but if
you're eating potatoes without oil
that's how it works that's why donuts
cakes cookies
all that stuff is bad for you it's fat
and carbs it's fat and sugar that's how
it works
so because of that you get the insulin
resistance so i'm trying to give you a
little run down on that same thing with
barbecue sauce so if you're actually got
barbecue ribs
going on the grill and you think you got
a protein source right there but you
slap on barbecue sauce you just put a
sugar
on top your barbecue ribs whatever
you're on your ribs you put a sugar on
top of it you just cause an insulin
resistant issue with sugar
and fat very important understand so
realize this is not free from that it's
got a lot of sugar in it
to keep a baby chicken actually so baby
chicken can grow
it can gain muscle and strength and be
able to break out of the shell
and that's how it works so eggs are not
a perfect food for diabetes that's the
whole point
so you can you can read more information
about this too in my books i talk all
about that
liver rescue is a great one for get your
liver healthy and actually you can get
so many conditions behind you it's
ridiculous you can actually really heal
you can learn how to heal the whole bit
um and you know what i'm going to be
doing a keto live ketogenic live
diet you know ketogenic diet live too so
we're going to do that eventually i
can't wait to do that cover all of that
that's going to be fun
um so here's the other thing people have
to understand too
okay eggs are high in fat so remember
that too
so it's a whole nother thing so they're
high in fat so when you put the sugar
combination of fat and sugar that's when
you get the problems
that's the bottom line and then the
person feels stabilized but
really they become destabilized more and
more and more and more
and they end up getting in trouble so
and the reason why they feel stabilized
for the moment by eating eggs some
people feel stabilized because it's got
a lot of calories
it's got a it's got it's packed with
calories it's the bottom line so
if you're going to eat a caloric foods
you're going to feel stable for a little
while so anytime but
you're going to set yourself up for
pre-diabetes you're going to set
yourself down the road for liver
problems because eggs clog up the liver
cause pre-diabetes and so forth and
that's one of the things that gets us in
trouble down the road
um so that's something i wanted to cover
there many people eat their eggs fried
or in omelets butter or oil the whole
bit now here's something i got to talk
about this is fun just let me get a sip
of celery juice right here
so coconut oil let's talk about coconut
oil and eggs
just because you're frying your eggs and
coconut oil
that's not the answer that's not the
answer because you're still
feeding any kind of pathogen any kind of
virus any kind of bacteria that's in
your body that's causing any of your
symptoms
you're still feeding any illness you're
still feeding any disease so what
happens is if you take
take eggs and you fry in coconut oil or
you cook it in coconut oil
it's a way a term i call bullshitting
yourself that's what it does you know
it's like
you think it's healthier you think we're
told it's healthier all you're doing is
adding more fat to your meal
so you're having like a double fat meal
eggs which have fat in it then you're
adding coconut oil
into it and you're using that sure it's
better than using butter
definitely it's without a doubt it's
better using butter or bacon grease
without a doubt it is so i like that's
what i like about the coconut oil with
eggs and stuff but at the same time
you're not getting away with something
the most important part
which is this is responsible for all
those diagnoses
this is one of the things that are
responsible for feeding the viruses
and the bugs that are responsible for
autoimmune conditions and all different
conditions that are out there and
diseases and so forth
all the pathogens of viruses and
bacteria that feed off of foods it likes
this is one of those foods that's what
i'm saying this was a food that
raised them in the labs and they're in
our system and they're in our bodies and
then that's what everybody's
that's what everybody's fighting they're
fighting their
pathogens and they're fighting also the
information out there the misinformation
out there at the same time they're
finding two things
and i always say if you know the truth
you don't have to fight one thing
anymore
all the misinformation and all
of the the the information that's out
there that isn't right that doesn't work
that isn't good
and you don't have to fight that battle
anymore so once you have the real
information of what causes illness and
you know how to support yourself and you
know how to
empower yourself and heal that's one
battle that's over
the next battle is clean up your system
clean up the toxins clean up the bugs
and the whole bit it's so important to
that so
you gotta re-watch this live anybody who
came on now you have to go back to the
beginning of this live and make sure you
watch it right from the beginning to all
of it it's so important
no one is immune from getting sick
and no one's immune from bullshitting
themselves when it comes down to eggs
in order to support somebody's belief
system and they love eggs
they will themselves in every
possible shape and manner
because if you love the emotional
connection you have with
eggs and you're really connected and you
love the taste and you hear one good
thing about eggs out there
without fail you're going to pass it on
to the next generation you're going to
pass it on to the next generation and
you're
and it's going to happen over and over
and over again you'll carry the torch
into the next generation is what you'll
do because
no one wants to drop a belief system
that tastes good
and everybody's eating it's their
favorite comfort food or one of their
favorite comfort foods i've had people
tell me no eggs not my favorite comfort
food but they can't get rid of them and
they can't stop eating them
because it is i've had so many people
say well i don't really eat that many
eggs
maybe you're one of them and you're like
hey you know anthony
i don't really eat that many eggs i
think you're kind of like off in this
one
but then get rid of them get rid of them
and keep them out all together
keep them out all together and get rid
of them and you'll know where you stand
with
it you'll know you know if you're
someone who's going if you're someone
who is going to watch this
live and you're going to hop on the
research and science bandwagon of
researching
sites about supporting your comfort food
about supporting eggs about if you're
someone watching this right now and
you're like wait a minute i got to go on
the internet now i got to look up
studies and research
i got to look up things and and find out
how eggs are good for me and find out
how eggs are
you know realize that egg studies are
paid for
by their constituents they're paid for
that's how it works
that's how it's done nobody's paying me
to do this
nobody's paying me to do this to put it
simple
to put it simple okay because it's the
first thing that people are going to do
after seeing this this youtube
is they're going to be running looking
for research about eggs they're going to
say wait a minute where
how does eggs work how are they bad and
they're going to trust studies
that are paid for so you keep eating
eggs but that's how the world works
haven't you figured that out yet you
know it's pretty much just how the world
works with stuff
that's how crazy the world is because
it's all about keeping you sick
keeping the industry fat the fat cats
happy out there
keeping them nice and you know all the
money paid for all the investors all the
backups all that stuff
all that constituents happy and
everything they're going to make sure
those studies
are supporting eggs and that's the
bottom line it's going to get pushed
into the
alternative movement it's going to get
pushed in every movement it's going to
be in every diet system there is
except for the vegan system but yet the
vegans flip flop anyway and they leave
veganism and veganism the minute they
get a sniffle because their people are
telling them they need protein or
something so they run off and they're
now they're eating eggs again which is
you know which is sad because i like
anybody who's just staying off of eggs
no matter what diet belief system
they're attached to or whatever they're
attached to
the industry big pharma actually pushed
eggs upon us
they use them in the labs to get us sick
and they push it upon us to eat them
that's how it's done
and they know this they know this okay
i want you to know this and remember if
you like i said if you're a big science
research study fan
just know you know if they if science of
research had all the answers
why is everybody so darn sick
so many symptoms and conditions
conditions that are just
rising out of the blue over 250 million
americans alone
have symptoms and conditions they can't
get rid of so is that what it's supposed
to be you guys
are we all supposed to be sick is
everybody supposed to be sick except for
a few 20 year olds before they get sick
i mean is that how it's supposed to be
millions
and the millions getting sicker that are
coming
soon the millions that are going to get
sicker why are you
or someone you know why are you or
someone you know
still suffering with x-men psoriasis if
research and science had all the answers
why i mean do they go to enough doctors
don't don't they have all the answers oh
i forgot their body's attacking itself
that's right the 1950s theory
that was shoved in everybody's face so
realize
how research in science works with
chronic illness and how it's a
it's a house of cards and it just falls
and breaks and falls all falls down
you have to be able to see that or you
can't heal in the end
because you'll just be playing the
guessing games and you'll be running
around you'll be eating eggs then you'll
be on this diet then you'll be doing
this diet you'll be seeing this doctor
you'd be seeing this doctor he'd be
trying this
be trying this new thing this new herb
i'll tell you right now
get on your celery juice every day okay
every day
okay the industry doesn't like that
celery juice it's hurting everybody it's
hurting the pockets of everybody
get on that celery juice help yourself
heal learn what to avoid
help yourself heal get the books like
liver rescue and any of the other
medical medium new york times
best-selling
number one new york times bestselling
books and make sure you get those
you know really important so you're
gonna learn how celery juice gets rid of
pathogens
you can learn how to heal all this is
correct is critical
eggs are not the culprit for disease i'm
not saying eggs are responsible
i'm not saying don't make listen don't
mistake this
i'm not attacking eggs and saying
they're actually the culprit of disease
it takes a host of toxic heavy metals
mercury aluminum copper it takes
pathogens takes viruses such as
epstein-barr
it takes all of that and that's that's
what it's involved
with it just so happens that the eggs
feed pathogens the egg actually feeds
the viruses the viruses eat the eggs is
what happens
i know it's pretty silly right but it's
the truth and it is the bottom line
eggs aren't the cause of disease but
they feed it
so eggs aren't the cause of disease but
they feed it so important to understand
you guys that's like critical they feed
basically that's how it works because
the viruses that cause disease were fed
eggs
look here's the thing
okay i want you guys to have the answer
answers i want you to have the
information i want you to know you can
heal avoid eggs at all
costs is what i'm trying to say if
you're not sick now and you feel good
and you want to eat some eggs
okay fine i mean eat some eggs but we're
always one
egg away from getting ourselves sicker
so important to know look it sounds
ridiculous
probably to someone who's not feeling
too many symptoms or any symptoms at all
and they're like that egg didn't hurt me
when i hated
but what about the woman with pcos who's
really suffering with some kind of
reproductive system condition or the
worst endometriosis she's getting she's
getting surgery
and there she's told to eat an egg every
day and it's worsening the condition
rapidly or even a diabetic that's being
told
you might care about the diabetic in
your family and they're told to eat eggs
every day
basically the bottom line is have
compassion for the people
people who actually really are sick
struggling and going through hell and
back or bend through hell and back
and i want you guys to have that
compassion for them too because
but by having that compassion you'll
actually be more open to understanding
this information
and and about the eggs and what i'm
talking about in the whole bit
what about the people who are 102 years
old what are the people who are 90 years
old and ate eggs their whole life they
didn't have the pathogens we're up
against now we're up against mutations
that are different we're up against over
60 varieties of epstein-barr not one
variety of epstein-barr we're up against
toxic heavy metals like never before in
history we're up against mercury like
never before in history so you need to
know that we're up against all these
different toxins and all these different
poisons and we're up against things
we've never been up against
and and people that the the last
dinosaurs that are 102 102 years old
that are 99 years old and 98 years old
god bless them the last dinosaurs
have less of that in their system they
got less of that and they were exposed
to less pathogens but that changed
that all changed why do you think we
have teenagers that are laying in bed
suffering with like full body pain and
fatigue
why do you think there's there's there's
children that are sick to the degree
they are and getting diagnosed with
autoimmune every every minute why do you
think there's people in their early 20s
that can't go to college anymore or
can't pursue their career after college
or can't do anything
why do you think there's people like
literally suffering why do you think
everybody's getting diagnosed with a
thyroid condition
that never happened back then that never
happened with the old days of what
happened
so and look even if you raise your own
chickens have your own chickens
have the best chickens in the world that
egg will still feed bugs
bottom line you can still keep your
chickens if it's therapy you can still
keep your chickens and feed them and
have them lay eggs and and maybe there's
somebody that doesn't care about this
information you can give the eggs to
because they want to eat the eggs no
matter what and they don't care about
this information she could find somebody
but
the point is even if you raise your own
chickens just the eggs will feed
if you're con look i've known people
over the years raising their own
chickens
the most amazing eggs dark dark colored
yolks
like incredible dark orange yellow yolks
like incredible and but they're
suffering with like
fibromyalgia and rheumatoid arthritis
and they got all the joint pain and
their back creaks and hurts and they
they go out to the chicken to the
chicken shack and they're
and they're you know and they're they're
out there and they're they're collecting
their eggs but they're
they got all kinds of problems and they
got glaucoma developing and they got all
kinds of different
symptoms and they're they're in their
50s but they're like they're they're
feeling like they're 85-90 they feel
like they're a hundred
no don't eat the eggs don't eat the eggs
and what about you know look be mad at
the industry
that raised the bugs and pathogens
with your food that was a good food
that was a great food that's the irony
see i think eggs
was an amazing food you know back in the
old days
it wasn't the most nutrient-rich food
but it was a survival food that's why i
think it was an amazing food because
back in the old days
it was an incredible survival food when
nothing else was around in the moment if
you can get an egg
it was a really good high caloric
survival food that's why
that's i mean that's why i even like
eggs in that sense it's
it has a history of that but it's
changed
you know be mad at the industry for
taking those eggs and ruining them be
mad at the industry don't be mad at me
for dropping the news on you'd be mad at
the industry for what
they've done to eggs that's really
important to know
you know so what about the people who
can say i'm taking away everything they
can eat so what about those people
that's a good question because
you know that's a question i i hear all
the time is oh you know medical medium
you're you want everybody on celery
juice and you're taking away everything
they eat
that's not true medical medium
information in all the books gives you
the most food to eat than any of the
diet systems out there what about
what about when you go and get your food
allergy food sensitivity testing and
take away
30 fruits and vegetables and herbs away
from you're not even allowed anything
what about that i mean what about all
the diet belief systems out there that
all these years that strip people of all
eliminate all the foods elimination
plans
and they get rid of your fruit what
about all the diet systems what about
all the diet belief systems that get rid
of your fruit including the vegan
systems now out there they get rid of
your fruits and your nightshades
i'm the only guy out there the only the
only books and information
and give you more things to eat than any
of the other diet belief systems
so if anybody thinks i'm the food police
quite the opposite it's just that the
difference is i know what foods to avoid
because i know what causes illness
i want you to know that okay so the
medical medium information the book
series the medical books
it's all about knowing what to avoid so
you don't feed the bugs and the
pathogens
that's what it's all about and i only
tell you that what foods feed those
pathogens
and to not be fooled okay and don't be
fooled when you see young people because
it's confusing i get it
when you see them you know young people
they're seemed indestructible and
they're
and they're they're in the gym and
they're they're removing gluten and
removing some bad stuff out of their
diets and they're choosing
choosing to do egg whites and they're
cooking their eggs in coconut oil
and they're exercising they seem symptom
free it's a short
short duration of time it's a short
duration of time
because they may seem indestructible but
i've been in this for 35 years
and i and i talk to doctors all the time
and it's like no one's
no one's getting away with it bottom
line
that's what i'm trying to say and when
and when it does hurt you later i
guarantee you
one something something that when you're
young and you're exercising and you're
doing your thing
and you believe if you believe in what
you're doing and you're you're eating
pretty good and all of that and you
think you're indestructible and when
something happens
you start getting symptoms like you will
because everybody does
i'm gonna tell you right now you're
never gonna blame the egg
you're never gonna blame the egg you
won't be blaming that
but that you'll never blame the egg
bottom line so it's important to know
you know you'll blame a piece of fruit
you'll blame something else but you
won't blame the egg
so look i have nothing to gain like i
said about any of this
it's just about you healing so if i call
that some of the gain then
yeah i call that something to gain you
healing it's called you healing
being empowered and not disempowered so
a lot of
there's a lot of women disempowerment
going on with the medical industry still
to
to this day and everybody bought into it
women being told it's their genes
it's complete total disempowerment
because that you walk around as a woman
thinking your jeans are faulty
and then they're garbage that's what
they're teaching women right now
they're teaching women that their body's
attacking itself and it's their fault
they're also teaching women that it's
all in their head and they're creating
it with their thoughts
so that's another thing too okay you buy
into that
you just buy into their tricks and games
of disempowerment
of body shaming so remember that too
eggs are a catapult basically
they're a catapult of getting people
sick
here's how it works women are world
changers
they change the world the industries
know this
though in these industries have been
trying to keep women down
for decades and decades and decades
because women change the world for the
positive
okay they make things happen that's what
they do
okay we know that that's the bottom line
so keeping women disempowered
training them that their body's faulty
their genes are faulty and their immune
systems are attacking itself training
them to eat eggs
the very foods that feed viruses and
pathogens training them that it's all in
their head and they're creating it with
some kind of like woo-woo
training them that they're crazy or lazy
or bored and that's why they're fatigued
all these years so whatever it is that
they're training them to do
it's to keep them down keep them
disempowered because they're world
changers and that's the bottom line
eggs feed every tumor cyst every fibroid
every single cancer every single any
kind of reproductive system
eggs feed all of the very things women
are afraid of and worried about
that's what eggs feed okay so that just
goes to show you right there
endometriosis pcos eggs
feed these it's so important to know
this okay
so they're told to eat eggs every
morning they're told to eat eggs every
morning it's almost like a joke played
on everybody
so women are told to eat eggs every day
every morning to keep them sick
and disempowered and then when they get
the first hashimoto's thyroiditis
diagnosis they're told that their body
is destroying their own thyroid
it really breaks the soul down in a
woman and it breaks the soul down in
people and it breaks them down
it kicks them down a notch and it
weakens them
you can become empowered you can learn
you can learn about the information you
can learn about how to protect yourself
go to the library get the book out
take it out for free don't even buy it
just get the book out for free if you
need to
and just give it a chance read it know
that other people are reading it all
around the world in healing
it's important to know that you actually
feel like you have the support
so look these youtube live series i love
them
this is incredible you guys i'm honored
to be here too
um it's incredible i'll be doing more
videos with health like this where i'm
on here alone doing them
but i'm also going to have episodes
where i'm bringing on guests and
surprise guests
because i'm bringing on friends i'm
bringing on friends i'm bringing on old
old friends
special friends i think some of you
would be really really
excited about these episodes coming up
bring on personal
personal friends that are dear to me i'm
bringing on some doctors i'm bringing on
some dentists too some lab techs
bringing on some scientists and bringing
on some other people too
all of it people with their medical
medium healing stories
too so guests people healed from medical
medium information and bringing them on
to
so this is like a new thing and i'm
really excited about this i'm blown away
you're here with me and i'm honored
actually that you were here with me
today i hope you had some celery juice
this morning like i did
mine's been sitting for quite a while
it's been sitting all morning i made it
really early this morning and i never
got around to drinking it
um i know that i'm with you and i
understand
your struggles i understand you're
suffering i understand what you've been
through
um i know what you guys are going
through i know what it's like to go
through doctor after doctorate of doctor
out there because i've seen people do it
and i know what they go through
just know that i care and it's all about
healing and getting the right
information
so until we do the next youtube live
series i want you to be there keep your
notifications ready
click that bell make sure you got your
notifications on make sure you're here
with me
because we're not messing around we're
about getting the truth out
hell or high water no matter what okay
it's about making sure you guys get
better
and uh we're only working with truth
here we don't work with fake truth
only the real truth okay bless your
hearts
god bless you love you