aws bar and grill
yeah
we got buffalo chicken wings
we got fries
we got everything here yep we're also
running a sale
lyman's yep wymans.com
the yeah famous wild blueberry juice
okay
i just got to keep busy here
sir what would you like
shot of whiskey
here's one right here
and what would the misses like
okay mrs gets this
man what would you like over there
another shot
okay
coming right up
i got one here for you didn't grab right
there
i forgot about you guys you finished
yours
hopefully you're not getting too tipsy
did you get one too
yes aws bar and grill
we're here another shot
okay mrs ferguson would you like one now
too i see you just came downstairs
your husband would you like one
okay fantastic
we're gonna be making honey orange wild
blueberry refreshers would anybody like
that would you like one of those as well
i see you have blueberry juice on top of
your head
i am going to have to do something about
that
at aws bar and grill
we have the most excellence of service
here and i'm going to make sure we
take care of that wild blueberry juice
right on top of your head
there we go nice and good
fantastic did you like that
we pride in our service here aw bar and
grill yes we do indeed
fantastic we're gonna be making all
kinds of drinks here i have a new drink
idea at aw farm grill
we're gonna put some ice in here
we're gonna put some wild blueberry
juice in here too
oh this one's running low
i'm gonna have to talk to the boss
let's see we're gonna put a little wild
blueberry juice in here
fantastic we're going to get a lime
oh are you getting too tipsy
yes
you like that drink
fantastic
oh i forgot coming right up i'm so sorry
i have these
fried french fries right here can i move
your side over
okay
there we go
best service i'm gonna put wild
blueberry juice in here we're gonna put
some lime juice in here too
and then
we're going to pop a touch of orange
juice in there
fresh squeezed orange juice at aw's bar
and grill
we're going to put a little honey in
here too
this is called the aw special
would you like one
let's keep the top on
yes i'm an experienced bartender
over 25 years of bartending
what kind of glass shall we use for this
i don't think this is the proper
sir i know this is a champagne glass but
i'm going to use it
this is a champagne glass
now this is
there we go i hope everybody likes this
drink
this is a very good drink i
do say
so
okay
stay organized here
i'm going to try this delicious
spritzer i'm going to call it the
spritzer now
delicious would you like a little taste
of this right here
no
you wouldn't like a taste
i think you're completely drunk right
now
ah
okay
is everybody on
we're live right now and we're doing
this is the first of all lymans.com
10 off on your order you can get a case
10 off
two cases 10 off off
five cases ten percent off three bottles
ten percent off and if you do the
subscription
it's ten percent off in the first order
on the pers on the prescription
if you do the prescription
it's five percent off from there on out
on every order it's incredible the
subscription anyway wymans.com so you
guys i'm gonna make a couple of drinks
honey orange and wild blueberry
refresher you guys know i work with
wyman's i want to keep this stuff alive
i want to keep it out there because i'll
tell you right now
friends family anybody i've ever
recommended to they feel better
that's what they say they feel better
and that's what i love about it the
manganese content in this juice is off
the chart good to see you guys on tick
tock we're live on the other platform
stu we're live on telegram youtube
facebook rumble
we're even we're even live on twitch too
so which is you know twitch we're live
on that as well we're live on my website
and
medicalmedium.com we're live on
medicalmedium.com which is utterly
insane which is the coolest thing i've
ever seen actually you guys we're live
there so you can go to my website see
when i when i'm live and i'm on there
live now so anyway
we're making some drinks i'm going to
talk about wild blueberry
we're going to talk about wild blueberry
juice we're going to talk about the
antioxidants we're going to talk about
the power
the antioxidants have chris stitch
exactly is it twitch or it's twitch
right it's twitch it's switch i like
that one it's twitch all right
so
a lot of things to understand is as we
age why do we age like as we're aging
you can age good and you can age bad but
we all age you can't stop from aging you
can't shut aging down a hundred percent
where it stops okay it doesn't work like
that because
all right as the earth is traveling
around the sun
it's impossible to stop the earth from
traveling around the sun so you're going
to age
but
there's a difference between aging badly
or aging
goodly it's goodly a word right so aging
good or aging bad and that's the
difference right there so we're not
going to be able to stop the aging
process completely because the earth's
going around the sun
and every time it goes around the sun we
age regardless of what but
physically
everything matters as far as what we put
inside our body to stop from oxidizing
to stop the oxidation process
everything matters
to stop all of the decaying that happens
inside our body right stop the process
of acids eating us up alive stop the
process of chemicals and pathogens and
everything getting to our
bones and getting to our organs and
getting to our brain and getting to our
liver right
all of that matters
so
when it comes down to it when it comes
down to it we want that antioxidant
power
because that's critical
for our survival it just is antioxidants
play a huge role
in the whole free radical thing so what
is the free radical thing anyway what is
it
it's any kind of toxin that's floating
around in our bloodstream in our body
any kind of poison that's in the air
that we breathe any kind of
you know
toxic substance that we were born with
inside our body passed down from
generation from generation
anything we get exposed to
from anything that's floating around
anything we ingest right all of it toxic
heavy metals pathogens and everything so
basically that's just one summing up one
big free radical circus right there and
our cells are up against all of that
that's what happens so we can age kindly
and we can age unkindly right
so the key is how we protect ourselves
from that aging process at least giving
them a shot so as we're putting
ourselves through what we put ourselves
through all the years of caffeine people
have done or all the years of
pizza they've done or all the years of
burgers or all the years of exposure or
whatever it is that they're up against
throughout their life all the years of
stress all the years of adrenaline
it's critical that our cells stand a
chance so antioxidants are a big part of
it anthocyanins polyphenols antioxidants
all matter
and so the thing i love about wild
blueberry and wild blueberry juice has
manganese in it
right so it has
naturally occurring manganese in it and
a very amazing amount of it which is
incredible and that's the thing about
the wild blueberry manganese is that
is that mineral
right that links
the antioxidant use inside our body and
that's the connection right there so
manganese is critical when it comes down
to antioxidants manganese is critical
when it comes down to cells and organs
in every single part of our body and so
when people drink wild blueberry juice
and they say like a family member says
wow i feel better
because i had some and i feel better
or if someone drinks it and they feel
like they're stabilizing
or they feel like they're feeling
stronger or they feel energy come back
or they feel a headache go away or they
feel right
or they feel their dizziness go away
i got a friend that's
dizzy on and off throughout the day
every time
they started what they started up with
the wild blueberries you start doing the
wild blueberry juice they call me up
they're like how come it goes away
and so it's it's one of these things
where
and i'm not saying it does that i'm just
saying these are experiences people have
that i see out there right
and so anyway what i love about the wild
blueberry juice though is the color
it's one of the things i love those
anthocyanins that color
is very special all in its own so we
have to realize what's in that pigment
what's going on inside of there all
these things matter so anyway we're here
i'm making some drinks i just want to
give you guys a run down the sales on
right now wymansweymans.com
10 off
right
so 10 off on your first order or just on
your order right now
you can just order every day you can
order today you can order again two days
from now you can have a you can order a
week from now right now it's ten percent
off every single order you do which is
incredible and if you do their
subscription
so great so great you do their
subscription it's a whole nother thing
because you get the ten percent and then
five percent from there on out
every month so it's really incredible
someone asked sylvia said how much to to
drink you can do this thing where you
just do a little bit each day where you
do a shot each day right you do two
ounces
right first one down
well i had a couple of earlier a couple
of them earlier
before we had a tech problem
so you can do a little bit of a shot
each day
i have people they put them in my family
members i put them into their smoothies
they do them in their heavy metal detox
movies whatever people that put them in
their smoothies in general
all right so let's make a drink right
now we're going to make honey orange and
wild blueberry refresher
that's what we're doing now
so let's get a cup out
all right so in this one we're gonna put
a whole bunch of wild blueberry juice in
this
so let's crack open a new bottle
is what we're gonna do good to see you
guys
sophia said okay great just ordered
you won't be disappointed it tastes
incredible
you know what i noticed too
it's not sickly sweet so it's not when
people see this it's not sickly sweet
like grape juice no way
no way it's pleasant it's refreshing
it's not sickly sweet at all you can
taste the medicinal properties it's an
entirely different experience which is
incredible you gotta understand like
what it takes to actually get these out
of the field harvest them
get them to the press
press them
get the juice in the bottle and i'm
going to talk about the
why the quality matters and everything
else that's happening with the quality
of this as well so that's important too
does not raise blood sugar
right
low glycemic for the people who are
worried about blood sugar like raising
blood sugar or anything
because the berries are low glycemic
fruit that's what that is it's a low
glycemic fruit for the people that are
worried about that that's a whole nother
game all on its own right
all right so let's get some wild
blueberry juice in here that's what
we're gonna do maybe we'll get a
close-up to this drink too as well
so we're gonna put
a whole bunch in there because now we're
making
right
so i'm putting roughly about like you
know cup a little over a half cup right
there while blueberry juice right then
i'm gonna put some freshly squeezed
orange juice in there too
i'm gonna knock some of this in here
freshly squeezed orange juice this is a
delicious one
okay and then we're gonna do some honey
you can do maple syrup if you want
so i'm gonna put a little honey in here
this is an incredible drink all on its
own
so great so great okay
and then we're gonna put some ice in
here let me mix this one up a little bit
this is the honey orange and wild
blueberry refresher
all right you guys
so far we got the orange juice in here
we got the wild blueberry juice we put a
little honey in here we're gonna drop
some ice in there next
get a couple of ice cubes right here
you can put as much ice as you want in
there you can put four cubes five cubes
i think i put like five or six in there
okay
all right there we go that's the first
drink
and this drink is incredible right now
i'm gonna try this
that's insane that's insane
seriously you're looking at it right
there
amazing okay i'll show you guys on tik
tok
what do you think right there right
incredible
you have a little bit of raw honey i
mixed in there if you want to use maple
syrup you can i got the wild blueberry
juice i got the orange juice you guys
saw me make it how quick was that you
have people over you make them these
drinks i'm telling you they're going to
be blown away
and their health drinks
that's the whole point
david says that's insane renee says why
do you say to only drink two to four
ounces because
that's what i do when i recommend it for
family and friends for like medicinal
purposes right you can drink more than
that
but i'll say look take a shot of it
every single day
every single day take a shot of it
that's what i tell family and friends
every day take a shot right but i mean
honestly i drink a lot more than that
every single day
personally you know i'll take a shot and
then i'll take another shot i'll keep it
on my desk i'm working i'll take another
shot
i got one in the car
i got a bottle in the car the whole bit
but this one's really really tasty
a little bit of that orange in there and
that honey
this is really
an incredible
incredible flavor
let's make another one right here too so
i'm going to move this one over you guys
so
and you guys you can do a lot of
different things if you just want to
take a champagne glass
right
just a champagne glass alone you can you
can go that route too because i made
that
fancy drink
a little while ago right but you can
just do champagne glasses you can do
wine glasses
you can do a lot of different things
with it too when you have people over
all right so the next one we're gonna
make is a sparkling wild blueberry juice
and lime so let's do it
that one we're using a champagne glass
here it is okay
so this is gonna be fun we're gonna put
a little bit of blueberry juice in this
one
we are
okay
a little bit of blueberry juice in there
like that then we're gonna do some
sparkling water
next
we're not going to do ice in this one
little sparkling water
here we go
this is a champagne
i think we're going a little too high up
on that
we're not trying to fill that
now we're gonna get a lime
don't throw fruit around when you have
all this going on
all this blue juice going around don't
throw anything that's just my advice
if you have carpets that's a lime with
no juice in it how do you like that oh
we got a little bit in there
so we're gonna put a little lime juice
in this one so we got the sparkling
water
this is the sparkling wild blueberry
juice and lime
drink
nice
you don't want you when you're serving
it you don't want it kind of gross
looking where there's some lime or
something on the side let's just clean
that up
right
and then
this is what we're going to do we're
going to get another lime
right here
we're going to cut this you guys want to
look at this for a second
we're going to cut a nice little wedge
here we are look
you guys on tick tock we're making
drinks hang around non-alcoholic drinks
although
baby grogu
and baby grogu's cousin
had a lot to drink today
so how are you doing are you feeling
better
we're gonna cut this little piece here
here we go
all right we're gonna do this little
pop this right here
that's this one right here you can feel
very sophisticated with this one too
right
this is a great one if you have company
over and one of them is a snob
so you have company over and somebody
brings a snob over to with them you know
and they're like what is this they come
over there and
and you got a snob there you can just
you can just give this one to the snob
and say here like thank you
just kidding gail says so
you are okay with sparkling water would
love that once in a while is a fun drink
you know i wouldn't be drinking
sparkling water every single day i
wouldn't be drinking it
every hour like you're doing lemon water
or you're doing some kind of water or
spring water i wouldn't do it that way
it's just for fun
drinks get together or something like
that
yeah
and uma says we thought it was grogoo's
gf yes that's what it is
it's grogue's gf exactly
this is a really good good drink
you guys
this is really good
really really good you would love it i'm
telling you all right so
now we have two drinks already we have
the honey orange and wild blueberry
refresher we have sparkling wild
blueberry juice and lime we have shots
now too i'm going to move these shots
over
we have the shots
i mean i knocked down a couple of shots
every single morning i mean that's what
i do i'll just knock down a couple of
shots every single morning
and then you can do all kinds of stuff
you can do the wine thing if you want
right you can do that like
i mean honestly i treat this like a wine
now i'm not a wine drinker
right
but you can treat this like a wine
very easily
especially if you have company over
fantastic and it goes great with meals
too
dinners
any kind of meal goes really good with
too so
and you can
yes
i have a glass of wine here
oh yes
oh dear
i think this is the too much of a dry
wine
i didn't want it this dry
let's see how dry it really is
i think i learned at this one place that
you can spit it back out
you can just spit it back out is there a
spitting platoon here
i need a spitting platoon i'm at a wine
tasting
winery right now everybody spits
they all spit into a platoon they do i
need a splatoon please
yes
i have to find one
okay i'll take another sip of this dry
wine
ah
wait a minute are you charging me for
this wine
how much is it fifty four thousand
dollars a glass i think that's a
perfectly good price
especially since i'm a trillionaire it
doesn't affect me at all i'm gonna buy
this vineyard yes indeed
yes it's so good to be rich
why honey would you like a glass of wine
i will pour you one myself but i've
never done anything before like this
yes
i'm a spoiled rich person who's never
done a thing
i've never worked a day in my life and
i'm pouring a glass of wine for my deer
instead of having the butler do it
yes butler am i doing it right oops bye
dear i'm gonna give you a glass of wine
myself personally here you go dear drink
that glass of wine
oh dear i dropped it all over the place
okay
anyway you can do the wine you can go
the wine route if you want which is a
great route i'll take that back thank
you
you can go to the wine room and you can
just make a whole bunch of drinks you
guys can get creative what you do is you
can just get
right you get the you get the blueberry
the wild blueberry juice
got a it's not blueberry it's wild so
it's a wild food we're going to go into
that a little bit too you get the wild
blueberry juice and you can do anything
with it you can switch this out you can
make a lot of different drinks what you
can do
is this frozen
i gotta get my bartender skills back up
what just happened
i think it's a slippery
if you use white towels i just have a
little
tip just
be cautious if you're using white towels
victoria rising from the ashes says
thank you for the laughs mmm
what do you mean i wasn't trying to be
funny
now i'm embarrassed
you're welcome
now you can do a lot with this okay you
can get a lot of drinks going on so what
i'm going to do is just to pour the rest
of this because i don't want to waste
any of the juice
i will drink all of it and
so you can do you can do some amazing
things with it you can do a lemon
version okay so let me cut open a lemon
right here now lemon honey
goes incredible together right
so i'm gonna drop some lemon in here
some reason i'm trying to find my way
here we go
so i'm going to drop some lemon in here
getting kind of messy you guys by the
way there's a sale i forgot to
mention forgot to mention about the sale
wymans.com you guys know i'm working
with wyman's this is a gift
in my opinion this product
because it's it's actually supersedes
what's out there this is wild you can
use the code wild when you do it too
code wild
wild the code wild right 10 off on any
order
incredible what an amazing amazing sale
which is which is just phenomenal right
okay but it's a it's a gift
i mean from heaven really that the wild
blueberries are even here on this planet
to help us which is incredible all on
its own and then the harvesting being
able to harvest them get them into a
juice and we'll talk about this this
juice is not hpp
and that's something to understand right
so
people think they're buying raw juices
when they're not someone said is this
raw no it's not raw raw is
you take the fruit like this
right
and you squeeze it and you drink it
that's raw
now if you see something that says it's
raw
on the shelf and it's got like an
expiration date of two weeks or a month
and it's all those juices and they're in
bottles those aren't raw
those are not fresh
those are hpp they're pasteurized so you
have to understand what's happening so
you're not getting any raw juice unless
you take celery or something and you run
it through a juicer
or you take a raw fruit but the wild
blueberries they're only around in north
america for this very short window of
harvesting so no one has the chance to
just get it fresh right meaning like
picked off well what they do is they
pick them
right
they freeze them
so we have the frozen wild blueberries
which is incredible that's one of the
amazing things about the wild blueberry
you freeze them right we can also
press them
and make them into this incredible juice
which is a whole other thing too
but when someone says oh it's not raw
it's pasteurized what they don't
understand is every juice that's in the
market doesn't matter where it is in the
cold section you think all the juices
you're getting are raw when they're not
all those different brands all those
marketing strategies they have or
they're fresh and they say raw they're
not they're actually it should be legal
when they say that should actually be
illegal because
they're not disclosing the fact that
it's every bit of it's been pasteurized
and here's the problem
they're using hpp
that pasteurization damages
damages the integrity of those
phytochemical compounds it damages it
because they're using
uh they're using a high pressure
pasteurization which
injures
the cell structure of everything people
don't realize that so
they don't do that here right they don't
use that which is incredible so that
part alone is off the charts amazing
which which is a big deal so the
medicinal properties stay intact that's
the whole point with this
and that's what i love right there so
that's important is all on its own um
okay so you guys sail wymans.com check
it out right
and ten percent off five well ten
percent off with the code wild wild so
you can order as much as you want ten
percent off which is incredible and you
can do another order and ten percent off
if you do their subscription it's 10 off
for the first order then 5 percent you
don't need the code wild for the
subscriptions just letting you know
so is it okay to drink wild blueberry
juice while on the mono eating cleanse
look i have i've done all the mono
cleanses
i have but it's up to you you know i
mean you don't you don't have to right
doesn't call for it you could wait til
your monoplans is over
or whatever but that's that's what i
tell family members because i have a
family member on the mono cleanse now
right and they're like can i have some
wild blueberry juice
so it was like yeah i mean you could you
could
technically have some but i but if
you're doing the cleanse long term i
have a family member that's been doing
the monoclines long term they've been
doing it for eight months
right
and since they're doing it for eight
months
you know i said well you can drink the
juice anytime you want after the eight
months because you're doing it so good
you're doing the monocline so perfectly
this family member's doing it so
perfectly so long term
right and then a doctor friend of mine
is actually on the mono cleanse too
and loves the mono cleanse got rid of
all his problems got rid of his ibs got
rid of his digestive problems got rid of
his acid reflux got rid of his bloating
got rid of his fatigue like all these
things it got rid of and he was like
well can i have wild blue red so i'm
like yeah i mean at this point you
easily could and you can when you get
off the monoclines you can have it
so yeah incredible
so you guys you can make any drink
really with it that you like you can get
really creative so i put lemon juice in
here
all right
so you can do the lemon juice
let's get that going
we can put a little honey in there
you can put a little sparkling water
this is a lemon honey with sparkling
water
it's really good
right then you can take some mint
right just crush it
then you can drop a little bit of
blueberry juice wild blueberry juice in
there too
and this is a really good one right here
you can mix this one up
you can do so much and i'm only using
some ingredients
all right
for some reason that decided to blow
open and guess what that's why i like
doing things live
all right
i am going to change my shirt after the
show not now
so anyway
and then you got yourself a drink
i have 25 years of bartending
yeah because you're never supposed to
shake that
pressure builds up you ordered your case
of 12 today rudy amazing
darlene says oh no yeah
that's going to be fun
amazing
i'm back
we're going to capture that blooper you
guys 10 off every order
that you do which is amazing 10 off all
right five percent after that if you're
doing the subscription you don't need
the code wild
amazing you ordered three to try jamie
incredible
you won't be disappointed
what i recommend friends and family
is
you do a little bit
anytime you're feeling kind of low for
energy or anything like that
cold white spring may does soc think you
are so funny too
yeah something i'll tell you with soc
things
about
aw and what aw does third person
yeah i had mint in it yesterday's drinks
absolutely cat would do definitely
yeah i mean we're having fun here
you guys
got some french fries here too
because i'm going live
on ig
i'm going live on ig
in just a couple of minutes i will see
you there guys i'm turning ticktock back
on i'm turning telegram back on we're
going live
we're going live
i'll see