are you talking about foods that get us
in trouble and how important this is
foods that get us in trouble and what
it's all about so we're you know on the
medical medium number one New York Times
bestselling author of the medical medium
book series on healing people around the
globe books are all over the globe
helping people heal today I'm going to
talk a little bit about thyroid healing
and the epstein-barr virus too so I'm
covering deep into the epstein-barr
virus information no one's ever heard
before information that since I were
healing plus some other little tidbits
about it but I'm gonna go into foods -
foods that get us in trouble and why
they get us in trouble because it's so
important when you're sick and you're
struggling and you're suffering with so
many different symptoms and conditions
it's critical to know you guys what
foods can make it worse not because of a
theory not because of a theory out there
like avoid gluten because you know
inflammation but that nobody knows
anything about it or avoid dairy
products because of lactose intolerance
or it's mucus forming we're gonna go
into like the real reasons the true
causes to why foods get us in trouble
and how we stay sick and how that
affects our lives and where that gets us
in all of it so this is really an
important important show in episode
probably one of the most critical
episodes so we're gonna go into the
epstein-barr virus is responsible for a
lot of things and this is a critical
aspect of it because when you know what
its responsible for then you can
actually learn and how to heal it's the
most comprehensive book as I read
healing about the epstein-barr virus out
there this is the virus with over 60
varieties of mutations and strains so
what does that mean that means it's not
just one virus one pathogen that's what
it means it means that we have lots of
one kind see how it goes so that's an
important thing to know right there
because what that means is it's hard to
detect hard to find hard for doctors to
see it hard for bloodwork to even show
it all of the above it also means that
they're not on the radar of research and
science so when viruses mutate in
homes they actually become a little
different form of themselves creating
different illnesses and they have
different appetites towards foods that's
why what I was saying is foods that get
us in trouble because bugs actually eat
food so we're gonna cover all of this in
detail and you know and this is powerful
information you don't want to miss this
you want to stay on for this this is
gonna be really important so look
epstein-barr is responsible for a lot of
symptoms and conditions Hashimoto's
Graves
CFS ms hypothyroidism all of the next
most rises that'll I go anxiety even
depression and you know symptoms vertigo
tinnitus brain fog PCOS endometriosis
and that's just that's just a little bit
of it
EB V is responsible for a lot of
different things people are going
through so if you're saying to yourself
hey wait a minute I have balance issues
I have a little bit of her to go I have
some tinnitus I have different died
popping in the ears I have twitches and
tingles and numbness and I have fatigue
that the doctors not sure what it's
about they think it's my adrenals or
they're not sure I've seen bars
responsible for these and so much more
and that's why it's so it's so important
many people think I just believe evb
causes everything and they take issue
with that and I completely understand I
do I completely understand and it comes
down to one thing
so when critics skeptics think that I'm
all about epstein-barr and epstein-barr
only comes down to one thing those
critics haven't read the medical medium
books they haven't read the books it's
so important and many people think of
the celery juice guy and that's what it
is so it's all about celery juice and
celery juice only by the way okay come
buy celery juice right here and it's not
a real big one today but that's alright
so many people think I'm just a celery
juice guy to the guy that started the
celery juice movement around the world
and sure okay that's that that's true
but it's not that's not what I just
damned so what they don't understand is
that epstein-barr is not just one virus
creating people sicknesses it's the over
60 varieties
and they haven't read the medical medium
books to learn that information so it's
easy for a critic to just pop that out
there and say oh he's all about I've
seen but I don't even know about the 60
varieties and strains and mutations and
so it's really important seeing each
mutation does different things it's a
different beast so every mutation is a
different beast causing different
symptoms and conditions and that's
what's so important to know this means
that there's over 60 different pathogens
under the label epstein-barr so that's
why not just one virus not just one
pathogen under the label epstein-barr so
and each one has a different appetite it
likes to feed off of different foods
they all like the feed off of eggs and I
talked about that earlier so I tucked
that with why eggs make you sick in the
last you tube but you've got to see the
last one and I have an egg in front of
me right here but there's a lot of
different varieties of epstein-barr they
feed off of different foods and
everybody has different varieties that's
how it works
and so for example some varieties of
epstein-barr really love toxic heavy
metals so they like copper so here's how
it goes with eczema and psoriasis and
these I discussed these in thyroid
healing I discuss all these different
symptoms conditions and illnesses and
thyroid healing if you don't have this
book get it and educate yourself and and
be able to protect yourself and your
family it's so important so when the
Epstein when a variety of epstein-barr
virus likes copper sets the toxic heavy
metal that sits inside our liver it it
actually consumes it feeds off of it
releases it and when it releases it it
releases a powerful Dermott oxen that
floats through the bloodstream unknown a
research in science floats through the
bloodstream its services to skin and
when it surfaces to the skin the body
tries to push it out and that's what
causes eczema and psoriasis and that's
one variety of epstein-barr and so you
know what they what the race bridge
research in science loves to say is that
your body's attacking itself that your
body's attacking its own skin which is
impossible the body doesn't work like
that I can go into that a little bit
more later some varieties of
epstein-barr you guys likes mercury and
everybody has
in them everybody has certain levels of
mercury the toxic heavy metal mercury in
them is why I love the heavy metal detox
movie so I'm not just all about the
epstein-barr all about celery juice the
heavy metal detox loubies critical if
you want to heal it's so important and I
want you to know that so the medical
medium heavy metal detox movie is so
important and I could talk about that a
little bit later too so when a virus
like epstein-barr loves mercury when it
feeds off of it it releases instead of a
derma stalks in so much it releases a
neurotoxin so when it consumes the foods
it likes which I'm going into it why
foods get us in trouble I'm gonna go
into that a little bit it consumes the
foods it likes releases it eliminates it
goes to bathroom like we go to bathroom
when we eat okay viruses have to go to
bathroom pathogens have to go to the
bathroom and when it goes to the
bathroom it releases a potent powerful
neurotoxin and that neurotoxin floats
around in the bloodstream and wreaks
havoc on what its neurotoxic so it
wreaks havoc on the nervous system a
central nervous system now most of these
Epstein bars release a little bit of
derma tox ins along with it if you have
a little copper inside of you if you
have a little aluminum inside of you and
so you may get the combination of
neurological symptoms like fatigue which
is a neurological symptom or you may get
fatigue and a little bit of rashing
which could be very mild axilla or
patches rashes like lupus like when
people get diagnosed with lupus not just
the butterfly rashes but the different
rashes that's because you have the
neurotoxin surfacing and the derma
stalks in so that variety of
epstein-barr releases these especially
the neurotoxin it gives you the fatigue
it gives you problems like that you can
get diagnosed with multiple sclerosis
Lyme disease lupus chronic fatigue
syndrome and me so that's what the virus
does so this is powerful information
this empowers you this can take you out
of literally the hell of suffering this
information because it has it already
has for millions of people globally for
over 30 years
been doing this for 35 years helping
people get better with this information
that comes from my source so it's
important to have this so you can
actually move forward is this an about
anything else besides you healing it's
critical to know that so some varieties
of epstein-barr virus like the feed off
of cell tissue itself so they like the
feed off of cell tissue so instead of
just feeding off of a toxic heavy metals
like mercury or aluminum the virus likes
to feed off of your cell tissue so
thyroid disorders Hashimoto's
thyroiditis the inflammation that's
caused inside the thyroid and I talked
about that really really clearly if I
were healing okay and that what happens
is that variety of virus feeds off of
cells cells inside your thyroid and it
causes inflammation see it's not your
body attacking itself like they want you
to believe because that disempowers you
want to go into that a little later how
that that body shames and disempowers
and just really makes people feel like
the faulty really makes people feel like
they're worthless so I'm going to go
into how that works later on so when a
virus feeds off of cell tissue in like
forensic example feeds off of your
thyroid cell tissue you can get the
thyroid asaurus hyperthyroidism
Hashimoto's thyroiditis you get the
beginning stages of hypothyroidism and
you can be you could get the stages of
nodules you can get the stages of cysts
thyroid cancer so that's one variety of
epstein-barr many of them go to the
thyroid so many of them go to the
thyroid and do different things in the
thyroid so the viruses have mutated over
time there's over 60 varieties like I
talked about before but that's one type
and then you've got the aluminum feeding
viruses which is the epstein-barr
variety that loves aluminum and guess
where that goes to guess what happens
when that virus has an aluminum you know
desire and it eats aluminum and what
happens there is you end up with
vitiligo you end up with the white spots
the discoloration because here's how it
works so important to know this and the
virus feeds off of aluminum which sits
inside the liver that's where all our
toxic heavy metals go in that's why
say hey you guys you got to get rid of
your toxic heavy metals it's so
important and it matters so much that's
why I want you to do that really huddle
up look good good spirulina I always
talk about all the good stuff that you
need and and how the heavy metal detox
smoothie and the wild blueberries and
all of it because you've got to get rid
of the toxic heavy metals out of your
liver because when aluminum is sitting
inside the body and sitting inside the
liver you guys what happens is that
variety of epstein-barr loves to feed
off of it and when it eliminates it goes
to the bathroom and releases it it
floats around it surfaces to the skin
and it kills the melanin pigment cells
it destroys them and that's why you get
the spots the white spots everywhere
that's that variety of virus so you know
these are some examples of you know
foods that these different varieties of
epstein-barr like to feed on in the
moment I'm going to show you some other
foods and that's that's that's gonna be
a big one today - a big part of today so
you want to stay on for this this is you
don't want to miss this this is gonna be
really fun - look we eat to stay alive
we have to stay alive or we die okay
that's how it works here so does every
single packaging every single micro
organism on the planet living organism
has to eat something so when science
research keeps that all from you and
they don't tell you that they use
Mercury to keep these things alive in
labs that they feed all these bugs eggs
okay like I said and why eggs make you
sick if you haven't seen them and you
got to go back to that one and look at
that YouTube you know when you can at
that episode after this but so because
these these bugs need food so critical
to know every single living
microorganism viruses and different
varieties of viruses like different
foods this is advanced medical
information straight from my source that
public research and science is unaware
of yet and it's so important so when I'm
talking about what foods get us in
trouble and how foods get us in trouble
and all that one I talk about that later
it's advanced food information that
isn't out there because no one knows
they're all playing guessing games and
they don't know why foods really make
you sick so this is so great to notice
Nathan's been delivering it for years
and years okay so viruses take different
pathways so I'm going to talk about the
pathways where they go from the liver to
the thyroid to the ovaries different
areas okay one variety of epstein-barr
goes from the liver to the thyroid so
let's talk about that now we're heading
we're gonna head into that and then
what's left of that virus goes to the
ovaries and creates PCOS so PCOS a
reproductive condition okay a cystic
reproductive condition is caused by
epstein-barr that's what creates assist
assist a fluid-filled cysts cannot be
created on its own it doesn't work like
that I know they want people to believe
that it's the woman's body that's faulty
if something must be wrong with her and
then she's causing it I know this is the
medical system big pharma and you know
whoever else wants women to believe that
but see a fluid-filled cysts can't
develop on its own it doesn't work that
way there has to be a cause and there is
the epstein-barr virus and does go to
the ovaries it goes a reproductive
system it causes a lot of reproductive
problems I'm going to talk about that a
little later too so then also the the
epstein-barr virus it's inside the liver
and it goes straight to the fiber it
goes to travels to the thyroid it
creates hypothyroidism later for women
and and it can create it years later
somebody could have a milder form of
epstein-barr virus and it could create
hyperthyroidism years later somebody
could have a much more much more
aggressive variety on the 60 varieties
and it could create problems even more
aggressively coughs and bam you get the
worst Hashimoto's thyroiditis you're
really sick you're at the doctor's
office doctors telling you it's your
body attacking itself it's listed under
not on the in condition when really you
have a viral infection and that's what
it really is talking about thyroid
healing - incredible book to have if you
don't have it you got to go to
amazon.com and get it or go to the
library and get it for free I tell
people get it for free doesn't matter to
me I just want everybody to have being
from
and he'll so okay so let's talk about
other things here while another variety
of epstein-barr will go to the thyroid
but it'll also stay in the liver most
all varieties of epstein-barr do you
stay back into the liver a little bit
where they feed off of copper like I
said they feed off of other pollutants
inside the liver the livers a garbage
dump and that's why you know I wrote the
book liver rescue okay that's why I
wrote the book liver rescue livers a
garbage dump it harbors all these
different toxins so you know and and so
these viruses like the stay back into
the liver in the whole bit and they like
the feed off of copper to create eczema
and psoriasis viruses like the
epstein-barr love to create eye problems
they love to create floaters in the eyes
they even love to create glaucoma that's
one thing that happens
Epstein Marcos the breast tissue creates
breast cancer another variety of
epstein-barr will cause lupus will cause
multiple sclerosis another variety will
cause Lyme disease Lyme disease our
neural basically Lyme disease is
neurological Lyme it's neurological
condition it's basically neurological
fatigue and different tics and spasms
and twitches and weak nervous systems
and like you feel like your legs or
cement bags and it can be listed under
Lyme disease it dr. be like well you
probably got Lyme disease another doctor
might be like whoa you got a little bit
of this you got a little bit of that
everybody gives it different diagnosis
but so let's go into like that as we can
doctors are finally learning now because
of this information that Lyme disease is
viral so we're gonna cover that for a
minute if you got if you guys got a
second I'm gonna drink a little bit of
this because I'm I'm seeking out the
information got a little bit of celery
juice I hope you're doing your celery
juice I hope you are so important
okay so Lyme disease is no longer
bacterial sure the doctors will still
call it bacterial some of them still
think it's many of them still think it's
still bacterial but it's it was a
bacterial theory is what it was so all
that bombardment of antibiotics to women
mostly women and some men
over the decades the amount of
antibiotic abuse the negligence
over the decades I mean the Lyme trail
is brutal the line past is brutal it's
unbelievable
it's still not much better but because
of the medical medium information
because it went worldwide in all the
books around the globe and people got
wise and they learned that Lyme disease
was viral it's all changing now
that's how cats claw the herb is now
being used in doctors offices across the
globe and around the country
that's from original medical medium
information going back many years and so
there's a reason for that because it was
always viral and I'm gonna tell you
something that's really interesting if
you're like okay there's no way that's
not what it says out there he's wrong oh
yeah they secretly moved Lyme disease
into the autoimmune disease category
okay now in order to move Lyme disease
it can't be bacterial that's how it
works the medical medium books and
information has pushed the medical
system into the direction of putting it
in to autoimmune they wanted to classify
that now because it protects them is
what it does it also determines that
they don't know the true cause because
autoimmune disease causes are all
unknown by research and science the Lyme
disease was put into the autoimmune
category so that means they just decided
behind everybody's back basically they
just decided that bacteria is not the
cause that causes unknown for Lyme
disease so you got all these doctors and
all these decades of work and they're
all been told as bacteria and you got
the line labs all kind of working with
that and I could say well why does the
line lab come up with this and that the
line labs they work on a basis of
inflated inflammation so they work on
inflammation so when they say a Borrelia
and they say you have art nella and they
see it the B Ziya they don't see the
Bartonella they don't see them Ibiza
they don't see the Borrelia they just
see inflammation
system just like an anti-nuclear antigen
antibody test just like c-reactive
protein tests they're all inflammation
detecting tests so it's the whole thing
has been a scam and a sham for so long
with Lyme disease and they've been
making billions because of it on
antibiotics cuz that's the whole point
it was to make billions and billions and
billions and billions and hundreds of
billions of dollars off antibiotics for
decades and that's how it works so so
Lyme disease was placed into the
autoimmune category which they know they
don't have an answer now that's how it
works but you got all these you got all
these old dogs meaning they've been
doing it for so many years of pumping so
many antibiotics and so many people for
decades and they just you know they're
already married to their system that
they've been that they've been involved
with that was created by by the theory
to begin with and it's hard to come out
of that but the younger doctors doctors
have want people to heal they're
learning now about this information and
and some of the older doctors too and
have a lot of experience of learning
about it and it pushed it into the
different category so it's so important
to know this
um Borrelia Babesia Bartonella they're
not superbugs they can be killed off by
antibiotics extremely easy
they're not superbugs they're not like
MRSA nurses got a much higher rate of
healing through antibiotics is an
incredible mercy so much Merces a
superbug literally a superbug
but for some reason mercer can be healed
with antibiotics so why why can why
cannot be healed without the antibiotics
but yet Borrelia Bartonella can because
it can cause it does get killed off
because when you're viral
antibiotics do not stop viruses so
that's what happens you got a whole wake
of people suffering from Lyme disease
even today right now and getting Lyme
disease diagnosis and they were
bombarded with antibiotics that's why
Lyme doctors now are doing less and less
antibiotics and smaller amounts and
smaller dosages and milder forms of it
and then they're bringing in supplements
and all kinds of herbs and different
things because they know they're
learning because the antibiotics wreaked
havoc and broke people down made them
sicker for so many
decades I'm not against antibiotics I'm
not against antibiotics in the use
they're needed for for certain things
that's not what this is about but for
Lyme disease this huge mistake was made
see Lyme disease in early 1970s when it
was discovered there was a group of very
smart intelligent doctors and for 'allah
gist that believed it was viral but you
can't make money back then in the 70s or
the 80s because there were no
medications for viruses when a doctor
attorney when diagnosis was viral or
they believed a diagnosis was viral
there was no answer so no money was made
ever except for the doctor's appointment
itself but there were no drugs being
sold so they classified it as bacteria
so Big Pharma classified it as bacteria
to make sure they can sell tremendous
amounts of antibiotics that's how the
business runs so it was put so all these
doctors were indoctrinated to believe it
was bacterial so they bombarded people
on the MARTA people for decades made a
wake of hell and and I mean so many
lives were lost over this and it wasn't
the doctors fault I mean that's not what
it is the system creates this bacteria
cannot cause neurological symptoms I'm
gonna go into that for a little bit
right here thank you for coming on my
new youtube channel little bit covering
serious topics so you can learn and
he'll talk about thyroid healing you
don't have the book at amazon.com and
get it it's you won't make a mistake
getting that book when you read it
you'll be blown away I can't cover even
a fraction of the information in that
book so let's go into the whole bit here
of where we're heading now bacteria
cannot cause neurological symptoms
bacteria does not cause the aches and
pains it does not cause the tangles in
numbness does not cause the ringing in
the ears does not cause all the
different neurological symptoms the eye
floaters two twitches the spasms the
burning pain all over the body the
neuropathy burning pain on a feet
burning pain on the hands all of that
bacteria doesn't cause all of the
neurological impatient conditions
including that neurological fatigue the
eye floaters like I said the vertigo the
dizziness the tinnitus the severe
anxiety bacteria can't cause severe
anxiety so important to know they cannot
create neurotoxins see this is how it
works
bacteria when feeding off of food
can't release a neurotoxin only a virus
can so when bacteria eats the foods that
I'm going to show you guys if you guys
just came on and everything and you're
here right now I can't wait to show you
the foods and we're gonna talk about why
foods get us in trouble which foods get
us in trouble you won't believe it you
will be very happy about this episode so
when bacteria feeds off of foods then it
likes it can't release a potent
neurotoxin remember what I was saying
before a neurotoxin creates damage to
the neurological system it creates
damage in a way where it hampers it down
it dampers it down it brings it down and
he'd get fatigued and your legs feel
kind of heavy and you feel fatigued why
am i slept all these hours last night
why am I still tired I slept a zillion
hours last night why am I still tired
and that's what happens where you're
like what's going on and then you get
diagnosed a little bit of dream fatigue
then you get told your hormones are off
because the doctors have no idea why you
have T then you think well loss of
libido fatigue and all these other
things it must be my hormones it must be
something else and that's it happens and
if the fatigue sticks around too long
after they've played around with all
your different step stuff after if it
sticks around too long you might get a
final you might finally get a lot of
disease diagnosis you might get some
kind of other diagnosis then all of a
sudden they're looking for other things
so many women around the country mostly
women and then now this fatigue is
neurological fatigue and it's not
bacteria bacteria can't create a
neurotoxin which hampers and weakens the
nervous system you guys should watch
this whole thing all over again I'm not
even halfway done here but you gotta
watch this whole episode all over again
the information is really intense and
and I understand that so the body aches
and pains nerve pain all through the
body the fibromyalgia the tics the
spasms twitches these are all viral
symptoms you guys and people suffer with
it and it breaks my heart to know people
suffer that bad they don't have answers
they've been to ten neurologists so even
if you go to one neurology so you go to
your internist you go to your GP you go
to one a neurologist it's just too much
you know making appointments making
having your life all I've seen with
younger people to twenty years old and
nineteen years old and their life is
already about doctor's appointments I
mean what kind of world are we in right
now where science of research just
doesn't have the back
of people for with chronic illness when
there are answers it's amazing really so
look fibromyalgia multiple sclerosis
lupus PCOS reproductive problems and
then we Teresa's all these things all
these things that people go through the
hot flashes the heart palpitations so
many different systems it's symptoms
it's based on viruses it's based on
viruses releasing poisons and causing
problems this is why so many people's
Lyme disease get them to get the thyroid
test I mean their thyroid problem okay
they're one of the reasons why they were
put they pushed Lyme disease into the
autumn the autoimmune category is
because it was getting kind of
suspicious too with the medical medium
information going out there teaching
people about the thyroid problem being
viral and the thyroid problem being
epstein-barr because that information
came from the medical medium information
stats came from this source only that
your thyroid problem and your
Hashimoto's thyroiditis is caused by
epstein-barr and now you'll see data out
there because what they do is you know
they don't want the medical medium
getting all the credit all the time so
then they try to put they try to put
articles out there as if it came from
somewhere else but this this was way
before all of that I mean it's that well
document to be way before all of that
and what happens is the the epstein-barr
virus that causes thyroid problems for
the when they noticed everybody with
Lyme disease was getting thyroid
problems so that was another thing so
doctors are like scratching your head
they're like well you know what I mean
it's everybody has the thyroid problems
everybody has these other issues
everybody all the Lyme people have
fibromyalgia so just starting to belief
wait a minute we're off here because
bacteria doesn't cause any of that so
it's viral so it's so important to know
these things
that's why a majority of people have not
gotten better that's why a majority of
people have not gotten better on
antibiotics what I mean in majority I
mean the majority and antibiotic
treatments for Lyme disease that's why
they haven't gotten better because it's
viral so I'm just trying to spell it out
for you see you have you're empowered
you have the information you have the
strength all of it
and so many have suffered terribly I
mean it's it's devastating they lost
their lives they lost
likelihoods careers all these different
things people suffer with and they're
going through that now even when they
don't get a Lyme disease diagnosis and
you just got fatigued and you're broken
down I've seen people lose their
relationships I've seen I've seen so
many women lose their relationships you
know their fiance's and their you know
their husbands and so much going on
because cousins like well scratching
their head wall wait a minute how did I
did I buy into this this what is this
hush modus thyroiditis cuz you know how
guys are
I mean heads are like what is this
Hashimoto's thyroiditis what is this
what are these symptoms come on get out
of bed let's get moving what do you mean
you're tired and you can't you can't
function
I've seen people literally in tears you
know over the years crying to doctors
that are friends of mine the doctors
telling me about these stories and and
I've heard it myself too over the years
it's just unbelievable how it how it
works so so uh so uh the bottom line is
is Lyme disease is not what people think
it is what's going to the another
category here let's go let's talk
everybody has at least one EBV who's
sick
anybody who's sick doesn't just have one
variety it's easy to get two varieties
it's easy to get more it all depends on
what's happening in your life that's why
you want arm yourself know the truth
know how to he'll know what to do and
and and what you need to do to heal it's
so important so listen on this topic
today and everything else we're gonna
talk about the foods that get us in
trouble what that means how that gets us
in trouble what happens and I'm talking
about the epstein-barr epstein-barr
virus talking about this thyroid healing
book the whole bit so we're going into
it almost every person on the planet has
one variety of epstein-barr one variety
of epstein-barr it lives in the organs
it lives in the liver in the organs
going undetected by tests and
undiagnosed from doctors for years this
information I'm sharing with you is
still unknown to medical research and
science doctors do not know where to
look
for epstein-barr it's hard tests cannot
detect EBV in the liver or organs
there's no test
can detect epstein-barr in your liver or
organs that's how it works and they do
have tests for at EBV but not in the
liver and organs see doctors are looking
for symptoms and linking it to EBV now
because of the medical medium
information they're looking for symptoms
okay here's how it worked in the old
biggest Epstein Barr because some of you
might say well you didn't come up with
the ethene bar diagnosis or to figure
out like the Epstein bar no I didn't
Anthony Epstein you know that doctor
okay that genius found that virus okay
he did but see that viruses only
contributed to one thing back in the day
called yuppies disease that's that's
what it was contributed to malaise a
little bit of fatigue a little bit of
listlessness for a little bit in your
life and that's it
but it's that that's not what it causes
it causes that times a hundred in
everybody that's how it works so here's
here's the thing doctors I've worked
with over the decades
I help them troubleshoot their cases so
I spent years and years and years
helping out doctors with their
troubleshooting cases doctors have
compassion and they want information no
matter what because when they realized
after they come out of medical school
when I talk to doctors all the time
about this and the information isn't
there what they need why people are
filing in with all these symptoms and
conditions they want more and want more
and a lot more because they got into the
medical industry to get people better so
fatigue and listlessness and malaise of
the old days of Epstein Barr then that's
not how it works Epstein Barr causes so
much more look expand it be up see more
information and thyroid healing in this
book go to amazon.com or to go to the
library and get it for free this is the
Epstein Barr book of all time tyreq
healing medical medium series now
doctors around the world are using this
book so right here this book is in their
practice around the world and when
people find a doctor that's using that
book it's like a reprieve
it's like what so my body is not
destroying itself so if body's not
destroying the thyroid
actually can heal this is a virus and we
could work on trying to get some
antiviral protocols going and and
something changes in the person they
know they can heal so important to know
so look let's let's talk about some
other things why are there so many
epstein-barr mutations how did this
happen and how did these varieties of
epstein-barr get into our bodies so so
many people everybody has one variety
okay around the world basically but many
of us have two varieties three varieties
epstein-barr was raised in labs long ago
I'm gonna go into a big food thing
pretty soon I got a whole bunch of foods
here I'm gonna talk about what foods get
us in trouble so you've got to stay on
for that here's an egg that's a theme it
gets us in trouble you see you saw some
of you saw the why eggs make us sick if
you haven't go back to that one after
this one watch that YouTube learn learn
how to heal so epstein-barr was raised
in labs on chicken eggs that was one of
the fuel sources so chicken eggs the
hormones inside chicken eggs the natural
occurring ones not talking about the
agate ones that the industries do now
you know free-range organic whatever the
natural occurring hormone okay and the
natural current proteins
fed viruses raised in the labs that's
what they did okay somehow these viruses
escaped erasing labs and they escaped to
the public so you know we could use your
imagination on that many of you like to
think where could how could that have
happened
but they did and it happened the
original epstein-barr existed before
this the old epstein-barr before the 16
mutations the original epstein-barr
existed well before this and that was so
much it was so less aggressive it wasn't
problematic you guys but since that new
newer varieties that are severe and
potent very strong powerful and
neurotoxic have submerge or emerged
these strains have mutated over the
decades and now we're dealing with the
over 60 varieties I just want to cover
that really little deeper and they're
going to continue to me you take and
grow as the years move on why do you
think we have so much chronic illness
around the war
literally out of pace no one's ever seen
before
when I talk to doctors did like they're
like even with all of the health minded
information and no gluten and then this
and the bad and all the supplements out
there and those stores shelves pack of
supplements it's rising like never
before and so because the viruses are
tough they're tough to deal with and
they're passing from person to person so
let's talk about how that stuff
relationships body fluids that's how you
be these passed around a lot that's a
big one so I'm just saying so you know
you wanna you want to be careful along
the way is you're meeting people and
everything else because body bodily
fluids that can happen and and okay if
it happens and it happens and you get a
beat in the epstein-barr and they're
sick two years later or three years
later you work on healing it and you
work on healing it you get getting rid
of it and moving forward with your life
bottom line restaurants is a big place
to restaurants now I'm not trying to rip
down restaurants you know the industry's
a you know it's a it's industry you know
the sort of food and make people happy
so and a lot of people have the heart
soul in the restaurants but restaurants
are also place its Forks utensils that
aren't washed or sterilized properly
it's shrinking glasses that aren't
washed or sterilized properly if you got
lipstick on a glass it wasn't wiped off
completely and that and it's still there
it can contain and hold the epstein-barr
virus within the lipstick so if you've
got a coffee cup and you got old some
old lipstick on it that didn't kind of
scrub off you know in that diner or
somewhere or that place that holding
contains an Epstein bar virus very
easily this is how across I'm not trying
to make you phobic about it I'm not
trying to make you feel like you can't
ever eat out it's not it I'm just
letting you know it's easy to get the up
steam barbwire sharing plates of foods
to you know sharing plates of food
drinking down to somebody's clacks and
everything you know it's with a friend
and I was out in a restaurant and I
didn't finish I didn't finish my the
food I had in my plate and and and and
you know that with a few friends when
the friends grabbed my plate you know
we're really hungry and I go what are
you doing then they're just finishing it
off and what are you doing and they go
well with you I'm not worrying about it
maybe with you I'm not worried about it
but it's easy to actually get something
passed you know from one person to
another because that's how it's done
bodily fluids that's how the bug gets
around public bathrooms that's another
way this is important information it all
sounds innocent but the door handles on
public bathrooms you know I mean put
paper on the seat whatever you do I use
you should ship with paper on the seat
you know that's one thing here's a tip
in the public bathrooms to try not to
get things as you you know always have
some handy wipes in public bathrooms you
know washing your hands at the sink
everybody else does just kind of like
everybody else just went to the bathroom
now they're at the same touching
everything well you know what I like to
do is keep some handy wipes on me I
think that's actually a better option
but the other thing too with the public
bathroom thing that's one way that's
really popular with with transmitting
with actually getting the epstein-barr
virus is you want you in a public
bathroom flush the toilet before you
even start going to bathroom even if it
looks like it was flushed before
just give it a flush so whatever could
gremlin says could go in there and hold
it and throw some paper on the seat yeah
it sounds silly to a lot of you a lot of
you don't care like I get it and I have
respect for you 100% but that's what I
do
ok that's what the medical medium does
and he does it for a reason a good
reason so let's go into the four stages
of epstein-barr and we're almost to the
food part two no it's gonna be fun let's
go to four stages epstein-barr I've seen
bars four stages researches Sciences
unaware of it completely doctors are
aware of it now because of the medical
medium information you know if I were
healing book make sure you get it go to
amazon.com make sure you have that book
I can't I can't cover a fraction of that
book it's not even possible so stage one
the early stage you get up scene bar and
it incubates it sits in you that's one
of the stages you can get it passed down
from parents you can get your Epstein
bar passed down from parents you can get
it from other family members too you can
get it from other family members and so
it's important to know that meaning just
living in the house so you've got
brothers and sisters and you know and
they get it somewhere out there and
they bring it back and everybody's
sharing food and sharing this and
sharing that and absolutely so it's easy
to it's so easy to get different
projects but the early stage it can but
what happens is it sits in the bodies
person isn't it sits in the bloodstream
sorry about that sits in the bloodstream
and it lays dormant so that's what it
does that's the first stage you get you
pick it up somewhere you get it in
bodily fluids you get it at a restaurant
and get in a relationship and now it's
sitting in there incubating that's what
it does but things going to happen in
life you can be under a lot of stress
you can go through a lot you can you can
be you can go through something in your
life it's very difficult that causes
your immune system to weaken so it could
be a loss it could be a betrayal it
could be trust breakage it could be
somebody stabbing you in the back it
could be a relationship that went wrong
it could be somebody broke up with you
it could be maybe you're just a
miserable person because you're just to
your beer you just you're just been
through so much so much whatever it is
that's going on and and you've had a
hard time and you've had a hard life or
whatever the hardship is even if it's
not that hard to one person but it's if
it could be hard to you it could be a
big deal to you and you know people go
through so many different things and
they take things to heart and personal
ways that another person might not have
and that's everybody's right to feel and
have their emotions and all that but
heartbreak and betrayal all of that is
painful can weaken the immune system so
if you have that incubating epstein-barr
that you caught somewhere and it's just
been sitting in your system for a year
or two years three years five months a
month and then you go through some
adrenal stress you go through some
fight-or-flight you get some heartbreak
you get some betrayal your immune system
drops down a little bit it looks for
this and then there's the poor diet the
poor night we're going into that right
now let's talk about foods and the whole
bit a little bit why someone can eat
gluten or dairy or corn and not have a
problem and be fine when someone else
can eat that and get really sick or it
makes them sicker over time whether they
know it or not what
symptoms and conditions so let's go into
foods and food talk hope everybody is
doing good I got my celery juice right
here heading into a new part of this the
next part of this I see a lot of
comments and I really appreciate that
because all that's good so start with
right here so I got some milk right here
all right now they're all good companies
every every company I'm showing right
here it's all good companies but it's
not about that so I'm just covering
labels and you know I'm not ripping down
any brands or anything of course I'm
supportive of everybody trying to
survive out there in the world but milk
milk is actually a problem just so you
know so I'm gonna let you know milk
feeds the epstein-barr virus it does and
what happens is people think lactose
intolerance they think wait a minute you
know lactose intolerance is my problem
that's why I can't drink milk that's why
I have to stay away from milk but that's
fear so lactose intolerance is it
actually is an actual theory just so you
know what's really happening is the
epstein-barr virus feeds off of lactose
it feeds off of proteins in milk it
feeds off of sugars and no so it's
really important to know there's also
natural occurring hormones in organic
milk and really good milk high-quality
pasture-raised and so forth and if
somebody's heart is in creating the best
milk out there or the best product that
I'm gonna show I support them in that
sense because their hearts in it they're
creating good stuff but I'm talking
about sickness and the epstein-barr
virus I'm talking about happens when you
have the virus in you it's incubating
it's sitting in you and what happens
okay so when you're drinking milk see
none of the other diet systems that say
stay away from milk if there's one that
says stay away from milk knows why
people get sick and they're just playing
guessing games that's not what this is
I'm gonna teach you how you get sick
when you're drinking these things or
when you're eating certain foods so
you're really empowered so you have the
original information a source that
started basically this kind of stuff
going back 35 plus years ago so it's so
important no bugs love to feed off of
lactose protein and next
hormones occurring hormones in milk so
and milk will you'll see you'll hear out
there all with mucus forming you'll hear
from the different diet belief systems
out there well I'll commute this forming
stay away why is it mucus forming nobody
knows why it's mucus forming they just
say stay away from Dairy it's mucus
forming you'll hear that all the time
and all the different diet belief
systems and all that but what they don't
know is it's mucus forming because it's
feeding viruses and pathogens of all
kinds that's what happens with this kind
of thing when you're doing their
products you're feeding something when
you feed something it creates mucus this
is why so many people can drink milk and
eat cheese and eat other things and not
have mucus it's also why people can also
eat gluten they can take a nude stereo
they can do whatever they want and they
don't get sick and they seem okay
someone else drinks some dairy they're
in the bathroom because above fed off of
the lactose released it created
inflammation and now you're sitting in
the bathroom with IBS because of a
pathogen not because of a food because
of a pathogen this is why somebody else
can eat the food and not have that see
how important it is to know these things
the power of that can do me for you in a
lot of different ways it's not that you
have a faulty body it's not that you
have an enzyme theory there's a theory
that an enzyme you don't have to in
order to actually have dairy products
that's a theory because they don't know
what causes illness still science
research has no idea and science
research knows nothing about food they
don't know nothing about food when you
drink it or consuming or eat it and it
enters in the stomach you think there's
an actual test or a machine that can
determine when you eat something what's
happening is scrambling through the body
and the body is breaking it apart or
what's going on they don't have anything
in science at all there's nothing they
have they just have theory and guesses
and so it's so important to know this so
when it comes down to it that's the no
when it comes down to and then we got
some cheese right here okay
same thing with cheese now remember
there's also fat in milk and there's
also fat and cheese there's fat in dairy
what the fat does is if it strengthens
the virus more so it strengthens
hodgins more strengthens epstein-barr
more so when you're eating the cheese
you're putting all that fat inside of
you when you're when your blood gets
filled with too much fat inside and I've
been saying this for decades and decades
when it's when it's when when your blood
gets so filled with fat your oxygen
levels drop what do you need to stop
epstein-barr not just your immune system
but you need oxygen in your bloodstream
the higher fat content in your
bloodstream pushes out and basically
hampers down oxygen levels inside the
bloodstream so those oxygen levels are
how we fight and battle epstein-barr is
how it works so you know the bottom line
is when you have epstein-barr incubating
in you getting ready to fire up and
start and you're you're eliminating your
oxygen levels because you're bombarding
your liver with all this fat intake you
got the dairy products even if it's good
dairy even if you're having it once a
week it's still like it still can get
you in trouble you'd if you're drinking
milk and just your coffee or whatever
you're doing you know it still can get
you in trouble but these are the things
these high-fat dairy products or even
low fat dairy products still can feed
the epstein-barr from what they have in
it so here's an example right here some
feta cheese that's another cheese -
because some people say why you'd feta
cheese that's much better it's it's
lighter I can have it on my salad I can
have it still feed epstein-barr virus
and it'll still go off after the
hormones and the best energy is possible
and the best cheddar cheese and the best
Swiss cheese and so forth so you have to
know that this is why we get sick from
foods this is why we don't do good with
food so you be somebody that does great
with these foods for a little while and
all of a sudden start getting act and
you're like what's going on and you
start getting acne you start getting
something else they'll feed any pathogen
like a please caused by streptococcus
it's caused by that bacteria but this
will feed any pathogen everybody so you
need to know that and that's how it
works so I'm going to show you some more
foods too in a second so I just want to
cover that a little bit so when you're
eating cheese you're actually there's
hormones in that cheese
naturally occurring even if it's
free-range organic sino so many of
you're like well what if it's work in it
what if it's pasture-raised what if it's
that I'm letting you know the natural
occurring hormones and the proteins okay
and let the sugar lactose is going to
feed any pathogen possible so whatever
you got incubating in you if you have
strep sitting in you from when you had
strep throat as a child if you have an
Epstein bar incubating or an Epstein bar
that's not incubating that thing's been
causing you pain and suffering or
symptoms and conditions or anxiety and
and fibromyalgia aches and pains and
fatigue and and and foggy head and brain
fog and all that if you have all that
going on absolutely you got to get rid
of these foods this is why foods will
get you in trouble but you're not gonna
hear anywhere else or from any other
source of why they get you in trouble
besides the theories maybe you're
lactose intolerant well that's a great
guessing game okay you know I mean there
may have in a way that they don't even
have a way to tell it's impossible
literally and so that's how we're so we
walk around without knowing that we
actually are viral and we actually are
getting sicker as the years come on and
look if you're indestructible and you're
in that age right now each bracket and
you feel like yet nothing's really
happening to unique and that you can
just get in a gym and exercise and this
stuff's crazy I'm staying away from
gluten I'm staying with this anyway I'm
all fine but if you think but you're not
if you're untouchable you're wrong
because every single person is getting a
symptom no matter what along the way at
some time in their life or symptoms or
sickness or disease it's just the way
it's heading there's no way around it
unless you know what to do power
yourself heal the whole day get this
from the library for free go to
amazon.com and get a copy it's not
expensive um so so important so here's
how it works
bugs feed off of these things and you
know here's a book here's butter right
here okay so I've got some butter high
quality butter alright so I'm not
shaming the companies that make this
food but all dairy these bugs and paths
yes and dairy puts that high fat and
burns liver and beats it down so path
that's a passion
pathogens can thrive like epstein-barr
inside the liver and if you have more
than one epstein-barr virus if you have
more than one variety to sitting inside
the liver that's sitting there eating
and thriving all of those dairy products
over time you're gonna get the hot
flashes or heart palpitations you're
gonna get the sluggish liver you're
gonna get the waking down the road down
to yours you can get all these different
things the liver can't help us when it's
over burdened with too much fat and it's
loaded up with poisons because the liver
is the garbage dump
and so when you're got pathogens when
you got sickness when you have all these
different symptoms you've got a couple
of different viruses inside the liver
creating your fibromyalgia lupus your
your eczema or psoriasis all these
different conditions your anxiety your
thyroid disorders all of it then you
can't detox you can't cleanse and you
can't detox now it's so important to
know you listen it's like the lemon
water thing right you've heard a lemon
water by now okay see you know medical
medium information did not create a
lemon water people have been putting
lemon in their water for centuries
they've been putting lemon in their
water for centuries that said they're
putting lemon in their tea but the
information that I did bring to
everybody through my source okay was
that when you use lemon water in the
morning if flushes the liver that comes
from medical medium information that's
the original source and it's been out
there for years now and so there's a
reason why you want to flush your liver
with lemon you want to squeeze lemon in
water and drink it there's a reason for
that
because it flushes the liver it flushes
out the poisons in the morning and
that's the original medical medium
information so if you ever heard that
and everybody's been squeezing lemon to
flush out their liver or flush out their
toxins that comes from medical medium
information and I noticed it's gone
around the world doctors tell me all the
time
thank God you told me that 15-20 years
ago thank God you put it in all your
books because it's really helping a lot
of my patients I hear that all the time
and if somebody might say well hey you
didn't start lemon water no of course
not people are put in lemon lemon in
water
or lemon in their teeth long before I
existed and long before you existed but
that wasn't to flush out the liver
nobody knew about that parts and now
people are doing their large lemon
waters in the morning I'm so glad you
guys are doing it too because if you're
on the high-fat diets and you're putting
like this should not be consumed in your
diet if you got symptoms conditions
issues happening if you got acne
whatever it is bugs will feed on but
natural occurring hormones in here bugs
will feed on the sugars in here bugs
bugs will actually grow because of the
amount of fat in here that's naturally
occurring so it's really important to
know these things so that's the butter
butter we'll get in trouble butter
doesn't make you strong butter doesn't
make you indestructible butter just
feeds viruses along the way so you get
your Lyme disease diagnosis winter 52
years old or you get your Hashimoto's
thyroid affect you know thyroiditis
diagnosis when you're 32 or you get some
symptoms or you get more acting along
the way and you're going to doctor the
doctor and you still don't know why and
you get off of lutein and you get off a
couple of foods and your acne starts
getting a little bit better but then it
comes back again and then they say well
it's your hormones and so it's so
important to know what foods to stay
away from let's cover more foods this is
fun so we've got some kefir right here
so it's keeper all right now people say
what about kefir Kieffer's good for me
Kieffer's got the probiotics in it the
whole bit kefir what the kefir is going
to do it's going to do a lot more harm
for you then it's going to do good for
you critical to understand okay because
it's still gonna feed any virus or
pathogen in your body and yes it's
better than milk in a way but it's still
going to get you sit down the road
that's how it works so there's the kefir
that's something to know so I showed you
the milk I've got some more foods on the
way to that I'm gonna show you that are
really important so sour cream - another
one - so many people do sour cream
that's one right there you know there's
a sour cream people say well that's
different you know you can do that it's
a different kind of Derrick and do a
little lump of sour cream and and that's
you know but
gets you in trouble too it feeds it
feeds all the bugs and everything like
that so let's talk about some other
stuff so let's talk about this smells
good though
you know it's a bad guy right who
doesn't like a bad guy it's pretty fresh
too so alright so the whole thing with
wheat gluten so everybody knows hey you
know we wheat gluten celiac problems
people have people have allergies to
gluten the protein so we know all about
that but what no one knows is that why
does everybody suffer when they have
gluten not everybody but a lot of people
do whether they know it or not and when
they remove it they realize it was the
gluten that's what I mean because a lot
of people don't know it how come because
gluten feeds pathogens see that
information wasn't out there until the
medical meeting information now doctors
are actually putting it out there now
recently there's been some doctors that
they have books out there I have a
feeling they don't like the fact that
you know millions of medical media books
have gotten all around the world and in
doctors offices I think it does hurt
because look everybody knows I'm not a
doctor
everybody knows that and I've never said
it was a doctor but it does it does hurt
I think the ego and a lot of people and
so and they they know the information is
solid and so they end up start saying
well no no I knew I knew about you know
pathogens feeding off of gluten oh yeah
well no one knew and it never existed
before the medical medium information
and so you need to know that gluten
feeds epstein-barr bars but it feeds all
pathogens and that's where the problem
lies why do you think you can be 80
years old and eat all the gluten you
want and never have a problem you know
how many grandparents that can eat all
the gluten they want and they don't
understand why their 16-year old
granddaughter can't have gluten
because the 60-year old granddaughter is
dealing with different varieties of
strep which I'm going to talk about a
streptococcus or they're dealing with an
Epstein bar and or they're dealing with
some some others have
pathogen that the grandparents don't
have or didn't add it's the same thing
it's like why do you think young people
can't eat gluten but yes unless so many
older people can because the change of
the times the different varieties of
viruses the times are changing the
mutations the fact that they're getting
everywhere now the fact that the older
generation had the older older varieties
and many of them had no varieties it's
why you've given nine year old that
still can go and eat the gluten and so
forth and what do they usually get they
just usually get the heart disease
because the heart disease is caused by
all the other poor foods and the end of
standard American diets and all that
stuff they usually get other things but
they don't get all the different
symptoms and conditions and the
neurological symptoms that these younger
people that all you guys lived in so
many people there could even be watching
this is that I'm getting because the
gluten feeds the epstein-barr virus it
feeds the pathogens I'm talking about
thyroid healing here you might want to
get this book amazon.com I can't even
touch us touch all the information it's
in here it's going to something else do
so here we are here we've got pasta
right so we got some pasta so that's
another one too gluten so that's where
we get in trouble so you got the pasta
you got the gluten but so many people
can eat pasta you know it's with
somebody and they're just like I was
with with a really older friend it was a
retired doctor and he's 79 years old and
I'm out with him and I'm out with him
and we're out of place we're getting
some teens so he gets like a pasta dish
and it's just straight out pasta it's
got eggs in it it's got wheat the whole
bed he's enjoying himself and you know
and he can but someone else can't some
reason for that and there's a reason for
that
that's how it works I'm trying to give
you the rundown how viruses work on
packaging worst and then
you got the corn chips right there I got
the corn chips
so Lauren feed viruses it feeds bacteria
you have to know this this is why if
your corn used to be a perfect food a
life-saving food it used to be an
unbelievable food wheat was actually a
good food a long time ago corn was
actually a good food is the corn
tortilla this is actually a fun one
right corn tortillas so anybody just
logged on its foods why why we get in
trouble with certain foods and talk
about the epstein-barr virus and talk
about sickness I'm talking about all
these different symptoms conditions
people are going through struggles are
going through you want to stay on for
this talking about thyroid healing my
book the bottom line is corn will feed
pathogens though see these foods were
ruined on us they were like the eggs
okay so we've got the eggs here the eggs
it's not your fault that this food that
was a survival food that people actually
need it and used and it was an important
food it's not your fault they took it
they raised bugs in labs and they let
the bugs out and that's why sicknesses
develop to the degree it has and it's
exploded to the degree it asked and how
young people are sick with so many
symptoms and conditions okay this is why
so it's not your fault okay it's not my
fault I'm not trying to be the food
police here they ruin the food not me I
mean if they didn't ruin it I'd probably
showing up some of these foods in the
whole bit
and then I want to talk about this food
for a little bit right here there's that
one you guys this is fun I hope you're
having some fun it means a lot of
information it's really intense you want
to watch this whole thing back again if
you just hop down you want to you want
to watch this from the start
there's no question it's a powerful
powerful episode to actually help you
heal this food is an interesting food
this is bacon now this is what's
interesting here this won't feed viruses
but you're going to think hey I could
eat bacon now no no no no no don't eat
bacon pork won't feed the epstein-barr
virus okay so see it's not about hey is
he vegan is he not is he about
plant-based is he
is he is the anti a IP is he is he blood
type would it what is he I don't I don't
subscribe to a belief system because
they're all wrong they're all wrong in
so many ways every last one of them even
the vegan diets don't even have the
right even that even the vegetarian
diets even than even all the different
ones the paimio guys because they don't
know what causes illness see I'm not in
the food Wars
I don't fight over the little stuff I
talk about the real stuff in the food
wars ok so because what they're doing
out there they're kept busy like the
vegans are throwing you know fake
science that the paleo aliens are
throwing fake science at the vegans
because it's all paid for they don't
realize it and everybody's throwing all
the stuff back and forth and then you
have you know diets like the IP and all
AIP and all these are different diets
and and it keeps on going but none of
those diets know what causes illness
they don't know about that what you're
learning here they don't they don't know
about the epstein-barr virus and how it
works and how it feeds and what foods it
feeds on and it's sad because because of
that they flip-flop everybody's playing
guessing games and the vegans get scared
and they run to the Palio's again and
they start eating animal products or
starting to eat eggs or whatever it is
and it's sad and then the Palio's they
all get scared they don't know what
they're eating they run to veganism and
they run there and the plant-based and
nobody realizes it and so everybody's
confused and nobody really knows what's
going on and all these different diets
are made and everybody's trying to
figure it out and it's sad because we're
covering it now times but epstein-barr
what it feeds off of now let's talk
about bacon bacon doesn't feed FCU bar
it doesn't feed viruses but you would
think hey if Anthony's saying that then
hey maybe it's good to eat no it's not
that I'll tell you why
bacon burden is a liver it kills the
liver and pancreas and that's not good
if you have epstein-barr that's not good
if you have a virus that's giving you
eggs and pains pains tangles numbness
ringing in the ears tinnitus vertigo
even if you have past doubts of it but
you don't have it now that means you got
the epstein-barr in the system and so
hot flashes heart palpitations
thyroid disorders of all kinds all the
different diagnoses
talked about Lyme disease behind the
epstein-barr or more than one
epstein-barr in your system what can
happen is if you're eating the bacon
you're bombarding your liver with so
much fact that it can't do its job it
can't even hold up to its own immune
system delivers own immune system which
I talked about in the medical media book
series this is tyreq healing today
though it's important to know and what
happens is with all that fat in
burdening your blood system depleting
your blood of oxygen like I was talking
about early like the dairy products
where your oxygen levels are depleting
and dropping down okay and the fats
Werdum in your liver and it's burning
your pancreas you can't defend yourself
against the epstein-barr so it grows and
LIF rates it proliferate and actually
expands and grows over time it can speed
your process up to getting sick down the
road that's what it can do so that's
what happens when you eat a food that
doesn't feed the virus but yet puts you
in another way so important to
understand so we covered a few we
covered a few foods right now okay
here's a really big part right here you
have to learn about illness because you
can't blame yourself you can't blame
your body you can't blame your body
being faulty that you created it so
here's the thing that's happening now
you guys and this is the war I feel like
this is the worst what's happening is
the industry's Big Pharma in the medical
industries all the industry is now
including alternative industry all
bought into something they bought into
the body attacking itself they bought
into the body the theory that the body
is attacking itself or the theory that
genes are behind your condition these
are theories they're not proven and
that's the theory of your body attacking
itself like in celiac like an autoimmune
see autoimmune means they don't know the
cause so they say you're the cause
that's how it works in autoimmune
diseases of all kinds eczema psoriasis
and celiac anything any kind of
autoimmune disease doesn't matter what
it is they believe that you're the cause
you see how it's been flipped that's how
it's done they believe your body's
attacking
self so here you are going to dog here
you are 20 years old or 20 years old are
40 years old whatever it is you're going
to doctor to doctor and they're like
okay I'm trying a different diet now I'm
trying to new AMA IP diet no I'm trying
to new this diet a defog mint diet or do
whatever it is and you're doing like
you're trying to do new thing every
minute and you're trying okay I'm going
to this alternate practition they say
get rid of this and I'm trying to this
and they say this you have to know
something they all believe your body's
attacking something you have an
autoimmune condition if they diagnosed
you with that autoimmune or been told or
you've been told that's what it is or
whatever weather is that some psoriasis
or so forth and that puts the blame on
you the system's been setting us up and
setting women up for a reason I'm gonna
go into that a little bit it's such an
important episode right here it sets
women up for disempowerment that's how
you keep women weak that's how you break
them down and you beat them down and you
break their spirits this is how it's
done okay because there are real reasons
why women are suffering and they're sick
in and - but there's real reasons
there's the epstein-barr liars wreaking
havoc there's other viruses to them
they're going to all the different
viruses and so forth
there's real reasons why they're sick
the system created the situation on this
theory that there's an auto antibody
discovered back in the 1950s that's
responsible for the body turning on
itself first of all it's impossible look
at technology in 1950 okay
trust me medicine 1950 was the dark ages
dark ages the scariest thing you ever
want to know how do I know
I took the plenty of people I took the
plenty of doctors from the from the
yesteryear it was a nightmare
okay testing and medical testing and
understanding of the body and everything
was the dark ages in 1948 1949 okay and
this is remedial at best let me see you
need to know how it works so here's the
deal when it comes down to the theory of
hey it's autoimmune your body's
attacking itself that was a very design
because people were streaming into
doctor's office
nobody know what made them sick women
were piling in to doctors offices all
across the globe I talked to a doctor
really old doctor who had a practice
back then to retire really old doctor
had practice back then and he said and
he said it was like something they've
never seen before and they were shoved
by the medical industry this theory of
the body attacking itself as being the
blame and doctors knew it couldn't be
possible he knew the body wasn't
attacking itself but they had a they had
to be trained that from there on out in
the medical universities and the medical
schools so what happens is its ultimate
disempowerment it's body shaming it's
body shaming is what it's doing so I'm
gonna talk talk to you about how it
works okay about a few other things with
that so it's not genetics it's not the
autoimmune theory of the body attacking
itself that's messing people up it's not
you creating it either
okay it's not that what happens is we
become deficient over time we're not
getting the right foods in us we're not
getting the things we need our immune
systems we can do stress due to other
problems heartbreak and so forth and all
kinds of things poor diet occurs too as
well
so you're got the bacon in there and
you're knocking out the oxygen so
there's no option to stop any viruses or
pathogens you've got the gluten in there
you're feeding pathogens you're feeding
things that's what you're doing you're
drinking some kefir because you think
that's the answer and you're doing that
you're eating some eggs and you're
actually feeding the viruses and the
pathogens is what you're doing and
you're doing that and at the same time
you're weakening your immune system
you're lowering your immune system and
the diet gets the diets poor along the
way you're losing trace minerals like
zinc because of stress and because of
life there's all kinds of iron mental
toxins coming in you're getting broken
down you're getting heck toxic heavy
metals you might have already started
out in soil for toxic heavy metals and
that's what's happening and then boom
you end up getting mononucleosis or your
first doubt of it that's not discovered
stage 2 happens and you get this your
first mononucleosis and it's hasn't even
discovered because you just tired for a
week and then it goes away it could be a
real mild one or it could be a severe
one either way that's how the virus
moves into state
- so I talked about the foods I talked
about how that works I've talked about
how women are being disempowered because
women on this planet or world changers
their powerful world changers and they
just wanted to tell you that last part
but when you get run down
and you stand you get the flu and you're
not eating good and you're getting
deficient and you're not taking care of
yourself and all these other things are
happening because you're not being
taught to take care of yourself or you
just got too much going on in your life
and then you get heartbreak or something
else and you throw it all in or just
stress of every day everything the
immune system starts to weaken and break
down is what happens and you end up
going to the doctor with the diagnosis
it's not even the right one
it's not even hey you're viral now we
have to get some antivirals in you we
have to get you better instead it's wait
a minute you might have autoimmune and
your body's attacking itself and now
you're driving home from the doctor's
office thinking your body's worthless
and it's faulty so with all that else we
have going on this is how this
empowerment for everybody goes so the
body's immune system is that war with
epstein-barr in stage 2 I want to go
into that a little bit there's a stage 2
with epstein-barr so first of all stage
1 is about it incubating in the body
stage 2 is about the war that occurs
with epstein-barr time our thyroid
healing the most comprehensive Epstein
Barr book on the planet now make sure
you get it there's over 60 varieties of
Epstein Barr remember that so everybody
could have a different one different one
some could be more severe so it could be
let much less of the earth some another
person's immune system might be stronger
than another person's they might have
less toxins they might have less issues
going on their life so they're they're
mononucleosis is really mild somebody
else had mononucleosis could be really
severe they got much more of a severe or
aggressive form of Epstein Barr really
important to know but the body's at war
with the epstein-barr stage two is when
there's a war going on so that's what's
happening there so that's the stage
stage two is stage two is your immune
system so that's your white blood cells
right here so you got all these
different white blood cells going on me
guys so hang in there for this little
show get lymphocytes she got monocytes
you got neutrophils you got you got the
whole bit okay I'm trying to make it
interesting anyway you're in me to get
your killer cells right we just say that
your
so we have those they're there and they
become the they basically go into war
with the bad guys is what happens so
here's your virus the epstein-barr virus
that stage 2 comes out of incubation and
now boom there's a war happening but the
virus over time realizes realizes that
it's going to lose the war because your
immune system tags it your immune system
releases a hormone a chemical compound
your immune system releases is it what
it does so your white blood cells
releases chemical compound chemical
compound attaches itself to the virus is
what it does so the chemical compound
released by your immune system by your
lymphocytes okay
tagged the virus so then when they tags
the virus the virus knows it can't be in
the body in the bloodstream fighting too
much longer because that means you're
gonna win the battle so there's this
battle going on in stage 2 epstein-barr
happens to everybody in anybody's life
it doesn't matter if they felt like they
thought they just had the flu for three
weeks or the flu for two weeks and it
wasn't the flu or it was a flu trigger
off their epstein-barr or whatever it is
what happens is they have their white
blood count their white blood count
releases a phytochemical compound I mean
sorry chemical compound for the body it
goes right on to the virus sticks to the
virus and now the viruses days are
numbered okay you start winning the war
so that's how it works you start winning
the war your your spit your mono
symptoms start to die down you start
getting your strength back your sore
throat your fever or headache and rashes
whatever it could be happening
whatever's going on could start to die
down and that's how it works okay
symptoms can come and go over time but
it starts to die down because your white
count is winning but then your virus has
to go somewhere so the Epstein virus
actually has to go somewhere so it picks
a home is what it does it heads
somewhere it heads for the liver is
where it loves to go it can head to the
spleen to but the spleen but the liver
is where it loves the most and it's the
most important spot because it has the
most fuel has the most food it has all
that food I'm talking about stored up in
it
how's that bacon fat in there it has the
gluten I talked to
it has the milk in there it has toxins
it has toxic heavy metals as mercury and
they're defeated it's got aluminum it's
got cadmium nickel arsenic it's got lead
it's got all these different copper it's
got metals in there and so the virus
likes to sit inside the liver inside
that garbage dump and it goes to sleep
feeds and then sleeps just like
Thanksgiving right you're getting a big
turkey and then you hop on this finan
you hop on the couch and now you're
going to sleep you know and it just sits
inside the liver and it has that that
Thanksgiving meal and then it goes to
sleep and then it has another
Thanksgiving meal and it goes to sleep
and then it start to reproduce itself is
what it does because it still reproduces
itself it grows its numbers it
proliferate s-- over time causing
problems and unfortunately that's where
we go into like the ant we go into them
and if you're not doing it to a virus
and if you're not taking away the foods
that it loves to feed on and if you're
not cleaning up your toxic heavy metals
it grows inside the liver and get us in
trouble and that virus gets in trouble
and the immune system doesn't even know
it's there anymore the immune systems
going around the body and doesn't see it
in the bloodstream anymore and thinks it
won the war so your immune system kind
of goes back into dormancy to not
dormancy back into the usual grind the
everyday grind of life is what it does
and this virus FC Morra stays inside the
liver and incubates in there that's how
it works okay going into another part
here okay we're going into stage three
epstein-barr so let's do that then it
happens a lot of information gonna have
to have some celery juice right there
but--my back up so stage three a lot of
people experience mono but don't get it
diagnosed with mono so they experience
mono so so many people experience
symptoms they get rundown in college for
a little bit they don't go to a doctor
they get it running down not everybody
goes to a doctor doctor does even look
for mono so what there's millions and
millions and millions of people who had
mono that didn't even know they had mono
but yet they have little Iran symptoms
they have stage 3 because they don't
know they even had stage 1 because they
were never even guys
and even if they weren't diagnosed
there's no information out there but the
medical meeting information that tells
you how the stages work so Stage three
is when the virus leaves the liver and
heads to the thyroid so it goes to the
thyroid masque what happens so the virus
starts to go up the thyroid that's what
it does it goes up to the thyroid to say
this tortilla your thyroid the virus
swings up the thyroid enters the thyroid
and you start getting your slowly start
getting your thyroid conditions and it
could range in any of them so you're 38
years old you're a woman you're 38 years
old
you get discovered that there's a little
nodule on your thyroid that's because
I've seen bars been there for a long
time working on it that's how it works I
talk about this information all in
thyroid healing so maybe you're getting
hypothyroidism it's not going to show up
on a blood test it's not going to show
them there because you've already had
mono once before so here you go
the virus can actually travel to the
thyroid it's not going to show up on a
blood test this is how it's escaped
their medical system this is how it's
worked
doctors will most likely see antibodies
to a past infection that's how
indicating you had a past infection if
they're really looking hard but they
won't believe your thyroid problems or
know their thyroid problems they believe
it when they learn so many doctors are
learning this information now from
medical medium book series but they
won't know that that's what's causing a
thyroid problems your hypothyroidism
your hyperthyroidism these your
different writers of epstein-barr you
can have hypothyroidism and
hyperthyroidism all at the same time you
can actually have them both because you
can have two varieties of I've seen bar
inside your thyroid that's how it works
this is where the mistake happens
meanwhile the virus becomes active again
it travels from the liver to the thyroid
causing problems and it fills your
thyroid with toxins and poisons and it
fills your liver with toxins and poisons
and your lymphatic system gets all
clogged up with these toxic the toxic
poisons your lymphocytes get weak your
lymphocytes around your thyroid get weak
and they're not doing the job they're
not even able to actually knock down
epstein-barr because we're still eating
the wrong foods we still have to toxic
heavy metals we're still not cleaning or
system up we're still not doing all the
right things for ourselves medical
research in science
yet detected this information or
detected the epstein-barr your thyroid
has its own immune system research the
science doesn't know that your thyroid
has its own immune system well what
happens is over time the virus will
distract and wear down your overall
body's immune system so I want to talk
about this next part you got to watch
this whole thing over again this
information is really intense
over time the virus has in stage four it
wants to go to stage four okay that's
what it wants to do that's a viruses
want to do they always want to go to
stage four and so this stage what they
do is the viruses leave the liver and
they start to break down the immune
system they start to wear it down they
stay in the liver and wear down the
immune system the livers immune system
they go out and they leave they wear
down the immune system they release a
tremendous amount of by-product toxic
byproducts so these viruses release
toxic by-product and that toxic
by-product starts to break down the
immune system throughout the entire body
and that's when people start getting
some different symptoms you start
getting hot flashes and they start
getting different heart palpitations
because they got all this viral
by-product floating around through their
body and this is how this is how they
start getting brain fog so what happens
is you get the brain fog because you're
on the edge of stage three stage for
epstein-barr nobody knew it's been
traveling throughout the body over the
years it might have one or two varieties
because the viruses that viruses are
releasing a battery of poisons and
toxins so that's what the epstein-barr
does it releases a battery of poisons
and toxins and as these poisons and
toxins are floating around and floating
around they weaken the immune system the
reason why is because they need the weak
in the immune system because they want
to get to that next level they want to
take your lymphocytes and distract them
that's what the viruses want to do they
want to distract your immune system so
the thyroid becomes naked so it's there
for more viruses to feed into your
thyroid to go into the thyroid to feed
on it so there's an action strategy
viruses use that may sound scary but not
if you have the right information not if
you know how to heal that if you're not
going to heal like so many thousands and
hundreds of thousands of people all over
the planet that use them books and heal
you can actually arm yourself and
actually heal you can heal your head
and you could reverse it you could
reverse all these different symptoms
conditions all the stuff is really
important so Stage four occurs when the
body's immune system has been distracted
and then the virus deals with the
nervous systems that's when all the
neurological symptoms start the eggs the
pains the neurological fatigue all the
different symptoms people get
neurologically the anxiety the anxiety
is caused by toxins being released by
the epstein-barr virus floating around
getting into the brain short-circuiting
neurotransmitters a neurotransmitter
camera holes weaken they start to
dehydrate electrical impulses start to
short-circuit
that's what the virus does in stage four
and so you start getting neurological
symptoms your vagus nerve gets affected
and I want to go into the vagus nerve
for a couple of minutes you guys I know
there's a lot of information and
probably surprised you today with this
live but it's so important so vagus
nerve that's you're nervous that runs
that he comes out of the brain it runs
right down through your neck it runs
right down your chest right down to your
stomach right there that's the ultimate
anxiety creating nerve it's not because
your faulty it's not because you're
mental it's not because you've got all
these problems not because you're a bad
person stuff because you're creating it
with bad thoughts it's not because of
any of that none of that helps if you
got bad thoughts of course none of that
helps but if you have a weakened vagus
nerve that's already slightly inflamed
from neurotoxins being produced in stage
four by epstein-barr virus you're gonna
have more of a sensitive baby star if
you're gonna get tightness of chest
you're gonna get panic attacks easy
you're gonna get on and off in your life
you're gonna have anxiety you're gonna
feel all kind of like jittery you're
gonna get shakes you're gonna get
tingles and numbness you're gonna get
different things all of this is symptoms
of epstein-barr including you have
ringing in the ears on and off and I
know that a lot of you are like wait
there's ringing in my ear someone's
talking about me no that's not how it is
ringing in the ears
on and off intermittently on and off is
an early sign that you got some EBV and
you have to address it now because 20
years from now you won't be saying hey
somebody's talking about me anymore
you'll be out of 10 doctors trying to
get rid of your tinnitus it's important
to have this information the one thing I
don't play around with is fake
information that's out there that just
travels around and all of the healing
modalities and all the healing movements
that's all just I don't even know where
this stuff
from you have to deal with real
information in order to heal and not get
tricked in full this is just the way it
goes
ringing the ears periodically you gotta
know you want to catch that early before
it turns into odds not a lot of tinnitus
down the road you got to know that
tangles have numbness tingling numbness
is sure you know when you're talking
about ghost stories and it's at night
and you're watching a lady outside of a
ghost story show or something like that
you might get the tingles up the back of
the neck and the goosebumps and
everything but I'm talking about tingles
and numbness that comes periodically for
no reason whatsoever you know connect
restless leg syndrome tics spasms
twitches floaters in the eyes and
buzzing buzzing in the ears sounds in
the ears popping in the ears heart
palpitations plantar fasciitis brain fog
confusion anxiety depression all start
to occur with stage for epstein-barr you
can have stage for epstein-barr at age
13 14 15 16 whatever age 25 age 30 age
40 the whole bit should just even know
that neuro fatigue fatigue where your
legs feel like cement you know it breaks
my heart when I know people even go
through any of this it kills me because
especially when they've gone to doctors
and you know they're yeah playing around
with diets and things are getting a
little better here and there and whatnot
but they're not safe until they know
what to do and he'll wash it for too
many times I talk to too many doctors so
the neuro fatigue the legs feel like
bags of cement on them you know or you
just feel like you can't push through
you got to take naps during the day you
need a nap in the middle of the day you
got to lay down on the couch you got to
close your eyes
and and that's really hard for so many
people and then you can't function you
can't work or you you're working but
you're not working at the peace and you
get the brain fog with it all of it is
so difficult and they can't get it man
what about the people they can't get out
of bed at all you guys and some of you
probably know that are and some of you
are them then you can even get out to
get out of the bed in the morning and
you have the deep neurological fatigue
that's medical medium information
neurological fatigue that's the whole
point it's not just fatigue neurological
fatigue it's your nervous system and
there's a way to heal that's the stage
for epstein-barr so many some people get
a three Epstein bars foot around our
system and it could be releasing these
neurotoxins
get out of bed and then Shannon Denham
you're eating butter you're drinking
coffee and having butter in your coffee
to make you sicker and then you're doing
eggs because you know no one's taught
you that eggs actually feed the viruses
nobody tells you that it is viruses so
this is how you get in trouble and
everybody is getting these symptoms
decades before their grandmothers got
the symptoms they're getting it decades
before you know what I mean that here's
how it works look what I mean by decades
before the grandmothers that means their
grandmothers didn't get the symptoms and
in their life until later on in their
life the grandmothers got the symptoms
later on in their life most of them and
now younger women are getting it at all
ages and when they have a window where
they're not having it and they're able
to go to school they're able to go to
college and able to graduate and they're
able to start a career and they're able
to go out to restaurants and drink wine
and do whatever they want and go out
with friends and all this other stuff
and go travel around the world and all
this it's only a short window it's
wholly a short window it's this
information they should take the heart
it's only a short window unless you know
what creates illness what creates
chronic symptoms and conditions because
it sneaks up on everybody no matter what
I'm watching it I have watched you for
over 35 years
doctors watch it every day it's no one's
getting away with it unless you know
what the heck is going on and know how
to heal it know what you need to do know
how to heal it get the fiber and
information get know what foods to stop
know what all of it and other stuff too
listen it's getting worse than ever once
before and faster it's getting worse and
faster EBD is more aggressive than ever
was before and people are collecting
them like collecting stamps and
collecting coins look I get it if you're
a critic or a skeptic and you don't
understand how epstein-barr works and
you don't understand
how it's the blame for a huge part of
our populations illness I get it you
know you're gonna be like hey no way
this doesn't make sense I get it I get
it but it's actually the way it is you
know this live is critical for you to
know if you're a skeptic watch this live
a couple of times be open-minded be
open-minded for the people that need the
help it's really important
Epstein Barr is a blame for our
population sickness a huge part don't
get me wrong I talk about other viruses
and I'm gonna go into that a little bit
regardless of anyway the Epstein bars
and entered your body through areas of
the body fluids or any other way
it runs these four stages and you can
stop it and you can heal and you can
move forward that's why people heal from
the Lyme disease I'm medically in the
information multiple sclerosis on there
and medical medium information all these
different symptoms conditions on it
that's why they get their lives back
that's why they lose weight the stories
everywhere Women's World magazine that
publication showcases it has a spread in
the magazine every month every other
month medical meeting people actually
healing from all the stuff they did they
would never pay to do it they did it on
their own they did it with the books
they get it with the information first
for women always also talk about that so
these different publications that know
the informations healing people they see
if they see these miraculous stories you
guys see it every day so let's talk
about some different things epstein-barr
is different because it runs through
different parts of the body
EB V goes through all kinds of different
parts of the body causes different
problems I've explained so I've seen
Barker go to the thyroid it can go to
others it goes to the liver it goes to
the reproductive system it can go to the
brain it can do a lot of different
things neurotoxins and float around and
go to the brain so let's talk about why
a woman for a couple of minutes why
women in such greater numbers are
getting affected with chronic illness
and getting epstein-barr to such a
degree one of the biggest physical
differences is the menstrual cycle when
a woman has her menstrual cycle eight
percent of her immune system gets
knocked down okay so when 80 percent of
our immune system gets knocked down once
a month it leaves everything open for a
virus of pathogen
anything else so say a woman has two
varieties of streptococcus and they got
they got acne all the time or they had
strep throat in their life and they have
acne okay or they had ear infections
when they were younger when they have
their menstrual cycles when they're
getting older their immune system drops
down 80% of the immune system drops down
because each month the reproductive
system in a woman demands a tremendous
amount of energy and resources it
demands full attention for it for
resources is what it does the
reproductive system needs almost its
entire immune system governing over it
so that she could prepare her body to
having a baby so what happens is that
when you have your reproductive system
coming up it's the body puts be
preparing that's the body preparing
itself to have babies the menstrual
cycle is critical so what happens here
is 80% of the immune system drops down
and goes to the reproductive system is
where it goes and it goes towards the
womb it's critical that it goes towards
the womb and there's a reason for this
because it's preparing it's guarding and
preparing cleaning and prepping the
reproductive system to to you know pass
on generations and generations and
generations to start generations it's
our way to survive and live so the
immune system drops down so ok so that
means once a month just with that alone
a woman's immune system drops down and
weekends so if there's an Epstein bar
just caught recently through a
relationship or through a friendship or
through anything or through any kind or
in a restaurant all the different things
or a public bathroom or a family member
and Epstein bar is passed on to one
person to another and that menstrual
cycle is happening and then also stress
is happening in that person's life in
that woman's life and stress and
different things or hardships or
whatever it is the immune system can get
kicked down a lot throughout the body
and the virus can actually proliferate
because of that reason alone and then
there's ovulation where 40% of the
body's immune system has to go to the
reproductive system during ovulation
once again preparing the woman for
conception and the whole bit this means
twice a month a woman's immune system is
weakened down one of the men's
man's immune system is not that's why
men don't get chronic illness to the
degree women do okay so that's one of
the big reasons it's also why women get
acne during the menstrual cycle because
since our immune system lowers after
being accursed
because acne is caused by streptococcus
not hormones C hormones was the old
blame game it started out with hormones
and it started out with the body's
attacking itself now it's now it's going
to genes these are all blame games on
women and their bodies trying to train
them their bodies were faulty that their
bodies were weak or they create it and
that's what it's all to sell hormones
it's all to sell different drugs it's
all to sell things and that's why that
whole system was created back in the day
but what causes acne during during
menstruation during a cycle causes acne
is streptococcus so that's what causes
it strike strep bacterias and strep
bacteria streptococcus is a cofactor to
epstein-barr that means it's trucks
around epstein-barr lives in the body to
always remember that so if you have
strep as a child that means there's an
Epstein bar in in in the child too
that's how it works there's over 50
groups of strep with multiple strains
per group and science research is
unaware of this there's way more way
more letters in a group than alpha that
than the alphabet has for streptococcus
that's how many varieties of
streptococcus and streptococcus is
becoming superbug now it's becoming
antibiotic resistant that's why
everybody gets the acne that's why
there's so many problems it's why people
get infections why kids getting there
from ear infections and you're doing the
so you're doing the antibiotics and it
can't get rid of the ear infection it
keeps them coming back that's why UTIs
urinary tract infections bladder
infections bacterial vaginosis all of
these things are streptococcus related
the reason why they don't get better
with antibiotics or they get temporarily
and it's on and off because it gets more
resistant and there's ways of healing
this and they talk about all the
different conditions and chronic
symptoms conditions in the book you
should get the thyroid healing book men
suffer from prostate cancers and and
prostate problems because of
epstein-barr virus and streptococcus
something to know about
epstein-barr treats prostate cancer and
men's
all of that breast cancer I've seen Bart
causes breast cancer miscarriages
infertility preeclampsia caused by
breast caused by epstein-barr buyers so
miscarriages not all miscarriages don't
get me wrong on that a lot of
miscarriages are caused by reproductive
issues created by epstein-barr virus a
lot infertility issues not all
infertility but a lot of infertility
mysterious mysterious miscarriages
mysterious infertility those are much of
those are caused by epstein-barr virus
so there's something no preeclampsia
that's symptoms of epstein-barr virus
because the immune system drops when a
woman's pregnant and so because it drops
if you have a certain variety of
epstein-barr you can get a lot of signs
of preeclampsia and so that's really
important to know so let's go a little
bit further here I have look I have a
whole section in thyroid healing on
these topics really important remember
there's over 60 varieties of Epstein
Barr not just 160 varieties of pathogens
is what it means not just one type of
virus if you're a critic skeptic watch
this whole thing all over again if you
haven't seen it from the beginning make
your own judgment call I'm totally fine
with that critics are smart they're
smart they know what they're saying you
know haters are different but critics
critics are smart intelligent people
that want to learn and know and they
want to have an open mind so make sure
you look at this look at the book if I
was a critic get the book and read it
you don't want to pay for it go to the
library get it out for free blaming our
bodies on being autoimmune and our body
attacked in itself blaming our genes
blaming the facts the fact that we think
we created it because of some emotional
thing that's deep down inside is a
really dangerous situation especially
for young people it's kind of it's it's
bad enough for older people like in
their fifties in 60s and 40s telling
them that they can handle it a little
better but telling people that are 15 16
years old 17 years old 18 years old that
their body is attacking itself when it's
not when it's an outdated theory and
it's really devastating beyond
devastating telling a 15 year old that
it's their genes is devastating when
it's not their genes it's devastating I
mean don't you think so or or do I live
in a bubble it's just unbelievable
it's the greatest body shaming
techniques I've ever seen
by Big Pharma and it's right under
everybody's noses and I'm the only
person talking about it literally the
only person talking about it and that
breaks my heart alone because well
because it's just that's how literally
full people are you want a body shame
somebody tell them that their body's
immune system is destroying your own
glands when it's not when it's not the
body's body doesn't work like that
when it's a theory that was created
because they didn't know what causes
illness when autoimmune disease they
have no they have no car they don't know
the causes of it so just remember that
or it's attacking the skin like eczema
psoriasis so that you know when you do
that you're really but you're really
hurting people kicking them down body
shame shaming them disempowering them
and that's what even they do that so
that the industry's Bank on women's
suffering and keep them down because
their world changers never forget that
because that's what they're doing so
don't get fooled don't get pushed into
it still critical you know somebody just
said I was one of the 14 year-olds when
psoriasis and depression started and
skin disease and they said it was her
genes I just saw that comment come up
right now yeah you and so many more and
it's painstaking thank you for writing
that comment thank you somebody said I
hope Anthony is protecting himself I
worry about big pharma you guys I get
more more stuff thrown at me than you
guys ever even knew or shouldn't know
and then is not easy
but I try to kill myself to get the
information out there and get the books
out there and you know I don't do what
the other authors deal where they try to
sell hundreds of millions of dollars of
items out there in the world so they
could just make money and they eat me in
the book is just a way of doing it I
don't do that
I write the books spirits information
spirit of compassion my source I get it
to you so you can heal it's all about
YOU healing I'm forgiving for listen I
want to talk about the unforgiving for
for a minute unforgiving forests
pathogens like we've covered a little
bit heavy metals it's another thing
radiation will always get exposure and
old DDT that's all in our system
everywhere and everybody's body even
younger people I also include all that
information about the end
before and thyroid healing just know
that pathogens including epstein-barr
over 30 varieties of shingles something
to know about to sign of Meckler virus
HH b 6h h d7 h HB 12 13 14 15 strep
bacteria and over 50 groups cover it all
in here
how strep is becoming a super bug how
it's all discovered undiscovered I mean
it's all undiscovered information all
incredible to have strep bacteria
information is important so all of that
I'm looking at the comments now I didn't
get a chance to do that before it's
incredible you guys are running
something off some comments right now
I'm actually reading them I was reading
them in and out of it before but I
couldn't read them all so I hope you you
forgive me for that I feel bad about
that this book is the most complete and
comprehensive guide there is about
epstein-barr virus period period period
it also includes seven great mistakes
including the autoimmune carried the
gene theory
it includes all the mistakes these are
critical so you can not get pushed
around anymore she don't get pushed
around you know no one wants to be
fooled and no one wants to be pushed
around no one wants to be left in the
dark no one wants to be you know a joke
to be played on them because that's what
the industry's do I promise you that and
they do it on the alternative industry
and you know what's sad you guys an
alternative industry is doing it there's
a lot of traps in the alternative
industry - I am NOT totally Pro
alternative industry and I'm not totally
Pro the conventional industry I know the
good parts of our conventional industry
I know the good parts of it I know good
surgeons I know all of this and I know
also the bad parts and I know the good
parts of the alternative movement and I
know the really bad parts and there are
a lot of bad parts just know that I
covered almost hundred different
symptoms conditions and thyroid feeling
book includes 98th iron rehab cleanse
just know that's in here I got a list of
supplements that you can you know hey
you can learn about so you can heal I
don't sell supplements but you can learn
how to get supplements the right ones
that heal all that stuff out there I
have an entire chapter on insomnia so
many people suffer with sleeping
problems - do you have seen bar and
other things and incredible this book
can help you improve your sleep this
book is critical for anybody on the
planet right
now just know this we're up against
epstein-barr virus it's over 60
varieties if you have the book already
read it and study it okay that's what I
would do
listen I want to talk to you guys
heart-to-heart for a second okay I know
so many of you suffer and struggle and
have been through a lot and when you're
not sick and you've never been sick yet
that person can never understand that
and I get it it's the hard part about at
all when you're the one in it's in your
shoes and you got the plantar fasciitis
and you've got the eggs and pants or
your feet hurt and your knees hurt and
you don't know why and you got the
fatigue and you got the thyroid
diagnosis and you got you've got all the
different brain fog and then you know
confusion brain fog got tics and spasms
whatever it is a burning pain or you've
got all these different issues going on
and you're the one struggling and you're
the one going to doctors and your life
becomes about going to different doctors
and healers and just know that my heart
is with you and I believe in you and I'm
sorry you have the misinformation that
floats around out there in the world and
I'm sorry that it's still out there and
it's just hurting everybody like it is
and some of it is helpful but the
majority of it still doesn't get people
to where they need to be and I know that
you struggle them you suffering and
you've been through hell and back even
if it's on a small level to a big level
just know that I'm right there with you
and I understand and you know with the
skin conditions when you can't even
close on you can't even wear clothes and
you can't even get out of bed or you
can't even lay in bed because of the
skin to the condition it's so bad and
babies that have the worst eczema and
psoriasis and in your mom and you're
seeing your children suffer and you're a
mom and you're seeing your daughter
suffer at age 13 or age 14 with with
really bad fatigue and really bad issues
and you're just like what's going on
here and you quickly learn that science
and research knows nothing about chronic
illness science and research those
literally nothing about chronic illness
are the cause of chronic illness and how
hard that is and when you think about
that I understand and I understand you
and I understand what you've been
through
I believe in you and I believe in you
100% and I realize when people aren't
sick and those are the critics and they
don't real and they're out there and
they're driving around and they're not
sick yet and they're exercising and
doing their thing and they don't know
what it's like to be in your shoes and
they can't understand you I understand
that too and but just know this that you
can heal and I believe in you I love you
guys okay and you got my heart you got
my soul thanks for caring about me like
you guys do so many of you have put
heartfelt comments in there and take
care god bless you