four is now released okay
killing you smelly episode four is
released
the medical medium podcast at apple
podcast
that's where you you listen to it okay
it's about
chemical fragrances the bad stuff
air fresheners the whole bit air
fresheners
uh clone perfume scented candles
really it's incredible show for the
chemical sensitive people an incredible
show for them
and for everybody really and you don't
want to miss this
episode killing you smelly it's an epic
episode and i say that because it's so
packed with information to help people
you don't want to miss
out on that just really an incredible
message in there
all the way i mean i mean that's just a
part of how incredible it really is so
there's so much there
so much there so i just wanted to
mention that so
like i said episode four released
killing you smelly
there it is you can find it uh medical
medium podcast
at apple podcast so i'm letting you know
where it is
where you can find it i want to talk
about some other stuff too which is so
important
um so did you uh
did you hear the brain meditation mind
mind blower
the brain meditation did you hear that
it's a guided meditation have you
tried it i know many of you have tried
it really really powerful
jade says i find it very difficult to be
around anyone wearing perfumes
the chemical because of the chemicals
involved really really hard
um and uh joshua hello sir
you're the man you're the man too the
proud of you joshua all the good work
you do out there spreading the message
and everything
um so i'm just proud of you just know
that and and i know you're working hard
you're doing all kinds of stuff
so the medical medium podcast uncensored
you guys there's a difference
uncensored do not miss out on these
episodes chemtrail episode number one
episode right there chemtrail
but it's not for the faint of heart be
careful with that episode it's a shocker
shocker that's the that's the chemtrail
episode fruit fear episode
whole another one there too it's a
shocker too
just saying be careful with that episode
that's episode number two
episode number three brain meditation
the brain meditation
takes you through a guided meditation to
heal
fear trapped fear that's in our soul and
between our soul
and our physical body and i'm going to
talk about that a little bit in a minute
and you can do that brain meditation you
know every single day to help heal
so episode number four release this
morning killing you smelly
air fresheners scented candles perfumes
colognes you don't want to miss that
episode
and these are all uncensored okay at
apple podcast
that's where they are they're uncensored
if you if you listen to them or try to
list them on another platform that's not
apple
then it's censored most likely clip
snipped
even if the minutes look the same i'm
telling you where you can see it and if
you don't have an apple device fine
you can just go to medicalmedium.com
medicalmedium.com
go to the menu look for podcasts in the
menu
and boom you can listen to it you can
listen to it
one thing i wanted to say which is
really important um
is that there's no infomercials there's
no advertisements
there's no sponsorships there's none of
that in
these episodes because i don't do that
kind of thing
i made a choice not to do that with this
kind of level of a podcast
i made sure that this wasn't going to be
there because you know it's so important
to know that so you're free from all of
that
share the pod please share the podcast
please please please
anna says all podcasts are amazing
four times brain meditation so good
love you thank you spirit of compassion
spirit of compassion loves you thank you
for
for listening and everything um my
husband suffers from perfumes
i saw that the comments are going up and
i miss that sorry about that i couldn't
read the rest of it
and what happens is what you smell
becomes you that's what happens what you
smell becomes you
if you smell it it's already inside you
so the minute you smell something those
chemicals are already inside of you
that's why it's important to take care
of yourself important to cleanse
that's why i got that book right there
in the back a cleanse the heel
so important to know brain meditation
had me in tears
cindy says brain meditation had me in
tears thank you the brain meditation you
can do over and over again
and more fear leaves and leaves and when
we go through life with all kinds of
different things that even happen on a
daily basis it's important to get
rid of that fear so important um do you
ever think about the area
area breathe you know i know that
chemical sensitive people
they think about it i think pretty much
they think about it you know and it's
important to know and here's a good
point to remember if someone who's a
canary okay nicole mine
somebody who's a canary and they're
sensitive to chemical
smells chemical treat treated soups
chemical soups that are in these air
fresheners and
and scented candles and all that they're
sensitive what happens is
they're a human right they're human
you're human too if you're not sensitive
but you're still being affected just
like they are
but physically you just don't feel it
yet but we collect
all that chemical and all that chemical
and they eventually we end up with
problems we end up with the migraines
and all kinds of other issues from it
um so uh
allah says killing you smelly i never
knew thank you for opening my eyes thank
you for all your podcasts they are
powerful
exhilarating um they're they're
uncensored
i'm glad you've got a skin and you can
handle them they're uncensored at apple
podcast
so just so you know um and i'm sure you
do know you're listening to
him your brain meditation was
outstanding uh the flood of tears and
the emotions and release were amazing
it's incredible thank you
you are incredible thank you so much for
your powerful podcast i'm honored you're
here
oh i'm honored you're here and i'm
honored you're doing them because that's
what i'm here for
i'm here so you can have some tools to
heal
and chemtrail fruit fear your eyes are
open incredible
um i'm proud of all you guys really
if you have anxiety migraines chronic
sinusitis
chemical sensitivities uh you know
you have different symptoms like tingles
and numbness and burning skin and aches
and pains and fatigue
those chemicals those chemical
soups that are in those air fresheners
and send a candle spirit of compassion
always told me
that they were trouble and i just wanted
in the clones of perfumes too and i
wanted you to have
an episode that really really went into
all of it you don't want to miss these
episodes there's no advertising there's
no sponsorships there's no infomercials
i mean literally it's there and done for
you you guys have been getting two hours
of sleep because of those things
i slept an hour and 45 minutes three
days ago
because i was working on one and then i
slept three hours the day before that
i slept a two-hour night last night
and then i tried to get a nap for an
hour
in between because i'm working that hard
on
trying to produce this podcast for you
guys and the information and guess what
i'm not getting paid
there's no money there's no
advertisements so i can get money
there's no sponsorship so i can
there's none of that and i'm dumping
money into it i just want you guys to
have
the tools and the chance to heal and i
want to talk about the brain meditation
for a second
i coveted that and i feel bad i did i
coveted that years
year throughout my life because spirit
of compassion gave me that meditation
when i was younger
and i only gave it to some close friends
and family throughout the years
and i said wait a minute why why don't i
give everybody that meditation
what am i doing and it just dawned on me
and so i decided to make sure you have
that epic meditation so
you have every chance to heal and i
didn't think about it
until recently and i was like until a
few months ago when i started developing
and working on this podcast for you guys
i was like
the brain meditation has to be in the
first week they need the brain
meditation it's
critical pressing prince
hey there you are i remember you last
time i i read your comments
love all your podcasts brain meditation
i do every morning
and night i feel amazing every time i do
it i feel
i feel so light it's that powerful free
um and like i can take on the world it
gets better every time i do it
definitely sharing with people thank you
for sharing it pressing prints thank you
for sharing with people because what
that does is it's going to help others
it's going to help others tell them
apple podcasts though the link is in the
description
so the link is in the description if
they don't have they don't have an apple
device
tell them to go to med help them go to
medicalmedium.com
okay there's no service you have to pay
anything you don't have to do anything
go to medicalmedium.com and look at the
menu
see podcast in the menu and you can
listen to it right there with any device
so tell share with everybody please
share
because you know what it's hard to even
get the stuff out there because i'm
shadow band as it is with so much you
know going on out there
and because i'm censored everywhere and
censored here censored there
so share it if you can help people heal
in the whole bit um so important so
um okay so so liz uh
um you're a migraine sufferer sufferer
and
sense and other smells trigger my
migraine and asthma
yes that's what why i did this show and
people who aren't sufferers of anything
it's gonna trigger them too these
chemicals are taking over
these air fresheners are everywhere and
everywhere i mean colognes are
everywhere too but
scented candles everybody's burning them
and i talk about it in the episode
where there's people who are like gurus
and they're into health and they're
burning all those centered candles
they got people coming over and they're
lighting all these scented candles they
got one on the coffee table
one on the dinner two on the dinner
table they have friends over
and they're being choked out by chemical
scents by chemical soups meanwhile
they're into health they're into
exercising and all this i talk about
how people just aren't aware
sue erickson hi how are you loving your
uncensored podcast
thank you i just i had to do it i had to
do everything i could
to get the uncensored information out
there for you guys i had to
because i'm censored everywhere please
share please share if you can
the link is in description link is in
the description please leave a review at
apple podcast if you do that others can
find their way
i don't want to ask too much you guys i
don't i don't i like
to give free information i always tell
you you don't have to buy the cleanse
the heel book
even though it's on sale and everything
at amazon and all that it's
i i don't even tell you to get it i just
go to the library i know you guys
heard that a million times you heard me
say go to the library get it for free
but you know but it's on amazon 1699 in
amazon right now in the us
um but the point is is that it's i just
don't want to ask
much of you guys and but if you can
share it
it would be so helpful to get it out
there it would be so helpful
um so margaret says great podcast please
continue sharing thank you so you
totally get it
you totally get it ashley kevin i love
this i love this podcast thank you so
much for having giggling during this
hard
hard to stomach information you know i
got to tell you something about that
you're well
so you're also saying i'm a canary and
it meant so much to me so
grateful for your hard work i totally
understand i understand what it's like
to be canary like i get the whole thing
where
it's really difficult people don't know
you can even get ptsd from so much
you're up against as
a canary and when you're sensitive thank
you and you know the funny thing is
is that when you're saying that i'm
giggling during the show a little during
the real hard moments of information
that's how i've always coped my whole
life
because since i was four years old and
spirit of compassion started speaking to
me and giving me
scary information about the world and
about people suffering and about answers
to why people are sick that are like in
the cleanse of heal book right behind me
and what happens is that it's always
been hard
it's always been hard for me because i
feel people's pain i feel they're
suffering i feel what they're going
through
so one of the ways i've always coped is
i try to keep some joy still
within my heart and so i i giggle
i giggle a little and and chuckle a
little
in in a way it's how i cope with
terrible news
you know that i have to even deliver
things that are happening in the world
um william kerr hey how you doing
uh podcasts are wonderful thank you
spirit of compassion you're welcome
um hey lunelle hey how are you
like you like know you like know so much
stuff it's just unbelievable like you
know medical medium information
you know like it's just so cool i thank
you so much for sharing the brain
meditation it's truly incredible
i am already feeling changes so much
it's life-changing already for me lunell
that's amazing i'm so proud of you by
the way but i know you work hard
on your healing like i know that you're
also a meditation expert you know
meditations you've done a bunch of them
i think that's what i think i read in
your comments
and you know you know what it takes the
work you have to do involved and
and i'm honored that you that you love
the meditation because if you love it
that means a lot too because you've
you're really seized and a lot of people
you know that some people never even did
a meditation yet and
and so but uh which is great which is
fine
um look the chemtrail episode i want to
talk about that a little bit
uh the chemtrail episodes still remind
everybody it's not for the faint of
heart
it's a shocker a big shocker the
information
the details in the chemtrail episode are
unlike anything else
that's when you know it's unique and
original information like all medical
medium information is but
it's a shocker and you can put the
pieces of the puzzle together once you
listen to the episode
and you can protect yourself you can
protect yourself because that's what
it's about
and then the fruit fear episode oh my
god it's a whole nother one you have to
hear that one
uh wyla green just she said hi hi hi
back
proud of everybody here um
and deborah says get the book
yeah the book the cleanse the heel book
is a medical textbook
with with answers to so many different
conditions over 200 different conditions
deborah lynn um says is this going to be
your new
permanent platform for current past
podcasts for current podcasts
for current podcasts i'm sorry uh
apple podcast is yeah is is the platform
that's the platform for the medical
meeting podcast
talking too fast i've been talking all
day
so yeah hey
dr fan hey sharing it for all my
patients and family
amazing doctor incredible md incredible
guy doing an amazing amazing work
healing so many patients
uh incredible incredible the amount of
work he he does
and the commitment he has to his
patients and the compassion he has
to his patients is just it's just
unbelievable really is it's an
honor to know you a whole bit um
and yeah the canary um the link is in
description
so you know so the link is in the
description so so you can find the link
to the podcast it's a medical media
podcast that apple podcast
uncensored uncensored whole another
level
jennifer says keep a light heart i
listen yeah gotta keep a light heart
through it that's what you have to do
there's no question
trisha said you had me giggling if
the air freshener sent the candle clones
perfumes
that's that's a yeah that's a funny one
there's gonna be
some pretty intense podcast episodes
coming okay
okay two more
podcasts this week two more episodes
i'm releasing this week okay
so i know there's a little suspense in
there but two more
and yes they're gonna be above board
uncensored powerful information and
subscribe
to medical medium podcast at apple
podcast so you can be notified
if you're if you have an android or
another device or anything like i said
go to medicalmedium.com
go to the menu look for podcasts in the
menu and just listen that's all you can
listen on any device
sign up to the newsletter if you want so
you can get notified that way
sign up to the newsletter medical medium
newsletter medicalmedium.com
um kristen says chemtrail episode
podcast was amazing
uh incredible incredible
so happy so so glad you like you guys
like it so i want to say about the brain
meditation for a minute
just so you know what the brain
meditation does
is it bridges the gap that happens with
our neurons we get physical injuries
with our emotional center the neurons in
the emotional center of the brain
when we get bad news and breakups and
betrayal and broken trust and losses
and friends friendship issues and
everything else we've ever had in our
lives and and terrible losses and all
kinds of things
and promises broken all of that when we
go through life
what happens is every time we get some
bad news we end up getting some ptsd and
our
soul gets shocked out of us and it gets
shocked out of us and shocked out of us
and a distance occurs
and when that distance occurs this is
just being just beat out of us
basically when we go through hardships
what happens is fear fills in the center
so all this fear fills in the center
between
the soul and the physical brain and when
that fear fills in the center
it stays there and we just we live in
this whole thing where we're
we're highly sensitive we're fearful
we've got
trust issues that don't heal all of it
and
and then we also make decisions that may
not be the best because of the fear
this brain meditation okay bridges that
gap
not only does it the more you do it you
heal the neuron in this in the emotional
center of the brain
the more you do the brain meditation do
it every single day
every single night you fall asleep doing
it if you want it heals that
that those those neurons that get
tattered and burnt
out like burnt out from
trouble we go through bad news and
hardships just get burnt out
what happens is in the soul just comes
closer
and it just bridges the gap and the fear
disappears when you do that meditation
it's hard to explain with like this
but when you're in that meditation
you'll feel it you'll feel it
um let's see rebecca jean says could you
please talk about lupus absolutely we're
going to do an episode
uh i'm going to do an episode on lupus
there's no question it's going to be
coming up so
hang in there but cleanse the heel right
there you just look under the autoimmune
section of cleanse the heal
and you'll see you'll see in that when
it's all because lupus is
considered autoimmune so you just look
for the autoimmune section so you can
get guidance there and you could there's
so much you can do
for lupus think take the book to the
doctor if you want get it free at the
library if you don't want to buy it at
amazon
amazon's 51 off right now which is
unbelievable
51 off on the book it's a medical
textbook it's so packed with information
75 recipes over 200 symptoms and
conditions and answers for them
amazing um but anyway about the podcast
you love the podcast too
about the podcast it's one of these
things where
the episodes are going to be shattering
in a good way
just mind-blowing in a good way
informative in a good way and
healing in a good way i just i've been
telling you guys i've had an
announcement to make and i've had an
announcement to make in all this and
it was the podcast and that's what it
was
and it was about making sure that this
podcast was
released and i needed the right platform
apple's apple's the platform for it and
and i need to make sure it's uncensored
and all these things and there's no
infomercials no advertisements no
no no sponsorships you guys and i get
told
you should have that you know it's like
what what do you mean it's
you don't have to have that why would i
want why would i want
that in the way of the episodes um
so trisha says it is a very divine and
powerful meditation
very much appreciated for you sharing
this with us trisha i'm so proud of you
i'm honored you're doing it
please know that thank you for being
here thank you for just commenting
tonight
and thank you for sharing it and i'm
sure you're sharing it i'm sure you know
and i don't want to ask
anything from you guys because first of
all i just got to tell you something
most of you guys are struggling you mean
you've been through hell and back
you've been through a lot in your life
you've had some hardships you've been
sick you've been struggling with your
health and working on your healing
process i don't want to ask anything
from you guys it's the last thing i want
to do i mean you guys have it hard
enough with your symptoms and many of
you suffer from struggle that you're
and you're working on healing many of
you have healed already because you've
done the medical medium information
many of you haven't done the medical
medium information so you're not there
yet but you're working on
the point is i don't want to ask
anything but if there is anything
just share the episode with others keep
it going keep it out there flowing so
people can heal and that energy
comes back and it's just so important um
kristin
hello harris trisha marie is the
meditation on the podcast
the brain meditation is at the medical
medium podcast
okay at apple podcast you can subscribe
so you get notified
when each episode is out that's where it
is if you don't have an apple device go
to medicalmedium.com
menu go to the menu and find podcasts in
the menu and listen to it there
and the link is in description the link
is in the description so
um really incredible so if you have
brain the thing is with chemical
sensitivities
brain fog migraines chronic sinusitis
eye problems chest tightness depression
burning skin
what happens is these chemical soups
we're like the rat
we're like the test animals we're like
the test subjects the rats
as these chemical soups are tested upon
us
and they can trigger off anxiety they
can trigger off migraines it can trigger
off brain fog
that's what these things can do and so
important to know
what can happen here um
constance says the meditation is awesome
amazing
so glad you're doing it share it with
others
um michelle l hey i think mercury is a
big issue for vision
mercury is really real toxic heavy
metals like mercury
definitely affect the central nervous
system they affect the optic nerve they
f they affect the neurons they they
affect
so many things going on with people when
you have the toxic heavy metals
absolutely
um so teresa says how do i find out
about the meditation
so it's the link is in the description
so
um teresa you can see the link right in
the description you take you
right to there and you can listen to it
so that's what you can do
so i'm proud of all you guys so this the
fragrance show
is really an eye opener it's because you
know a lot of us have to
we're forced to have to breathe in all
these things
and it's good to know how you can
protect yourself too and it's good to
know what
what's happening with that all of it's
important it really is
um so
that's funny so anyway i'm really proud
of you guys i truly am so i hope you
catch the brain meditation episode i
hope you use it
use it because it it's there for you
it's there for you to heal and
share it so others can heal it's not a
man-made meditation know the difference
it's not man-made it comes from above
it's not something you could even
make or create it actually comes from
above that's where it came from
originally anna says i have an android
so i'm getting the podcast from emails
is this as good as apple if it's from
the medical medium email
then yes it is
yeah so share it on ig and facebook
incredible
anyway you guys and it's so great to be
here i'm glad i had a chance to talk
about the brain meditation and what
happens in our brain
the connection that occurs the soul
coming back to the body
all of that um listen to the episode
uh you know killing you smelly which is
air fresheners scented candles all that
clones perfumes
if you get a chance the chemtrail
episode the fruit fear episode was the
number two episode
number three episodes the brain
meditation you should be bringing that
in every night
and try to listen to these episodes and
share them if you want there's so much
information in them but killing you
smelly is the episode that's on
right now i mean the newest release
today
get a chance to hear it lindsay says i
listened to both episodes today they are
great honored i'm so happy i'm so happy
incredible so um
yeah uh joni says thank you sir love the
podcast and so glad
and i'm so glad that you're listening
because i mean that's why i did it
that's the whole
that's the whole point it's the whole
point you guys
you guys are amazing love you so
just know that i care i stand with you
guys
share with other people with the podcast
episodes
make sure you um you know try to leave a
review at apple podcast if you can i
mean if you're up for it if you can
that'd be great so other people can
can you know hear what's going on and
all that and
proud of all of you i believe in all of
you and i will
see you next time there's two more
episodes coming this week
look out for them look out for them
because they're really
packed they're really packed and so
so important subscribe so you get the
subscribe to medical medium podcast at
apple podcast so you're first to get
notified and you don't miss
any of them so you mean you get the
uncensored versions no matter what okay
all right bless your heart know that i
care love you guys
and keep a light heart i believe in you
and i'll see you next time