now not two nights in a row at Cafe
Gratitude four nights in a row they
graciously open their doors to the
medical medum community for two more
nights and not only is it the 22nd and
the 23rd but it is the 21st and the 24th
so it's 21st 22nd 23rd
24th dinners meet and greet I will be in
Cafe Gratitude it's the collaboration
between Cafe Gratitude and medical
medium the it's going to be a four
course
dinner it's going to be incredible and
you guys know what happened okay all the
tickets sold out in the two nights okay
for two different locations of Cafe
Gratitude the tickets all sold out in 3
minutes or something like that but what
is going on now is Cafe Gratitude they
graciously opened up for the 21st and
the 24th for the medical medum community
so there you go they felt bad I feel bad
we were just mortified that it sold so
quickly so quickly that it I feel like
whoa what what happened right was
because someone got a hold of the link
um you know they sleuthed out the link
and they passed it around and it was all
sold out before we can even present it
and then we try to present it today but
now it's even it's even more incredible
absolutely incredible it is the 21st and
the 24th two more days added to the
already two days so it's four nights in
a row but it's not just medical medium
and inredible food elevated by Chef Drew
over there at Cafe Gratitude it's also
me being there in person I'm going to be
eating there I'm going to be there in
person I'm going to be meeting and
greeting everybody it's an intimate
setting so it's even different in like
true medical medium fashion now we have
four nights which is actually incredible
thanks to Cafe Gratitude we have four
nights which is amazing so here's the
deal here's what you have to look out
for here's the
information okay get on the waiting list
anybody who got the email today about
the two nights you'll see right there
that there's a waiting list right so
check it out get on the waiting list and
then Friday at 12:00 Pacific 3:00
Eastern we're going to release the link
we're going to go live with the link so
anybody on the waiting everybody on the
waiting list has a chance to get onto
one of those two extra additional nights
so we have to understand like there's
going to be two more additional nights
and you have a chance to get on there
but you but the link goes live on Friday
like I said at 12:00 Pacific 3:00
Eastern so just letting you know exactly
when it happens so you have a chance to
get in there it's going to be incredible
I'm going to be there I'm going to do
some talking in there I'm going to be
there meeting greeting everybody on an
intimate level I'm exciting the waiting
list link okay is in the description of
this video so you can check that out
um and uh in the profile of Instagram so
on the profile and in the description of
this video the waiting list link is
there get on the waiting list that's
what you need to do if you're interested
in going anybody in California anybody
anywhere else that wants to make the
trip this is going to be an incredible
experience I am completely excited so
what's happening it's this collaboration
right amazing collaboration between Cafe
Gratitude a Legendary Legendary
restaurant
legendary restaurant and medical medium
and we're collaborating and we're going
to have a four course four course meal
on all four of those nights the 21st 2
October 21st October 22nd October 23rd
October 24th I will be there I will be
there to see you shake your hand it is
going to be an intimate setting it's
going to be incredible I'm excited I'm
going to be there so I'm just letting
everybody know that I'm really pumped up
about this and seriously I feel really
bad about how people were like wait a
minute when it was supposed to come out
tomorrow and then somebody sleuth the
link they got it they spread it around
hey I mean I mean it happens I don't
know how or what but it happens and
everybody just bought the tickets up but
listen this is incredible because this
is celebrating the launch of the
collaboration between Cafe Gratitude and
medical medium where October 15th is
when they start putting the medical
medium recipes on the Cafe Gratitude
menu which is
incredible absolutely incredible so I'm
excited about that it's very special so
October 15th but that's not the date of
the these special dinners the dates of
the special dinners is 21st 22nd 23rd
24th I will be there it's going to be
really awesome really amazing really
special and you got a chance to actually
get a ticket and be there because we got
two addic
nights that is amazing the 22nd and the
23rd are all sold out so October 22nd
and October 23rd are all sold out but
what will be open is October 21st and
October 24th those two will be open and
so I hope I got this information across
to you guys because I'm really I'm
really excited me Tobe 787 says might
need four more nights is I was you're
saying four more
nights I'm really excited get on the
waiting list the link is in description
link is in the profile right on
Instagram get on the waiting list okay
and please um please you know let let
Cafe Gratitude know that you appreciate
them for this because we really do you
let give them a shout out let them know
how you appreciate it you know
appreciate what they're doing the extra
nights and everything uh let them know
how you guys are excited I'm excited
medical medum team's excited we're going
to be there we're all going to be there
I'm really really pumped up and wait to
you taste these dishes wait till you
taste them like okay if you came over my
house and you were in my kitchen and I
made them for you they would taste all
right they would taste good right they
would taste good but what Chef Drew did
in this collaboration and what we did is
it was elevated he elevated them he
brought that Cafe Gra itude flavor
profile right in there these dishes are
insane utterly insane I'm just letting
you know I was in Cafe
Gratitude I know so anyway I just want
to let you guys know what's going on I
want to give you the 411 so just to
recap really quick right Cafe Gratitude
medical medium
collaboration okay October 22nd 23rd are
sold out but Cafe Gratitude graciously
opened up October 21st October 24th okay
link is in the description on the
waiting list so you can see the waiting
list link is in the description link is
in the profile to get on the waiting
list and then come Friday 12 12:00
Pacific 3:00 Eastern we're going to get
that link going live anybody on the
waiting list has a shot has a chance to
be there it's going to be a meet and
greet right there in the restaurant with
me it's going to be incredible four
course meal I'm going to be in there you
guys don't want to miss it so anyway and
Cy gratitude let them know you want to
do more of these let them know because
that's what we should do we should do
some more of these along the way and I'm
really excit of you guys anyway look
check it out when you get a chance uh
we've been posting about it but now
we're just like this is a whole another
level we got two more nights it's
mindblowing two more nights so I'm
really excited about it so I'm looking
forward to it I'm looking forward to
seeing you guys it's been a long week a
long day working day and night I have
been doing a lot of hours and um yeah so
I might get some sleep tonight anyway
you guys I love you much talk to you
soon and uh take care I'm going to sip
some lemon balm tea