facebook youtube telegram and probably
somewhere else too
and we're doing some great stuff i'm
showing you right now we're making
cherry
banana soft serve ice cream i'm just
showing there's some frozen cherries
right there which is going to be really
great
we're making
garbanzo bean chickpea hummus that's fat
free we're making it with this machine
you can make it in seconds like this
with this machine
seconds it's going to be incredible
right
we're making
almond milk which is going to be really
cool because everybody's going they're
all going to buy their almond milk
they're all going they don't know what's
in that almond milk it's a lot of msg
and everything else they're all buying
our own no we're going to make almond
milk that's free of all that and guess
what
extra surprise here
we're going to make
roasted almond butter
and you're going to be blown away
because i'm blown away because last
night i was making some roasted almond
butter and i was just like this is
insane can't wait to show you that and
not hey we're not done we're gonna make
some carrot
puree
or carrot baby food too if you have a
baby right and then
if you think that
is a lot
we're making kale
juice
kale celery juice
but we're using celery as a carrier to
drive the kale home to our brain nervous
system and everything else so you do
your celery juice in the morning and
then at the end of the day you do your
kale tonic right so this is going to be
great all with this machine i'm pumped
up so here we are i'm anthony william
the medical medium number one new york
times bestselling author and
of the medical medium book series right
most popular book series in the world in
health seven years running imagine that
fancy that with no pr and campaigns and
millions of dollars behind it it
happened because people healed when they
got the book and the information so
austin good to see you the omega 1500
makes eating healthy so much easier oh
that's so incredible that that's so cool
i really feel the same way i really love
it so the unmanned 1500 i just want to
let you guys know it's on sale it's 80
off
and you get a free book the sale is
going to be ending pretty soon
okay but it's right now the sales on 80
off for the mm 1500 link is in the
description link is in the profile i'm
just letting you know it comes with
cleanse the heel okay a free book so 80
off plus cleanse the heel
incredible really is so i want everybody
to know that
let's go
so we're doing it let's start with some
ice cream let's do that and let's make
sure we don't drop the book again
let's get some ice cream going
yeah
we're on
so i got the machine running it's nice
and quiet it's not going wow
boom it's not doing all that stuff and
all everybody's machine
like crazy sounds and all that metal in
everybody's machines all the metal the
centrifuge metal the grinding metal
gears right and all those other juicers
where everybody everybody's getting
flakes of metal and they don't realize
it this machine's not doing that
all right
let's start with some ice cream right
now
let's do that
just grabbing myself
a little hand towel right here
so i'm gonna drop some
cherries in here
a couple cherries
right
now i'm kind of doing a blend right some
cherries
a little bit of banana so i'm making
cherry banana ice cream
okay a couple more cherries
right so we're making some ice cream now
we're not messing around
so this is a cherry
banana ice cream this thing is insane
look at that
i think i'm gonna get some cherries in
there though
i'm like nervous
i'm like nervous what the heck
i'm nervous because this is incredible
it's like what
i can't wait to have some people over
some family over
and i'm gonna make some ice cream for
them
that's what i'm gonna do
[Music]
make some killer ice cream
ice cream that doesn't kill you because
it's ice cream that doesn't kill your
heart
how about that
there's no buttermilk in this ice cream
there's no
butter fat
milk
dairy
so you're not killing the heart you know
what i mean especially everybody having
heart problems right now you hear about
it every day everybody's having heart
problems right now it's actually insane
it's got a little piece right here
so we got this beautiful
ice cream here
right so we can even make it really nice
too
there you go
look at that
look look at that is that unbelievable
cherry banana ice cream right there
you guys see the close-up right there
amazing
really is
incredible tiktak you guys just made
cherry banana ice cream this is dairy
free all those people that are like
worried about dairy right this is
incredible right there
boom happened that fast that's amazing
so all right let's move on we're going
to make some other things too so i'm
going to move these bananas over
and these cherries over
so i'm excited
so if you guys just came on here
what what you're witnessing right is the
mm 1500 it's 80 off right now the
megajuicers.com link is in the profile
link is in the description don't miss
out it comes free with the cleanse the
heel book right over 200 symptoms
conditions protocol supplements dosages
medical information in here
okay
we're going to the next thing so let's
make it we have our ice cream
we're good with that so we're going to
the next part
we're going to do
the carrot
the carrot baby food or puree the carrot
puree
so that's next
that's what we're doing
get it together
get it together all right here we go
remove my ice cream over so here we go
we got some carrots right here these are
steamed carrots
okay you guys
and that's what we have right here
steamed carrots
so we're to make this puree
it's always good to have something like
this on hand so when you guys like
someone gets a root canal
you know someone gets
someone gets you see the root canal
video right in the newsletter make sure
you sign up to my newsletter so you can
see exclusive videos right every sunday
every week we're doing that
and someone gets a t they get you know
something a tooth pulled they get
a wisdom tooth pulled they get dental
surgery they get an implant
they get a you know something else going
on in their mouth or whatever maybe they
have a really bad canker sore sometimes
it's good to just have like food easy
like this so you don't have to chew
somebody with trigeminal neuralgia right
all of it
so sometimes it's a lot easy so let's go
we're going to make some
i'm going to make a little carrot puree
right here
i can't find the link courtney's asking
it's in the description
i hope it's there
right mm-1500
should be in the description right there
so here we go we're making
steamed carrots these are steamed
carrots are actually still hot we're
making puree
and you can spice it you can add things
to it if you want there's nothing wrong
with that if you want to do that there's
nothing wrong at all you can add stuff
to it you can spice it you can do you
can do anything like that
these are really juicy carrots
right
so we got our carrot puree right here
we're good
so i'm just going to show you guys
right here
so that i mean it's incredible for baby
food the machine is amazing for baby
food seriously
you got your puree
also people that
they have jaw problems teeth problems
trigeminal neuralgia burning pain in
their jaw you know maybe they had some
dental work done
whatever i mean or you can use it for
different recipes so you can make these
purees for different recipes so that's
really cool that so we got that that's
the second thing we've made just now
move that aside
now we're going to make the hummus
now you guys i'm gonna tell you right
now i'm really excited about this
the hummus is gonna be really cool so
this is a garbanzo bean chickpea hummus
so let's do this
so this is going to be fun just moving
this over
here we go
you guys just came on here we just made
a sorbet which is made ice cream banana
cherry ice cream if you guys just came
on
we made some puree carrot puree if you
just came on to to see that right
machine's 80 off this is mm-1500 now
we're doing some hummus
so i want to show you something here we
go we'll do a close-up on this if we can
let's get a little close-up on here
all right so what you see here
there you go you see garbanzo beans
right
can you guys see that
and
we're making hummus
now we're making a fat-free hummus
because you can
really easily make a fat-free hummus
with this machine
that's what's so awesome about this
we're gonna we're gonna make a smooth
hummus
that's fat free you don't have to add
all that oil in there to actually get it
to go and do its thing so this is going
to be really fun right here so let's get
ready for this
so i just need a bowl to actually this
to put it in here we go
all right
firing up the machine
we're doing it
love how quiet this machine is
so
now what i like to do is i'm going to
add a little bit
of sea salt to the hummus
as it's coming in okay you can add a
little bit of sea salt to the hummus
can you see that you guys you see the
hummus going out
add a little bit more sea salt check
this out
now i'm going to do something i'm going
to take it to another step
that's what we're going to do we're
going to take it to the next level
i'm going to cut a lemon right now
grab my knife
let me cut a lemon
check this out
i'm going to drop a little bit of a
little bit of lemon juice in here
and then i'm gonna put the garbanzo
beans and there's no fat in here this is
incredible
right
look at this i'm gonna put a little bit
more lemon in here i'm gonna add a
little touch more salt
get some more garbanzos in here
you guys this is fat free hummus being
made quickly
really quickly
and i'm just like yeah i'm fooling
around i'm putting a little lemon in
here
putting a little touch
just a little touch of sea salt adding
their garbanzos come on
amazing
some more garbanzos in here
this is really cool a little bit more
lemon touch more sea salt
so it's all evenly mixed in there
yuda says i just told my husband there's
a new mm juicer that even he can make
ice cream he can do ice cream he said
buy it buy it he loves my ice cream meat
only from fruits
incredible
still making some great hummus here you
can do black bean hummus you guys you
can do chickpea hummus like i'm doing i
mean how cool is that i'm adding a
little bit more lemon
right into it straight into it with a
little bit of sea salt watch that come
out
man
but here's what's crazy that's a smooth
amazing hummus right there
with no oil in there no no
start stopping artery collecting
plaque building oil even if it's just do
you know healthy ones healthy ones still
build up in our system
you know this is fat free right here
this is a fat free hummus
look at that we're gonna add a few more
of these garbanzos in
the rest of them
this is just too great
i'm gonna keep this bowl because i'm
gonna use this bowl
so what i'm gonna
i'm do pop in a little bit more lemon in
here
there we go
there you go
you got your hummus coming out
look at that
shut the machine down
all right i'm gonna drop this in the
bowl
okay you guys all right
drop the hummus right in there
it's all done
okay let me see if i can get it in into
the uh camera eye
right here
okay so that's the hummus right there
fat free garbanzo bean chickpea
boom
incredible
maybe with that juicer just like that
what
this is a juicer did i just say this is
a juicer because i just made hummus i'm
confused wait a minute here
how did i just make a fat-free
incredible chickpea hummus
i thought this was a juicer
it is a juicer
so here you go and you can just you can
just prepare this in any way you want
right here so
so there you go that's your hummus right
here
and
what i'm gonna do like you can add now
spices to this how incredible is this
get ready
let's put a little garlic powder in here
we'll drop a little bit of garlic powder
in there garlic
as i always say make sure everybody else
in the family has a little bit of garlic
because whoever didn't have garlic is
going to be like hey
everybody smells like garlic
right a little bit of cayenne
right there
love cayenne inside the hummus right
there that's a that's a great one a
little bit of paprika in here too you
guys
how crazy is that if you just got on
here mm 1500 is 80 off right now you get
a free medical medium cleanse the heel
book with it
i just put spices in here i mean you
could chop onion in there if you want to
hey you can run onion through there as
you're making the hummus you could run
anything through there you can be
creative you don't have to do it like
this you can come up your with your own
way of doing it i'm just mixing some of
that
some of those spices in there i mean you
can do it any way your heart desires
that's what's incredible about this
you don't have to do it the way i'm
doing it
be your own person do to your own way
how incredible there we go okay
let's get this
let's get this plated now
so
gonna put this beautiful hummus right
here this is fat-free hummus
all right
so you don't have to you worry about the
weight gaining too right because that's
a thing everybody's like oh i'm gaining
weight well how much oil how much fat is
in your diet that you have going on
right
so this is like
guilt-free
but it's not just that
it's also this is isn't it this isn't
just that it's not about guilt-free or
anything it's about keeping your fats
down so your body can heal so if you're
somebody who's chronically ill right if
you're somebody who's chronically ill
someone who's sick someone who's
struggling keeping the fats low is one
of the ways we move forward because you
don't bog down the liver you don't bog
down the immune system so this is a way
to actually heal this is that's why i
call this machine these machines medical
devices medical machines
okay and that's what's so great about it
[Music]
i don't know what that means let me see
here put this over here
there we go
so i got this beautiful hummus right
here
how is this better than humans made with
a blender are hummus made with a blender
is elizabeth's saying how is this better
than hummus made with a blender all
right so you can make hummus with a
blender there's no question but when you
do fat free hummus it's hard to get it
smooth
it's hard to get it smooth and creamy so
what you have here when you have this
machine the difference is you can get it
smooth and creamy and this is fat free
so there's no oil in here
but yet it's smooth and creamy
that's the difference between getting in
a blender when you put in the blender
you have to add a big hunk of tahini in
there too like that's something people
do to try to get it that kind of creamy
texture when you're doing the blender
you don't have to do that this way
literally we just put the garbanzo beans
the chickpeas right into the machine
and you didn't have the oil you didn't
have all that tahini or olive oil you
know what happens people put ounces and
ounces of olive oil in their hummus at
least the restaurants do you sit down
you know you sit down in the restaurant
you're like yeah can i order a hummus
okay sure yes you can bring me some
crackers too okay thank you they dropped
the hummus down you wouldn't believe how
much olive oil or canola oil is in that
hummus if you couldn't imagine how much
is in there so that's the whole thing so
it's important to know that this is
creamy and smooth this was pulverized in
such an incredible way that that's the
difference right there
so i hope that answers the question
right
link is in the profile link is in the
description this is the mm-1500
it's 80 off really incredible so what
i'm going to do is put this in here for
a second if you guys don't mind right
here
so here we go
you got your hummus
you've got your crudite you've got your
crackers right here you can have a nice
cracker you can dip it in your hummus
like that
there you go you got your crackers you
got your carrots you got your radishes
you can take a little bit of a radish
right there
it's really good
no stoner jokes
right
so that's something you can do
all right
we're moving on to the next one we're
making some
green juice
we're making some serious juice we're
doing that now
excited about this
all right so
we're going to talk about celery for a
couple of seconds right
now
when it comes down to celery juice
to get celery to do its thing and move
the needle
okay to get celery to do its thing and
move the needle you guys
it has to be by itself it's herbal
medicine you juice on its own
but you can also use celery
as
a carrier
and that's a different situation
so what we're doing is we're making a
kale juice right now
but we're going to use the trace mineral
salts and celery
to become the carrier for phytochemical
compounds
from the kale
to go deep into the liver and so forth
all right
so that's important to know so let's do
it so we're not just sitting here making
celery juice you do your celery juice in
the morning that's what i do i do in the
morning empty stomach 32 ounces that's
what i do
the end of the day this is an option for
people at the end of the day where we
now do a kale juice but we're making
sure celery is the carrier so let's get
moving on if you guys just got on here
we made a sorbet because i see new
people coming on we got a sorbet right
here banana and cherry made it with this
machine boom that's icy cold right there
we got a carrot puree baby food and
carrot puree right there okay
we just made the hummus if you guys just
came on here right
we just made the incredible fat-free
hummus
with this machine now we're making kale
celery juice
let's do it
we're on
so i'm gonna run some kale through here
right now
this is beautiful kale i have right here
gorgeous you guys on tick-tock
you've entered the twilight zone
guys on telegram you guys are in the
matrix
okay
this is where we take health to like
always the new level right
mimi says
can we add an apple to the kale and
celery does that reduce the nutrition
you can add an apple to it because
you're not doing celery by itself
anymore
telegram you guys have entered the
matrix
tick-tock we're in the twilight zone
right now
so what i'm doing right now is using
celery as a carrier
okay
i'm using the trace mineral salts in
celery which is an herb to carry
the phytochemical compounds
of the kale
so kale
enters the body what about us on youtube
i love you guys on youtube you guys i
love you guys on youtube are you kidding
youtube doesn't like me
youtube doesn't show my videos to anyone
rumble you guys know i love you guys on
rumble
you guys on rumble man you have en
entered planet mars
we're on planet mars right now
so what i'm doing okay so let's let's
talk about this for a little bit let's
let's kind of get a grip let's get a
grip here
before i start talking a little too
silly and everything and then next thing
you know what i'm i'm like
somewhere else check this out okay you
guys
all right
what you're doing is
you're you're you're using herbal
medicine so this is important to know
for so many people here when you're
dealing with celery you're dealing with
herbal medicine
herbal medicine that's easy on the body
easy on the system easy on the
intestinal tract lining easy on
everything this is different when we go
and try to take all this crazy stuff
that someone recommends and we try to
take something else and we just burn a
hole through our gut
that's not what this is right this is
herbal medicine that really turns things
around inside of us but we're using this
herbal medicine
to do something for us we're using this
okay
right we're using this to do something
to give us something else so what we're
doing
is we're using the celery
to bind onto
to carry phytochemical compounds in that
leafy green so you're looking at those
leafy greens
that's what that's what we're doing
it's important to know
and i want to show you about this how
the juicer works a little bit too with
this you're seeing dry pulp come out
see that's dry that's because this has a
celery end cap so you're seeing the dry
pulp come out just like the mm-900
which is my favorite juicer the mm-900
but you're seeing the dry pulp come out
and tick-tock
the reason why this is the twilight zone
right now is because that pulp is
supposed to be so sloppy wet
that it's supposed to even be filling
juice in that container and that's money
out the door money out the window
sandy says where do you find the
discount for the m for the 1500 hit the
link right there link is in the
description
well right where it takes you to there
it should show you how much you've
gotten off 80 off
so i'm running some more kale through
here
so you're witnessing
you're witnessing dry pulp coming out of
this machine
that's dollars going in your pocket
right there so that's dollars going in
your pocket the one thing about the mm
1500 and the mm-900 is they pay for
themselves over time they actually pay
for themselves and that's the difference
with these two machines they pay for
themselves
so we're running a little bit more
celery through here we're running kale
through here i'm running a celery stick
in here then i'm running kale through
here
and i'm doing a blend right here
i'm using the celery herb
the herb as a carrier
and what you're seeing is dry pulp
popping out
another thing
you're seeing
is there isn't metal
now all involved in there like the other
juicers were all that metal particles
from the metal gears doing this and
central fuse all the metal you're not
seeing that either which is amazing
all right
so
we're running kale we're running some
celery through here
now you're seeing that dry pulp come out
right you guys
there it is now listen don't get me
wrong you can take the mm-900
and still run kale
and cilantro with your celery through it
here we go but here's the thing with
inflation and food costs
this is helping
that's what i love about it with
inflation and food costs
cosmic alchemist hey how are you i see
you always leave a comment once
on
youtube
now whole foods organic celery price
inflation from 1.79 to 299 i save a
bunch of money using the mm juicer
that's the whole point food costs go up
the juicer is extracting more
it's less there's less moisture in the
pulp
so i'm going to show you how that works
too in a second you guys
so let me shut this down for a minute
okay so let's let's just show you how
this works
so that's the pulp
now with other juicers here's what goes
wrong right here right
i'm gonna take the pull belt
right i'm gonna take the pulp out
you don't see
any any liquid dumping out do you see
any liquid dumping out in my hand i'm
trying to get a spot here it's like i'm
okay here we are
it's like a it's like being in a fun
house right you're walking around you
see like
it's like you don't know where you are
but check this out right here
trying to get lined up with the camera
if you guys see this you don't see
liquid coming out of my hand
is someone trying to read my spirit said
someone's trying to read my palm
unbelievable
that's interesting
spirit of compassion just told me that
someone out there is actually trying to
read my bomb lines
i know i never had that happen
you're probably a gifted palm reader too
just just don't just don't see anything
in my palm that's scary please like you
know what i mean like they're finally
gonna they're finally gonna get them
they're finally gonna get them
or he's gonna work himself to death and
then he's just he's gonna die because
he's gonna he's gonna work himself to
the point where he burns a candle six
ends seven eight ends instead of one end
both ends all right
so the point is you don't see liquid
coming out
someone was trying to read my palm lines
that's what spirit of compassion just
said and i'm impressed that was that was
smart that was smart of someone trying
to do that
okay so what you're seeing in my palm
now is you're seeing pulp
that's drier than the other juicers that
means you get more of that celery juice
more of that kale juice
that's when you buy kale and you squeeze
every last bit out of it to use it as
medicine someone said i'll just eat the
kale leaf okay that's smart you eat one
kale leaf two carrot leaves four kilo
leaves five but that's not gonna cut it
you're not going to extract what you
need to extract out of that kale like
you can with the juicer right
but here's the thing this is such a
pulverizer this is a cold pressed
machine with such a pulverizer that
you're getting that out of there
right and you see there's no liquid
pouring into my hand and i've seen some
juicers out there with just it's almost
like what
so
w smith said there's no link for the
juicer juicers the link should be in the
description i'm pretty sure link is in
the description and it's the mm-1500
megajuicers.com mm-1500
i wonder what someone's thinking when
they're trying to read my pump they're
probably like whoa
whoa
yeah okay so we got it we got it we're
going to move on we got a lot to cover
right now so that's what we have to do
so let's get moving on a little bit
so i'm going to get this juice in a
container now
right
spirit of compassion also said someone's
falling asleep on me right now
someone's watching and they're falling
asleep they didn't sleep good last night
and they're falling asleep right now
maybe i can tell a bedtime story well
there once was
there was a magical lake
in that magical lake a whole bunch of
mermaids
were swimming out
and then a sea monster came along
and then
but somebody's falling asleep okay there
we go we got
when you when you've been hearing a
voice since age four
you just do the best you can
all right you guys
right there you're looking at the kale
juice you're looking at the kale and
celery and just know this
what i did
was i used celery as a tool in a
different way i used it as a carrier
to
okay
hold on to the phytochemical
phytochemical compounds of the kale and
to carry that
in to your brain and body right
and your liver so that's what we did
jennifer
i'm sewing a mermaid tail watching this
and you're cracking me up that's
incredible
[Music]
that's incredible
how many people sew a mermaid tail
that's interesting
all right you guys
we we got some fish to fry we got some
fish to fry
so uh
so
we're gonna move on to the next one is
what we're gonna do okay
[Music]
all right
going we're doing some milk now some
almond milk now that's where we're
heading now
here we go
so how many of you guys are drinking
almond milk i want to let me ask you
guys a question
let me ask you guys a question
how many of you guys are drinking almond
milk
how many how much almond milk is in
everybody's refrigerators that's what i
want to know okay right
that's underneath you guys just got on
here i want to show you a couple things
ah this is actually starting to defrost
a little bit this is my
cherry banana sorbet you gotta watch
that it doesn't melt down the sides do
you ever you know when you're having
your ice cream
so good cherry
cherry ice cream
okay that's insane
all right you guys
if you don't mind i'm just gonna sit
down and eat
and we'll get back to this in a few
minutes
i'm gonna pull the chair up all right
we're just gonna take i'm just gonna
take a little eating break here
this is so good
i'm just kidding around we're going
we're moving we're moving
cherry banana ice cream
okay the the mm-9 the mmm 1500 is this
one
i know the mm-900 is an amazing juicer
it juices the celery it juices the kale
but right now it's the mm-1500 it's on
sale 80 off you get a free book i just
made hummus let's go to that
we got some hummus right here too
fat-free hummus right here
i'm grabbing a radish in this one
mmm that's good
that's really good
fat free hummus why does it taste so
good i got lemon i made it through the
machine
incredible
yeah
i'm doing everything i can not to do a
stoner joke
because i don't smoke
right
and there's the puree right there
let's keep it going we got stuff to do
victoria rising from the ashes
amazing handle by the way
do the stoner joke
it is so funny all right we'll do one
later
all right we'll do one later don't worry
we'll do it we'll do a stoner joke later
you know and it's not like look you guys
it's not like i'm trying to make fun of
everybody who smokes that's not it or or
whatever or they vape it or
they put it in a little whatever the
little
machine and steam it up into them or
whatever you know i'm not trying to make
fun of people i'm not i get it people
it's a hard life it's a hard world
people are going to be smoking pot
they're going to be smoking pot i don't
smoke any
debris says hand over the hummus anthony
yeah no it's mine
stoner jokes are funny though julie says
i know look and i didn't mean to say
yesterday i told you about my friend you
see you know his wife left him
and i feel terrible because he's asking
me for a job
and i told him you're not even wearing
socks right now
and
he got mad at me because he wasn't
wearing socks and the reason why he knew
he wasn't wearing socks
is because i was on the phone with him
in spirit of compassion told me he
wasn't wearing socks
so he's sitting there asking me for a
job i said when's the last time you had
socks on
i mean i get it there's a lot of guys
that do hipsters and stuff or they like
to wear they like to wear whatever
birkenstocks or sandals and i totally
get that's perfectly fine i mean that's
awesome
but i'm just saying that he's he hasn't
been like he he's been on the couch for
20 years his wife left him because he
doesn't even take out the garbage but i
get it that's fine but he smokes weed he
smokes weed every day he smokes weed on
the couch
and i said to him i said you want to
work for me the first thing you got to
do is put your damn socks on
and then
take a shower and then
get something to eat
and then maybe we can talk about like
working
or something and he's like well you know
he had pizza boxes oh what i'm trying to
say is okay i'm sorry about the story i
know we're talking about the mm-1500 my
friend had pizza boxes on the coffee
table
and his wife once in a while stop his
ex-wife now stops by and she cleans up
the pizza boxes once in a while because
she feels so bad for him even though she
left him because he's a stoner
the point is is that the pizza boxes
were on the coffee table when i was on
the phone with them and spirit of
compassion said he's got also the pizza
boxes all over the coffee table and i
said
i said and get the pizza boxes off the
damn coffee table if you can and he said
he goes how am i going to work for you
spirit of compassion knows everything
i go why are you trying to like hide
some what are you talking about
lorraine elle says
you just have a good sense of humor aw
and love it so okay let's get going
we're moving
we're making almond milk right now
and um but i have a lot of compassion
for anybody going through anything of
course you know all right let's go you
guys
all right let's move it we're on almond
milk right now
so
okay
note to self
all right
all right we're moving
we're making the almond milk right now
so what you see right now are almonds
right here
these are soaked overnight
they're soaked overnight
right
adding a little bit of water to them
soaked overnight rinsed them now we're
making almond milk
right here we go
dropping the almonds in here
now almond milk is notorious for having
msg in it natural flavors
msg
[Applause]
see you guys
people say well i'd love to be hanging
out with aw well you're just gonna hear
stories like that and you'll be bored
off your butt so
no i wasn't that fun hanging around with
aw all he does is tell stories like that
[Applause]
about his friends all right listen so i
have almond milk being made right now so
you can get a close-up into this right
here so what you see is almond milk
being made now
almond milk has fillers in it you don't
see
so if you got your almond milk there
could be fillers in it you don't know
that are in there plus carrageenan is
msg so msg builds up in our brain
it creates deposits in our brain that
msg and it builds up in our brain and it
and it creates deposits
okay so you can be
i was doing a live a live performance
okay
in front of a big crowd years ago i
think it was about seven years ago and
a really a nice person came up
out of the crowd and said
you know like to get a reading
and spirit of compassion said the person
had msg deposits
in their brain causing problems with
their head
causing severe problems
and then she said
she eats chinese food every single day
for the last 50 years seven days a week
that's what she said she said she's had
chinese food
from the chinese food restaurant down
the street for 50 years
where she lives
i said
every day every single day
for 50 years for lunch
and i said well all that msg
right
builds up a deposit in the back of your
brain so she touched the back of her
head and said that's where my problem is
the pr what people don't realize is when
you're having
and there's msg in every single food
there's msg in
every food all kinds of food
around the world
in every store in every restaurant
okay so we just made some almond milk
right here
so we have
this incredible almond milk
and guess what this almond milk is free
of msg and fillers it's free of msg free
of fillers free of the bad stuff that's
what this
almond milk
is free up what people don't realize
nowadays in any restaurant right
any restaurant the msg is insane
people don't know it it's in food it's
in all the different food products it's
natural flavors natural flavors that's a
big one right there
all right so let's let's pour this right
here
i'm gonna mix it up first of all give it
a little mix
right
so i got it right there
and i'm going to make a nice glass of it
now
this is real wholesome real pure
real clean
there's froth in here you just gotta mix
up too
and that's it right there you're looking
at it right
that's your almond milk just pure as it
gets that's as pure as it gets you guys
on tick tock pure as it gets you guys on
telegram
piers it gets on youtube rumble facebook
right
that right there
is
really incredible okay someone said how
much fat is in almond milk well here's
the problem almond milk is in the store
they add oil to it
to enrich in it so they add oil to the
almond milk you buy in the store
so that's added oil which is leading us
to the next place
we're gonna make
some roasted almond butter
and that's next so i'm really excited
about that
all right so let's put this aside
too much fun too much fun if you guys
just came on here let's give you a
rundown this is the handman 1500 okay mn
that's the sorbet i made with it that's
the banana cherry sorbet which is ice
cream right no dairy products in there i
just made the almond milk that's free of
msg carrageenan natural flavors no oil
added
free of that i just made
right the baby food or the puree
right the carrot that steamed carrot
we got the green juice but we got the
celery kale juice right there that i
made too
and of course
don't forget about the hummus right here
so we have the hummus the fat-free
hummus right there which is incredible
now we're making roasted almond butter
let's have some fun let's do this
all right
so when it comes down to the roasted
almond butter
someone left a comment
by the way tomorrow's the last day for
the sale right here someone left a
common nice
a nice person
left a comment
and said
well wait a minute now
all that all the oil you see in the nut
butter you know like
you know the oil that's mixed up and and
floating at the top of a nut butter in a
jar all that oil you see isn't added oil
it's because the nuts were heated or
roasted so i got some roasted nuts right
here
so i'm kind of curious
is these roasted nuts gonna create like
four ounces like two ounces
right is it going to create like two
ounces of
of oil
that float on the top and make it so
it's like that so we're going to take a
look we're going to do some
that's really cool
split screen was really cool all right
let's go let's make them almond butter
now when you buy an almond butter
you have to know
they add oil
so if they say their almonds comes from
the the finest family farms
the finest family farms in india or the
finest family farms forever
in the u.s finally the finest family
farms in
in europe whatever they say the oil they
add to it is from a different place it's
not from those nuts so it's like you get
this cheaper bulk grade oil that they
add into
that they add into it so okay so that's
important to know
david scott nobody on the planet works
as hard as you for our health you're the
best
thanks david i'm honored
and i'm honored to do it okay
all right so i'm making some roasted
almond butter
do you guys like salted almond butter or
do you guys like no salt
just just curious
i know a lot of people look they'll grab
the jars and they'll pick the salted
roasted peanut butter salted roasted
almond butter
salted roasted right
so yeah so let's take a look so what i'm
going to do is i'm going to drop in
these almonds
right
so what i'm doing is i'm making almond
butter right now roasted almond butter
i'm gonna add a little salt in here too
because i'm making the salted roasted
almond butter right now
[Applause]
right
so let me show you how incredible this
is right here all right
so i want to show you this
so check this out okay i want to try to
level this out
okay
how incredible is this machine
all right i'm just going to shut it down
for a second
and kind of break it off here all right
so what you're looking at all right
you're looking at
almond butter being made right there
look how incredible that is look how
amazing that is right there
how incredible is that
look at that
so i'm gonna put it back in here that's
how
awesome this is right this is pure
this isn't with all that rancid oil they
add into it so all that rancid oil that
they add in
so we're making our own almond butter
how insane is that so let me drop that
back in
so i'm going to put a few more down in
here
i'm going to add a little bit more salt
because people like their salted ones
right
there he goes look at that
[Applause]
is that insane or is that insane oh
oh out of control
what's going on here i'm gonna have a
little salt here too
gotta multitask
oh
there you go
the almond butter i'm gonna drop it in
the container
so this is roasted almond butter i'm
making
and
you're not
you're not getting like
just annihilated by all that rancid oil
they put in
just think about that
i'd like to know where
there you go
get the rest of it in there
okay
all right so check this out you guys
so what you're looking at right here
okay you're looking at almond butter
roasted almond butter okay there it is
i'm gonna put it in the jar now
but what's missing here that that's not
missing on the store in the store when
you go to the store so you walk into any
of your health food stores and you buy a
jar of
peanut butter almond butter roast it raw
you'll see oil in there whether it's
mixed in there the reason why they do
that is they give you
less less
less
nuts and they give you more rancid oil
so they add all this oil they give you
less nuts and they add all this oil
that's how it's done
so i'm just letting you know
that's how it's done so when you're
making your own you don't have to go
through that
so let's let's put this in here
now you can press it down in here is
what you do okay you press it down in
here
so that's what i'm doing i'm pressing it
down with my hand
okay so i'm making
a little jar of roasted almond butter
right here putting it all together
right
so i'm just pressing it in
like this right
now here's the other thing you can do
with it which is incredible
so i'm just going to add a little bit
more now you can add honey
to your almond butter
right
you can add honey to it so i'm going to
get a butter knife out there's a couple
things you can do with this so
let's go
okay i'm gonna grab a cracker
got myself a cracker right here
take a look you guys
i'm gonna grab some almond butter
okay
spread it right on there
there you go
take a look at that
guys on tick tock
but the almond roasted almond butter i
spread it right on there look at that
how incredible is that
you can even do something else
you can add honey
okay
you can add honey to it so i'm gonna do
that now
so i'm gonna add some honey in this bowl
right here
put a little honey in there
yeah
right i'm gonna add a little bit of
almond butter
and i'm gonna mix it into the honey
okay so you can mix it into the honey
like this you can do honey and the
almond butter like that
right so you can make a honey and almond
butter
version
i'm gonna get a little spoon here too
for this
so that
so i'm mixing this really good right now
if you can see so that's with the honey
here in here
okay
right
and you can now spread that on a cracker
so let's do that
all right i got a cracker here
and i'm putting this nice honey version
on here too
and you can make that like that too so
you got these and you can do it honey
you can do without the honey right
that's incredible so let me cap this off
right here i want to put the rest of
this almond butter in this jar
there you go
now what you're not seeing here
this isn't a magic trick or anything
okay
take a look
see you guys
where's the two ounces of oil
where's the four ounces of oil where's
the oil
how come i can't drip all the oil out
because there's because the system is
rigged
in the nut butter world
it's rigged
they
cut corners they remove the nuts
they give you some nuts
and then they add all the oil that's
bulk and cheap
and they mix it
and then you get the jar
and it's half oil mixed in with whatever
nut butter that is in there the oils
from a different farm a different place
on the planet
and it's going rancid it's not even the
same nut
and that's what we do so it's like you
buy the beautiful jar of olive oil i
mean basically sorry you buy a beautiful
jar of nut oil is what you're buying
and not really getting nuts and the nut
oils coming from different places around
the world
much of it's rancid it's old it's bulk
and it's a cheap way they do it and you
can have the finest organic
nut butters out there but they're giving
us so much oil
and so yeah
nicholas says omega has outdone
themselves incredible so we have
an option this is about staying healthy
this is about looking out and staying
healthy you can make your own
right
incredible
truthman says hi this is anthony from
china awesome glad you're here
incredible
amazing so yeah
erica says shelf life good question
i mean you can keep a nut mud or nut
butter that you make homemade you can
keep it in the fridge for a long time
definitely i mean easy month easy longer
than that because it's so freshly done
easily longer than that
probably have it in there for a few
months and just just eat eat from it a
little bit at a time so we got that one
you guys i'll give you a rundown
everything we made so far if you just
got here
we've made a mess a little bit of mess
so you made
this incredible hummus chickpea garbanzo
bean hummus
from the mm-1500 it's 80 off right here
we got the hummus right here i'm gonna
actually grab some more
dude
dude where did you put in this
hey dude
summer
summer what did you put in this one
you mixed it up with the brownies
what do you mean
you put the brownies in here
oh man
mmm that's really good
hey guys
check out tiktok right i'm doing
exclusive videos on
i tiktok my tick tock page i love tick
tock
exclusive videos on tik tok that i'm
doing check them out today's was about
phrenic nerves so if you guys can
later on today go to my tik tok page and
check out the video the exclusive video
on phrenic nerves i talk about how the
phrenic nerves that run through her
chest causing all kinds of symptoms
neurological symptoms so if you can
check out that video
i'm also doing um
i'm also doing i just posted an
exclusive video on snapchat too
yesterday so i opened up a snapchat
account
and now i'm putting um videos on there
exclusive videos check out my newsletter
so you can get the exclusive videos
excuse the videos
shows the videos those are the videos
close the videos
robot roll back exclusive videos good
deliver deliver deliver videos deliver
videos
all right today's was about root canals
i was just told to chill out
telegram
audio exclusive audios too
all right so let's just cover what we
did
we got the hummus
we got the almond milk from this machine
we got the roasted
homemade roasted almond butter we got
cherry banana ice cream
we got the puree the carrot puree hummus
was fat free no tahini added michelle l
no tahini at it michelle good to see you
no tahini
we got the
celery kale juice
but the celery kale juice right
with the with the dry pulp
too squeezing the heck out of it there's
no liquid on the bottom of this dripping
out
it saves you money
mm fifteen hundred eighty dollars off
you get the free cleans the heel book
which is insane
luna knight says the robot is the best
if the robot gets too out of control
everything's going to start i'm going to
knock everything off of here so i got to
be really careful i got to do the
the com robot is what i was doing you
guys i'm heading off to ig
and i'm turning tick tock back on you
guys so i'm putting tick tock back on
i'm putting telegram back on and then
i'm turning instagram on and we're gonna
do this again
and maybe
the real stoner will come out right the
the crazy stoner will come out no
this great stoner is not going to come
out
the robot's going to come out all right
i love you guys
i will see you soon