freaking ground breaking I can't believe
I have it in my hand finally
for skin and the immune system right
there
the buffered micro C powder
that's it right there and what's
incredible
free lemon balm it's insane a free large
lemon balm almost four ounce bottle of
lemon the best stuff actually out there
in the market
when you get the micro C powder
unbelievable right here the immune
powder so I just want to say that right
off the running so I'm going to make all
kinds of stuff right here with this I'm
going to show you how to use it it's
going to blow your mind when I hear
vitamin C out there I shrug
shrug
you know why because I think about how a
vitamin C is going to rip apart
somebody's stomach
blow out their stomach acids
rip apart their intestinal tract yeah
rip into it ascorbic acid and all that
stuff this is not that this is buffered
this is the micro C so gentle
the micro C immune powder so gentle with
everything coming around here the flus
the colds you name it this is what I've
been waiting for right here this is sick
what's in my hand it's mind-blowing I'm
just gonna take a link is in the
description I want to tell you right now
because you need to know about this and
you get a free lemon balm with it so
critical to know
which is incredible the link is in the
description right there they already put
the lemon balm in the cart for you how
incredible is that they already put the
lemon balm in the cart for you you can
get the right there
the full size one the link is in the
description for the full size one the
link is in the description also for the
trial one there's there's a trial one
right there amazing you could also go to
vimergy.com V is in Victor i m is in
Mary e r g y.com and you can see all the
instructions to how to get it with with
the lemon balm free I don't know what
more they can do here's what's
incredible about this
collagen it's not collagen it's collagen
Builder
that's the difference too so not only is
it the micro C this is why it's so
mind-blowing not only is it the micro C
November see I'm like I can't believe it
I can't even believe it but it even is
for the skin the nails the collagen
building properties it's got the organic
bamboo silica in it this is
revolutionary this is groundbreaking I'm
telling you right now this is when
Denver G takes something and they just
they just take it to a level no company
can touch they take it to a level no
company has ever done
and that's what they do that right there
is incredible and then what do they do
they reward you
and that blew my mind they reward you
with a free lemon balm along with it you
guys know I work with these guys because
of these kinds of things because it's
the buffered
buffered vitamin C easy on the stomach I
can't wait to show you how to use this
I'm gonna make a green smoothie and I'm
gonna put this in the green smoothie I'm
also gonna make a whole bunch of other
little things which are going to be
mind-blowing I even have avocados with
me right now because I'm going to show
you a trick with avocado
and garlic like I got some stuff in
store for you guys even have avocado
with me today okay not just that I got
spinach I got oranges with me what you
see right there is mango
that is steamed potatoes there's a
reason for that
and I've seen a bunch of you guys have
already found this and you're freaking
out I think a bunch of you guys are
already using this I saw that the micro
C powder
the immune powder and you guys are
freaking out because you know how good
it is and with everything happening
right now with the pathogens the colds
the flus this is what is needed and that
right there feels good to know that the
battle is on baby the battle is on
against the pathogen the microscopic
world
that's what I love the microscopic world
you think you can rule the roost nice
try the battle is on that's right
microscopic world
okay colds Foos bugs microscopic world
you think you're gonna rule the roost
you think you're gonna rule everybody
you think take everybody down
yeah well that's what I love it battle
is on that's right battle ready anyway
you guys I'm gonna make a bunch of
different things I'm just letting you
know how incredible this is
this is the micro C pack Julie says how
is this different than micro C capsules
it's enhanced the micro C capsules are
amazing but here's the difference you
don't have to open the capsules anymore
so many people who open the capsules
because you're doing the vitamin C shock
therapy you're doing the medical medium
vitamin C shot therapy and you're
opening up the capsules right and so
many of you are opening up the capsules
for the kids
that's how this is different all on its
own and then that's not the only reason
why this is different but that's how
it's different everybody's opening up
the capsules you see I think half the
people out there easily open up the
capsules because they're mixing it and
things they're making the vitamin C
shock therapy they're they're opening up
the capsules for the kids all of that
well you don't have to open up the
capsules anymore the other thing is
organic
bamboo silica
when you have organic bamboo silica in
the mix of this already potent collagen
also building properties that are in
here with the immune enhancing because
immune system in the skin
immune system is in the skin
and so when you feed your immune system
and it's in the skin and then you've got
the organic bamboo silica it's the other
different
different powerful thing about this
anyway you guys link is in the
description they just want you I have to
let you guys know because I am so beyond
a study I'm telling all my friends all
my family everybody I know that this is
here go to the links
um on the medical medium Instagram
profile go to the links here you'll see
two links one for the trial one if you
want one for the
the bigger size and you get the free
lemon balm with it I can't even believe
I'm saying this like I'm like what like
I'm actually saying this right now like
this happened like we have this kind of
powerful nutrient dense product right
here in my hand this immune Vitamin C
powder and that's buffered and easy on
the stomach easy on the system that's
groundbreaking and that's revolutionary
right there
and then you get the free lemon balm
with it
I mean when you think about that it's
just unbelievable wondering wondering
wishing says I have opened so many
capsules for kiddos in me and hubby I
know isn't that great isn't it crazy
what this is and then you get the free
lemon balm with it I have to tell
everybody as you're coming on because I
can't believe myself I have a whole like
I have a whole presentation here that I
want to show you I got a whole bunch of
different foods here I want to show you
I'm going to make a few different things
but I had to talk about this is such an
exciting time for the medical medium
Community there's nobody doing this
there's nobody out there doing this you
guys need to know this if someone's like
oh he's got vitamin C no one out there
is doing this this is important to know
no company no supplement company nobody
out there is doing what these guys are
doing and that matters when you're
trying to move the needle and you're
trying to move forward
why am I passionate about this because
when you're sick and you feel like crap
and you're down
it's the worst it feels like the worst
and it really really stinks and when
there are tools
that are obtainable they're tangible
it's just it's a whole nother level this
is groundbreaking Tate Holloman says I'm
getting the capsules too I want both on
hand so you're getting the capsules to
the micro C I take the capsules the
micro C capsules every single day and
then
and then I got this
and I'm like oh my God lupus free with
celery33 no more losing product when you
open the capsules I started ordering it
this morning I want you to guide I want
you guys to know something right here
we're going to cover I wanna
I got so many things to talk to you
about
in regards to the immune system in
regards to the the micro C powder
regards to your immune system how to
connect with your immune cells how to
connect with your white blood count
so it gobbles up gobbles up the
pathogens how to connect with your
immune system so it gobbles up pathogens
so you fuel it with
the immune powder
it's just insane I'm excited I got a lot
there's a lot to cover a lot to do so I
want to get right into it but I just
want to give you guys the introduction
right here to know like what this is
that you know how people are like trying
to get College they're trying to eat
collagen out there everybody's been
tricked with that collagen game for
years you guys know that right by now
the eating collagen itself
never worked for anybody did you know
how many people got totally taken
throughout the decade of like the last
10 15 years but eating collagen products
like collagen does collagen doesn't
build collagen
that's like eating an eyeball to fix
your eyeball that's like eating if you
have a problem with your tongue that's
like eating a tongue to fix your tongue
it doesn't work you can't eat collagen
and that's a medical if you heard that
before from say somebody out there that
was mm mm put that stuff out there it
was mm info about you can't just eat in
a sheep's eyeball to fix your eyeball
you can't eat a cow's tongue to fix your
tongue if you have a tug you can't eat a
tooth to fix your tooth
you can't eat collagen to fix your
collagen you can't eat a bear's tooth to
fix your tooth your teeth
you can't eat eyelashes to fix your
eyelashes you can't eat a nose to fix
your nose you can't eat a liver to fix
your liver I'm sorry but you can't eat a
liver to fix your liver I don't want to
get everybody upset but you can't
you can't you only bog your liver down
more you can't eat your pain a pancreas
to cure your pancreas you can't do that
it doesn't work
I'm just saying you know you can't eat
an ear
to fix your ear
it doesn't work so what happened was
people throughout the years have been
tricked by eating collagen to fix the
collagen on your skin to fix the
collagen on your skin to fix your
elasticity of your skin you can't eat
collagen to do that you need collagen
Builders you need building blocks you
need things that actually help to build
the skin you guys know this
right
ground freaking breaking
right there
you're looking at it right there
collagen building nutrients and immune
power
which is the micro C powder I I don't
you know what before coming on here I
was just like
your freaking wait I can't freaking wait
to tell everybody this
like do you know what this means
if you know what this means and the
thing is like I said a shrug I shrug
when I hear vitamin C out there because
I know it's going to burn people's
stomachs
ascorbic acid all the vitamin C packets
you see at the health food store I'm
like oh my God that's just gonna burn
everybody's stomach and guts up it's not
even the potent stuff it's but it's
gonna burn their stomachs up with all
that acid
this is
the Imaging buffered two kinds of
vitamin buffered vitamin C two kinds you
guys
talking about a chance to heal two kinds
of buffered vitamin C to get to your
immune system
vitamin C to stop oxidative stress
breaks down and oxidizes our brains our
minds oxidizes our bodies oxidizes Our
organs right you got two pipes a
buffered vitamin C in this
immune powder two types
it's like your immune cells are like
wait a minute you're giving me one type
wait a minute you're giving me two type
what are you talking about
That's The Power of this
it's incredible so it's your immune
system just gonna be like you're giving
me two varieties to choose from your
immune system has Intelligence you guys
and it and that intelligence is used so
your immune system has these Intel this
intelligence and it's like you're giving
me two choices to choose from
that's important lymphocytes
lymphocytes have two varieties of
vitamin C to choose from
that's accessible assimilatable buffered
think about how sick that is how insane
that is right your white blood count has
two
two vitamin C's to choose from your
neutrophils basil all of it
lymphocytes monocytes all your immune
composition your immune cells all have
two varieties of buffered vitamin C pH
PhD up this is insane this is
revolutionary this is groundbreaking and
these are the things that make the
difference these are the things that
move the needle it's kind of like the
celery juice look what the celery juice
has done in the world
how many millions of people are drinking
celery juice every day it's all you hear
out there I'm drinking my celery ship
because my celery juice is helping me go
to the bathroom for the first time in
weeks my seller juice is helping me do
this my celery juice is helping me do
that it's helping my child it's helping
my grandfather it's moves the needle we
need groundbreaking things
that are tangible in our hands and this
is one of those right here this is the
micro C
immune powder and you get a free lemon
bump I don't know what else
they can do I don't even know because
that's insane right there all right you
guys I want to make some things I want
to do some stuff this is a big deal this
is an exciting moment right here I have
avocados something I know on IG you
can't see probably everything I got a
whole I got a whole presentation here
I'm going to show you some little immune
system trick with the avocado I'm going
to show you a little immune system trick
with a steamed potato I'm going to show
you a little immune system trick with a
banana I'm gonna show you an immune
system trick with the green smoothie I'm
gonna make
and I got mango right here in a bowl and
I'm gonna make the
medical medium vitamin C shock therapy
and I have this right here you know we
need
we need powerful tools what I call
weapons against
the microbe world
we need that and I'm also going to give
you guys a small presentation of course
of
how to get connected to your immune
cells how to make them work for you even
harder how to get connected how to
Envision things that you need to
Envision that are very important and
very critical
all of this
boom bam
bao
okay
all right let's get ready let's start
the vitamin C shock therapy let's start
with that to begin with I got right here
a glass in front of me and I'm hoping
also we can do a little camera work
today you never know
all right
so I got some honey with me I have some
water over here so I'm gonna make the
vitamin C shock therapy that's first but
here's the difference I'm gonna make it
right here with this
I'm gonna make it with Oop There we go
and make it with this wrapper oh you can
see that right up there
I'm excited there it is
all right let's start working on this
right now first and foremost
I'm gonna get some orange a half
squeezed orange in here but I'm gonna
get some warm water
right off the kettle
[Music]
nice
let's get an orange cut
okay
I'm gonna squeeze an orange in here
amazing
got just keep on here we're covering a
whole bunch of different immune power
tools
we get that in there like that I'm gonna
drop some honey in there too so this is
Vitamin C shock therapy if you guys know
this so many of you guys have used this
this is really powerful
[Music]
okay
and here we go
like I said when I see out there vitamin
C's
I shrill I shrug and there's a reason I
think about the stomach aches the kids
are gonna have I think about the belly
aches the adults are gonna have I think
about the acid poops people are gonna
have the acid poops
the acid runs the squirts
because you can't take enough of the
other vitamin C's out there without
crapping your pants you can't take
enough of the other vitamin C's out
there without having the runs or
diarrhea you can't take enough of the
vitamin C's out there without burning
your stomach and that's the difference
right there so I know if you're here out
there oh vitamin C is good for you
vitamin C try this one and know what
what people don't realize it just burns
it burns it burns an ascorbic sharp that
acid and then if you take too much of
those vitamin C's out there you know
what happens you're doing the squirts in
the bathroom your stomach's all upset
you can't take enough of it to actually
work in your favor to help yourself all
of these things they get in the way and
it matters when you're somebody that's
trying to heal and trying to move
forward and get your life to where you
need to get it it all matters this
squirts exactly so okay let's get now
let's get this in here
putting a serving of the micro C powder
I just got it right in there
now I'm going to mix it
okay
can't even tell you what this means for
the chronically ill what this means for
people who are sick what this means for
people who struggle with a lot of
different things this is really good
this is the vitamin C shock therapy
there it is right in the camera we have
it up you guys see me you see me and the
camera too you see me in this
newfangle technology today let's do it
there it is Vitamin C shock therapy
At Your Service with two kinds of
buffered vitamin C this is the immune
powder and the bamboo the organic bamboo
silica for skin for collagen
instead of the old trickery or what you
call decree
whatever bleepery
the amount of Livery out there with
collagen products out there you can't
eat collagen to fix collagen can't eat
somebody's ear to fix your ear
it doesn't work
it's important to know really important
to know it's 101 it's 101.
Straight Up 101 but anyway that's the
vitamin C micro C
shock therapy sitting right there in
front of you and it's the buffered
powder with two kinds of vitamin C so
what I what I do right here
and this is important okay
when I'm taking this
um
oh why is it so good too
all right and by the way if you guys
just came on here watch us from the
beginning you'll see what happens here
with this you'll see about the lemon
balm that's free with it link is in the
description it's already loaded in your
cart
[Music]
okay and so and this is incredible for
people who are on a budget that's the
other thing too
you know higher quality that works helps
people when they're on a budget because
success is critical with what you're
trying to do so that's important all on
its own okay the other thing is the
powder
you can work with it differently if you
need to and then you get the free Lemon
Ball talking about a steal all right
so I'm letting this kick in right now
this is the
vitamin C shock therapy hmm
instantly when I'm taking that sip I
want to tell you guys I want you guys
you can do this with me too if you'd
like
what's happening is it's entering my
body the first thing I'm saying is
immune cells are you there
okay lymphocytes are you there
white blood count are you there
and I'm connecting with it my immune
system because what's entering my body
is revolutionary it is groundbreaking
this is an incredible vitamin C and
vitamin C
halts that oxidative stress so all the
stress and oxidation that's happening
inside my body from all the stress I'm
under all the different stuff that we
have to deal with the environmental
pollutions coming out of the sky
everything else
right now I'm just seeing this vitamin C
run through my body and start to break
actually start to break that cycle of
oxidative stress the next thing it is I
want my immune system to receive
and see it and recognize it and start to
eat it and Gobble it up so this is
important I'm going to have a little bit
more
in the micro C shock therapy
if you guys just came on here
we're talking about this right now
all right
so what I'm envisioning is my white
blood cells
they want to destroy microbes that are
not supposed to be in me that's what our
white blood cells love to do they seek
them out they look for them
but if they're under fed under fueled
they don't work as good
if the white blood cell is under fed
malnourished not fueled to its capacity
it doesn't do the job it needs to do so
this is important to know
so I'm envisioning that white blood cell
right there
all of a sudden running into
that vitamin C that's going coursing
through my bloodstream right now
and what it does is our immune system
loves to gobble up vitamin C it loves to
use it
getting fueled is critical so I like to
Envision my immune cells taking in that
vitamin C
so good so delicious
and as it's taking in that vitamin C
it's strengthening and I see and
envision my immune system strengthening
coming empowered
getting strong
because you want your immune cells
strong you want this immune powder
to get infused into your immune cells
this is a critical exercise right here
an important one
it has its gobbling up and gobbling up
and absorbing
that immune powder that's mainlined in
your system
okay it's getting stronger and you
envision that you see it
okay and then you give your immune
system Direction
I want you to go after things that are
not supposed to be in me I want you to
go after the microbes that are not
supposed to be in me I want you to go
after those little buggies that aren't
supposed to be in me
and you get your immune system to work
with you and work for you and that is
powerful all on its own
and that's what I like to do
so this is the
vitamin C shock therapy I'm enjoying it
right now I'm actually in a very good
space with it very good mood Oh indeed
this is actually tasty hmm
very good very good
cheers
hmm can't get enough of it actually okay
we're gonna move on with a couple more
things if you guys just came on here
that's the vitamin C immune powder right
there the micro C
we're gonna put this now in a smoothie
is next so what you see in front of me
is a blender you guys on IG you can see
this right
and in this blender I'm going to make a
green smoothie
I got some mango I'm gonna use that for
the green smoothie
I have some spinach I'm going to use
that for the green smoothie and I have
some celery sticks I'm going to use that
for the green smoothie
but I'm gonna change things around a
little bit
I'm gonna add
the micro C powder immune powder in this
green smoothie
that's what I'm gonna do
I was really excited about this because
I wanted to do this so bad now the green
smoothie recipe I'm using right here is
in cleanse the heel I don't know if you
guys have this I want to show you
that's the green smoothie recipe it's
three medium sized bananas I prefer
mango in this one right now I'm excited
about that
or three cups of diced mango so let's
get the three cups of diced mango in
here
so great
I love mango
so I prefer some mango in this green
smoothie right here
we're gonna do three cups we're gonna
get a decent amount of mango in here
now if you you know what happens is that
so many people break open the capsules
they open the capsules because they want
to take a lot of this incredible vitamin
C this micro C because it's buffered
it's easier it's easy on the body
easy on the stomach easy on the stomach
lining easy on the intestinal tract how
incredible was that all in its own all
right
so
the green smoothie recipe is not only
that it's now one to two stalks of
celery chopped
so I'm gonna chop a couple of stalks of
celery I'm gonna get that into this
green smoothie just bear with me
so many things you hear out there
one to two stalks of celery
foreign
okay next thing is four cups of tightly
packed spinach so I'm gonna get a
measuring cup possibly here we are
four cups of tightly packed spinach now
what I like doing here
is putting that buffered
immune powder
in a green smoothie
yeah
there we go I want a tight tightly pack
this in right here
you know you hear out there all the time
vitamin C vitamin C and it's like
meanwhile it's like
yeah
vitamin C all right what kind
is it two kinds of buffered PhD out what
kind is it just ascorbic strain acid
burns a hole in your stomach or is it
the kind with the fatty lipids attached
to the ascorbic acid which has got awful
because it the that inhibits the vitamin
C you know getting to where it needs to
get okay so that's four cups tightly
packed spinach
let's get this in here
one cup of water
if you really want you can put some some
orange juice in there too if you really
want
all right spinach is going in
all right let me blend this you guys
really quick
here with me and add a cup of water
and before I blend it we're going to add
this I want to show you
here we go give you a close-up
there you go I just want to show you
this first and then I'll bring over the
blender
guys can take a look there we go that's
it right there
now I'm going to pop it in here
get a little close up there too
nice
all right let's give it a whirl
[Music]
I'm gonna bring it over here
foreign
there we go
green smoothie with the immune powder
the micro C immune powder right here
collagen building properties
I've been waiting so long for a really
powerful collagen building property
[Music]
here we go
nice
you take all nuts
when you take all that spinach
and you bring that spinach
with that vitamin C together so all
those trace minerals from the spinach
and you actually
take that vitamin C and you mix it in
there oh incredible
that's our green smoothie right there
wonderful with the immune building
powder right there
incredible there it is
I don't know if you guys can see that
but it's so perfect
that is the green smoothie with the
micro seed powder
so not only are you actually getting the
micro C powder collagen building effects
right there you're bringing it into the
green smoothie
how good is that and what you won't see
in this green smoothie is a whole bunch
of fat you don't see a whole bunch of
oil put into here or coconut oil because
that inhibits what you're trying to do
you especially if you're dealing with
something or trying to battle something
or you got a cold or you got something
you're under the weather
you want something as clean as this
green smoothie without all the junk in
it without all the garbage in it that
all is natural flavors and I want to get
to another point with that
what you won't see in here are the
anti-caking agents so understand that
not only is this
literally the best the best there is on
the market but what you won't see in
here and once you won't have to
experience and eat
is the anti-caking agents
they don't put that in here
that is groundbreaking all on its own
that's revolutionary people don't know
how good that really is and what that
means because what happens is all these
anti-kicking agents are in everybody's
powders and they don't know it because
you don't have to disclose it
there's a rule you don't have to
disclose a certain percentage of
ingredients in the supplements out there
in the world and companies will say how
good and quality and how great the great
it is but they'll never say
there's no anti-caking agent in our
product because they can't
vimergy can say that there's no
anti-kicking agents in this immune
powder in this collagen promoting immune
powder
that alone is mind-blowing not to
mention no alcohol not to mention no
natural flavors which is MSG
no vinegars no caffeine
it's a whole nother thing all on its own
that's
mind-blowing we got the green smoothie
made let's make some other things too
while we can while we're here
all right
let's move on to the next one raw garlic
therapy for colds have you guys been
doing any of the raw garlic therapies at
all for colds
anybody anybody's trying any of that are
you guys doing any of that
because I just want to go over that for
a little bit let's go let's hit it
okay
all right let's take the avocado out
nice avocado right here
right
gonna scoop the avocado out
I'm gonna scoop it in the bowl
there we go
you guys see that
so we're doing is garlic
an avocado
we're gonna mash the avocado up
I mean you could eat your avocado in
pieces if you want you can also mash it
I prefer to mash it I like it slightly
with like hunkier pieces I don't like it
where it's just like a cream cream
I don't like avocado puree but that's
just my opinion that's my taste that's
my choice you can make it any way you
want to make it so I'm mixing this up
there you go then you can use a garlic
mincer
if you like
I'm just gonna crush it chop it with the
knife
one garlic clove
you feel like you're coming down with a
flu you feel like you're coming down
with a cold you feel like you got the
scratchy throat you feel like you got
the sore throat coming on you're under
the weather anything like that
you can do this
so I'm chopping up some garlic
[Music]
I'm gonna chop it up a little finer
if you guys don't mind the bug season is
coming I hear it all the time people are
coughing they're sniffling are they
armed with the immune powder are they
armed with the vimorgy immune powder
all right we got some chopped minced
garlic right there
amazing
let's get that right into the avocado
nice
okay
[Music]
look at that
then you mix it in there
that is
amazing
there you go
all right and then you can eat it just
like this
you got the garlic in there
um
so good
so good one clove of garlic half an
avocado
raw garlic therapy for colds and flus
get ready for the next one
gonna eat that later
next one let's go come on now
steamed potato
you can do that three times a day you
can do this three times a day we're
doing the potato version right here get
ready
so I'm just gonna chop up the potato a
little bit
chop it up
a little potato version
there we go let's get it in the bowl
here we go
let's get this here
can you guys see that
all right
we got that one now we're gonna Mash
that one up we're gonna kind of mash
that potato up a little bit break that
one up too
there we go
this is a steamed potato I want I don't
want anybody confused thinking that this
is a raw potato that wouldn't be good
because I don't think you're going to be
able to really do this in fact you're
not going to be able to do this has to
be a steamed potato or a cooked potato
maybe you have a baked potato and that's
what you have
when you're doing that and that's fine
so we're mashing this potato up nicely
I feel so fueled
by that
vitamin C shock therapy with the micro C
it feels so good coursing through my
veins I love the feeling
tastes so good there you go so you got
some potato
all right
get another clove of garlic real quick
there you go there's the potato right
there
I'm gonna move the potato over and I'm
gonna get the garlic
garlic clove now you can do this three
times a day too
great immune system power
mashed garlic a little bit now I'm gonna
chop it up if you guys don't mind
there you go
all right
one more get that little piece out there
this little
garlic cover
there we go there we go
okay we're good SS but he says not to
have avocados in this morning not to eat
too many I've said that depending on
what's happening with your health
overall but
this is this is a different situation
this is when you feel like you're coming
down with something this is cold and flu
garlic therapy for colds and flu
you don't even have to start it in the
morning who says it has to be morning
that's the next thing too you can do
this three times a day and start this in
the afternoon do it later in the
afternoon and at night and this is an
option you don't have to use avocado
either that's the other point too this
option right here is potato there's no
avocado in this option so you have this
to do you don't have to say wow my only
way to do this is just avocado how am I
going to do that that's actually
actually you have all these different
options that's the potato one right
there
okay I'm gonna try it out if you guys
don't mind
hmm
garlic potato
three times a day you can do that now
remember if you want to do the avocado
version you don't want to avocado in the
morning exactly you don't want to have
the avocado with your celery juice then
you do it later on
how great is that
[Music]
[Applause]
all right
where are we going next third one
you might have guessed it already what
are we gonna do for this third one
let's get a nice big clove of garlic
if you're fat free you can stay focused
and keep it fat free if you're not fat
free anyway you can add the avocado in
people are doing different things
with the medical medium information not
everybody's doing the same thing with
the medical medium info
all right this next one I wanted a nice
big clove of garlic for this next one
but before that let's go into banana
here it is we got a banana
all right
there we go check it out you guys
bananas next
let's mash up the banana
yeah
and we got the banana version how great
is this this is the fat free version
just like the potato it was the overt
fat-free version think about it
here this is the banana version
look at that mashed banana all right I'm
gonna move this over
you guys don't mind let's get the clove
of garlic right there
boom that's a big clove
I wanted a big clove for this one
try to get the biggest clove as possible
I'm gonna smash it
right and then I'm gonna chop if you
guys don't mind we're gonna get this in
the banana
nice some good good chopping action we
got to get this done
[Applause]
okay
I had a friend a friend over and they
said is that on is that on videos that
in fast motion
said no that's not in fast motion that's
that's a chopping technique
all right getting the garlic in there
look at that
nice let's get a little bit more garlic
in there
there we go
let's mix that up let's mix that garlic
up with that banana
all right there we go so that's the
banana and garlic one right there three
times a day this is the fat free version
meaning overt fat free three times a day
I'm gonna have some now
[Music]
um
so good
wow
you can do that three times a day this
is the raw garlic therapy for colds flus
and then got one more one more coming
our way
let's go let's grab a little a little
dish here it's gonna be a smaller dish
all right
let's do it get ready for this one move
this over
get ready for this one
all right can do a tablespoon of honey
okay
now you can keep it in the spoon I want
to put it in the in the little dish and
I want to mix the garlic in the little
dish
but you can keep it in the spoon if you
want to and but and you can put it back
you could actually spoon it out once we
do this
all right
what do we need to do we need to get
another
clove of garlic got it right here
all right
let's get it peeled
you can do this three times a day this
is the overt fat free version another
one okay smash that there we go get a
little chop
there you go
nice that goes in here
there you go take a look here you guys
can see that right up close
nice
putting that raw garlic right in that
honey
look at that
there we have it check that out I'm
gonna mix that up a little bit
Little Mix
you can do this three times a day think
about the antimicrobial properties the
hunting has think about the
anti-pathogenic power the garlic has
right think about all of that
how incredible then you can take a spoon
and Spoon it out just like this
there we go
so good
garlic and honey three times a day
you do it once a day if you need to
two times a day
if you want to do less garlic then do
less garlic if you want to use a smaller
clove of garlic use a smaller clove half
clove do half clove that's okay too cold
and flues
and bugs coming our way it's critical to
have tools these are important tools
right here so you can do the potato
version that's the honey version right
there
okay that's the banana version right
here
that's the potato version right here
make some room come on
that's the avocado version right there
the overt fat version just fine that's
what you want to do look at those you
guys let's try to get them all in the
picture here
whoa nice there it is you're dealing
with raw garlic therapy for colds and
flus powerful simple tool you can use
every day scratchy throat you don't feel
good starting to get a cough
starting to feel under the weather
starting to feel kind of like whoa am I
getting sick if something's going on
here you've got raw garlic therapy for
colds and flus and little bugs and
things and sore throats you don't feel
good you're under the weather you think
you got a little fever going whatever it
is
you have this option it's simple it's
easy you do it three times a day if
you're somebody and you're doing fat
free all morning like like would be
great to do medical medium information
right you stay fat free all morning and
you want to do the avocado version at
the end of the day or later on do it
three times later on do it in the
afternoon then late afternoon early
evening and then at night
the other ones you can start at any time
of the day that you wish or choose we
also cover the green smoothie
a green smoothie with the micro C I want
everybody to know this is groundbreaking
what I have in my hands right here
immune powder two varieties of vitamin C
that our immune system will gobble up
like crazy
keep that in mind right collagen
building properties you get a free lemon
balm with it
I can't believe I'm saying that
like why
why is it really getting a free lemon
balm thank God they are but I can't even
believe I'm saying it though like I
don't see that out there that's how
incredible this is it really is and
you're looking at a vitamin C the micro
C powder that won't
make all those things that I talk about
happen with the vitamin C packets out
there the vitamin C and the fat lipids
out there you take too much you're on
the toilet and you got the runs and the
Squirts and your stomach's burning you
can't give your kids too much they get
the belly aches they get the acid
stomach they don't feel good but yet we
need the amount of vitamin C that we
want to take without having that kind of
stuff happen
and this is the Emoji micro C immune
building powder the immune powder I mean
I don't even know what to say of how
incredible this is and what's going on
here
so this is loaded with two gentle forms
of natural I cut all this garlic I just
see what all this garlic now I'm gonna
take all those later later like I'll do
one here I'll do another one here it's
so good but anyway this is loaded with
two gentle forms of natural vitamin C
powder which is incredible buffered it's
number one right there organic bamboo
silica for collagen I don't even know
what to say Karen says can we use this
micro C powder
during mono I would I would if it was me
if I had Mono I would but ask your
doctor what's right for you
ask your doctor what's right for you of
course you know
yep and um but yeah but I would if I was
sick I would if I had Mono yeah I would
if I had a cold I would
I'm gonna do it anyway I don't have mono
I don't have a cold I'm gonna do it
anyway
geisie says can you do that with roasted
garlic you can you can the raw garlic
stronger
raw garlic is stronger but if for some
reason it's too strong for you it's
really intense and do a little bit of
raw garlic do a little piece of the
clove if you want let me get a little
clip like one here and I'll show you
I wanted to show you real quick
so I'm taking a small piece of a clove
right there if you can see all right I
opened it up right there can you see
that you guys
see that right there
okay if that's all you can do because
it's raw garlic and raw garlic is so
pungent it's so strong it's it can bite
it's very bitey sometimes if that's all
you got to do then use a little bit in
that garlic therapy for cold slews and
so forth that I just showed you but if
you can't do that because raw Garlic's a
little too hard on you do the roasted
garlic do it the same way I showed you
apply it the same way
with roasted garlic I would probably
recommend doing a little bit more than
one clove if it's roasted garlic this
way you get a little bit more of the
garlic because it was roasted it's going
to lose some of its properties and some
of its value so you want you can
actually do more than one and that's
fine
show you guys I'm just saying check out
vimorgy check them out vimergy.com
Linkus is also link is in the profile
right there so the link is in the
profile in the description
you'll see you see the big size you see
the trial size you get the free lemon
balm with it
but honestly no anti-caking agents no
MSG no natural flavor crap no alcohol no
caffeine none of the junk never mind you
know when you see products go no soy no
whatever it's like yeah but you got you
got anti-caking agents in there buddy
and you got natural flavors in there
buddy and you've got citric acid in
there buddy which is really bad and you
got you got forms of alcohol that you're
not even disclosing you got all that in
there but you ain't telling the
customers or the consumers because
you're allowed to do that
vermergy isn't that
and that's the difference and that's why
I support them I could support
any company I want
companies knock on my door day in and
day out
over the years thousands of companies
get aw on board but I won't support
anybody I won't support any company
unless they go so above board and so
Advanced and so ahead of the Curve
and they do it in a way that's good for
the customer in every way possible
and only thinking in their behalf on
their behalf and that's what I'm talking
about you guys know I work with these
guys because of that I want this company
to stick around for The Chronic Leo and
people don't realize it
there's always going to be a company out
there saying they got this and this and
they got fancy this and that
but they ain't in it for the chronically
ill and I know that I know because I
know the people behind the companies out
there I know what's going on behind the
scenes I talk to a lot of people and I
know a lot of people and I know the bull
crap that's out there okay on IG
so very pleased vimergi are doing
Vitamin C powder this is my most useful
supplement my most used supplement it's
available in the UK right now too whoa
available in the UK right now too guys
that is freaking amazing that's all I
can say I mean look
it's like
people need the right stuff
because we can't waste time and we can't
waste energy
we can't waste I mean we're only here so
long on the planet even if you live be
200 years old you're here for 200 years
but either way we don't want to waste
time life is precious I want the right
stuff for the people that need it
Shamrock says I knew I love the new
micro C powder because it makes the
vitamin C shock therapy so easy but now
I cannot wait to see how good my skin is
going to look I can't wait to see how
good my skin is going to look too
because I'm excited about my skin I'm
pumped up about that
but you guys know I'm 28 years old right
um
you guys know I'm 28 I'm 32 years old
and my skin needs a little help I am
psyched about this it's got the organic
bamboo silica in here along with two
kinds of vitamin C buffered there to
help us
match your service you guys in any way
possible
shape or form citric acid's terrible
terrible citric acid Kate says citric
acid is made from old citric acid not
from oranges citric acid the kind they
use in the supplement industry that's
put in foods and supplements garbage I'm
the one that blew the top off that
citric acid thing it was medical medium
and spreading the word you would be
surprised who is hiding behind the
scenes leaving all the negative comments
they hide behind fake profiles and act
like real medical medium people but they
are not I just had to say that I had to
say it
had to say it you would be surprised on
who's hiding behind those fake comments
and there's a lot of that going on today
there's a lot of that going on
in that love the techniques they're
using
I love the Shady crap they're doing it
just shows how sick they really are you
guys
look and I don't mean chronically ill I
mean you know sick demented and demented
way imposters too so look out and don't
just know I don't offer consultations
you'll see that all the time I'm Anthony
William man I got I I want to give you a
consultation just make this payment here
and uh here's my email and um yeah
you'll see a lot of that too
but either way you guys
um what you see in front of me is
groundbreaking revolutionary
right there
if you get a chance check it out arm
yourself with it okay because the bugs
are coming they're on their way I see
people sniffling coffin all that stuff
sick fevers in bed for days and days
that's what's happening out there and
we're at the beginning of that whole
storm
of a crap ton of RSV
rsvc
RSV cold blue boom boom all of it
stomach flu this flu that flew all of it
it's on its way
I just thought I'd tell everybody
because it is it's already here
Lisa says Anthony your skin looks
amazing right now thank you I'm honored
I do appreciate that
thank you but I would love to see how my
Skin's gonna look
as I'm using this along the way I'm
gonna use this every single day anyway
I'm excited I wanted to tell you guys
about this and the free lemon balm you
get with it which is sick
like what like what when I heard that I
was like what are you talking about like
don't don't talk stupid what do you mean
what do you mean a free lemon balm with
this
like why what yeah of course I want
people to get a free lemon balm that's
my dream come true but what
yeah you guys
keep that
you know keep that in your back pocket
keep that feather in your cap you guys
know I care about you so check it out
you got the raw garlic therapy for colds
you've got of course right there the
vitamin C shock therapy medical medium
I'm using the micro C immune powder in
it with the collagen building plus you
can't eat an eyelash to grow in eyelash
you can't eat bite the tip of somebody's
nose off and swallow it thinking the tip
of your nose is going to change or
something's gonna get fixed with it or
heal you can't eat somebody's toe to fix
your toe you can't eat a cow's toe to
fix your toe you can't eat a cow's heart
to fix your heart it's not gonna happen
and you you can't it's not gonna work
it's 101 and it's 101 stupid out there
but they've been doing it to people and
tricking people for years I you know how
many billions of dollars of collagen has
been sold and used
when it can't fix your collagen
think about how demented that is all on
its own and don't get me started on
other crab too like the other farces out
there like call like um colostrum and
other crap don't even get me started on
this how horrible all that stuff is and
it doesn't work anyway
I trust
the micro C immune powder with the
organic bamboo silica that's what I love
right there
so yeah
Chelsea Field yo yo real Chelsea Field
say hi to Scott Bakula for me say hi to
the family I just saw you on there in IG
I saw you laughing are you laughing at
the college and thinking you're loving
that door you can't eat somebody's tooth
thinking it's gonna fix your tooth I got
a whole bowl of teeth right here I'm
gonna eat and Munch down I got a whole
bowl of broken teeth that I got I got a
whole bunch of animal teeth and I'm
gonna ground down and eat to fix my
teeth this will fix my teeth a whole
bunch of animal teeth that'll really fix
it right
yeah
okay you're right anyway you guys this
has been incredible
try some of these things
you know
the immediate you
the immune powder is in here I love you
guys
so good