right here we're live so um
new episode coming out tomorrow morning
really exciting so just letting
everybody know
new episode tomorrow morning it's about
the air we breathe
it's something you really should listen
to for sure so have you heard the other
three episodes the chemtrail episode
the fruit fear episode and then the
brain meditation
so i'll answer any questions regarding
those on the chemtrails the
fruit fear and brain meditation the
brain meditation is
really really healing people right now i
hope you guys experience that or have
experienced that
um you know did you do the brain
meditation did you do it twice
did you do it three times some people
are doing it more you can do it every
night
every day it's life changing
the difference between a meditation
that's not man-made
means it really works now i know that
sounds kind of confusing like what does
that mean it means that
when meditations are man-made it's hit
or miss
when a meditation comes from above it
really works so i'm preparing you so
when you try the meditation the brain
meditation
i'm preparing you with the power it has
and how it really works so just keep
that in mind because
there could be some tears there could
there's going to be an emotional release
a powerful emotional release so
what happens is when we have um losses
in our life and betrayals and broken
trust and we get hurt
we have fear we have shame we have guilt
we've been judged we've been
misunderstood
and we've when we lose friendships
when betrayal happens people cheat on us
or we get
hurt or harmed in any way emotionally
mentally
all of that those wounds stay there
because fear
kind of fills in the gap so in the brain
meditation
it's it's a way to rid fear in a really
powerful powerful way
i'm wondering wondering if you
experienced it yet um celia says
how do i get a link to this brain
meditation so the link is in the
description so the description look for
that okay
uh the description on facebook
description on youtube
so make sure you look for that link and
so you could get there so
it's medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast so that's the official platform
it's uncensored any other platform i
can't guarantee that
i'm censored everywhere else pretty much
so um
yeah so apple podcast is where you want
to listen to it it's why i launched it
on apple podcast so
the brain meditation is really powerful
you can use it to fall asleep
and it can still work on healing you it
still pulls fear out and you're going to
feel much lighter you're going to feel
like a weight's been lifted off of you
you're going to feel the change the
brain meditation
not only works but it's life-changing
look out for that danielle says
i always had trouble doing meditations
before but i love this one it's so good
well danielle what happens with this one
because it's above
it it's not going to be difficult
because when the meditation comes from
above
and it's not man-made then it's it's
it's made it's made for your soul it's
made for our souls to really do
so there's no struggle in it versus some
guy making up a meditation somewhere you
know what i mean
because that's what happened some guy in
the 1960s making up a meditation
and then it kind of like passing around
and someone else kind of adding
something to it another person adding a
twist to it
and then in the 1980s then you got
somebody else is doing a meditation and
adds a twist to it's all man-made it's
everybody throwing in you know their
their their their thoughts and ideas of
what a meditation could be or should be
well this isn't any of that so the
medical media meditations are from above
they're really really powerful and easy
to do they're supposed to be easy to do
a meditation is not supposed to be hard
to do
this is life changing so what's going to
happen when you do the brain meditation
it's gonna work and um and be prepared
the tears are gonna come out for a lot
of people a big emotional release for a
lot of people
cindy said good evening anthony thank
you for sharing your gifts i've listened
to chemtrails
and fruit fear going to listen to the
meditations tomorrow morning
well there's going to be a new episode
cindy tomorrow morning okay
two so yeah listen to the brain
meditation when you can get a chance
thank you for listening to chemtrails
thank you for listening
to fruitfear i'm so happy you did that's
so awesome
and share it with someone if you guys
could share share the episodes with
people please
do and the brain meditation share it
with everybody
so people can heal um now there's a new
episode tomorrow morning okay so it's
about those fragrances those chemical
fragrances and what they do to us
how they play a role in affecting our
body and our health it's critical to
know about that but it's really a
powerful show
i take it to a new level because it's
uncensored
um make sure you are subscribed so you
can be
notified about each episode that comes
out so you're the first to be notified
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast okay
subscribe that's the platform to
subscribe to then you know
meaning medical medium podcast and
listen to it on apple podcast
tomorrow more morning should be morning
could be a little later but the
episode's coming out tomorrow
letting you know um daisy says haven't
done it yet the brain meditation is that
what it is
you should try it when you get a chance
um
alejandra says yes i did it two nights
already cried both
times love it the crying happens because
it's really working
the the fear gets drawn out um heather
says love the brain meditation brought
me to tears of joy and
you can do this brain meditation see
this is this is a secret
brain meditation so what i mean by that
is
secret in the sense where i've never
shared it so i only shared it with
friends and family
for for years and years since i was
younger okay
and now i want you guys to have
all the meditations that i know from
above
and it's it's needed now it's just
needed
and i have meditations in the medical
meeting books
and they're powerful and i'm gonna even
do some of those
and and do those and and make them
guided so i can help you guys heal
because those are changing lives
but there's some i haven't put in the
medical medium book and
this is one of them the brain meditation
so this is one that i've been coveting
all these years one reason is it's so
powerful
and that that it's really intense
too for a lot of people but so worth it
to heal
jody says feeling better every day from
brain meditation i feel calmer and more
at peace
sleeping better after weeks of insomnia
what happens is when that fear builds up
so check this out you guys when we go
through life and we get bad news
it's like whoa what what just happened
you know
um what do you mean are friendships not
working out what do you need what do you
mean
um you cheated on me what do you mean
it's time for a divorce or what do you
mean for
you know some loss or some great great
uh disappointment in life
something that hurts us in a way
emotionally breaks our heart broken
trust or we get judged or
or we or there's an injustice and you
know that we feel or we're not
hurt and we're just feeling we're
feeling like you know we've been through
so much where we feel shame and guilt
and fear
what happens is that we have these
out-of-body experiences where our soul
leaves our body for a moment
because the shock is so great to the
emotional center of the brain where the
electrical impulses are going in the
emotional sense so when you get that
news like that bad news and
that news it's a shocker the you get a
charge
an electrical charge like a fire bolt
like a lightning bolt
firestorm a lightning storm in the
emotional center of your brain
and that shock throws the soul out of
your body for a moment so you get the
out-of-body experience
so it's like what what just happened
oh my god like you know and and when
those losses and
that hurt comes and we've been harmed or
we've had an injustice or a betrayal
broken trust anything that electrical
shock blows up in the emotional center
of the brain
and when it blows up in the emotional
center of the brain your soul gets
propelled
out you get this out-of-body experience
for a minute and when that happens
there's a distance between your soul and
your physical body
the brain meditation brings that
together
and as we go through life it keeps on
happening with more news or
more hardships or another struggle
emotional struggle
more fear and pain and maybe something
we don't even realize
that happened but it still sits with us
even if it was
kind of seemingly small and not
bothersome it was
it was hurtful in the moment so our soul
then
then takes on a distance from our
physical brain when that shock happens
in the emotional center of the brain
so in the emotional center of the brain
that shock occurs in there
then you get the out-of-body experience
and then fear fills the gap what the
brain meditation does
is it takes you on its guided journey
to mend the bridge that's been injured
the bridge in the neurons that's been
injured and to bring the soul back to
the body
and back to the brain and it's critical
back to the emotional side of the brain
so
the soul comes back all the way and the
fear gets removed in the center
so the power of that is just unlike any
it's unlike any other so um you could
use it to use it as a sleep meditation
you can use it every night before bed
share it with everybody you can so the
the description the link is in the
description if you're if you're
wondering where it is
and the official platform for the brain
meditation which is medical medium
podcast at
apple podcast really important important
to know it's the uncensored version
if you listen to the meditation at
another platform
maybe a platform that the old radio
shows the medical media radio shows run
or something
it's going to be censored it's i can't
trust anything at this point right now
i'm getting no guarantees so
so apple podcast the best place to
listen to it if you have an android and
you don't have an apple device
go to medicalmedium.com so
medicalmedium.com
okay and other people know that are
commenting and here that know
where to go so medicalmedium.com and
in the menu you see podcast and you you
click on there you find it and you can
you can listen if you have an android or
something so it's important
um yeah and
um hey dude said loving the meditation
doing it every night
usually fall asleep thank you anthony
soc love you
it it's an important time to do it also
is at night and that healing occurs when
you're about to go to sleep and you do
it at night
you'll get a better sleep and you'll
work on getting more
fear out you can do it then listen to it
do a meditation in the morning too first
thing in the morning
you wake up if you wake up early in the
morning and you're somebody who does
that do it first thing in the morning
um get it done as an exercise excuse me
get it done
as an exercise every single morning
kathy says it works
um it really is powerful um
kathy tell anybody you can about it
share it please
share it so they can experience the
brain meditation you guys got to know
something okay
there's no infomercials in these
podcasts
in these episodes there's no
advertisements i
i can't say it enough what that means
there's no sponsorships
and i could do all that and i don't
this is a pure source and
share it please help me and share it so
people can heal
it's not helping me by making me money
or anything because it's not there's no
advertisements no sponsorships
no infomercials so it's not doing
anything for me on that level
but i'll tell you how it is helping me
it's helping me because i'm here
so people heal i've been here with doing
this
my whole life so people can heal and
share it
so they can get a chance to heal it's so
important
um leave a review on apple podcast
that's really helpful for me
so please re leave a review really
really helpful
if you can
amy bachelor says i love the meditation
i felt like i came home to myself
hi amy um that's incredible that really
is
that really is i'm so proud of you for
doing it so happy you did it
um helena says i've already done the
brain meditation
five times with a laughing face
um it gets what happens is when you do
it every time
um your experience will change as you go
along the way because
it's going to get more and more hurt out
hurt that you didn't even know was there
hurt that was buried deep inside hurt
that was buried deep inside the soul
it's gonna get that out it's gonna get
that out
um kathy king says love the podcast so
did you listen to the chemtrail episode
do you do you have you got a thick skin
right you can handle that one
it's amazing fruit fear because the
chemtrail
not it's not for the faint of heart the
chemtrail episode it's mind-blowing
just absolutely mind-blowing maura says
i lost my husband to a car accident
years ago
oh my god my baby was just nine weeks
old at the time
i felt so disconnected since then and if
people ask me about
it it's like i'm outside my body
exposing it to them
will the brain meditation help me yes it
will that's that's
what it's for that's why i released it
because
with devastating news where there's just
no word no words can describe what
you're going through
i can't even attempt it it's just to go
through that
it's unimaginable and um just know i'm
truly deeply sorry
and yes the brain meditation is there to
help
because that's the out-of-body
experience it just it it just
it pushes it literally that shock
puts puts your soul out of body it's a
survival method
for the moment that's how we work so
that we don't
stroke out during severe news
and to get the soul to come back and
bring the fear and broken trust
of life out the brain meditation is
there to help
um okay sandy says
hope you're off you offer more
meditations in the future i got a
surprise
you know coming so yes i'm going to be
offering more the brain
one is beautiful been doing it every
night sammy keep on doing it every night
because then i know that you're you're
working on your healing i know that
you're
you're healing every single night that's
why it's
there and please share it if you can
sharing it makes all the difference
especially since i'm censored
on all my platforms except for apple
podcast
so especially since i'm censored so in
everything in shadow band and everything
so
for sure sharing it really does help
change the world out there
alexandra hey alexandra is this brain
meditation we should do
daily for the rest of our lives it's
amazing yes i'm going into very deep
sleep right after what i do before bed
it it's the gift that keeps on giving
it's truly the gift that keeps on giving
so you can't go wrong you can do it
every day okay
i've been doing it i've been doing it
my whole life okay and i'm no spring
chicken
okay so i've been doing it my whole life
and i have family members
and friends doing it their whole life
since they've known me
and that's going all the way back 35
plus years okay
so spirit of compassion gave me this
powerful meditation
so yes you can do it your whole life
it will be powerful all the way through
cindy says i listen to your podcast in
the morning while getting ready for work
that's a great time to listen to him
chemtrail podcast is just
so powerful and moving and the messages
in the end from spirit of compassion
the messages the end of fruit fear so
powerful and moving great time in the
morning
um karen says where do i find the brain
meditation
okay so here's where you find it okay
it's the medical medium podcast
okay at apple podcast the link
is in the description at facebook and
the link is in the description here on
youtube
so the link is in the description really
important to know
hit the link if you don't have an apple
device that's okay
go to medicalmedium.medicalmedium.com
and you'll look in the menu for podcast
and just listen to it there
uh lauren henry lauren i enjoy the brain
meditation yay
thank you thank you means means the
world that you're doing it and
and you absolutely love it heather says
chemtrail episode is mind-blowing and
opening
um it answered a lot of questions i've
had for some time
thank you the chemtrail episode
is definitely a shocker i still have to
give everybody who hasn't heard it a
forewarning
that you will see the sky differently
after that episode
and you might not want to listen to that
episode you may not want to listen to
that
episode is it free
yes absolutely brenda
it's free but not only free it's free
listening
you don't hear infomercials
advertisements and sponsorships
and none of that's there okay so
which is foreign totally unheard of
right now at this point
with the podcast this you know with with
being a new york times
selling author and all that other stuff
i mean
there should be i mean there should be
stuff like that there infomercials in
the whole bit but i won't have it i just
won't do that
it's not only free but it's free to your
ears
so it's just lots of information to heal
barbara says i'm afraid to do the
meditation a second time in case it
doesn't do what it did the first time
barbara i understand but i have friends
and family
who have been been doing the meditation
for
35 years and because it's that healing
and that powerful
not to be afraid and there's plenty of
people it's it only gets
better too
marie said oh my god chemtrails i
couldn't get through it
i understand okay i understand it's
really that
mind-blowing and i said it at the
beginning with that one it's
mind-blowing so um what fruit fear could
you get through fruit fear could you get
through that episode did you do the
brain meditation
are you ready for tomorrow morning
tomorrow's new episode so tomorrow news
that tomorrow's
a new episode sherry said chemtrails i
can't stop looking up in the sky
on my way home tonight i counted six or
more long trails
i'm so sad for our planet all god's
creatures and what's really sad is
those are the ones you see but then
there's this haze
those are chemtrails that were released
way way way someplace else and then
they're just all filling in the sky it's
crazy how it works
um sharing is caring darcy lee says
sharing the episodes is caring without a
doubt
um just so you know have confidence when
you
share the brain meditation episode that
there's no infomercials
there's no anything when you share the
chemtrail or fruit fair episode or any
of these medical media podcast episodes
with this medical meeting podcast that
there's no
advertisement so you're not telling a
friend
you're not sharing it knowing your
friend's going to get bogged down
and hammered with all this
advertisements infomercials
and all that other stuff please know
that so you're
sharing it in really good conscious like
you're sharing it with confidence that
they're not going to have to go through
that
what i call annoyance uh maya says
healed my ocd
thanks to you anthony oh my god ocd
so glad you got that better so happy
i've talked about ocd for years i like
the brain meditation for ocd too
i've talked about it for years and it's
just so important to get that better
what's my bridge joe grumman says what's
my bridge look like anthony
yeah i know the bridge that you
envision in the meditation is
could look different than the bridge
that i envision or the bridge that
somebody else envisions and
when i do it i see this bridge when i do
it i see
a fairly big bridge not a massive bridge
but a fairly big bridge
enough that more than a couple of
like two cars can at least two lanes for
sure
so it's a bridge that could have two
lanes for for for the cars okay to go
one way the other that size and it's
it's over it's high so it is high up
so that's for sure too so i see it that
way as well
and it's a fairly large bridge where
cars are on it
and it's high up above water
um i've completed the brain meditation
twice and cried so much i felt such
tremendous fear when i had to step
off the edge into the hole once i was
safe i felt such a release
it's really i mean and
what happens is that
you're re-directing the neurons you're
healing you're bringing your soul back
but you're repairing neurons in between
so the emotional center of our brain our
neurons get damaged
when we get bad news and hurt and broken
trust and all these things in betrayal
the neurons in our brain and the
emotional center of the brain they get
injured
they fry and what happens is that you're
doing the
brain meditation and you're on the
bridge and you're walking
those neurons are starting to heal
you're getting electricity throughout
those neurons and it's starting to heal
because it's getting them prepared for
the soul coming back and the fear to get
leave to exit it's really unlike
anything that's out there it's just
it's it's incredible um emma says more
more podcast episodes tomorrow morning
tomorrow so make sure emma make sure you
subscribe
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
see the link in the description right
here
okay and so you can get notified so you
subscribe so you can get the notif
notified that
the podcast the episode the episode
is really good the episode tomorrow
um jesus said fear uh fear fruit was
almost
more intense than the chemtrail episode
so fruit fear was
it's really intense
fruit fear itself is not for the faint
of heart it's really intense
evis evil says i love that no no
interruption no inter in protect
you know what happens is the the brain
meditation
the chemtrail the chemtrail episode the
fruit fear episode
no infomercials and advertisements no
sponsorships okay it's there just pure
listening
free source and and
please share it please share it if you
can
i mean anything you can do to share it
so so i just want to cover a couple
little things brenda said
does it help ptsd yes it does it's made
for ptsd
um it can't it spirit of compassion
brought it down here
for me to be the messenger so you can
heal your ptsd
that's the whole point when we get bad
news and betrayal broken trust and hurt
harm we break up relationship breakups
we get cheated on
divorces whatever happens throughout our
life we get this
out of body experience we get shocked
and the ptsd can occur from it and fear
fills in
and the brain meditation is there to
really restore that now
there's three new episodes coming this
week i'm letting you guys know
i was i wasn't gonna do three new
episodes
for this coming week i was gonna do two
or maybe one
but i'm doing three i'm just letting you
know so
three powerful episodes
this week the first ones tomorrow so
make sure you're prepared
make sure you listen to it
trista says i look forward to tomorrow's
episode
what is in the air we breathe i have
been expressing how unhealthy air
freshener scented candles perfumes are
this is going to be a mind blowing
episode because they are
more than unhealthy and so when you hear
this episode it's going to be really
intense
remember these you know lauren henry new
episodes yay so exciting lauren
it's incredible lauren is an expert at
medical medium information by the way
um she's got the book club she
you know she she knows all the medical
medium tools
lauren henry's just in it she she's a
resource all in its own so if you ever
check out her stuff check her out on
instagram and facebook
and and everything so lauren yeah new
episodes are coming
three of them this week i'm actually
you know i'm actually like oh my god
is everybody gonna be able to handle
these episodes because they're intense
there's a lot of truth powerful truth in
there it's uncensored
and i'm excited i'm really excited i'm
going to be doing
episodes on all the different symptoms
and conditions too
so you got to remember that like i'm
going to be doing episode episodes on
symptoms
all the different diseases conditions
symptoms all that
lupus ms fibromyalgia r.a
lyme disease the list goes on eczema
psoriasis anxiety
depression um breath breast stamp
breast implant illness like i'm gonna be
doing so many different
episodes
and you know i'm trying to keep up the
funny thing is had two hours of sleep
last night
the night before i had three hours of
sleep and the night before
one hour of sleep i'm actually doing
double time right now
and trying to get these episodes done
for you guys
and oh my god um yeah tomorrow brand new
episode coming out
so i'm hoping i can catch some sleep
tomorrow for a little bit if i can
but you know and you guys if you can
share these episodes if you guys saw
how hard i was working on this you'd be
like is he crazy
because because why is he doing that for
everybody
because i care and i want you guys to
have this powerful information i want
you to be able to do the brain
meditation
and heal because it matters it matters
if you guys are suffering or struggling
and
no one's going to just be like out there
and know that your soul's been out of
body
and you've been literally struggling
with fear inside
no one's going to realize how to fix
that or do anything so i have to be the
messenger to get the information so you
can do this
karen says karen smith says i love that
you're i love
that your voice is in the meditation i'm
honored i'm honored
um constance says i listen to them over
and over
thank you can you share it too i bet you
you are i'm sure you're sharing it
you know to anybody you know um allison
said did the meditation yay incredible
incredible so the brain meditation is
um okay sherry said hey sherry whipple
will you do a caffeine episode so i
could finally give it up
uh i have a caffeine episode coming out
it's not this week
but i have a caffeine episode coming out
pretty soon
and um it might be more shocking than
chemtrails
i'm letting you know the caffeine
episode that i'm going to be releasing
is probably more shocking than
chemtrails
i'm actually afraid to release it
but i'm gonna i'm gonna
anyway it's a free resource you guys
make sure you listen to it on the
platform that i launched it on which is
apple podcast
look if you guys have an apple device
and you're not listening to it on apple
podcast can you
please switch over to listen to it on
apple podcast
one reason because you're not listening
to the full episode without realizing it
even if the minutes are the same
second reason it's going to be censored
third reason i didn't launch it on any
other platform
even though it might be found on other
platforms i launched it on apple podcast
so please just if you have an apple
device listen to it on apple podcast
leave the leave the the platform that
you're listening to
and bring it over didn't you know to
apple podcast and then share it and tell
people they could hear it there
please do me that favor because when you
do me that favor then i know
the person you share it with is getting
the uncensored version
because there's nothing more annoying
than
thinking that the per that when you're
sharing it
and you're telling people to go at a
different platform that i
didn't do the official launch at then
they're not going to hear the full
episode
even though you may think they are and
it's really annoying because then
i'm like why am i doing all this work if
everybody's sharing it and no one's
hearing
really what it is it's just kind of it's
really hard so please do that if you can
joe grumman says first we do the podcast
then the meditation to calm us back down
yeah the podcasts are really intense but
like i said
i am going to do a caffeine one and it's
going to be released fairly
fairly soon and
it's probably more shocking in many ways
than chemtrails that's how
that's how intense it is but tomorrow's
episode is about
the air fresheners to send to candles
how we really have to be careful with
that
you know i talk about incense i talk
about all the
i talk about clones and perfumes and i
talk about
why it's important to be very cautious
with that
it's it's uncensored it's it's a
powerful episode i'm actually really
excited because it's just
such a mind-blowing episode subscribe
medical medium podcast the medical media
podcast please subscribe to it
at apple podcast so you get the
notification
of the episode coming tomorrow so you
get the notification
proud of everybody um thanks for coming
on tonight
now you guys i'm doing a live tomorrow
night letting you know so tomorrow night
i'm doing a live
and i'm going to talk about all the
episodes so if you have questions
anything like that i'm talking about all
the episodes tomorrow night i'm going to
talk about the new episode i'm going to
talk about the brain meditation
keep the brain meditation going so you
can heal do it multiple times a day if
you'd like once a day once every night
share it with people please share it
with people
and i'm gonna talk about all the
episodes tomorrow now three episodes are
being released this week
one tomorrow and two others
and the other two others
that are being released mind blown
mind-blowing
mind-blowing so i'm really excited you
guys all right
i will see you tomorrow night michelle
says never dull moment with mm
i'll see you guys tomorrow night bless
your heart god bless you and i'll see
you then