[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere where else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who has 10 or 20 or 30
years to wait for answers to their
illnesses I know people who have waited
a long time and you know I mean I hear
it all the time it's like eight years
have gone by with on and off symptoms of
Lyme disease you know and Hashimoto at
the same time and the aches and pains
and all kinds of different fatigue and
you know brain fog and memory problems
and just waiting waiting for answers is
it mold is it fungus is it candida is it
lime is it goes on is it lupus you know
what does the blood work say and it's
it's not a fun place to be in it really
isn't it's not a fun place to be in and
so many people today are in that place
where all of a sudden they're not
feeling good and they got the symptoms
and and there's really no explanations
for the symptoms no real answers unless
it's packaged with one label you know
and no one tells someone what renald
syndrome is you know no one tells them
what what's causing it and you hear that
here that's the whole point anybody new
who's logging into this show that's what
it's about at the medical medium radio
show I've been blessed with a gift to
hear a voice perfectly clear that
provides information so I've helped tens
of thousands of people regain their
health reclaim their health back and
move forward with their life and it's
about having Advanced information and
that's what's what it's all about so
you're not confused so you're not
hanging on to a label or you're you know
what's going on so we can figure it out
figure it out and it's the most
important thing health is the most
important thing in our lives it really
is so that's what we're talking about
today is health and we're talking about
a lot more about that because today's
show is about the healing powers of
herbs and
spices you guys know about herbs and
spices you're using them I'm sure you
are they in your life one way or another
um and sometimes people they're not
familiar with it and they like they like
their food plain or they don't like
something spicy well maybe there's ways
of getting some of this medicine into
you when you know what it's doing for
you how about that when you know what
it's doing for you so today we're
exploring what these herbs and spices do
for our health how they change our
health for the better what they do in
our body why they're important there's a
lot of confusion around herbs and spices
even to today but we're going to you
know air that out now lot lot of the
information all the information I'm
pulling out is out of my lifechanging
Foods book and you guys are going to be
so happy when you get this book and so
the information's coming out of this
book and it's information from Spirit
and so what's exciting about this is
that it's not just um the same old stuff
it's not stuff that's been circulating
over and over and over again because
what happens in the health field is that
when information just gets repackaged
and then repackaged with a new bow and
then repackaged with a new you know with
new paper and new bow and but it's old
information and we can't do that anymore
we can't I can't do that I'm never going
to do that I never did I have to give
you guys the information that's real
that's accurate that's uh that's on the
Forefront that's leading the way that's
pioneering the way because it's the only
way to get you better it's the only only
way to get you better it can't mess
around here at all cannot mess around
your life your health everything is so
important to you to your family to your
loved ones to me it's important too for
all that because for your loved ones in
your family I want your friends healthy
you healthy I want you getting what you
need and so we're going to cover that
with the herbs and spices this isn't
repackaged information over and over
again okay so this is brand new and it's
important to know this never before
released so um it all started for me if
you just logged on it started for me at
age four heard a voice perfectly clear
uh The Voice told me my grandmother had
lung cancer um and that's where it
started I had to diagnose my grandmother
lung cancer at age 4 uh and um you know
it it Stir It created quite a stir up
with my family family and my life
because it never went away this gift it
stayed there you know part when I was
growing up part of me wanted it to just
go away you know just big part of me
wanted it to go away every day you know
there was a time where I was so down
about it when I was you know Seven 8 n
years old I was so upset about having
this gift hearing this voice perfectly
clear just like someone's in the room
this isn't channeling this isn't this
isn't about channeling kind of you
know whatever thing that's you know
coming this is about a voice I hear um
and spirit of compassion that provides
me information on people's Health
groundbreaking you know ahead of its
time science and research ahead of
science and research its time so we have
a chance down here in many ways in
chronic illness and um and when I was
younger you know I suffered with it and
I know you guys know that I've talked
about it before but I remember
specifically just waking up every
morning with with Dread because I knew
it was another day I would have to know
what was going on in somebody's health I
know 78 n years old I knew that okay
it's another day it's not going away I'm
going to have to know you know who has a
brain tumor I'm going to have to know
who has pancreatic cancer I'm going to
have to know who has liver cancer I'm
going to have to know who has a
problem of you know different kinds of
problems and it and it was just you know
happening and happening one of the
things that helped me through it one of
the things that helped me through it was
knowing information about like herbs and
spices knowing information that didn't
even ex I mean I mean really the the
information that comes out of
life-changing Foods doesn't even exist
out there in any books now but
especially especially back then you know
to know what these things were good for
you know to know why people you know
they they didn't just know why people
were getting help without realizing it
as they were taking or ingesting or
using it in cooking or using herbs and
spices in some kind of food that was the
that was the fun Parts there were fun
Parts um it was like being over a
friend's house and they were putting
oregano on you know Food and Spirit
downloading information immediately on
what oregano was doing at age 9 years
old and it just coming through of all
the information of what it kills in the
body all the bad bugs and what it does
to help the immune system system all
just coming straight through at 9 years
of age and so it was really exciting it
mean meaning those that part those were
the parts that were exciting so I
dedicated my life to helping tens of
thousands of people recover and I'm here
now I'm excited so we'll talk about a
little bit oh don't forget about the LA
event coming up try not to forget about
that I mean if if you're interested um
tickets are selling pretty quick so just
you know keep keep keep on that um
meaning like check your schedule if you
want to come and um and don't forget cuz
what happens to every event is I we hear
it all the time this is why everybody
forgets tickets are sold out and then we
get we get everybody gets very angry and
very upset and very frustrated and very
sad and they're bombarding us with calls
and emails and everything possible about
how come they can't get a ticket and
it's last minute so if if you're one of
those people I do the same thing I do
the same thing it's the last second
thing last minute if you're one of those
people just try to make a note and and
just you know consider consider maybe
getting a ticket a little bit
earlier um if you can I know life has
got you know a lot of crazy stuff going
on we're going to do the light blast
spirit's going to send light down up
down from heaven and send it down okay
and right on top of everybody's head at
the event it's going to rush through
everybody's body it is a rush it is a
rush I will say that and um and um as
I've always said after that happens
don't operate heavy machinery no
bulldozers you know no backos don't hop
in any big you know don't navigate a
ship right after right after that event
and um you know at least for half an
hour at least after the event because
it's intense when that light goes
through us so um that's happening at the
events and uh so I'm I'm looking forward
to that so let's get into health and
everything you know I'm to tell you
right now when we wake up in the morning
right when you wake up in the morning we
got I mean the first thing on my mind is
what does it look like outside you know
weather that's kind of on my mind a lot
um you know I maybe maybe younger people
don't think that I I don't know you know
I I felt like when I was younger and
know when I was in my teens and when I
was now 10 11 12 13 years old I always
wanted to know what the weather was like
out there so maybe I'm wrong about that
maybe young people um do the same thing
but we we you know I I always think
what's going on outside when I wake up
and that's one thing you know the next
thing is you know so like is it is it a
blue sky today what's the weather like
is it going to rain is it cloudy um you
know what's going on there uh another
thing I think about is is is the if I
have to go somewhere is the car okay is
the car okay you know is the is the car
running okay is it safe does there air
in the tires um that kind of gets my
mind a little bit another thing too is
did I sleep okay you know did I sleep
okay um that's something I mean I know
you know we we worry about as sleep a
lot of people don't sleep good you know
insomnia everything else we don't sleep
good uh people deal with Epstein bar
issues so they don't sleep good
neurological problems if they don't
sleep good sleep apnea which is by the
way like
neurological uh most sleep apneas are
neurological not just blockages and all
that and inflammation but actually
neurological um so you know we deal with
all these different things with
sleep and around sleep so that's
something I I think about too okay did I
did I sleep okay I mean with me a lot of
times I'll do readings uh on people in
the middle of the night that I haven't
met yet um which uh has been that's been
a difficult thing for years I'll sit up
and I'll actually be doing a reading uh
on somebody um in the middle of the
night and then you know I'll meet them
and I'll meet them later on so I'll
actually meet them either that week or a
year later and um and I you know it's
amazing because spirit's giving the
information and I'm talking to the
person and I'm giving them information
to heal and helping them heal I have no
control over it or when it happens or
who it's chosen who is chosen but that's
what spirit's been been having me do
since I was a child um so I don't always
sleep that great when those those nights
are happening but the point is is these
are some of the things that I think
about what's going on with the weather
outside what's going on with the car I
slept okay great I slept good or you
know I had one of those nights where I
was doing a reading or you know you know
that kind of thing how's my family
members you know how are my pets these
are kind of things that I think about
are they things things you guys think
about at all right when you you get up
you start your day and then you know
regardless of our busy lives and
everything going out around it and work
and everything else and going around it
these are kind of like those concrete
those etched and stone things we kind of
think about you know right away or you
know they're part of our lives and then
what's the next on the list is food
which is probably you know the biggest
of all you know what food am I going to
eat okay where you know like you know
open up the refrigerator do I have any
fruits and vegetables what am I going to
eat this morning you know what do I feel
like eating can I get a smoothie going
you know it's it's like that's all
there and but what we don't think about
a lot and look some people just grab
coffee and piece of toast you know
whatever you know some people don't eat
anything they just run off and which I
don't think is a great idea but the
bottom line is what we don't really
think about though is the power the
power hidden power in our food the
hidden Powers the real hidden Powers now
first of all we don't really know about
the true hidden Powers the hidden Powers
until life-changing Foods is is released
and I say that because when you look at
it you'll be like oh my God I didn't
know that this existed so we're about to
learn the true hidden hidden healing
powers of our food coming up pretty soon
when when when when you know when we get
a Cofe in our hands
but other than that we do know food is
medicine it's been told it's medicine
you hypocrates all that it's Med you
know the quote you know food is I
medicine and we know that and and but we
don't concentrate it on it that much we
don't concentrate on it that much we
just eat get fuel in you move on with
your busy
day and you know do what we have to do
do our chores do our work do our careers
and but when you
connect to what your food's doing and
what it's really
doing and you connect to
that it ignites the healing process
because your immune system your
emotional state mental state your
physical state attaches itself it it's
connected to your soul it connects even
more when your soul in your brain and
your soul connects to your physical body
and you know what food is doing for you
it's like it makes it even more powerful
even more powerful
so if you're eating a you know something
that's healthy if you eat a carrot or
you eat a yam or you eat an apple or you
eat you know whatever it is that you're
eating and you're eating something
healthy it's going to help you it is
going to help you whether you connect
with it or not it has medicine it is
medicine but when you know what it's
doing when you connect that dot
that's when even more healing occurs
more healing when you know you're eating
something and it's knocking down an
illness knocking down a condition
killing off a virus killing off a bug
lowering your
inflammation actually making your label
for your illness or disease
obsolete
changes everything it changes everything
so when you're eating something and you
know that that food is getting rid of
your
label getting rid of the label you've
been
handed
okay then it changes it it changes
incredibly I mean this is critical
information that you're about to learn
and so this is the power of healing is
someone you know a lot more than someone
I've had so many people over the years
well how do you heal what does it take
well first of all you have to know
what's wrong with you and that's number
one and that's what we're always
bringing to the table here at the show
is finally for the first time connecting
the dots to the symptoms to what's
really causing it and that's only been
happening here only been happening here
I say that once again just so you don't
end up somewhere else getting you know
misinformation and because it's not
going to help you want you want
information that's that's actually going
to help you heal and what happens is
that when you know what's wrong that's
half the battle knowing what to do is
the other half and part of knowing what
to do is knowing what your food's doing
for you knowing what your food is doing
for you for the first time in your life
for the first time it changes
everything
so let's talk about that a little bit
let's talk about herb and spices and the
power they have for
healing so lemon bomb you guys lemon
bomb lemon bomb Melissa that's you know
the herb some people have it growing in
the garden you can get lemon bomb tea
you can get fresh lemon bomb out of the
garden if you have lemon bomb growing in
your garden a lot of people don't that's
not something everybody has or growing
in a pot on the back patio or or
somewhere but you can get dried lemon
bomb and lemon bomb is really powerful
for healing because one of the problems
that we have is neurotoxins
neurotoxins you know mold causes a Mot
toxin that's not as bad as a neurotoxin
neurotoxins you know what happens
there's this debate out there right now
they think they think mot toxin is a is
neurotoxic um actually no it just it
just it's immunotoxic so it it drops
your immune system down it lowers your
immune system down so mot toxin comes
from mold mold knocks your immune system
down so that another problem can take
over which is viruses that create
neurotoxins okay if I'm going too fast
because I'm talking fast today because
we got a lot to cover then just you got
to go back to the archive and and take
more notes because we're going to talk
about a lot of stuff here and you know
and uh get you know sit back relax at
the same time put your seat belt on too
and so you know here's here's the deal
so the neurotoxins that are produced by
viruses such as Epstein bar or the
shingles or you know
simplexes or hhv 6s hhv 7s and
undiscovered hhv 10s and 11s and 12s
that science doesn't even have their
finger on that cause kidney damage and
all kinds of other things we're we're
light years from that information coming
out and um so all these neurotoxins that
we deal with they give us Tangles and
numbness that gives us you know feelings
of of of brain fog light-headedness
balance issues vertigo
issues okay all these neurotoxins that
cause tentis neurological symptoms Lyme
disease symptoms these are all
neurotoxins they're not bacteria they're
all from the viral
Family well these neurotoxins inflame
nerves like the frenic nerves nerves
that run through the chest frenic you
know that's that goes you know it's
connected to the word frantic anxiety
nerves the ones that run through the
chest anxiety when you have anxiety you
have tightness of the chest like you
need get the tightness of the chest and
tightness in there tightness of the
throat and you feel funny in the head
then that's the anxiety those are the
anxiety nerves the frenic nerves
neurotoxins tend to tighten those up get
them inflamed same thing with the Vagas
nerve and these neurotoxins from Epstein
bar and shingles cause the Vegas nerve
to get inflamed
and we first of all the information is
doesn't even exist out there about what
I just told you except uh in the medical
medium book um and in the podcast that
when I talk about this stuff in the end
of the neurological episode and
everything else so um first of all
that's you know that's what's happening
there but second of all knowing what to
do for it is another thing meaning
knowing foods that help and herbs and
spices lemon balm helps with this
condition it helps when you have this
lemon balb is antiviral it's
antibacterial too and we're going to
talk about that but it's antiviral
against the viruses like hhv6 and
Epstein bar against the viruses and and
different kinds of herpes viruses that
we have that cause neurotoxins that
cause all these symptoms that are
mysterious that are Unknown by even the
lime doctors by even all everybody else
that doesn't know what connects these
dots to these symptoms so lemon bomb is
that powerful now if you're someone with
UTI and you get UTI bladder infections
kidney infections
tonsilitis um those are all from strep
strep a
cacus so
laryngitis um
cystitis yeast infections urin Ary tract
infections these are all from strep and
lemon balm is a strep killer if you're
someone that has hpylori if you were
diagnosed with H pylori you want to have
lemon bomb tea consistently in your diet
every single day so what I'm saying is
no when I wake up in the morning I'm
like okay what's the weather like it's
blue sky okay is it sunny is it raining
what's going on out there it's my car
running okay um you know what's going on
with the family what's going on you know
and all that's just concrete things or
all those are foundational things before
we think about oh work and then whatever
else and then you know sure but one of
the concrete foundational things is I'm
going to get this lemon bomb tea and me
because you know what I'm going to start
killing off that hpy
Lori I'm going to make sure I don't get
any more future
UTI because I'm going to start knocking
down the
strap I'm going to start knocking
down everything that shouldn't be there
I got this lemon bomb here I'm going to
start knocking down my upstein
bar and um that's the power of lemon
balm I mean it helps it helps with
symptoms like trouble sleeping
anxiousness loss of appetite nervous
stomach sensitive stomach you guys have
that at all out there heart palpitations
caused by Epstein bar lemon bomb helps
with that hot flashes night sweats
frozen shoulder from
shingles frozen shoulder from Shing I'm
the first one to bring out there cuz of
spirit not cuz I'm special I'm not
special it's Spirit that's special that
frozen shoulder is the
shingles is the shingles that's a
shingles virus in the body causing
Frozen
shoulders lemon bomb helps clean that up
gastritis too much gas and
bloating
fatigue diarrhea IBS you all of this
urinary track frequency urinary track
urgency you your weak limbs when we feel
like we're feeling weak and even things
like mineral
deficiencies and when we have people we
know people with seizures all of this
including histamine reactions when
people get
overreactive it's a power of lemon bomb
and I'm just touching Upon A Touch of
this touch of the power lemon bomb helps
with sibo that overgrowth of bacteria in
the gut which is
strep and on top of all that emotional
support it offers
did you ever feel fearful about you know
about what's going on around the bend
you know I have people that tell me look
I'm just afraid of the future I'm like
you're afraid of the future like yeah
you I'm just worried about is there
going to be another thing coming around
the Ben you know is there going to be
another you know they come in threes I
said don't don't yeah don't fall for
that it comes in three thing you know
don't don't fall for that and you know
and and people tell me they're nervous
they you know they're nervous about the
future
holds well Spirit tells me about lemon
bomb having power to help with that help
ease your mind so that you're not in
fear of what's in the future what's
around the Ben okay and that's the power
of lemon balm so I wanted to kind of
cover that a little bit you guys hanging
in
there are you um are you drinking
something good right now are you
drinking any herbal tea are you relaxing
are you getting ready for this this is
this is intense stuff all right it
really is ginger are you guys doing any
Ginger at all do you know when's the
last time you had Ginger I haven't had
ginger in a while so I'm going to make
sure after this show that I'm like
looking for ginger you know you can do
some ginger spice ginger tea you can do
fresh ginger I like the fresh ginger I
like getting big hunk of the fresh
ginger chopping it up throwing it in a
jug of water putting it in the
refrigerator and just letting it sit
there for a day or two days or just
leaving it on the counter for a day or
two and let letting that Ginger like
really
arrogate that water or or Infuse I mean
Infuse the water and because Ginger is
really important when's the last time
you've had Ginger it's very helpful um
what I like about Ginger is that it
stops us from that
hyperreactive state because we react
we're a society that reacts you know we
just do it's easy to react like what
what what do what do you mean what
happened it's easy to react it's like
reacting every minute as emails that
workflow in and we hear something or
some news or something comes in and it's
hard in this day and age to stay
completely calm completely calm and
unreactive in that unreactive state and
I'm not talking about emotional L you
know emotion you L I'm not talking about
that
you know I'm talking about having you
know having normal emotions in our lives
we're supposed to we're supposed to feel
and we're supposed to feel things but
I'm talking about hyper reacting do you
know anybody that hyper reacts at all do
you guys know anybody Ginger is critical
for him and it doesn't stop it on the
first day it's when it's brought into
your life and it stays in your life it
could knock that hyper reacting down 50%
and change your life
life it really can so these are some of
the things to think about so let's go
over Ginger some of the other things
Ginger can
do Ginger is incredible for pancreatitis
pancreas problems anything pancreas
related pancreatic cancer anything
pancreas related gall stones you know
people worried about gall stones Ginger
helps dissolve gall stones we don't know
that out there we don't until right now
and until we open up not the
life-changing spook the life- changing
food book cuz it's in there adrenal
fatigue it's an amazing adrenal fatigue
you know like rebalancer reverser
reverser and it reverses adrenal fatigue
okay it's that powerful colon
what's a colon what's that I'll
tell you what it is it's a cramp it's a
cramp that's unexplainable and you go to
the the the doctor and you go to the
colon doctor and you go to the
intestinal doctor and you can't you
can't get Cancers and you're getting
colon oopy and you're getting you know
an endoscopy and you're getting all
these different things no it's those
cramps it's those
spasms and Ginger is incredible for it
sleep apnea neurological sleep apnea and
non-neurological sleep apne what I mean
by non-urological is if you have extra
weight on your body and it puts pressure
up up in the chest or you have a high
hiatal
hernia that's happening Ginger's
incredible for for it it helps with that
kind of apnea or you're always
congested congest it there's always
stuff in the lungs cuz you're eating
cheese or milk or butter once a week or
you're having some eggs and you're just
getting that that sinusitis or postnasal
drip and it's causing sleep apnea
Ginger's amazing for
it bladder what's
bladder that's like urgency to pee
that's pains in the bladder that's a
feeling of burning all the time but you
don't have a UTI so Ginger and
incredible for that insomnia sleeping
problems Ginger's wonderful sibo once
again sibo overgrowth of bacteria
Ginger's amazing for that thyroid
disease thyroid disease so if you're
diagnosed with thyroid disease some kind
of thyroid problem make sure Ginger is
in there ral's
syndrome you know it's it's really it's
really sad when we don't know what
causes anything out there but we put
these labels on them and we're just not
we're we're not honest we have to say we
have to say yeah no here's a label
here's a word for it but we just don't
know and have any clue idea what what it
is I I'm just waiting for that day to
come it's like the minute they put a
name on
something I think we're supposed to just
you know comply like okay all right well
that's what it is it's a name Hashimoto
thyroiditis uh okay that's what it is
ryal syndrome but what's causing it ryal
syndrome is a reaction from having blood
toxicity from having a lot of Epstein
bar virus in the liver itself producing
byproduct lots of toxins and it filling
the bloodstream and it not leaving the
bloodstream and it discolor Ates the
skin cause the purple purple feet purple
hands all that kind of stuff the blotchy
hands all that so Ginger's incredible
for that incredible for radiation
exposure you've been to the dentist you
gotten too many of those those x-rays
okay before they were even digital the
radiation is still in you from years ago
before they were even digital where
there was less
radiation so let's do something about it
let's make sure Ginger's in there all
the time right thyroid cancer Ginger's
incredible for thyroid cancer for the
variety of epsteen bar that creates
thyroid cancer you're only going to hear
that
here
and yeah the spirit taught me a long
time ago and I've been helping people
and telling them well that it's caused
by your Epstein bar so let's do
something about the Epstein bar and
that's what creates thyroid cancer
pancreatic cancer celiac disease celiac
disease Celiac is is a pathogen feeding
off of a food creating inflammation it's
not your body attacking itself once
again the autoimmune tag that we address
all the time and and try to you know get
you to understand and get everybody to
understand and and and I I self think
about it all the time because it blows
my mind that we've been told our body's
attacking itself when it's not that just
blows my mind that we're told that so
all of us have to get on board with with
with that you know that misleading
information and get that right it's
going to help us heal it's about helping
you heal and it's about helping you
protect your family and your friends and
your loved ones and your patients and
your clients um Celiac chronic sinusitis
incredible with ginger and helping that
these are some of the things these are
just some of the stuff the power it has
symptoms lightheadedness dizziness
congestion cough that doesn't want to go
way fast if you get colds and flu get
ginger in you all the time
incontinence that is something that
Ginger helps over time weight gain I
mean if you feel like your weight's not
leaving and you got rid of eggs and
dairy and your weight's not going away
and you lowered your your animal fat so
your liver can recover and your weight
is still not dropping as fast as you
want it to do bring in a lot of Ginger
bring in a lot of Ginger and stay off of
pork no pork no no no bacon no no no
pork if you want your liver better okay
so you know you can do a little bit of
turkey if you want can do a little bit
of turkey you can do a little bit of
chicken if you really want but no pork
no pork um these are some of the things
Ginger
does and did you ever feel stifled did
you ever feel like you couldn't get your
voice
across did you ever feel like you
couldn't like say something to somebody
or you just couldn't get it out at work
or anywhere in your life and you felt
like you're being kind of held back I if
you've ever felt that I I felt like that
as a child um in a lot of ways because I
couldn't tell everyone the information
that Spirit had but we all get a touch
of that right that we just can't feel
like we can't use also our intu of
abilities and we can't you know say it
like it is sometimes I mean of course
when at the right moments and all that
well Ginger helps remedy this it really
does what when you have ginger in your
life every day it is
responsible for getting an emotional
state in the body rewired the part that
we get kind of stifled that we get held
back to what we want to say and when
Ginger is in your life you'd be
surprised all of a sudden you can say
what you need to say I mean not a
hurtful thing or anything else like that
just things that are important that we
feel like we can't say to someone or
some somebody or even to
ourselves so Ginger is it unlocks that
door it unlocks that door to when we
feel like hey you know we're feeling
locked up we're feeling
stifled and you know there's a beautiful
thing that happens with ginger and that
alone so these are just some of the
things with ginger
uh you guys hanging in there cuz this is
intense and this is a lot of stuff a lot
of
information garlic you guys eating
Garlic at all you folks eating any
garlic because garlic is good garlic is
good but hey wait a minute you might see
somewhere where garlic is bad garlic is
bad wait a minute garlic is good garlic
is bad am I confusing you yet well
that's what it's like out there that's
what it's like out there there you can
hop on the internet and you can play
around there all day and it's like
Garlic's bad Garlic's bad Garlic's bad
Garlic's good Garlic's good Garlic's
good let me tell you what garlic is
about and and this is what's
incredible garlic has
phytochemicals that run on the same
frequency as harmful
bacteria harmful bacteria harmful
bacteria and harmful
viruses and worms okay worms are you
know worms really aren't the parasitical
family worms are worms worms are the
worm family that has to be separated
that's that that's not in the
parasitical family even though they they
they put those in no worms are worms
that's a different whole family than
parasites different whole family than
mold different whole family than viruses
and
bacteria but there's a frequency that
these bugs run on a frequency that
Epstein bar runs on there's a frequency
that bacteria like staff and merca run
on these are there's an actual
frequency garlic runs on the same
frequency it does now you think that
would be bad well does that mean garlic
is a bacteria does that mean garlic is
bad no no no no no no garlic runs on the
same frequency which makes it even more
powerful the phytochemicals that are in
garlic are Act extra antiviral
antibacterial antifungal antimold anti-
parasitical anti-worm they're extra
powerful because they trick out the
bugs they trick out the bugs the bugs
are protected in our bodies they have
little walls around them they Harbor in
places that are toxic in our body they
have they have protection methods you've
heard of bofilm well there's a part of
the bofilm information is correct most
of it's just wrong and needs to be
thrown away but bofilm is basically
byproduct byproduct produced by bugs and
these bugs hide in that the
phytochemical and garlic breaks in there
because they think it's one of them the
phytochemical runs on the same frequency
as the bugs the bugs let it through the
door they let it in the
door that's what
happens it's basically like a whole gang
a whole gang of B bad guys sitting in a
little private Hideway and a knock on
the door
occurs and they're like who is this and
the garlic phytochemicals are like I'm
one of you let me in so the bad guys
look at each other and don't think it's
the police at all they don't think it's
the police at all they look at each
other and they say because they feel the
frequency the frequency of garlic
phytochemicals it's their frequency said
like you know what this is one of us
they open the door and they let it in
and the garlic rips them apart the
phytochemicals rip them apart and that's
the power of garlic okay just in a
nutshell this is some of what it does um
so as far as conditions and everything
else around it with garlic I mean you
can you can you can go to town with this
it's crazy um you know it helps the
lymphatic system it kills harmful
bacteria everywhere staff you know
hpylori annihilates H pylori now here's
the thing to understand about garlic
garlic does not kill good bacteria this
is a mistake in alternative medicine and
conventional medicine right now out
there don't fall for that mistake if you
eat garlic it's going to kill all your
bad bacteria I mean all your good
bacteria sorry about that if you eat
garlic it's going to kill all your good
bacteria that's a mistake that's not
right that's misleading garlic kills all
the bad bacteria that's what it does so
this is really important to understand
don't forget this one um so it it it
rips apart H by Lori it does things like
protects us from esophageal cancer so
esophagus cancer of esophagus prostate
cancer so if you're worried about
prostate cancer and your you know your
uncle your husband your friend whatever
and you're worried about you that
happening make sure there's garlic in
the diet in any way you can possibly do
it people with Lyme disease that have
neurological symptoms from V viruses not
from bacteria you want to use garlic it
kills off all the different viral
properties all the different viral
bodies of Epstein bar and shingles and
all these different hhv6 all these
different viruses and CMV that stand in
the way of lime that are in there in
Lime so we want to make sure we knock
those out and if you're one of those
that believes in Bartonella being the
problem of lime or babesia or bellia
then garlic kills off those no problem
in fact it really kills those off easy
at one shot a few meals of garlic and
and right through the bloodstream those
bugs just die so that's the power garlic
has so we have to start using it like
that it's a
medicine and emotional support let's
talk about the emotional support I mean
were you ever at a fragile Point are you
at a fragile point now I've been at a
fragile point in in many times in my
life you know I'm I'm I've been there
you know I know and spirit told me
to bring garlic into my life it made me
less
fragile and it made me feel stronger at
times in my life when I was younger and
different times you know in our being
when we feel a little bit of little bit
of that fra fragileness you know
and so you know when we feel like we
just need a little extra shelter a
little extra protection lot going on in
life I mean if you're ever feeling this
way make sure you have some garlic in
here because it helps change that it
does help change that so let's knock
these out we got to keep on going
cilantro you guys using any cilantro at
all yep you're not in your head oh you
are cool cool great I'm glad about that
because I want you using cilantro every
day it pulls out the the heavy metals
detoxifies the heavy metals but I'm
going to give you some information
that's mind-blowing about that because
we know that out there I actually I I'm
not responsible for cilantro being you
know the heavy metal
detoxifier that part isn't mine I knew
about it from Spirit since day one but
um but I didn't spread that information
out there in time you know so that that
was out there and it's incredible
information that's that's when we have
to pick our gems and jewels in the
information that's out there flying
amongst misinformation and
misconceptions and fads and Trends we
have to grab our jewels and we have to
pick those out and leave the rest take
what you can and leave the rest and
cilantro being heavy metal detoxifier
yes take that one in from the outside
but let me give you some of the inside
that's not out there it's the living
water in fresh
cilantro the living water in its stems
and
leaves that have the ability to take
phytochemicals through the blood brain
barrier and to take the phytochemicals
through the bloodstream because the
living water in cilantro is comprised of
sodium pottassium and
chloride okay these Bond onto potent
phytochemicals okay and they travel in
our Highway in our body in our
bloodstream are precious mineral salt
highway so they combine themselves they
get into the stream into the stream of
the precious mineral salt Highway that
keeps us alive that gets up to our brain
this precious mineral salt Highway that
gets up through our spinal cord it gets
into that blood brain
barrier and cilantro Living
Water okay with with which is comprised
of these minerals of chloride potassium
sodium bind on to the
phytochemicals in cilantro take it into
the stream in the highway of our
precious mineral salt Highway that goes
up to our bloodstream lymph fluid and
then finally spinal flute and then up
into the
brain and
then they combine with Glycine and
glutamine amino acids that help make
them even more powerful for extracting
toxic heavy metals out of the body
hopefully I didn't run that by so quick
because I'm like you know I'm talking
like like really quick right now because
I know we're running closer to our time
um so the our brains you guys our brain
is a magnet for mineral
salts so it's like drawing from
whereever it can and and the
phytochemicals and the mineral salts in
the Living Water of cilantro literally
get drawn up into our brain and this is
the power of cilantro so okay let's put
it in a nutshell something you know
something just you know easy to just you
know on the Fly understand real quick
when you eat cilantro it has special
powers magic powers to get to the brain
like nothing else and to extract poisons
out of her brain like nothing else
bottom line and that's what I love about
it um so that's one thing about cilantro
conditions it helps OCD anybody you know
with OCD at all um obsessive compulsive
disorder on any level do you know
anybody with that I mean do you are you
dealing with that at all because it can
hit us in so many different levels in so
many different ways it's not even funny
it just really OCD is a tough one for
people I've seen people suffer from it
I've seen people go through hell with it
I mean I've seen people lock them lock
themselves in their house and then in
when they're in their house they're
tortured I've seen everything under the
sun cilantro every single day just it
has to be in there it has to be
Alzheimer's disease dementia cilantro
heavy metals are responsible for
Alzheimer's dementia cilantro cilantro
cantro depression anxiety neurological
disorders cilantro
autism
cilantro PTSD post-traumatic stress
disorder
cilantro okay and the list goes on and
on and on memory loss brain fog
confusion spasms twitching numbness
tingles muscle cramps foot drop anxious
anxiousness sciatic pain back pain
dizziness if you guys got any of that
going on like any of that just cilantro
throw it in your guacamole I'll have
some with you today then I I'll make a
guacamole with you why don't we do that
together look you know when I get off of
here off this you know this show here
and you guys are you know you guys are
you know let's let's hour from now hour
from when the show ends let's make a
guacamole together I'll be making one
and I'm going to put lots of cilantro in
it and if you're making one if you don't
have cilantro then okay we'll put
oregano in it if we can we'll get
oregano if we can um let's cover cat's
claw good old cat's claw cats Claw is a
secret weapon in disease and illness
today right now in chronic illness every
single doctor's office from A to Z in
every Clinic there is every conventional
clinic and every altern Clinic that's
dealing with anybody with any kind of
label that's that's an autoimmune or any
kind of label that's lime or any kind of
label that's any of that neurological
problems neurological conditions catclaw
has to be in the mix it is the weapon of
the 21st century I'm telling you right
now lme disease incredible for it Michel
plasmas which are just you know stuff
that's just floating around and in us
you know bacteria overgrowth sibo ALS
pandis okay pandis and and you know
which is strepa cacus that one right
there ra which is abstein bar urinary
tract infections chlamidia people have
chyia they have it in system they had it
years ago took antibiotics it's just
sitting in their system just get the
cats claw going on migraines you name it
cats claw can do something about it
planter fasciitis from Epstein bar
Morton from Epstein bar you guys
probably know some of these things
basically I'll spell it out foot
pain foot pain okay cats claw all right
neck pain joint pain jaw pain
um restless leg syndrome all right cats
claw yeah Rosemary th Sage right I mean
you know all those or oregano oregano
kills H pylori kills eoli that causes is
diverticulosis diverticulitis make sure
you're doing a little bit of oregano oil
I'm not talking about the essential oil
of oregano talking about like the
extraction when you go to get the
supplement itself oregano oil put
oregano in your food if you can okay
great for sibo sostis everything ecoli
related um oregano is fantastic
rosemary Rosemary's
antibiotic meaning it is not
resistant to back bacteria antibiotics
become resistant you know like meaning
bacteria becomes you know resistant to
antibiotics that's where mes come from
that's where the strep comes from that's
where all these different varieties this
is all from you know this resistance
antibiotics creating so much trouble
with bacteria and so Rosemary can never
become this kind of this resistance
instead it just it kills off bacteria it
does a great job sea diff see diff you
know staff you name it Mera get Rosemary
going on to protect yourself if you're
in and out of hospitals you should have
Rosemary in your life if you're in and
out of hospitals Sage it's another great
one
antifungal incredible does so much it it
stops everything from you know mold Sage
is anti- mold you get mold poisoning
makes sure Sage is in you every day it
knocks mold right down starts to move it
out of the body
so this is this is a lot of good stuff
um I mean I can't even cover the tip of
the
iceberg with all of this um it's in
life-changing Foods check it out I mean
get a hand get get get a copy in your
hand and if you haven't you know if it's
still in the pre-order Zone just get one
so you know it's coming um I only say
that because I just don't think there's
going to be a lot in stock um it
happened last time but I think this is
going to be worse um I'm going to make
sure that you know I did my pre-order
for myself so I make sure that uh it's
coming to me my friends have pre-ordered
it's coming to them right away right
when it comes out my family all
pre-ordered so it's coming to them right
away and uh because we just want it in
our hands I'm really excited you guys
I'm excited about you getting better I'm
excited about you healing I want you to
incorporate these herbs and spices when
you can I want you to bring them in and
and take it one day at a time if it's
overwhelming just bring in a little bit
of Rosemary just bring in a little bit
of lemon balm tea and when you know what
it does for you even some of the things
it does for you it kicks up the healing
it brings it up even more it amplifies
it it amplifies
it it's just like it's it basically your
body hears it and your body heals and
your immune system gets stronger and you
move forward with your life all these
things matter
everything matters when it comes down to
this it all matters look just know
something know something that I stand
behind you I'm proud of you for
everything you do so when you're holding
off eating those delicious eggs you guys
know about the egg Shack I wanted to
have when I was a kid you guys know
about it you know what my dream was when
I was a child my dream was you know just
making light and fluffy scrambled eggs
for everybody you know and I I figured
let me have an egg Shack where everybody
can come in and it's like a shack and
we're cooking eggs in there and frying
eggs in there and people like them
Sunnyside up and they like them
hard-boiled and they like them poached
and they like omelets and eggs make
people happy and I totally understand it
was my dream to do that when I was 8
nine 10 years old I loved cooking them
up and spirit said you can't do it and I
said what do you mean I can't do it
spirit says you're going to be helping
people just like you have been since age
four you're going to be helping more
people and I said no no no no no I don't
want to do this and spirit said you have
to I said I don't care and spirit said
you have to care you have to care and I
remember Spirit telling me that that I
had to care and I sat on that one and
said I can't believe I have to care and
it dawned on me that I had to and I had
to give up the egg Shack Dream when I
was a child and now I have to tell
people don't eat eggs if you're sick if
you're sick if you're worried about
anything going on keep the eggs out I'm
proud of you keep the dairy out you know
let's move forward together you know
what to do you know all these different
things baby steps if you have to if you
have to do baby steps you do baby steps
one step at a time and I'm behind you I
stand behind you 100% I'm with you I got
your
back you know I heard a story the other
day from a client that said the
information has changed their lives the
whole family everybody's feeling better
remarkably remarkably better better with
all kinds of different
ailments that's what I get out of it
that's the part I get out of it but when
the gift was given to me it was given to
me for you and that parts for you you
know I get I get the relief that people
are getting better I need you to have
the you know to have the gift for you so
you can get better my part my reward is
knowing you're getting better and I'm
proud of you and I thank you for working
on everything get your celery juice
going I stand behind you believe in you
I love you take care and just know I
truly truly care and love you
dearly