okay
hang on hang on
hang on
oh you guys
here
okay okay check any integrity's friends
yep it's a busy day at AWS Bar and Grill
it's very busy there you guys go nice
turn down please calm down
I don't even know what to say right here
this is a busy day we've been on our
feet all day running around dogs guys
guys just squeeze you're driving me
crazy
yep AWS Bar and Grill
okay okay let's get this going here all
right
all right
you guys have enough how's things going
right there yeah busy day today AWS Bar
and Grill yeah medical medium wild
blueberry challenge day one today and
made everything up you guys I can't talk
I'm I can't see her on the phone
please I know you're excited yeah
they're all drunk on wild blueberries
yep it's smash yeah chickadee's friends
are totally totally shit-faced right now
yeah one's on the floor in the bathroom
and we yeah one or two could be his
friends threw up in the toilet and then
threw up all over the floor on the sink
yeah I know you're totally drunk right
now you guys you guys are partying a
little too much
um
what was that
want to check with these friends what
happened
okay take the car keys away from
Tiffany's friend please take the car
keys away yeah well we're yeah it's a
busy busy day at ew Farm ago right here
seeing you guys I can't hear a thing I
got a customer that wants
something yes
okay all right I I can get that total
right up onion rings we have onion rings
yep buffalo chicken wings so the buffalo
chicken wings aren't really chicken no
they're not chicken the buffalo chicken
wings are not chicken they're mock
chicken buffalo wings
yep we don't really do Buffalo Wings
because the chickadee and chickadees
friends do not want buffalo wings on the
menu and they do not want chicken on the
menu either you guys I know you're upset
check in on the menu no
yep no they're upset that's why we don't
have we have fake buffalo chicken wings
here at AWS Bar and Grill we're taking
these friends would be very pissed off
all right
okay I I'll get that I'll get that right
away there's too much to do right here
okay bye you guys we're day one of the
medical medium wild blueberry Challenge
and I'm excited
are you guys pumped
Pump It Up
let's go
you guys we're starting the challenge
let's do it I'm just gonna get a little
bit of this in me right here
let's show you guys
listen
I'll be knocking down some shots right
here
it's incredible
let's start this challenge you guys you
have your blueberry juice
let's do a shot together come on
you guys have your blueberry juice
pardon me
I'm wrong do you have your wild
blueberry juice blueberry juice isn't
going to cut it you need your wild
blueberry juice
so sorry that was insulting to say the
least
because that's wild blueberry juice
incredible I just knocked down four
shots
are you guys knocking them down with me
taking these upset taking his friends
are upset just took all their juice
you guys today we're doing
the hmds famous worldwide hmvs
that has done a lot for a lot of people
around the world I am so pumped up about
that and we're doing not just the famous
hmds
but the soon to be famous extractor
smoothie
and you guys know about the extracted
smoothie right it's right in here which
is exciting in the brain saver book so
I'm excited guys let me just get some
more shots going for chickadee I'm
excited you're knocking them down too
with me Louise says knocking them down
with you incredible I'm gonna get a few
more shots going here ready just in case
they want to knock down another bunch
you guys if I knock down
a whole nother round of shots I might
get through a whole bottle here
in one shot I just spilled a little
forewarning you the blue juice is very
blue that means the anthocyanins are so
powerful they will create an anthocyanin
color on your cutting board or anything
else so I'm just giving you the
forewarning right there
but it's that blue color that deep rich
color that matters because you're
looking at those anthocyanins wow
and you know there's something special
about that for sure I'm going to go into
in detail something special for
emotional
spiritual
mental all of it that's what's
incredible about the wild blueberry
juice so good to see you guys coming on
right here you got your hmds ready we're
gonna be making hmds we're gonna be
making the extractor smoothie we're
going to be doing that too now if you
take a look around you
you're going to see a whole bunch of
different things I got my parsley I got
my cilantro radishes you don't want the
Daikon radish if you have it then we use
it and that's all you got then we use it
throw it in when we make it we'll make
it together but you don't want the Decon
radish you want the other radishes not
the Decon radishes right you want these
round ones right here okay
we've got our wild blueberries kicking
around all of it so let's take a look
here let's the brain
s don't mind can I move the pink phone
all right I'm already getting lit by the
wild blueberry juice is kicking in it's
going to the brain why are the chicks
there don't insult the baby chicks
that's chickadee and chickadees friends
and they are customers at aw Bar and
Grill they frequent here often you guys
see you just got them upset you just got
the baby chicks upset unbelievable okay
you guys calm down calm down listen I
have some shots for you guys okay
aha all right so here we are okay we're
page 536 this is the
hmds right there you guys the famous one
here it is the one that's been around
the world the one that's changed the
shape of alternative medicine the one
that has literally moved the needle
there it is right there in the brain
saver book we're gonna make that
we're also gonna make something else
because it's day one of the medical
medium wild blueberry challenge we're
gonna make
the extractor
smoothie
big deal it's a really big deal right
there team Ginger page 536 brain saver
right there boom page 542.
Andrea says hmds changed my life excited
to hear about extractor smoothie
incredible I'm excited to talk about
extractor smoothie I'm excited to be
here right now
and thank you for being here if you guys
just got on here
anybody who got on here doesn't know
what this is like what's happening you
just entered a free Wild blueberry
challenge the medical medium wild
blueberry challenge if you just entered
here that's what this is I didn't hold
this off and put it somewhere else in
the world and then make everybody pay
and then you know we do this big thing a
program or whatever this is free this is
actually free free free free free I'm
here we're gonna have a lot of fun we're
going to talk about the wild blueberry
the power of the wild blueberry we're
going to talk about a lot of cool things
we're gonna down some shots we're going
to make the hmd yes we're gonna make the
extractor smoothie so it's really
awesome so if you're confused and you
jump into this you just enter in for
free and that's what's so awesome about
it and that's what I want
so let's go into it a little bit we're
going to talk about some tips too in a
little bit sign up and get your free
grocery shopping list because this is
day one of three days day one of three
days I have to repeat that because it's
important to know that you can still
sign up go to medicalmedium.com link in
the profile Link in the description as
well but go to medicalmedium.com sign up
so you get your free grocery shopping
list so check that out that's totally
awesome all on its own so
um
Chico Gomez says where can I buy the
bottles of wild blueberry juice okay the
bottom wild blueberry juice
just so you know is on sale
so wymans.com link is in the description
link is in the profile as well
wymans.com
w-y-m-a-n-s.com that's where you get the
wild blueberry juice okay now just so
you know I'm working with these guys
because I need this stuff to stay around
because it's unbelievable and it's a
sale on it right now ten percent off of
the wild blueberry juice which is
incredible
but I want this to stay in our lives I
wanted to stay here on the planet
because it's really difficult to
actually Harvest these berries this
incredible wild food and then press it
and get it into the bottle it's an
incredible resource for health and I
don't want it to disappear critical to
know that's why I'm working with these
guys and I'm honored and it's a
privilege for me to work with them 100
percent
Hannah says the extractor's movie has
been blowing my mind it works oh does it
ever and thank you Hannah and the
medical medium information in the brand
saver books is mind-blowing you guys
it's the brand saver books right there
it's also 40 off amazon.com us or get it
free at the library
go to the library and get it for free an
Incredible Book it's really six books in
one and that's one of two books two
brain saver books just so you know if
you just got on here and you don't know
about the brand saver books you want to
get your mind blown and you don't have
these get these
your mind's going to be blown you won't
even believe it every line every
paragraph every single chapter every
aspect of these books is mind-blowing
seriously so check those out when you
get a chance
I want to talk about the survival
of the wild blueberries that's a big
deal the survival of the wild
blueberries thousands upon thousands of
years these wild blueberries have been
here and what's incredible about them
is that it's not one species
it's hundreds
so when you look at a wild Blueberry
Field
it's not one
Gene you're looking at you're not
looking at one gene
you're looking at hundreds
of different genes
you're looking at a plant species that
survived because of hundreds of
different genes
that means that the blueberry this is so
incredible about the blueberry okay so
here it is the juice here's the white
blueberries right here
now
information is collected within the wild
blueberry plant
Century after Century after century
okay the Ice Age
they survived
okay flooding
everything they survived drought they've
survived
but they survived
because of the different genes that's a
whole nother thing too with this plant
species it's not one Gene and one plant
but yet it looks all the same
and the berries look the same when you
look at them you're like whoa that's a
wild blueberry that's a wild blueberry
plant you've got a wild Blueberry field
but yet
each plant
they're different than the other plant
it's their survival mechanism it's part
of how they survived all these thousands
of years each plant
has survival information in it going
back tens of thousands of years now a
lot of people they're like they love to
hear about ancient anything ancient
medicine ancient food ancient man right
and when we think about that
these blueberries which are wild wild
food have been here going all the way
back so any time a civilization was here
on this planet one way or another
whatever you believe whether it was the
first human being on this planet
these wild blueberries were here and
information was gathered
throughout the process of Life on this
planet information inside these wild
blueberries and these plants so that
information is all about survival
it's all about staying alive it's all
about protecting the person who is going
to consume them
and that's how you have to see it
this wild food has been here for Bears
to come and graze on for deer to come
and graze on for thousands of years
and then animals that are extinct that
aren't here anymore because the Earth
changed and the animals
died and dissipated and became extinct
but the wild blueberry stayed and
powered through
but they were here for all of these
centuries and thousands of years
for animals that have changed on this
planet to feed off of and humans that
have changed on this planet to feed off
of two
so these wild blueberry plants have seen
a lot a lot of history they've seen the
Earth change they've seen different
animals come and go
for thousands of years and all of that
information of survival stays inside the
plant
and it's there so when you actually have
that wild blueberry juice or you have
the wild blueberries it gets into you
that's that information goes into your
cells so information transfers
from the berries from the plants
from the earth and transfers into our
cells
if you just get on here it's 10 off the
wild blueberry juice right there which
is an incredible sale wymans.com
w-y-m-a-n-s.com so Wyman's that's the
wild blueberry juice and you know what I
love about this when I go when I look at
the ingredient list you know what's in
there
you would think like a whole bunch of
stuff right
just one thing wild blueberry that's all
that's in there one thing and one thing
only and that's incredible all on its
own right there so
you guys we're making we're making the
hmds we're making the extractor smoothie
that's what we're doing this is day one
of the wild blueberry okay challenge
which is really exciting you guys we're
doing three days and this is day one
just letting you know so let's talk a
little bit more I want to read a little
something inside here too in a little
bit so we'll just get to that
are you guys doing your shots I'm going
to take a shot down right now if you
don't mind can't help it
amazing
I'm taking chick of these friends shots
away though
which might make them upset but what am
I gonna do
you guys
you guys it's okay
here I'll put one here for you guys okay
they haven't had theirs yet
just some of them have and they're drunk
what happens when
baby chicks drink wild blueberry juice
they really get [ __ ] faced really
quickly and they run around and
they do all kinds of stuff and at AWS
Bar and Grill
like they're in the bathroom
okay
you guys get too drunk
all right so let's keep on going let's
talk about this a little bit
now when it comes to food people say
well food
you know food is everything food is
everything it really is depending on
what kind of food we're talking about
so if we're talking about a wild food
it's an entirely different story a wild
food
is different than a non-wild food so a
regular blueberry won't Harbor
a fraction of what's in a wild blueberry
it's two different things they're worlds
apart a cultivated blueberry will die if
you don't take care of it
so if you're a farmer and you got
cultivated blueberries you gotta water
them
they won't survive without water
right you have to you have to make sure
all the conditions are right you got to
make sure you feed them you got to make
sure you fertilize them
you got to make sure all of it when it's
a cultivated blueberry
when it's a wild blueberry
it has strength it can handle drought
and survive
you know a friend of mine years ago
um had a cultivated blueberry farm and
people would come and pick blueberries
and then what happened was
he had a bad year
there was no rain so he had to water
them but he couldn't water them because
his well wasn't working because his well
dried up so he couldn't get any water to
that Blueberry Field
and the blueberry Fields started dying
and then the next year only some came
back and then the next year only some
came back eventually he gave up on it
because it took a lot of work
it would be a lot of fertilizer a lot of
feeding a lot of consistent watering so
as time went on he checked out his
Blueberry field and literally not one
cultivated blueberry plant survived and
was left not one
because the cultivated blueberry is weak
that's why extremely weak
so blueberries are not the same if it's
cultivated versus Wild
they're two different species all
together two different species one's
weak yeah it's good for you it's still
good for you to eat a regular blueberry
you open up the clam shell you go to the
store you see that big blueberry
now what you'll notice too is with that
cultivated blueberry it's whiter inside
it's clear inside more of that there's
less anthocyanin on that cultivated
Bluebird that's what I've noticed that's
what I've seen in my life I've I've
actually purchased a lot of cultivated
blueberries and I've really studied them
and I've really analyzed them
and then I picked a lot of wild
blueberries in my time in my day I
remember laying in the wild blueberry
fields at that incredible moment at that
time of year and I've picked so many of
them
and I've experimented with them and I've
cut them open and I've like really done
my own work with blueberries and wild
blueberries and I noticed that the wild
blueberry has a lot more blue going on
it bleeds into the blueberry when you
actually cut it there's more
anthocyanins
and that's what's incredible all its own
that's what I've seen there's more of
that blue so like the cultivated
blueberry the big old one in the clam
shell is kind of like the white bread
version of a blueberry that's what it
kind of is it's got like the white bread
you know and versus whole wheat I'm not
saying whole wheat or white bread or
whole wheat or processed bread it's good
I'm not saying any of that I'm just
saying that cultivated blueberry when
you crack it open it's kind of empty
that's what I've seen it's not the wild
food the wild blueberry all on its own
so these are important things to know
people don't know this information they
think that all blueberries are the same
like okay okay yeah okay okay let me go
and they go to the store and they just
get the cultivated blueberry like I got
my blueberries I'm doing it in here I'm
doing my hmds and it's like no you're
not you're not doing it
if you're using that cultivated
blueberry so now if you can't get a hold
of a wild blueberry and you don't have
access to the wild blueberry juice or
anything like that if you don't have
access then use a Blackberry over your
regular cultivated believer get a
Blackberry so that's important right
there to know all in itself so I'm gonna
get into the hmds now
so let's make it
let's do it
give me fun
so you guys if you have everything you
need to make this right now
so it takes two cups
of wild blueberries
so let me get some in here
so these are frozen wild blueberries now
you can make the hmds with just the wild
blueberry juice
you don't have to use the berry if you
have the juice that's the option I have
the berries so I want to use those and
I'm going to put some juice in there as
well now two ounces of wild blueberry
juice is what I'm putting in next
so there we go
if you don't have the fresh stuff you
can just do the wild blueberry juice all
on its own just do two ounces of the
wild blueberry juice
you can do that but I'm going to put
something here
with that there we go
amazing
I'm gonna put two bananas in here too
incredible about the bananas
is that's a big part of getting glucose
into your system now here's how it works
without enough glucose you can't carry
the nutrients of an hmds into your cells
important to know
you have to have the glucose that's why
each MDS works so much it's designed in
a way to really do the job now
what you're trying to extract is
impurities
so I got a couple of bananas in there
which you could do two bananas now I'm
going to put some cilantro in here of
course
now I put a lot of cilantro in you do
one cup tightly packed
I'm gonna drop some cilantro in here
it's breaking it up a little bit
nice
all right
now I'm going to put some barley grass
juice powder in here a teaspoon
let's get that in there
that's the vemergy barley grass juice
powder that's critical to know that it's
not barley grass it's barley grass juice
powder that's important to know that's
the one I use that's the one I stand
behind I'm working with these guys I've
endorsed them full throttle because they
are just incredible but this is part of
the aggressive juice powder that is
important in details with the details
Details Matter when it comes down to
this people will use barley grass it
won't do the same thing it just won't
and
people don't realize that they really
got it I got my barley grass but it's
not good enough putting a teaspoon of
the spirulina in here
that's the beverages spirulina right
there
what happens is people will get a low
quality barley grass they'll get a low
quality spirulina they'll they'll put
chlorella in there you can't use it it's
not going to work chlorella is not going
to work I talk about that in the brain
saver books in all the books how it
doesn't work okay that's the beverages
spirulina
see we got that then I'm gonna go with
dose
now you can do the Atlantic dolls the
seaweed I'm going to do two dropper
fulls of the Dulce liquid
that's the vimorgeous liquid right there
a quality can't be beat that's that
incredible
and then you can do some water or some a
cup of water you can do coconut water in
here too that's something as well and
then I'm going to add some orange
now you don't have to put if you've got
a juicy enough orange you may not have
to use any water in there
I just put a little bit of water in
there but I'm also going to squeeze the
juice of one orange in here there you go
so this is the hmds a lot of you guys
know about this you're using it people
are using it all around the world
a lot of people are mimicking it they're
trying to poach it change it it's like
good luck you changed it it's not going
to work
and a lot of people do that they'll be
like well yeah what I do is I'll put
this in here or that in there I'm like
okay
just ruined it
Details Matter when it comes down to it
this is a really incredible smoothie
it's helped out a lot of people over the
years
so that that's everything in there that
needs to be in there we're ready we're
ready to blend
let's go let's do it
you guys are really proud of all of you
for being here I'm really excited about
this this is an incredible moment
let's see if we can get this Blended so
you guys just got here and he just
walked in
we're talking about day one that's where
we're at
about three days while blueberry
challenge
making an hmds we're also going to be
making these tractor smoothies just
letting you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
boom we're done
I'm gonna put this in this nice little
jar right here
do you guys want any
here we go
that is
you know when I hold this
I think about what it's going to do for
me
I connect with it
and I remember there's a wild food in
here
is it important to understand wild foods
have an ability to connect to the person
that's going to be involved to that
person that's holding them to the person
who's actually touching the wild food
wild Foods Harbor information
for human beings to receive
but it's another thing too to have that
intention that connection to want to
receive what good it has and I like
letting my body know so I like my
subconscious Consciousness my brain my
soul to tell my body
that this is actually going to be
entering
that color blue the anthocyanins
everything that's in there
I want my body to know impurities are
going to be leaving and so I actually
prep my body and I I actually connect
with it before I just don't gobble it
down sometimes I do if things are crazy
and all that but if I got a second I
like to make that connection right there
so it's important you guys go to
medicalme.com if you just got here sign
up
for this free challenge okay you'll get
your you'll be able to download your
free grocery shopping list so this is
day one of the medical medium wild
blueberry challenge we just made the
hmds
Lorraine says wonderful connection
that's what I love to do sign up for the
challenge link is to the profile link is
in the description download and get all
the details of the challenge so you can
be prepared I want you to know what to
have each day because we're going to
make some really fun stuff in the next
three days
Erica says the hmds took away my
crippling anxiety and panic attacks
incredible
that matters when something leaves us
like that it matters and I hear doctor
friends tell me all the time be like ew
you know like this is working for my
patients this is working for my people I
hear that all the time
and it's just so it's so happy it's so
great all right so let's take a look at
the brain saver book
I'm going to go to page 93.
here it is you guys I don't know if you
have a brain saver book yet
I have one right here
okay there's two of them I'm gonna read
out of this book here brain saver
there's also the protocols book right
here if you're if you're new here and
you don't know about the brain saver
books
this section right here is called making
peace with our healing timeline
it's really interesting
when we get sick
we start to track the timeline did you
ever do that
do you guys ever go through that
you get sick
and then you track the timeline
I got sick in
1997. I got sick in 2019 I got sick in
May of
2020 I got sick in June
of 2021 I got sick in the first week of
August in 2018 right
and so when we get sick we start to
track the timeline and if we don't
remember the year or the month
we remember something about it we tend
to track that timeline right
we count the days
we've been sick have you ever counted
the days you've been sick
because I know so many people have
literally counted the weeks the days I
know some people they counted the hours
and maybe even the hours we count the
weeks the months and eventually if it
lasts that long if you've been sick that
long we count the years have you guys
ever been there
sick that long Lori Maloney says I got
sick in April of 2013.
Lorraine L says I remember my age 34. he
got sick at 34 years of age yes I got
sick in 1997.
1997 I just saw that there Maria says
yes definitely know the timeline
and Claire Dunn says yes by months and
years I do
I've never heard anybody talk about this
in Alternative Health or conventional
health I remember when Spirit of
compassion was giving me the information
to put in the book it blew my mind
because what I was getting is that
information and it was making me really
think about it and think about like yeah
you're right like
that really does happen that's really
happening for people
Kelly Burke says over 10 years now
exactly yes and uh Rita says 1992.
I completely understand
so you know this is really important how
this works I saw someone said I don't
get sick well that's amazing and if you
ever do get sick because everybody gets
sick no matter what at one time in our
life even if it's in the later years you
know where to go
foreign
Coster says 1999
yep uh Elena peaser says September 2016.
this is a big deal so remember when
Spirit of compassion was was giving the
information and having me write down the
words and I was writing them down and I
wrote
when we get sick we start to track the
timeline I said the spirit of compassion
I said this is blowing my mind we count
the days we've been sick
maybe even the hours
we count the weeks the months and
eventually if it lasts that long we
count the years
something happens to us emotionally when
we when we remember the month we got
sick
I just when I was writing that down I
was just all blown away Pamela K says I
remember being sick since I was a little
child only noticed once it got worse
I really believe that I see so many of
you guys know the year you got sick
you know the month too so many of you
like I see 2014 I see 2016. I'm just
watching the comments you guys you guys
are just like you guys remember you guys
know I've never heard this spoken a word
in all my years 35 years working in the
industry 35 years just doing what it did
even before that when I was a kid
I never seen this and so when Spirit of
compassion made me write this down I was
like
this is just blowing my mind 2011 I see
that too 2016 1989 whoa
something happens to us emotionally when
we when we remember the month we got
sick the time of year
many of us remember the people we were
around when we first got sick do you any
of you remember the people you were
around when you first got sick because
that was another thing so in spirit of
compassion said that
I was just like no
you know so many of us remember the
people we were around when we first got
sick
and yes you do you remember the people
you were around when you first got sick
yeah so right after the night after you
gave birth I saw that
well and then the and here's another
thing too the job we were doing do you
guys remember the job you were doing
when we when you guys got sick the
commitments we had on our plate
time plays a large role in our emotional
brain
it's as if our emotional brain is
directly connected to time
which is really incredible sure we worry
about time on a daily basis
even when we're not sick or struggling
our responsibilities and plans are based
around time yet something changes when
we're sick
we see time differently
we start saying it's time to get better
I get emotional talking about this
because I know so many people have
struggled and I know you guys have
throughout the years
it's almost like time changes
and we end up just saying to ourselves
it's time to get better I have to get
better it's like time alters when you
become sick it's not about the time that
someone else is on it's about now it's
time to get better and that's what it's
about
or it's about time I'm feeling better
were we here it's in due time you'll get
better right you'll hear that one too
and do do time you'll get better
time is such a large aspect of illness
because if we're sick
we feel
like we're losing out
and yeah that part's a tough one for me
because I I've watched so many people
throughout the years
go through so much sickness
and one of their big things is that I'm
losing out if you guys just rolled in
we're reading right out of brain saver
saw somebody say what are we what are we
doing reading right out of brain saver
right here we're making the hmds I have
one right here which I'm excited about
if you guys don't mind I would like to
take a sip
that's so good
that is so good why does something taste
so good when you know it's so good and
what it does for you too but it's both
um
time is such a large aspect of illness
because if we're sick we feel like we're
losing out
time is passing Us by
at the start it doesn't feel as
threatening emotionally yeah I've been
sick for a week two weeks
the hands of time start to feel heavy
when it goes on too long that's why you
guys are warriors
all you guys are warriors seriously
you found medical medium information
through obviously some spiritual divine
intervention
okay you bent a doctor after doctor you
better practitioner after practitioner
and then
somehow the book landed on your front
door somehow it landed in your lap
somewhere somehow you saw something
somehow you were told check this out but
some kind of divine intervention
happened
spiritual intervention
where you found the medical medium
information
and you were like okay I have to do
something I've been sick too long I need
to change course and you found the info
and you're turning your lives around
the hands of time start to feel heavy
when it goes on too long you're not
quite better
you're even getting worse so many people
have been through that and now time
becomes doctor appointments and your
care schedule time is about how much
energy you have how much space you have
around your illness to do what you need
to do
and that's where time changes
it's like now I'm sick and it's all
about how do I how do I work my schedule
around this sickness
life can change when we're sick
causing restrictions making us feel
everything is so difficult we have to
slow down
that's why you guys are like Warriors
for real you have been through it all
you know what it's like
and then you found the medical beam
information and you're working hard on
your healing process and your healing
our emotional brain
puts due dates
and past due dates on our recovery
I gotta be ready by this time I got to
be better in a week I have to be better
here then
we end up putting like due dates on
things that's how the brain works it's
really kind of incredible
the emotional center of the brain
starts to create due dates
it's kind of like not you creating them
it's actually
integrated in the emotional center of
the brain to create these due dates
I have to heal or this date
and then I was supposed to be better
already I was supposed to be better
already it's another thing that people
say we can feel trapped in a Time War
our emotional brain wants us to be
healed by a certain time and our
physical body is not ready to heal
because it's not getting exactly what it
needs to heal and that's what's so
incredible right now
when you look at Medical meme
information and you look at the books
and you look at all that we're doing
and you look at the incredible healing
foods
it's about getting your body what it
needs
for the first time
a lot of people they're sick for many
years and they have these due dates
built into it and they want to be ready
by a certain amount of time but their
their emotional brain says I want to be
fixed now their emotional brain says I
want to be better in a week
but their physical body is saying you're
not giving me what it needs
that's what our physical body does
our physical body says
hold on a minute
I know you want to get better
I know you want to heal I know you want
it to be healed last week
but you're not giving me what it needs
I know that emotionally and mentally
you're there
you want to be healed
you want to be fixed snap of a finger
you want to think about some mastering
of the brain and logic and heal
you're even going to go uneven try all
kinds of different stuff to try to fix
it
but your physical body is going to say
hold your horses
until you give me what I need
your physical body needs
they're not going to get better
and that's what our physical body does
even though our emotional
brain
says no I'm giving myself two weeks to
heal I'm gonna be out of this
and then the two weeks go by and you're
still sick
I'm gonna go see this person I'm gonna
go see that person I'm gonna find a way
to fix it I'm gonna do it I'm gonna get
better and then you're still sick
because no matter what your physical
body didn't get what it needed but I
thought my physical body was getting
what it needed I went to this doctor I
went to dysfunctional guy I went to this
heeler I went to this natural guy I went
to this gal I went to all these
different experts in the field of
medicine in the field of alternative
medicine I went to everybody I thought I
was giving my body what it needs but
your body still says you're not healing
and you're not going to heal until you
give me what it needs
just because
somebody out there says oh this is what
you need or that's what you need doesn't
mean it's exact it's exactly what your
body needs
and that's what's incredible about the
medical medium information
it bypassed all of that confusion to
give people what their body needed and
that's why it has the most people
healing in the world than anything else
in
the world of Health right
then once you do get what your body
needs it can take time to heal depending
on what you're up against but you see
the results as time goes on because your
body's finally getting what it needs and
it's incredible
what's wrong with our physical body has
not been identified yet even with the
best of Specialists and best diagnoses
out there so how would anybody know
their body's getting what it needs then
when we put ourselves on a timetable to
heal we get let down when we haven't
healed yet I'm gonna heal in a month
month goes by not healed man I'm let
down now
then we register it as a failure I'm a
failure I didn't heal within those two
weeks I must be a failure that's what we
do
I failed to heal before the second
semester of college I failed to I failed
to heal before junior year I failed to
heal before it was supposed to go back
to work I failed to heal before my
wedding I've seen that a lot of times
happen out there it's like I didn't heal
before my wedding
I failed to heal before my child's first
birthday failure syndrome sets in why am
I not feeling better yet
how is it possible that I didn't heal
yet it feels like we're not getting
better in time to live our lives and
then when we're sick for too long time
seems to blur itself into one do you
ever see that guy do you ever see that
person out there and it's like
you've been sick so long that just time
just all blurs together in the end and
that happens too at a certain point
we're not keeping track anymore
only noting the landmarks along the way
trying to get better has become too long
drawn out and time-consuming real
process Clarendon says yes love to hear
this validation
I mean I was in tears believe it or not
when I was writing this getting the
information from SOC because I connected
to so many of you and so many people out
there that have just suffered for so
long it's just when you really think
about what they're going through
it's really hard
having faith and trust in your body
and your body's ability to heal is a big
part of not letting the time stamp of
every moment spent being sick lets you
down getting in touch this is such an
important piece of information right
here and this is why I don't do programs
and charge thousands of dollars because
this can we can package this up and do a
program people sign up and they learn
about their healing process Vital
Information they're not going to hear
anywhere but this is why we don't do
that
because this should be free
this information should be free you
should be able to get this information
and and actually fortify your emotional
brain work on your healing deeper
get answers this should not be held back
and then a paywall
having faith and trust in your body's
healing is a big part of not letting the
time stamp of every moment spent being
sick let you down
that's a big deal right there we have an
emotional attachment to time when we
become sick
we do we get this emotional attachment
to time Christy says what you are saying
is so much my experience
I believe it
some of it healthy some of it
unproductive part of this is the
conditioning we've all experienced so
what I'm trying to say you guys is we're
conditioned to be sick
the law of the land out there has been
set up for us to get sick
then when we get sick we're conditioned
to think a certain way when we're sick
which is all sick
part of this conditioning we've all
experienced institutions have
conditioned us to live on timetables
that are industrialized we're made to
feel like we're wasting time no matter
what we're doing we're made to feel like
we have to be on time for everything
when we get sick this conditioning is
still at work so we're conditioned about
time and then when we get sick the
conditioning is still there and that
makes it worse and we suffer emotionally
because of this institutionalized
timeline
God should get the brain saver books if
you don't have it and learn and learn
this stuff it's so incredible
when we get sick this conditioning is
still at work and the gears need to be
shifted we need to shift these gears
that's what this stuff does
this might be like a fun medical
meanwhile blueberry challenge but it's
always deeper than that and it's always
more than that
the emotional centers of the brain need
to get new messages remember when I told
you ancient food
ancient food that has inflammation and
messaging in it for thousands and
thousands of years
we can't be trapped by the everyday
industrialized timetable we've been
taught to live by we can't apply that
timetable to our healing we have to
learn to separate the two the
industrialized timetable
and our natural healing timeline
really incredible information right
there all on its own let's make an
extractor
wait half time you guys do you remember
the robot
chickadees do you guys want to do the
robot with me
chickadee and friends want to do it with
me
[Music]
all right half time
the robot
all right you guys that was the quickest
halftime I've ever seen ever
all right guys um
no laugh attacks I will have some of
this
ah the hmds is insane
it's so good so let's make an extractor
smoothie if you guys don't mind so
now here's the thing the tractor
smoothie
it aids in the removing different
varieties of toxicity
also freeing the path for toxic stuff
to uproot and leave the body
get the impurities out so let's make an
extractor smoothie which I'm excited
about so let's start
let's start right now
so you got your blenders ready are you
guys with me we're going to make this
together now if you don't have what you
need right now
fine that's okay I mean that's all right
so it starts out with one apple chopped
now if you have a really large Apple you
don't have to use the whole thing if you
want like a gigantic one this is a
medium-sized apple right here
chopping that Apple up
and it's going into the blender
we're making the extractor smoothie
foreign
saver books just so you know that's
where it is we're doing one apple
okay
now let's go find the extractor smoothie
if you guys don't mind
and remember you guys I'm at your
service always at your service I am here
I am working for you
okay
um
we're gonna go into the ingredients now
let's go find the extractor smoothie
it's over here I have it marked to get
to it real quick and easy here it is
you're looking at it
now
that's what it looks like
it's inside brain saver
all right so let's move this over
Colleen says when should I use this
extractor afternoon is great it's fine
if you're short of time and you have to
use it sometime in the late morning you
can possibly do that but I like doing it
at the other end of the day that's my
favorite time to do it it's a great time
to do it so you do the hmds
in the morning mid morning or whenever
you wake up later on right whatever
depending on your day you could wake up
at noon and then you can do your hmds
later on and then you do your extractor
by night whatever you know whatever you
want to do yours are Lori says mine's
already made incredible
all right let's get working on it so we
threw an apple in there
so we need some wild blueberries next
so that's next so one cup of Frozen
while blueberries or one ounce of pure
wild blueberry juice I'm going to do a
little bit
now I'm going to bring this over here
too
nice
amazing so let's put an ounce of wild
blueberry juice in there
that's good
nice if you guys know that's 10 off
right now I want to remind you if you
just got on here
which is incredible
okay so the next is going to be one
fresh banana
of course
we got our fresh banana in there
incredible
okay one tightly
packed cup
of parsley
so what I'm gonna do is just kind of
chop this up a little bit of this
parsley
now that's not gonna be a cup I have my
own measuring techniques here
all right
I'm gonna put a little bit more now this
is one strong
extractor
it's really really medicinal so keep
that in mind really medicinal
that's going to make a nice cup right
here this extractor smoothie is meant to
come later in the day like I said after
hmds
all right we're moving along one radish
root
can I throw it around a little bit
do you you know I put a backspin on it
I haven't had a chance to throw fruit
around in a while or vegetables or roots
putting in one of these in there
these radishes
I'm gonna stop fooling around can't be
all
fun and games
EO fruits and veggies says medical
medium has stopped progression of so
many symptoms but taught me I've been
sick my whole life I worry some damage
is irreversible
and yet to get relief from brain shots
and meditations any tips
I mean here's how it works everybody has
a different amount of poison toxin or
packaging like I was talking about many
times throughout the years especially in
the medical medium books right
and you got to think about a couple of
things
how worse would it be if you weren't
doing the right things
how worse would it be
think about that so many people would
decline decline decline if they don't
have the right stuff and Decline and
that's an entirely different thing you
want to stop that
so you want to stop the declining and
stabilize
right and then move forward okay some
people they heal literally boom like
really quick they got less pathogens
less problems with their neurological
system because of less impurities less
toxins less Metals less all this stuff
right and then there's other situations
like what what you may have used and are
you customizing so got to keep in mind
and I tell anybody who actually
and you could bring the books to your
doctor too
there's so much detailed comprehensive
information in the medical medium books
that you can customize your path
to take it all the way
keep that in mind you can customize your
path to take it all the way
but are you customizing it are you doing
the different Protocols are you doing
the different cleanses are you doing
like there's there's a lot of people
that I talk to
I ask them about it and they're like
well yeah I was eating chocolate last
month I go
I was like dude you you have no room for
eating chocolate a month ago if you need
to go the full distance you can't eat a
chocolate you know cacao nibs and cacao
bars and all that you can't do that and
I talked to another person they're like
yeah no I do caffeine once in a while
I'm like then stop coming to me saying
you're not healing all the way you've
only healed half the way or three
quarters because you're lucky you'll
heal half the way because at least you
didn't go backwards all the way to the
dumps but you can go all the way forward
you just have to know how to customize
it you see that the client you see the
declining out there in the world you see
the declining with people's lives and
health out there in the world when
they're not bringing the right
information and it happens every day it
happens fast out there I watch people
drop all the time out there but every
time I talk to somebody that's like out
there that's like look I've gotten
50 symptoms better I still have four
more symptoms to go where I got 20
symptoms better which I couldn't get
better anywhere else I hand it to the
medical medium info but how come I can't
get these other symptoms better and then
when you ask them and you talk to them
they were eating like charcoal pills
from some recommendation they were doing
apple cider vinegar gummies like two
months ago they were doing chlorella
they were doing like stuff that just
stops them from healing there then next
thing you know it they were doing
something else then they were eating
chocolate then they were back on gluten
like you just can't you can't control
the Free Will of everybody you can't
and I realized that over the years but I
was talking to somebody recently and I
sat there and almost pulled all my hair
out of my head because they were eating
gluten like a couple of months ago
gluten will set you back if you got that
many pathogens then they were eating
chocolate and they were redoing this and
then they were getting guidance to do
apple cider vinegar gummies and when
that happens is it's like
it's just you gotta customize your
pathway
and you got to watch out for the traps
in potholes
and you have to stay diligent and you
got to know the information and you
can't get derailed
so you're making the extractor smoothie
right here
which I'm excited about
so
we got the parsley in here which is
incredible we got the radish in here we
got the banana we got the wild blueberry
juice in there too now we're gonna put a
little bit of mustard seed as well so
one teaspoon of mustard seed coming up
Mustard Seed coming up one teaspoon
one teaspoon coming up here
now a lot of you guys might be like oh
whoa Mustard Seed is pretty intense
but you don't look this is the extractor
and that's the whole point like the
medical meme information is so Advanced
and there's so many options to move
forward and to customize you have that
option of doing the extractor it's an
incredible tool but if you don't like
the Mustard Seed then you know we can
then try one of the other medical medium
tools but it's really incredible
opportunity okay one cup of water or
coconut water
so I am going to put one cup of water in
here
I think we might be ready we might have
everything we need
so let's go
let's Crank It Up
extractors in process
all right guys I am still here
chickadee and chickadees friends they
don't like when the blenders on they
start to make noise
don't worry guys I got it I I turned it
off we're good I turned it off
listen all the tips about the extractor
smoothie are in the brain saver books
just know that they're in the brain
saver books right here there's two brand
saver books if you just got here 40 off
amazon.com us or get it free at the
library I don't care if you get it for
free at the library
just get it so you can actually get
started
now I will say this
medical meme information is there for
the chronically ill people who couldn't
get better any other way
people have struggled around the world
tried everything been there done that
seasoned people that came to Medical
mean information
it was always about
having the answers and the ability to to
have those answers use them and know
what to do to heal
that's what it was about
mm info was in something somebody goes
to first after they have to be around
the bend they have to know what it's
like out there because when you get a
newbie who doesn't know what it's like
out there but they've told to go to mm
first they sometimes take it for granted
because they don't realize how bad it
really is
the information here has saved so many
lives around the world it's unbelievable
when you think about it and it all makes
sense none of medical leave information
is common sense
it's above common sense because Common
Sense would never know any of the things
that we do to get people better and so
anyway you guys this is the extractor
and I have it here and I'm gonna try it
now
my God
it's unbelievable really when you even
think about it
the extractor
smoothie
the feeling you get
foreign
because it's about getting impurities
out that's what we're talking about here
when you actually utilize these tractors
movie
[Music]
you get a feeling that you know you're
getting impurities out
um
the link says yours since minty mine
tastes delicious
[Music]
it just tastes delicious
foreign
enough
I don't know which one I like better
I don't know if I like the hmds
hmm
for the extractor smoothie
I will tell you this I'm gonna take a
shot
bartender give me another
[Music]
um
bartender give me another wait a minute
I'm the bartender here
it's AWS Bar and Grill
post about the challenge I would love to
see your posts your reels your stories
you guys
tag at Medical medium medical medium so
I can share them share them which I
would love to do and help other people
too using your experiences because your
experiences someone else might see your
experience and be like I might try that
because we want people to have a chance
to heal grow and move forward and that's
what we want them to have of course of
course
AWS Bar and Grill is still open for a
few more minutes here so we're here it's
exciting you guys
the Wyman's w-y-m-a-n-s
the wild blueberry juice is on sale 10
off right now
forewarning if you get the blue juice on
a white sweater or sweatshirt I feel bad
for you
try not to get the blue juice on
everything
try not to spill it on the carpet either
so I'm just telling you the anthocyanins
are so blue
so blue and keep that in mind right
there okay but yeah that's the one that
you guys know I'm working with these
guys I want the stuff to stay around
because it is a miracle I believe it's a
miracle to even have it in that glass
bottle and come out of the field and be
pressed and put into the glass bottle
it's a big deal totally a big deal right
the answer is aw I love it when you put
your music on makes me smile incredible
you guys
I am very pleased
to be here with you today on the first
day of the medical meeting while
blueberry challenge I feel kind of Tipsy
you guys I'm feeling a little tipsy
I do
I think it's so much Wild Blue Ridge
oh sign up it's amazing I just love it I
can't get enough of it sign up for the
challenge download your free grocery
shopping list medicalmedium.com listen
guys I'm gonna be streaming this again
you can see the replay at
medicalmedium.com
you can see the replay of this video of
day one of the challenge it's for free
I'm streaming it for free there is no
pay walls at medicalmedium.com it's
there for you to actually learn grow
heal take advantage of it
and because you know why not
because you're worth it you are totally
worth it keep that in mind
yes
anyway you guys this is incredible all
on its own sign up for the challenge
download the free grocery shopping list
like I said make sure you are on the
medical medium newsletter too so you can
know when that light blast is coming
the other thing I want to tell you guys
got to sign up to the newsletter because
I want you to know there's going to be a
light blast and we're going to be doing
it and it's going to be exciting so you
want that information so you could be
there it's going to be really powerful I
haven't done a light blast
since
2016. I don't know when it was 17 or
2017 or something it's been a long time
it's going to be exciting you guys
um maybe it was I don't know maybe it
was a couple years ago but we're going
to be doing a late blast going to be
sending out a message to you guys soon
about it so you could so make sure you
sign up in the newsletter
okay about a month from now
or this month I'm gonna this month I'm
gonna be sending out a message about it
so I'm excited you guys so make sure you
sign up so you don't miss out that's
what's going to be incredible
so
you guys this was day one of the medical
meanwhile blueberry challenge
[Music]
for chickadee chicken starting to
okay you guys hang on
AWS Bar and Grill
hold on
foreign
chicken D and chickadees friends are yes
they're throwing up all over the
the bar bathroom right now because it
had way too much to drink today
did you know that chickadee and
chickadees friends are Dr nesbitt's
children
did you know that they're Dr nesbitt's
children ticketing and she could be
friends
these are all Dr neswick's children yes
that was babysitting today at AWS Bar
and Grill and they all drank too much
and they got me really upset because I I
have folks today I'm very busy with
awful final help
yep
I know
I know tricky the entities friends on Dr
nesbits
children yes
yep yep yep yep
aw Sport and Grill can I help you
yes
um
you guys stop I know you're Dr nesbeth's
children but you're driving me crazy
okay all right here you go
try not to get too drunk on these wild
blueberry shots
okay
I'm gonna take one too
yes
AWS Bar and Grill
it's a busy day today
I'll see you guys tomorrow
I think I drank two bottles of wild
blueberry juice
yep I don't know if my piece