Jones meditation Journey you should get
your video today you have 24 hours to
view it to watch it
don't miss out I hope you signed up to
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
because it's going to be utterly insane
an incredible experience Beyond you're
going to have a life-changing experience
you're never going to forget that's how
powerful the collecting Stone's
meditation journey is so please make
sure you're signed up
so you get to see the video start your
journey it's a seven day Journey today
is day one I wanted to let everybody
know link is in profile link is in the
description don't miss out whatever you
do I'm reading out of cleanse to heal
because it's the summer
and the summer of healing so we're doing
like the collecting Stones meditation
Journey I'm reading about cleansing a
little bit
because summertime is an incredible time
to do some cleansing and detoxing and
healing so I'm reading out of cleansed
heel right here so check this book out
when you get a chance get it free at the
library or go to amazon.com it is uh on
sale there so that's incredible
pathogens aren't always behind our
cravings
everybody's got pathogens everybody's
got strep
they have some type of pathogen within
them they'll have Epstein-Barr shingles
hhv6 cytomegalovirus they're hhv7 so
many different cold sore viruses canker
sore viruses so many people live with
pathogens all the time and I remember
the days before medical medium published
books where no one in the health realm
really knew about pathogens in the
Natural Health realm at all nobody knew
about pathogens being responsible for so
many different symptoms conditions so
this part I'm reading right now in
cleanse the heel is about adrenaline
release now we're talking about
cleansing so hang in there for the ride
I'm here Jacoby says I still need my
Stones it's storming out there so you
can't get it you'll get them later
amazing
pathogens aren't always behind our
cravings when we avoid certain foods
Cravings also have an emotional
component now the reason why I was
saying that is because
pathogens love to eat certain foods and
that can get us into the craving mode
so when we have all these different
pathogens inside of us they need to eat
pathogens don't just exist and that's it
they have to eat they have to reproduce
that's what pathogens do
Cravings also have an emotional
component
that's an important thing to understand
too so if we have cravings could easily
be an emotional component involved a
trigger have you ever been triggered
into cravings
have you ever had a stress trigger of
some kind that sends you into a place of
craving I'm craving that coffee I'm
craving that chocolate I'm craving that
salty fatty sweet snack I'm craving that
chocolate cake I'm craving those hot
dogs craving those cheeseburgers craving
those pizzas
I'm craving chicken fingers I'm craving
nuggets from the fast food chain
restaurant I'm craving craving craving
Cravings also have an emotional
component people tend to be long oh this
is really cool right here
people tend to belong to one of two
schools when it comes to eating and
emotions see if this resonates at all
with you guys in the one school are
folks who eat to take their mind off
their pain emotional pain do you eat to
take your mind off of emotional pain
where it's like get that food out like
maybe you're at work or something like
that you're maybe you're in the office
maybe you're wherever you are maybe
you're at a friend's house a family
member's house and you're eating to
suppress
emotional pain you're eating to take
your mind off of some type of emotional
trigger emotional situation
emotional pain
when we're in this school and we take
away certain Comfort Foods sometimes we
start to experience a few feelings we
were trying to use food to suppress
interesting if you just got on here I'm
actually reading out a cleanse Hill if
you don't have this book
if you don't have this book you're
missing out it's incredible book
Incredible medical textbook cleansing
information has so many things in there
so when you're in this one school so you
there's people that belong to usually
two schools when it comes to eating and
emotions and this one school or folks
who eat to take their mind off their
pain and when we're in this school and
we take away certain Comfort Foods we
start to experience a few feelings we
are trying to stuff down down inside
stuff down I see a lot of people asking
about the collecting Stones Journey
maybe they don't Maybe
many people didn't sign up and they need
to sign up
so keep that in mind you're getting a
video today which is going to be
incredible today's day one of the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
a seven day Journey please don't miss it
it's for free and it's going to be
life-changing I can't say enough about
it that's how life-changing it's going
to be
so that is a separate video then this
live you must be signed up to receive so
here's the thing this live is different
than what that is a seven day
collecting Stones meditations during you
have to be signed up
signed up I have three stones right here
but you have to be signed up for that I
hope you are truly
sometimes we start to experience a few
feelings when we take away Comfort Foods
because we were using those Comfort
foods to suppress and bury deep down
inside
Who stuff it down we're in pain we're
struggling mentally and emotionally and
we need to shove those emotions in
constantly so we need those Comfort
foods to shove them in deep that's how
it's done Comfort Foods shove them in
deep
that old familiar sadness loneliness
fear shame guilt
anybody yeah it just hits everybody
the sadness the loneliness the fear the
shame the guilt or anger
starts to cast a shadow over our
thoughts we remove that food
that was shoving it deep down inside
that emotional pain
we've removed that food and then anger
can Surface anger can get triggered
anger can steep up and start to take
over
that has that ever happened to any of
you guys because you take away those
Comfort Foods especially if you're
taking away this Comfort foods and you
don't have something really healing
really nutritious really
fortifiable for the brain if you don't
have that then we get in trouble
especially we get in trouble then
hmm
hopefully you don't mind
a little sip here
so even anger can start to Shadow over
our thoughts or even creeps in as a
sinking in the stomach or tightness in
the chest and in that moment the
pleasures of pizza or mac and cheese or
ice cream seem the perfect antidote it's
like when something starts creeping up
something is percolating up something
emotional is coming out of that Lion's
Den out of that Dragon's Cave and when
it starts to come up
we gotta shove it back in we better get
the macaroni and cheese out we better
get the pizza out and ready we better
get the chocolate cake going we better
get the chocolate going the cacao we
better get our favorite protein bars
chocolate bars candy bars that are all
natural filled with a whole bunch of
crap and garbage we just better get
whatever it is we better get stuff in us
that comfort food and shove it down deep
because that dragon's coming out of the
cave and it's surfacing and it's coming
out of there guys I'm reading how to
cleanse the heel
talking about cleansing because
cleansing and detoxing is critical in
the summer it's summer time perfect time
to do it you're not freezing your ass
off
and it's summertime unless you're on the
other opposite side of the planet and
you're cold but still it's a good time
to do it then too
it's a really good time
I say trying to suppress because
does eating really suppress emotions
does eating all those Comfort Foods
really suppress the emotions
or is it like a temporarily we shove it
down but does it truly suppress it all
because it comes back again and then we
need the Comfort foods to shove it back
down and then it comes back up again and
we need the Comfort foods to shove it
back down and what if you're somebody
where you're doing the Comfort foods and
it's not really working and the emotions
are just kicking in the gear and you
can't shove it down anymore and it seems
to be coming up right the wild blueberry
babe says no quick fix exactly so it
just keeps on percolating keeps on
coming out and we try to push it back
down
so I say trying to suppress
because does eating really suppress
emotions only temporarily are you
reading that did you see that
page 446 and cleanse the heel only
temporarily it says right there there
you go emotional liver
live a rescue I think I got live rescue
behind me right here
and is suppression the real goal do we
want to suppress it do we want to shove
down those emotions do we want to try to
keep it all down do you want to keep
that pipe from exploding
do we want
to keep that hurt down
deep
in is suppression the real goal probably
not healing is the real goal true
emotional suppression can happen
sometimes when you've been harmed and
the adrenaline that Harbors the pain of
the trauma gets stored deep in the
neurons of the emotional centers of the
brain that's usually not a bad thing
emotional walls exist to protect us I
want to talk about that for a little bit
here I am cleanser heal you guys I saw
somebody ask what book is it what page
446 and cleanse the heel
so as we stuff things down
to try to suppress the pain
and push down that emotional hurt
and we eat our comfort foods to try to
keep it shoved down
it still creeps back up
because suppressing it with Comfort
Foods isn't the answer
but it's a really hard hard time Rooney
says where do I sign up I think you sign
up and Link is in the description if I'm
not mistaken
sign up to collecting Stones meditation
Journey today's day one of a seven day
experience you guys are not gonna forget
if you didn't receive a video yet hang
in there it will be coming if you didn't
receive one yet
emotional walls exist to protect us
other than this truly suppressed trauma
though pain tends to resurface when we
start thinking about it again we feel
that urge to eat certain foods again
I'm keeping myself distracted
I'm eating
a nice big bowl
of macaroni and cheese
the cheese has got kind of burnt on top
a little bit so it's nice and brown and
crispy on top
just the way I like it
took it out of the oven
it's this tasty cheesy macaroni kind of
a burnt topping crack into it with a
fork
I'm keeping myself distracted this is
helping me emotionally in the moment
it's helping me
keep down that Dragon I've been hurt
I've been hurt bad
I had a bad day
I'm tired
crack open
that cheesy surface with the fork get
that mac and cheese in my system
then the pain starts resurface again
we start thinking about that pain and
that suffering again I'm not
being distracted enough again I need a
slice of pizza now
when we start thinking about food again
okay you guys I want to just interrupt
for a second we will be posting a link
to the help desk on all social media
platforms if anyone is having trouble
that signed up to the collecting Stones
meditation journey I hope you got that
little note I just read
on IG I am registered since first
announcement
but I didn't get an email or something
for login or a link
over there on IG
we will be posting I got an answer for
that we will be posting a link to the
help desk on all social media platforms
if anyone is having trouble that's
signed up to the collecting Stones
meditation journey and you're you're
lost in the moment
when we start feeling or thinking about
that hurt again that trigger again
we want to eat certain foods again and
that can keep happening over and over
again if we don't know which foods can
actually help our bodies heal while
we're going through emotional hardships
and I get it we can eat ourselves sick
when we're going through some hardships
now remember this is the school of
eating when you have a trigger this is
the school of eating Comfort Foods when
you have a hardship I'm not in the other
school yet so we'll get there too
and I realized that when we're in this
school of eating a lot of foods to
shove down emotional pain emotional
sorrow when we're using food as a drug
we're using food as a drug to shove it
down deep inside when we're in that
position we can eat ourselves sick where
the food we can't even get enough food
in us anymore to kind of numb things up
or help it out because their stomachs
can't handle any more food how many
people go through that delete a whole
cheese pizza or pepperoni cheese pizza
and they're stuffed they can't even
breathe but then their mind is on how
stuffed they are but if that trigger
starts happening again they're kind of
stuck because they can't go and eat a
whole nother cheese pizza to shove it
down and shove those emotions down
because their stomach is so full so
they're in this weird lull it's torture
for a lot of people
one of the reasons we consume Comfort
Foods in the first place is to sop up
the adrenaline that comes with emotional
disturbances and conflicts and I just
want to say that we don't know that
we don't know that I mean that's medical
meme info but people don't know that's
what's happening
where we don't know we're consuming
Comfort Foods in the first place to stop
up adrenaline nobody ever knew that I
mean that's medical meme info it's in
the books but nobody knew that that
that's what we're doing
but that's what we're doing that's one
of these innate Instincts by the way
because when you go through a hardship
in a difficult time you get an
adrenaline explosion
or implosion
which you get an adrenaline
surge
and when that surge happens it's
floating around through your bloodstream
it's throat floating around in your
organs it's hitting your brain and it's
got all kinds of information in there
that I was talking about that
information if I was hurt that trust was
broken I was let down I was betrayed
something happened to me something's
wrong I'm upset again I was triggered
that was a terrible argument I just got
into with with someone that's my partner
my friend I'm in a relationship whatever
it is that's happening
that adrenaline is coursing through your
system and coursing through your system
and then we actually take food and don't
realize it we don't realize that this is
part of an innate innate instinct is we
take food and we eat it because we're
actually trying not just because we're
hungry we're eating it because we're
trying to sop up the adrenaline surge
toxic adrenaline that has so much
information in it
traditional Comfort Foods think tacos
nachos Pizza mac and cheese ice cream
spaghetti with meatballs pancakes french
fries Lobster with butter
chicken wings pulled pork sandwiches
now I've never had a pulled pork
sandwich
ever in my life
and anytime I like hear somebody had one
or someone ate one or there's there's
one on some kind of thing on social
media or something and some chefs making
a pulled pork sandwich and I mean I
can't eat that I just can't do it you
know there's something about it I can't
eat a pulled pork sandwich I just can't
but I'm but I'm not shaming anybody that
can or anybody that does and I'm not
making fun of anybody that does and I'm
not judging anybody that does but every
time I always think pancreatitis you
know every time I see somebody playing
with pork or eating a pulled pork
sandwich or something like that all I
think of is pancreatitis it's like
pulled pork pancreatitis pulled pork
sandwiches pancreatitis
grilled cheese fried eggs are usually
high in fat that fat is what's
soaking
stuff up the fat is what's doing the
sopping up so here's what's happening
you get some bad news you got triggered
or you're just in a mode and you got
triggered somehow some way you got PTSD
and you got triggered
someone could easily have some PTSD and
they get triggered so now we're
triggered so now our adrenal is surging
it's coursing through our veins and our
organs and as that adrenaline is
coursing through our veins and organs
it's got information in it that's hurt
we're hurt fear
guilt shame anger all coursing through
our veins and then we go and we take
something that's greasy or fried and we
want to sop it up we don't know that's
what we're doing but we're innately
trying to stop up the adrenaline
and that's part of the whole suppressing
emotions that's going on that's part of
the whole eating to suppress eating to
shove it down deep inside that's all
part of it right there
so when we're doing traditional Comfort
Foods now you might be a vegan and
you're shoving it down with all kinds of
you know crazy nut butter concoctions
and donuts and cakes that are vegan
donuts and cakes filled with canola oil
and all this garbage right you might be
somebody that's shoving it you might be
a vegan or a plant-based person and
you're shoving it down with uh a vegan
bar or shoving it down with a chocolate
bar
all that cacao all that fat to sop up
that adrenaline because you're triggered
so you're trying to sop up all that
adrenaline so maybe you're somebody
that's like well I do healthier stuff I
like to have my cooking and ice cream
when I'm in a bad mood or I'm triggered
or got some PTSD let me go get some
coconut ice cream you know I don't do
lactose
but still we use it and we're shoving it
down and we're trying to sop up all that
adrenaline quick little Interruption
here the collecting Stones meditation
Journey emails are coming
from Hay House
not MediCal medium some people might be
getting confused looking for medical
medium and not Hay House emails I just
wanted to give you that quick update for
anybody
so when we're trying to shove stuff down
and it's not the more vegan or
plant-based options or something like
that that still may not be good for us
we shove it down with tacos and nachos
and pizza mac and cheese ice cream
spaghetti meatballs pancakes french
fries Lobster and butter I don't know I
guess some people will do Lobster and
butter right chicken wings chicken wings
people definitely
fried chicken wings
they definitely shove those emotion down
down with chicken wings no question
right buffalo chicken wings pulled pork
sandwiches pancreatitis
grilled cheese fried eggs they're
usually high in fat that fat is what's
doing the sopping up the fat coursing
through your veins and bloodstream
are sopping up
boom
Vicky Woody says thank you about hay
house I was going crazy to check Hay
House emails because Hay House emails
right now
are you know because they're hosting the
event with me right
Marlo 333 is there supposed to be live
meditation with the email I only saw
video nope it's a video a day
video a day
but I am here live right now talking
about it we're talking about other
things too
someone said hummus
yeah hummus with all that tahini in
there and olive oil in it to sop it up
so maybe you're a plant-based person and
you're sopping it up
those emotions
loving healing says once I accept it
that detox was going to be emotional it
helped ride the waves and finally push
forward with healing foods
amen that was really a really
interesting and spot on
Ro says
was hospitalized to pancreatitis twice
I'm so sorry to hear that and I believe
you were of course because a lot of
people that happens to them and I'm so
sorry you've gone through that
here's the key point
the fat cells trap the adrenaline the
adrenaline has emotions in it from what
you're going through your PTSD and
everything else
and with that
your adrenaline then gets trapped in the
fat cells and all the different fat that
gets stored up into organs
in the case of adrenaline that was
released at a highly emotional time
it holds information about the fear hurt
betrayal injury or stress overload we
were experiencing in that moment what
I'm trying to say is I'll just break it
down right here
I'll break it down right here
we get hurt
we have an emotional adrenaline surge
we might be experiencing some type or
form of chaos emotional chaos of some in
some way fear
anger all of it
adrenaline's floating around in our
bloodstream
coursing through our veins
we have this innate response
of shooting for a comfort food grabbing
a comfort food that's high in fat most
definitely and high in sugar a lot of
times it's not the sugar
but it's the high fat content that
really
stops up the adrenaline we eat that high
fatty food it soaks up the adrenaline
and then stores it deep in her organs
with the information of that hurt when
we cleanse
it comes out
some people don't eat when trauma
happens and I'm about to get to that
that's the second School we're about to
read and they eat and they grab Comfort
Foods at some point when it's later on
down the road because they have to eat
at some point so they have hurt they
have pain they have fear they're
triggered they got the PTSD and they
don't eat they've got the spigot off
they shut the spigot off and that's off
and then they don't eat but they gotta
eat eventually
let's see joking
says I am discouraged I receive so much
acne after the cleanse I know I should
continue but I am not happy because
first I had it hadn't it and now I have
it a lot so I'll give you a couple
little rundowns on that first of all
um
what cleanse are you even doing what's
going on in there many things could be
happening could have had exposure at
some point when people say they did the
cleanse I've had situations where it's
not even a medical meme cleanse that
we're doing a lot of people just are
just doing somebody's cleanse is that
something to know were you doing a
cleanse plus a whole bunch of different
other stuff were you doing a cleanse and
a whole bunch of different supplements
that were filled with all this garbage
which cleanse were you even doing was it
out of a medical medium book were you
eating something before the cleanse that
was crazy were you eating something
right after the cleanse that was crazy
it there's so many different aspects it
can go you can go on and on and on did
you get a recent bacterial exposure to
kick up the acne did the acne get
triggered by something else from some
other exposure that you were
susceptible to or mean or exposed to it
the list goes on so we have to be a
detective we have to understand the
books and the information and be a
detective understand what we're doing
some people before they go on a cleanse
they trash themselves with a ton of
crazy food and I can't be a fly on the
wall in everybody's house and
everybody's bathroom
but I do know this that a lot of people
before they embark on a cleanse
eat the out of a bunch of comfort
food that comfort food gets in their
liver it gets in their bloodstream in
their lymphatic system it feeds all
kinds of bacteria all kinds of other
pathogen matter then you go on the
cleanse but yet all that stuff is
sitting there feeding bugs so you might
have to do you know ask your doctor
what's right for you but you might have
to do another cleanse you might have to
do another one with it and then did you
look at protocols as you look at
protocols with acne did you look at the
supplementation protocols and read about
that because when you're dealing with
acne or dealing with pathogens did you
have any recent antibiotic use out there
I'm saying this to everybody overall
blankets for everybody blanket statement
for everybody did you use any
antibiotics for something recently
because strep is antibiotic resistant it
goes down from antibiotics and then it
goes back up stronger than ever and
that's how it works
um or was your body killing off so much
stress so much strep was your body
killing and eliminating so much strep
while you were cleansing and then you
had just all the toxic crap coming out
the strap was fighting for its life so
it came out because you're actually
making a dent in it and cleaning it up
I'm trying to give people all the tips
right up front a whole bunch of them to
take a look at and see what's going on
yeah I mean it's so simple as that
including you know new relationships
from six months ago before you started
your cleanse where you were already
coming into a place where you were about
to get a new strep infection causing
acne and other symptoms maybe a new
relationship whole bit it's the whole
whole thing so all these things are
including including drinking off
somebody else's glasses eating off of
somebody else's plates but in all of
that okay or like were you careful with
the grocery cart handles because I'm
going to tell you right now there's at
least at least 50 different varieties of
strep these days these days right now on
grocery store cart handles
so I would use a white bee on that
grocery store card handle just a minute
you even get up to it I would never go
up to it and just grab it and be like
hey I'm a warrior doesn't even matter
boom boom boom Going Through the store
or whatever scratch your face hit your
eye get your car keys out whatever do
this and this and this and then boom you
just got two more varieties of
streptococcus streptococcal and strip
might be someone who needs to get off of
grains and chocolate as well they could
be doing that while they're cleansing
they could be cleansing and doing
chocolate while they're cleansing I
can't be the fly on the wall but I wish
I had my flat on the wall friend aw here
who usually does fly in the wall stuff
for you guys which we will do Again
David witch and says do fly on the wall
soon again
yeah
indeed
see Lila Collins I took my time cutting
out fats five years later all I have is
celery juice smoothies raw foods fruits
and vegetables with beverages
supplements you can do it too which
means it's really helping you
so
all this stuff is important to know keep
that in mind
um just gave you a rundown on so many
different aspects of what's going on
of how it works you literally could be
coming down with a new variety of strep
you picked up three months ago and the
cleansing is critical because it's
helping to get it out you can also be in
a place where you fed it prior you can
also be in a place where you're actually
cleansing out old antibiotics in your
system for from 15 years ago 10 years
ago from when you took antibiotics for
strep infections for strep throat and
acne and that's coming out of your liver
so that can be a whole other aspect of
it but either way it for everybody
people got different situations stubborn
strep bacteria are like super bugs and
they can take a lot of strong protocols
for a while to get rid of them it takes
time for a lot of people here's another
thing everybody's acne is different
because everybody's acne isn't the same
strip
keep that in mind too that's a big one
right there someone can have such a
stubborn strep that takes time and
protocols
because it's so antibiotic resistant or
so stubborn there's so many strains
there's hundreds and hundreds of strains
of strep and someone can have multiple
strains of strep and this is critical to
know right here since we're on this
topic because I want to help out like
this stuff too not just the emotional
aspect but the physical aspect with
things and I just want to say
that you can be some you can have
someone you can have two different
people with two different forms of acne
nobody even knows the difference so one
person has one antibiotic stubborn
really really mean mean ass strep and
then another person it's not so stubborn
it's not so antibiotic resistant or
resistant to things and doesn't take too
much to clean it up another person could
have more strep in their lymphatic
system and less in their lymphatic
system the next person more strep in
your liver and the other person with
acne has less strep in their liver so
that's a whole other thing too the
different amounts and all that and you
can pick up a strap from somebody else
who took 20 antibiotics and that strep
was stubborn as heck and then you got
that same variety and that happens to
people a lot a lot of people get into
relationships and the person that got
into a relationship with has a stubborn
strep that they took antibiotics for 10
years for one that was giving them UTIs
and then they picked up that strep from
that person and now they have that that
strap in their system that's that's um
immune to 20 antibiotics and it's
stubborn so
oh dear lord
somebody could have a strep that's been
in 20 other people who took a hundred
antibiotics
and that
can happen too so I hate to say this but
someone
can be in a strap that was in
20 people
and 100 antibiotics it's that crazy how
it works so
before we go down the rabbit hole with
this
what it is is these things we can move
out of our body we can cleanse out and
we can beat out because we can starve
these bacteria and pathogens
we can starve them if we take away the
food that the pathogens like which is
medical medium information because guess
what nobody knew
pathogens like bacteria actually ate
anything and now you see how much people
how many people in the industry poached
medical medium information about that
acne is bacterial it's not hormones you
got acne you have bacteria causing it
so all good information we just ran
across a whole strap thing just now
Nicole says I need help with chocolate
I'm addicted
I understand completely it's it's not an
easy one chocolate is one of those
things where the caffeine has everybody
so jacked up once you come off that
caffeine ride it's intense really
intense and by the way there's an acne
protocol in cleanse the heel
good good good
Sarah
my fiance my fiance has cellulitis
two rounds of antibiotics and no relief
I started him on celery juice boom gone
Sarah incredible and that proves
something very important right there I
always say
everybody's different
their exposures what they have in them
and everything else so your fiance only
needed celery juice
to get rid of cellulitis
that's incredible I always say that some
people only need celery juice just to
get rid of one thing by the way I'm in
Clinton Hill you guys if you don't have
the book you're missing out
it's
by far
one of the most powerful books in health
out there in the world today
Millions
have gotten this book in their hands and
moved themselves forward and got rid of
some of the most
crippling conditions
okay
let's roll a little bit
once the fat has soaked up the
adrenaline the stress hormone becomes
trapped in our fat cells fat cells that
then become part of us as they take up
residents inside our organs so we got
this adrenaline that's taking up
residence because it's in a fat cell
it's building up inner organs and
there's information of fear and shame
and guilt and chaos and triggers and
PTSD all wrapped up in there and that's
how cleansing how critical cleansing is
to help get rid of and push that out of
our body how incredible is that
Kim Miller I get sick every time I'm in
a new relationship I always wondered why
there's yeah there's so much involved in
that but we can't be afraid of a new
relationship we can't be afraid
of being with people of seeking love and
finding partnership and partners we
can't be afraid of that we have to live
our lives people have to live their
lives
there's a soul mate waiting for someone
who doesn't already have one
all important things but knowing what to
do if you get sick because you find this
most amazing person in the world and you
get sick but you can do something
health-wise
and you can make a choice on how to heal
yourself but knowing what you're up
against health-wise is good idea too to
make a choice as well it's like okay
I know what I'm up against I can do
things there's things I can do for
myself
here's the key Point adrenaline holds
information in the case of adrenaline
that was released at highly emotional
times it holds information about fear
hurt betrayal injury or stress overload
we experience in that moment so I know I
was I was saying that anyway
you guys today is day one of the medical
medium collecting Stones meditation
Journey
I hope you're signed up it's going to be
an incredible seven days
you're never gonna forget it it's going
to be life-changing
Cold Light spring says I'm perfectly
fine with being afraid of a new
relationship laugh out loud
um
Brett Winters
how are you Brett
eating fat releases adrenaline to thin
out our blood but it also soaks up
adrenaline explain indeed so you're
talking about medical meme information
so what happens is that when we eat a
lot of fat
it takes adrenaline to try to become a
blood thinner for that fat so if you're
eating tacos load it with you know
greasy fat you're eating pizzas you're
eating fried or you're eating buffalo
chicken wings
in a bar somewhere whatever you're
eating these things
you're eating pulled pork sandwiches
mac and cheese whatever it is all that
fat that butter or that oil that grease
that animal fat or plant fat too A lot
of people take a ton of plant fat right
so all of that fat
is there we innately eat all of that to
sop up
the adrenaline
right that's the Comfort zop up
but Brett at the same time all that fat
we're eating is releasing adrenaline
to try to blood thin it so to try to do
like a blood thinner so we don't get a
heart attack so we don't stroke out so
we don't get a a clog
so we can get oxygen to our brain
because the more fat we eat the less
oxygen we get to our brain
mm info
I have to say that now
imagine that
the world we've we now live in okay
so when that happens
that occurs too so it's a vicious cycle
it's a catch-22 exactly that but keep in
mind this
when we're not going through an
emotional hardship we're not going
through a stress moment or a big Trigger
or PTSD everybody is still eating fat
because they're addicted to the
adrenaline cycle the adren adrenaline
surge so they can't break away from all
that cacao
that fatty cacao they can't break away
from those cupcakes and the donuts they
can't break away from the vegan donuts
and vegan cupcakes and the pizzas and
the vegan pizzas they love the vegan
pizzas because they're loaded with oil
there's no fat free vegan pizza in a
restaurant
excuse me um
I see you offer vegan pizzas here in the
restaurant yeah I am a person who would
really like a vegan pizza right now I
have been plant-based for a while and I
want a treat so I'm going to get myself
a big vegan pizza oh
um I'm sorry can you make that vegan
pizza fat free
I'm sorry excuse me fat free what does
that mean
um your pizzas aren't fat free
huh what um okay well
um make sure there's no vegan cheese on
there because vegan cheese is filled
with fat do you have vegan cheese on the
pizza oh you do whoa okay then there's
your fat wait olive oil's on your pizza
too you drizzle it with olive oil oh
there's more fat on that pizza wait a
minute you have a crust that has what in
it oh and there's more of that too
so either way we might be in the
situation where like I'm hankering for
that vegan pizza because I want to do a
fat bomb drop it into my bloodstream and
then I don't know it and I have no idea
but I'm gonna have an adrenaline surge
baby and it's going to be an adrenaline
High because whoa right before I bite
into this vegan pizza I've been waiting
to eat for the last two months right
before I even bite into this baby
I'm having an adrenaline happy place
already like whoa I can smell it here it
is it's coming to the table I'm in a
vegan restaurant right now here it is
they dropped the pizza right in front of
me I don't have my pizza prop with me
right here they drop a pizza right there
in front of me
and I'm already like I'm feeling a high
already my adrenaline is actually
running I'm feeling a surge
do you guys know this well anybody know
this and then I'm gonna eat that fatty
cheese pizza even if it's a vegan pizza
maybe you don't want a vegan pizza it's
a regular pizza with regular cheese on
it and regular oil regular whatever and
you're actually
oh whatever it's not pepperonis on there
right all the fat in the pepperoni
but you're eating that pizza and you're
getting a high you're getting totally
jacked
totally jacked on the fat because you're
getting jacked on the fat High which is
the adrenaline high and that's mm info
you know what's crazy mm info putting
out original info all the time in these
incredible books and you see influencers
out there steal it and act like it was
out there already when it didn't even
exist right it comes from these books
they steal it they don't cite it
it's like what makes a person do that
please tell me somebody is that an
Integrity issue
it takes time getting off the addictions
getting off of the the MSG in foods
the MSG in restaurant Foods the high
levels of salt the chemicals in foods
and the coffees and the coffee drinks
takes time to reset the taste buds
it takes time
of course you're going to be happy and
high when you eat those Foods you're
going to be really high
and they just taste so good in the
moment
it's not the same at home in the
restaurant they're packing it with MSG
too when you go out and get your vegan
pizza things loaded with MSG you just
don't know it but it's loaded versus
when you're at home and you're making
steamed potatoes
and you're like well I got my steamed
potato dish from medical mediums book I
got this I like my steamed potato dish
but it's not the same thing as when I
was with my friend and I was in a vegan
restaurant and we had those vegan cheese
pizzas and damn that was good tasted so
good whoa was incredible
you ever wonder why Foods don't taste
the same
when you're making them at home versus
when you're in restaurants or eating out
of packages food packages they're laced
with undisclosed ingredients all the
time
fact
all right you guys for having fun we're
talking about a lot of different topics
here let's see if we can cut through a
little bit more of this I just want to
make an announcement it is day one
day one
of the medical meme collecting Stones
meditation Journey
day one
I'm really excited
Max wood says
Max von says if I have to eat restaurant
food now it tastes so salty over there
on YouTube
totally get it totally get it
the minute we start taking away these
Comfort foods such as when we're on one
of the cleanses inside of cleanse the
heel book
Incredible Book
I don't know which ones are my favorite
the brain saver books are my favorite
medical medium New Edition we're
collecting Stones meditation journey is
and then cleanseal all of them are
thyroid healing life-changing Foods
Banna says after suffering from severe
acne I am finally much better following
medical medium morning cleanse even not
a hundred percent
now I want to be fully raw I am afraid
of detoxing in the form
of acne what can I do about it
okay we can't live in fear
it's just part of being here on planet
mess
part of being here in plant stress
planet Earth
okay we can't live in fear right moving
forward with our health and doing the
right things
is always important to do
and we can't be afraid
but if you're doing the morning cleanse
and you're getting relief incredible
then that's what you do
there's nothing wrong with that you can
go slower you can do it in with an ease
you can add little things in at a time
when you read the medical medium books
you can talk to your doctor too about
what you feel is good or your doctor
feels as good I mean but you can take it
baby steps you can just do morning
cleanses and morning cleanses it is and
only that and that's all you do that's
fine
and if things are in a great place
because of that then that's where you
are
so yeah
and a lot of a lot of times with acne a
lot of people they're just trapped in it
and they have to push through to get to
the other side takes time for a lot of
different people but a lot of people it
could just be like yeah you're doing
that one thing celery juice or a morning
cleanse and that's what you're doing and
you're in a good place
note not everything is detox too I I
apologize by the way that I haven't
gotten the medical medium Detox episode
out on the medical meme podcast
letting you know I've been working on it
I have I have
and I'm going to work on a lot of
episodes too with medical meme podcasts
just mind-blowing stuff
like for the next few months like
seriously some great stuff
what happens is if you have strep
bacteria a lot of times when people
cleanse
that strep is dying off that strep is
actually clearing out of the system it's
moving out of your system you're
starving that strep
but a lot of times you know acne can be
a detox
in the sense where if you're killing off
a whole bunch of it
keep that in mind so a lot of people
I've seen where and straps a really good
topic right now a lot of people they'll
have three or four or even 10 varieties
of strep in their system they're just
loaded it's all through their intestinal
tract
I just riddled in their intestinal tract
it's in their liver it's all in their
lymphatic system they got acne on their
chest they got acne on their back acne
on their neck they got acne on their
temples they acne on their face their
nose are just loaded with acne they got
a lot of strep in them they got
um antibiotic resistant varieties of
acne in them and the minute you start
dumping stuff in there to just keep
basically you're killing off the strep
there's a lot of toxins coming from the
bacterias as you know as it's also
exploding that can happen too if
someone's so fully loaded what I mean so
fully loaded people got diverticulosis
diverticulitis they got styes they got
UTIs constantly there's people out there
though
literally shrep is running their whole
life and we got to push it out of them
if you have strep bacteria
you'll have acne at some point in your
life that's not detox it's just a
symptom of strep bacteria
you will get acne one day if you have
strep we can't blame everything on detox
that gets people in trouble it does get
people in trouble when we blame
everything on detox too well a lot of
people don't realize if they have strep
they'll have acne at some point in their
life if they have strep so that that's
important to keep in mind too but there
is this thing
as I was saying before if someone's so
loaded with so many varieties
and now we're pulling Foods away from
that strep
and we're releasing all that old stored
up antibiotics that they took for years
that's in their liver and we're moving
all this stuff about
yeah I mean they can they can just be
sitting there with their acne that
they've had all along until it finally
starts clearing up blaming everything
though on detox
came outside of the medical medium
community
people who don't know what the true
causes of their symptoms and conditions
are
that's an important note for anybody
who's paying attention anybody who's
listening that's a really critical note
right there blaming everything on detox
is not a medical medium Community thing
or medical medium books and information
thing I think everything's just blamed
on detox oh that's detox oh what's that
that's detox oh that's detox first of
all
that's just not correct the correct way
it should be handled
that's just a term a blanket statement
and term that was created because people
don't know why people are sick and
what's wrong with them and that came
from outside of the community
that's where that came from from people
that did not know influencers or whoever
are practitioners that did not know why
someone had a symptom or condition so
they'll start blaming everything about
detox Pathways that are being clogged
they'll be like oh that's because your
detox pathways are being clogged that's
because you don't know your detox
Pathways really do you know your detox
pathways
you know acne for example acne is not
because your detox pathways are clogged
it's because you have strep
all this is important information for so
many people that are looking for this
these tidbits
as I see out there people do ask about
it I've seen a lot of questions
so keep in mind the whole blame
everything on detox is not a medical
medium thing if you read all eight
medical textbooks
you're not going to see riddled all
through these eight medical textbooks
that everything's detox and everything
everything is detox just blame
everything on there blame that symptom
that condition on detox you're not going
to see that you look through the
symptoms and conditions of all these
diseases and symptoms right of all these
conditions and illnesses and sicknesses
in these books you don't see a blanket
thing oh that's detox oh that's detox
nerve pain isn't your detox Pathways
clogged
it's viral it's injuries it's all kinds
of stuff but it's not your detox
Pathways clogged I'm giving you just a
little tidbit of what would be in the
medical medium detox
podcast
don't mind I am going to sip a little
bit here
okay
let's also not forget about the other
school of emotions and eating I just
want to cover the other school because I
feel bad I only covered the first school
the one school can I cover the other
school do we do we have time to do this
get ready for this
on IG acne also can be caused by thick
bile sludge check about it
really because science doesn't know that
research doesn't know that
there's nothing out there there's no
there's no study
there's no microscope anybody stuck up
somebody's ass or a microscope that they
stuck in somebody's throat or a
microscope they stuck into their body
and into their veins or down into the
liver that said oh thick bile that must
be why you have acne that doesn't exist
so there's that's just made up because
there's no signs of research this has
ever discovered that that could be why
acne really is
acne is instead an actual infection
so keep that in mind it's it's an
infection it's like a pushed wall an
actual infection
it's an infection
it's not thick bile or anything like
that
so I just want to cover that
let's also not forget about the other
school of emotions and eating in this
school are folks who prefer to avoid
food when they're in pain emotionally
so they avoid the food they're not
running to comfort Foods they're not
shoving down a pizza they're not pushing
something deep down inside
so this is a group of people that shut
off the spigot they're just like no I'm
not gonna eat I'm not gonna eat
in this school are folks who prefer to
avoid food when they're in emotional
pain often triggered because their
emotions have taken away their appetite
or made them feel sick I'm so sick from
that betrayal oh my God I'm sick I gotta
pull this knife out of my back
and
I just can't eat right now I'm so
disgusted I'm so upset I'm so angry I'm
so emotional I'm in so much pain
emotionally I can't handle it I can't
eat there's no way I'm putting food in
my stomach right now there's no freaking
way I'm ever gonna stick food in my
stomach right now when I'm upset
this approach can turn into an addiction
to having no appetite it can I've seen a
lot of people they're emotionally hit
every minute every which way and they
just can't eat
so it becomes an addiction
to not eat
over there in IG yes that's me I stop
eating
um start the Gypsy medium
and then Rainbow Bright says so there is
no detox acne just an ongoing infection
correct
yes it's always because of strep if you
are cleansing it
there can be some die off but it's
caused by strep either way
I can't tell you how many people have
used mm info completely I've gotten rid
of their strep debilitating strep
covered their whole body
gotten rid of it
use the protocols made sure they weren't
feeding it with the the you know the
foods that will feed it right making
sure they do all that and then they get
into a new relationship
they pick up a brand new strap or two
and they start getting some other form
of acne
and then they have to do it again have
to clean up and make sure you know
they're fighting to clean it up and do
the right protocols and boom get rid of
it
journey sg1 I am going to read
that comment there
acne is also said to be hormones yes
it's said to be hormones no it's not
hormones now there's going to be a bunch
of people that say okay that he just
lost me there he lost me it's hormones
hormones hormones hormones hormones
people don't realize is that strep Ebbs
and flows with the immune system
and so with women their immune system
drops during their cycle it drops during
menstruation it drops during ovulation
it drops during pregnancies and
childbirth it drops monthly
it drops during puberty with
um
with both both and what happened here's
what's important so here's what's
interesting
anytime there's an anytime there is a
hormone change
keep that in mind
whether it's puberty or menstruation or
ovulation
or something happening
hormonally right a hormonal change the
immune system drops and for women the
immune system drops
keep that in mind
the Divine list says blaming hormone is
propaganda to make women blame
themselves that's true
into the wild Blues yep I also break out
with acne when I'm sick
yep I always break out with acne when
I'm sick
so what happens is that we break out
with acne because when we're sick the
immune system drops and then strep Rises
up very important to know that like
that's how it works strep is always an
infection
it's always inside our body living in
our body it's an ongoing strep infection
when we when our immune system is
compromised like say betrayal or an
adrenaline surge because we're totally
stressed out from something
yeah adrenaline hormonal immune system
drops
strep acts up and Rises
menstruation
immune system drops in women strep Rises
up so that's why there was a connect the
dots
from mainstream medicine
mainstream medicine said that acne is
caused by hormones mainstream medicine
was only noting that it happened to a
lot of people when there was a hormone
shift
acne rose up but did not know why
because the immune system drops and then
strep gets stronger
so much information
I can't stop myself I said it keeps on
coming out
yeah
okay
so there's a whole bunch of people that
literally say my life is out of control
my life is out of control I just my PTSD
is out of control I just got hurt again
my trust was broken I was betrayed
I just got into a confrontation I just
people don't understand me I'm not
understood I'm not validated no one
understands me
I'm not going to eat because guess what
I can't control other people and I can't
control the crap happening to me and I
can't control the difficult time I'm in
I can't control the relationship that
was you know my boyfriend just broke up
with me or my girlfriend just broke up
with me I can't control any of it so
what I can control is food
so if I can't control anything else I'm
definitely not eating because I will
definitely not eat because I will
control my eating I will control my food
I am going to use that
I'm sick I don't want to eat I'm sick of
my stomach I don't want to eat so I am
now going to be like no I can't control
anything else out there so I'm going to
control my food
they already feel that they don't have
control over their environment or
situations happening around them or
people in their life and so whether
consciously or subconsciously they try
to exert extreme control over what they
put into their mouths
people from the other school those who
overeat often struggle with loss of
control too they happen to have a
different way of dealing with the
sensation for those who withhold food
while food cravings may still surface
and surface intensely they're even
stronger craving is not to eat or to eat
very little that's what they do to try
to hold control and maintain control one
doesn't always stay in this path or
pattern forever sometimes hunger can
become so overpowering because the body
can only function for so long with
adrenaline filling the critically needed
blood sugar
to the point that somebody ends up
switching over to the other schools so
the school switch the schools switch a
lot they switch a lot
eating a lot when I get hurt emotionally
switches to not eating at all
eating not at all switches to eating
emotionally eating a lot of it a lot of
things emotionally switching it on and
off
very good
so
you guys today's day one seven day
medical medium collecting Stones
meditation Journey
it's a free Journey please if you
haven't signed up sign sign up
okay
it's going to be an incredible credible
seven days
I have these feelings inside of me
of joy
of Happiness of excitement of Mystery
all of it
because I know what's going to happen
when you guys do the seven day
collecting Stones meditation Journey
I know you're going to have an
experience
and it's going to be extremely special
and you're never going to forget it
anyway
thank you guys for today for being here
and letting me
read and talk about a bunch of different
things cleanse a heel
get one if you don't have one
it's on sale
go to the library get it for free
okay
guys
I will see you
many blessings
and I'll see you guys soon