hated about this i got my celery stacked
up
sitting right here i know you guys might
not be able to see it but there it is
and i got lots of celery back here too
so i'm really excited and i'll try to
answer some questions as i'm doing this
too
um just got letting you guys know you
know about the black friday sale so i
just didn't want anybody to
lose out on a chance to get the juicer
for the this is an incredible celery
juicer okay so just wanted you wanted to
make sure you had a chance to
maybe get it if you wanted to pick one
up um it's the mm-900
hds celery juicer that's the one
specifically it also juices everything
else too
hello hi alyssa great to see you glad
you're coming on here
hello from vienna awesome great michelle
l good to see you
awesome glad you guys are coming on
incredible
how you said hello to the cj king that's
funny
um you're making your glenda you're
making your batch now
40 ounces nice josh you're on here
great great so great um
so it's good to see you guys from
portugal too whoa
netherlands right on this is great
love to see you guys here it's awesome
greetings from germany
cool cool so i got the mm 900 hds right
here i'm gonna do
celery that's what i'm gonna do and i'm
gonna show you something it's really
cool because everybody's totally
freaking out about the pulp
thing about how virtually i had no pulp
and it was dry to the bone and i had
this much celery juice
and that's because this specific model
there's other models that look like this
from omega but it's not this
model this has a device here at the end
that actually makes it so it squeezes
almost
every last drop out of that celery so
it's saving money like this year alone i
know i saved a ton of money half the
celery cost
easy half the celery cost so i'm not
throwing away my
my my celery juice through the pulp and
stuff or whatever discarding it or
throwing
throwing it in the garden or whatever
and then the juice goes with it
so what's amazing about this is this
machine is squeezing it out and i'm
going to show you how to i'm going to
show you how to do it and i'm going to
show you how the pulp works we're
literally it's just a handful of this
dry pull
i showed you guys the other day it was
insane i mean filled up with all the
celery juice and a little bit of pulp
good to see you guys glad you're here um
i think i'm gonna drink a little bit of
lemon balm tea for the moment because
i've been talking all morning
oh my god it never stops so glad you
guys
are coming on it's so easy to use and
clean did you see that this model is so
easy i just saw that comment
to use and clean it's it's unbelievable
so it's 60
off it's 20 percent 20 off black friday
sale omega
juicers.com link should be there
in the description so omega omega
juicers.com this is the mm-900
hds so the mm-900
hds celery juicer just letting you know
hello from finland cool cool so i'm
going to make some celery juice
i'm going to talk about the benefits too
you love yours jody
cool you're using one awesome that's
amazing
that's so good you guys it's worth it
because it saves money because that's
how i look at it to you it's like
this juicer right here has paid for
itself
so it's paid for itself that's what it's
done you know my other juicers that i've
had i have a closet full of a few of
them i have a garage full
of a bunch of them because i've tried
every juicer out there and
they don't pay for themselves and that's
what's crazy it's like i want a juicer
to actually
you know pay for itself to work for me
you know to work for me
and this one does it's crazy so you save
all that money
because you're squeezing every last drop
out of out of the celery
and it's a it's a big deal so it's
really cool so
um i'm gonna make sure you know gonna
show show you guys how it works going to
run it right now
juice a little bit can answer some
questions if i can too
so this is it right here
putting some celery in it as we speak
i'm just looking for my little plunger
it's uh running some now
is that juicer just for celery no it's
not angela
it's a celery juicer which is amazing
but you can juice anything in it because
it's not it's a top-notch juicer
like like the best in my opinion
personal opinion the best
so it's so great so i'm running some
celery right through it now
i gotta show you guys like the
difference with the pulp like what that
is how incredible that is hello from
ontario so
cool so if anybody just got on here now
um well that's a good question dr sebby
said celery was bad a hybrid thoughts
well first of all dr sebby was still
here
because i know he passed away if he was
still here and he saw what happened with
the celery juice movement
and he saw millions of people healing
and he saw tens of
thousands of healing stories people
getting out of wheelchairs
people getting their lives back acid
reflux going away
migraines going away difficult
menstruations going away
if he saw everything happening from
celery juice
i think he would change his mind because
i know he was theorizing because that's
what these guys do because there's no
there's no science that would state that
celery is bad
so he was theorizing that it was bad and
if he was alive today dr sebby
he would actually probably be bowing
down to celery juice because his
patients
would be coming in talking about how
it's saving their lives
like some of the other doctors out there
and stuff so that's how i kind of
look at it in that way plus when dr
sebby was here i was still here too i've
been doing this for 35 years
and and
i was already getting my people better
by the truckloads over the decades and
um and they were getting their lives
back from celery juice while
while he was telling people don't drink
it it's just really it just it's
unbelievable really
when you think about it so celery juice
has
shaped and changed chronic illness today
and when you think about how powerful
that is and how amazing that is it's
actually breathtaking like the results
so
[Music]
um i know you can't see it too easy
right you probably can't see it easy
i'll show you
i know someone's saying move camera down
i know it's difficult to get a good shot
today
so this is the i just saw a question why
do i feel like this is the best juicer
well
what it does is it's got a device on it
right
that squeezes all the juice out of
celery
i can't find a juicer on the market
that's ever done that
i've purchased them all so when i
purchased this
this one it was always the best juicer
company anyway but when they put the
device on it to make it just for celery
to get really squeeze that celery juice
out it changed everything
it was like okay well this is a miracle
because i'm saving a ton of money each
year
and that's that's a big deal celery
juice cured me from my debilitating
migraines michelle marie said
right i wonder what dr sebby would say
about that one
because he doesn't he didn't like celery
and it cured you of your debilitating
migraines
that's what i'm talking about that's
what i'm talking about that's
such a big deal that means everything
honestly that means everything
so you'll see pulp coming out right now
and this isn't just for celery you could
use anything in this juicer that's
what's incredible
that's what i love so i'm juicing a
little bit more i'm gonna put a couple
more pieces in right here
[Music]
[Applause]
so
i see it my husband learned in his
toxicology class celery
is celery is full filled with nitrates
not correct
sorry it's not correct i wrote a celery
juice book
all about that and i talked about that
in here everything about it and where
the confusion
fusion lies um that's in celery
powder for preserving things
and it they add nitrate to it so that's
only for the preserving factories for
preserving food
they they actually take celery powder
and they add nitrate
to it to try to preserve fish
so that's misinformation
i've i've actually seen
everything about that and then some
so i dispute it with facts
so here we go i got to show you guys
this this is incredible okay
this is just absolutely incredible check
this out right
seriously this blows my mind every time
if you guys ever juiced before
or juiced with other juicers you're
gonna know what this means right here
this is this is mind-blowing right okay
so
all right that's my celery juice okay
that's over 32 ounces all right that's
my celery juice right there
okay let's check this out okay that's
that
all right
look at this on my fingertips
do you see what i'm saying right here do
you see what i'm holding
and you ready it's a dry piece of rope
look at this it's a dry
piece of rope with no juice in it but
look at how tiny it is
look at this this little dry piece of
rope
that's the difference right there what
this is saving me money wise
each year because i juice like 60 ounces
40 ounces 100 ounces a day whatever i
just juice juice it
and and i know i know other people would
do the same
what this is saving us is unbelievable
this is dehydrated
it's there's no juice in it and it's
this tiny
little pulp look at that i'm not kidding
like
that's mind-blowing for all that
guess what there's no juicer on the
market that can do that i don't care
who's what how i've tried them all
and i love how they talk a good game
because they want to be like they don't
want
they don't want a mega you know actually
having such
an amazing amazing product because it's
competition out there so they'll talk a
good game
our juicer does just as good as a job no
it doesn't
no it doesn't this is the mm-900
hds celery juicer
i'm just telling you i i until this till
this day
this is this is unbelievable i keep on
thinking it's like a joke or something
i have i have the container and it's
this little piece
of dried rope with nothing in it
this tiny little piece of dried rope
right here
for this i mean honestly i'm gonna pour
it in and everything you guys
um celery has cured me of debilitating
migraines too
so cynthia says celery has cured you of
debilitating migraines too
oh my god amazing isn't that worth it
isn't that worth it how can i wash
non-organic celery you know what you
know what i do you guys
i i juice non-organic celery a lot if i
can't get the organic stuff
i'm always getting the non-organic for
celery always um
what i do is i wash right in here i make
sure my thumb goes in here
when i'm washing it and i actually do
this where i'm
i'm actually washing kind of scrubbing
this here
and i use a little tiny bit of natural
dish soap
in the bowl of water and i kind of rub
the sticks that's that's what you do
that's what i do i do it every other day
when i can't get it
um it's amazing my pulp is always full
of juice
deanna deanna this is really incredible
really
um jillian gray says what do you set
it on to get the dryness i have an omega
but it still comes
out quite wet i put the pulp through
again that's
well doing you have it omega but omega
has a bunch of juicers in and that's not
this one
this is the mm-900
hds celery juicer from omega
and it uses everything else too this is
an entirely different thing they did
this because you know they want it to
just
change people's lives with this i mean
no dry to the bone
i can't even tell you how i mean this is
this is unbelievable and it's only a
tiny bit
look at that tiny bit for this whole
thing right here so
um i'm going to actually pour it in i
mean honestly
every time i do it every morning
you're mind blown i mean seriously just
mind blown i use a strainer you gotta
strain
even though you just juiced it you
should still strain it
should still strain it that that's the
best way to do it there
it's still the best way to do glad it
guys are with me today i'm excited about
this so that's it
there okay
look at that okay incredible and i got
this dried out
little tiny bit of rope right here now
the difference is with that
is it can save me like
it's in the thousands at the end of the
year i buy so many cases of celery
and it cut the cost in half
just boom this juicer paid for itself
over and over
and over and over again and guess what
this isn't a 700 juicer
this isn't a thousand dollar juicer this
isn't like
a 1500 juicer or a 600 juicer
it's on sale it's 200 and something
dollars
it's it's it's black friday on top of it
it just doesn't
it just doesn't get any better than that
um
so uh natalie celery has fast-tracked my
healing from
graves disease thank you anthony natalie
thank you for doing it because when you
do it
it first of all you know when you
actually take that plunge and you're
doing your celery juice and you're
working on your healing process
you become a beacon of light for
everybody else
and and that's that's powerful powerful
because someone else is suffering and
struggling and boom
your word and you're you're you're doing
your work and all of a sudden
someone sees or hears about it and boom
you just you just change somebody's like
possibly save somebody's life robin
young buyer celery juice cleared up all
skin
issues robin that's incredible because
skin is just really brutal brutal for a
lot of people and they're really
difficult
and people really struggle and that
that's the best news i've heard
really is such good news i'm so happy to
hear that
so you're really happy to hear that um
rita asked does celery have sodium in it
yeah it has
natural sodium cluster salts a subgroup
of sodium
that's your medicine that's different
than salt
that's your medicine it's just
incredible
but you know yeah michelle aren't aren't
skin issues really bad they're so bad
people's skin issues are just terrible
terrible
[Music]
so celery juice is one of these things
that
has benefits beyond what research and
science knows first of all they didn't
know it had any benefits
medical medium information put out
information on celery juice okay there
was no information on celery juice
that existed okay it was all medical
medium information
and now people are toting it out there
everywhere they're saying it does this
that does that it does this they don't
cite back to medical medium but they'll
say it does this this this
lower blood pressure do this all the
stuff and they don't cite anything back
to medical medium they act like
there's been real research and studies
on it there isn't
there hasn't there hasn't been any
research
and studies on celery juice but guess
what
millions are healing and reversing
disease and symptoms and conditions so
let's talk about benefits a little bit
that's exciting right there so i got my
celery juice just juiced it right here
and if you guys just got on here
i'm just gonna show you this okay if you
just got on
um because
i just juiced over 32 ounces of celery
juice okay
that's what i did and in this container
it's it's a joke how much how how little
is in here
in this container right here there's
this little bit in the corner
look and
it's dry to the bone that's it
um i washed all this celery and i don't
need to juice it
i'm going to juice it later because i'm
still going to do some lives
but is unbelievable so it's just great
it's great so i want to talk about
benefits of celery
i'm going to grab a celery stick right
here
um just grab this one this is a great
celery stick
so everybody's been asking me to twirl
the celery sticks
like in the celery just video on tick
tock i'm just saying they've always been
there everybody's asking me can you do
it again can you
control it can you twirl it it's pretty
funny but um anyway
so the benefits of celery let's just
talk about about it a little bit there's
a vitamin c
in celery okay a vitamin c and
you can eat the celery sticks but you
don't get enough of all its medicine
it's vitamin c it's sodium cluster salts
and i'll talk about what these things do
okay um it's phytochemical compounds
right it it doesn't you can't get enough
if you eat the sticks
so somebody like well i'm just gonna eat
the sticks and be fine with that
no it's not gonna happen that way you're
not if
you if you chop up a little bit of this
and put it in your tuna salad you're not
going to get anywhere with it if you
have this crudite with this
and you're dipping it in some some ranch
dressing whatever it is
you're not going to get you're not going
to get the benefits if you eat it or
chop it up in your salad you're still
not gonna get the benefits you have to
juice it that's the key you can use and
you can use whatever juicer you have
you can use whatever juicer you have if
you guys got a juicer use it
okay i'm just showing you a place you
can go down the road
with a juicer that can change your life
for money-wise it can save you
so much money all of that and and plus
it's just
it's cold it's a cold pressed juicer
it's a cold pressed juicer which is
amazing on top of it
so it just it doesn't butcher the celery
it doesn't butcher it and heat it up and
butcher it so that's another thing too
but anyway go back to the benefits a
little bit all right
so there's a vitamin c in celery
that does not have to be converted
vitamin c has to be converted by your
liver in order to make it work
in order for it to actually work it has
to be converted
in celery it doesn't have to be that
means
that that vitamin c boom goes straight
to your immune system
instantly it doesn't go around the bend
to finally try to get there it doesn't
have to go
to the middle man which is your liver
see
vitamin c has to go
to your liver any vitamin c in food so
any vitamin c
if you've been taught eat this food
because it's got vitamin c
it has to go to the liver first
get converted and then it can go to your
immune system
well here's the difference right here
right here and you know what you know
why vitamin c is an important thing
right now well everybody's locked in
their homes
everybody's wearing you know outfits to
try to protect themselves
because of what's going down vitamin c
is critical
critical to help heal us so what happens
is this vitamin c in here
goes straight to your immune system it
doesn't go to the middle man it doesn't
go
to your liver it goes boom right to your
lymphocytes
boom right to your monocytes right to
your neutrophils
right to your basophils it goes into the
immune system your white blood count
gets it immediately and that's a big
deal right there so i'm just telling you
how orson vitamin c which is really cool
and then and then the sodium cluster
salts that are in celery juice too
so sodium cluster salts in
celery juice the subgroup of sodium
that's undiscovered by research in
science
kills off bugs so it starts to kill off
pathogens
streptococcus in our system staph
c diff epstein-barr cytomegalovirus
herpes simplex 1
herpes simplex 2 all this stuff
and it and that sodium cluster salt
inside
this this um this this herbal medicine
because that's what it is it's herbal
medicine
goes to the bugs and starts to weaken
them
starts to break them down if you got
acne that's strep
that's streptococcus if you have acne
cystic acne is strep in your system and
it and then your body
puts all this builds up all the sebum
oil to try to stop the strep and then it
becomes nothing but a mess
and this is good for that that's the
whole thing in eczema psoriasis that's
epstein-barr
and copper inside the liver plus
epstein-barr bar feeds off a copper
and then it goes the bathroom then you
got this dermatoxin well the celery
juice
goes into the liver and starts to clean
up that ebv
in there starts to break it down a
little at a time little at a time and
people start getting better
and they start getting better how much
are you supposed to drink a day
i talk about all the different levels
and dosages of what you can drink
by the way this is on sale to all the
medical media books i know that i told
you guys yesterday
they're on sale amazon.com us i told you
about that
but cleanse the heel i you can get it
free at the library too you can go to
the library get free
library if you need to um but i talk
about the different dosages
of celery juice i like 16 ounces on an
empty stomach
great place to start if you need to go
lower you can you can start lower than
that you can if you need to
that's perfectly fine you guys and
but you can work yourself up to 32
ounces a day
and you can do 32 ounces in the morning
so i like to do the lemon water first
thing in the morning wait about a half
an hour
then i do my celery juice i go into that
then after the celery juice i do my
the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie after that
and that's where i go if you guys just
got on here got the celery juice right
here
i just juiced it and this is what's left
right there that's the pulp so if you've
ever owned a juicer
you'll know what this means this is like
one of these like
little miracles it's just it's it's
incredible this is dry to the bone
there's no juice in it it's not wet it's
really really dry there's not much in
here
for all this celery juice and that's
because this is a celery juicer even
though it juices other stuff and
and you can go to omega juicers.com
omega
juicers.com but you have to get the mm
900 hds celery juicer because they got a
lot of juice reserved this is the one
that does it
um can celery juice help with eczema
mikey it already has for thousands of
people
it already has there's healing stories
everywhere
about people getting eczema to go away
i mean it's it's already happened and so
just so you know that yes you can get
help with it
is a healing tool for eczema because
it's already happened
everybody's claiming that with their
healing process their eczema is going
away so
it's already out there so you know and
that's cool if you check out
you check out the the medical medium
instagram
medical me and facebook and you'll see
the healing stories of people in their
eczema
and you'll see what's going on and
they're using sub they're doing celery
juice every single day
and they're doing other medical medium
tools which are helpful too but the
cellular juice is a big part of how we
can heal skin issues
it's a great thing to do um daniel
vitiligo too
exactly that's a skin condition vitiligo
that's having aluminum in your liver so
celery juice here's another benefit of
celery juice too
okay it goes into the liver and it
starts to clean it up
it starts to flush it out
and what's in our liver petrochemicals
ddt
herbicides pesticides rodenticides
insecticides all sit inside our liver
gasoline from the pumps when you pump
gas and you're breathing in the fumes
goes inside the liver plastics
go inside the liver pharmaceuticals
antibiotics
benzodiazepines anti-inflammatories
any kind of drug or medication you've
taken throughout your life goes into the
liver
thyroid medications go into the liver
and it gets stagnant
sluggish and then in that liver is also
little buggies
the epstein bar that's a big one that
sits inside the liver
so if you have toxic heavy metals in
there too copper lead arsenic aluminum
mercury cadmium nickel inside your liver
that copper and other metals feed
viruses then a dermatoxin is produced
and an aluminum-based one for vitiligo
and you lose your melon and you lose the
pigment that's how it works celery juice
goes into the liver
and it starts to do some healing plus
it's got phytochemical compounds that
help heal the skin and i talk about that
in celery juice book which is really
cool
um so yeah
i'm reading some more comments checking
things out trying to help in any way i
can't talk
dana said darn ebv i know i know it's no
fun it causes a lot of trouble
causes the fibromyalgia hashimoto's
thyroiditis r.a
lyme disease it causes a lot of trouble
in a lot of people there's different
varieties there's over 60 varieties
of epstein-barr and research and science
doesn't even know that they thought
epstein-barr just did this you know what
they thought
barr did all these years they thought it
just made somebody tired
and gave them a mild fever when they had
mono that's it that's all they knew
medical media information and books
published that epstein-barr causes all
these conditions
and guess what a few years later after
millions of books went into doctor's
offices uh
a few years later they decided to say uh
they think
now epstein barr is linked to
hashimoto's they think it's linked now
to r.a
they think it's linked now to
neurological lime
for medical medium information it's
pretty pretty amazing really what's
happened
and it's really great it's really great
um can we give
the wildlife celery juice
because of chemtrails is that i think
that's what you're saying the
wildlife i don't know i mean you can
look i i got squirrels i put out little
pieces of celery and squirrels eaten
out there for squirrels um and i think
the question i think was confused by the
question or the con
the question probably a little different
than what it looks like um
yeah ingrid you could use limes instead
of lemon i just saw that
in your lemon water you can have lime
water if you really need to that's okay
too
you can do that so yeah
so you guys the thing is here is that
when it comes down to celery juice
you're helping your body heal and that's
a big deal
and if you're somebody that's not sick
and you're not worried about healing
it's still good because it can actually
prevent things and that's what i love
about celery juice
that's why i drink it every single day i
drink it every day think of a single day
because i want to stay healthy
i want to make sure i stay strong i stay
hot stay healthy i drink it every single
day because of that
and you feed laurie you feed your dog
celery that's really cool
dogs love celery they do they do um
whoa you're dakarya whoa celery juices
help that incredible i'm seeing a lot of
celery juice
helping a lot of people it's really
amazing
when you think about it so you guys
um this is easy to clean by the way let
me run let me run that by you too
lorraine l says she loves squirrels um
this is easy to clean
that's what i love about this one too
it's easy to dismantle all you do is you
just take off this little piece right
here
like that and then you actually take off
this piece too
and then you're good you actually can
clean it and you're all set you can take
off this
and now you got this whole piece right
here and then you just take it apart
it's really simple to clean
it's really easy to clean i love this
juicer
so check it out when you can so
32 over 32 ounces i still got a little
bit left in a container right here
and that's how much pulp which is
ridiculous right there
but um you guys i'm heading over now to
ig if you want to come with me after ig
i'm going to tick tock after that
so i'm going to juice again talk about
it i think there's some stuff i didn't
even cover
so that's what happens usually there's
stuff and i'm gonna answer some more
questions too
um yeah that's this is a cold pressed
one
this is a cold pressed juicer you guys
should be doing the moon meditation
it's a full moon should totally be doing
if you can medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast the moon meditation it's
free
it's a powerful meditation we're right
around the full moon right now
you guys should be doing it every i did
it last night did it the night before
you guys should do the moon meditation
when you get a chance it's really
healing it's healing for the soul
check it out if you can medical medium
podcast at apple podcast
everybody should be doing it right now
and take advantage of it the magnetic
pull of the moon
and the healing power it has on the soul
on the spirit on the heart from wounds
emotional wounds
i talk about that all the time you know
the betrayal broken trust broken
promises
losses emotional struggles the moon
meditation hope you guys are doing it
when you get the chance
yes the moon is out and it's bright
that's incredible
in munich that's amazing and so if you
get a chance go to medical medium
podcast at apple podcast
vanilla says did the moon meditation
last night 100
full moon incredible guys do it again
tonight i'm doing again tonight
when you get a chance i'll see i'm going
to ig right now bless your heart just
know that i care
you guys are amazed