immune system building it preparing
for what's to come really critical
important information
we're talking about building the immune
system once again we're live on facebook
we're live on youtube
live on tick tock live on clubhouse
it's good to be back it's been a long
week
and so much to cover you guys i'm making
the healing broth medical medium healing
broth
um such a great great recipe right here
it's in medical medium new edition just
in case you want to know
right there and
it's one thing to talk about the immune
system
right it's one thing to talk about it
it's another to really know how it works
it's another to know how to keep it
strong
right and all this talk about immune
system hey guys glad you're coming on
courtney good to see you
lorraine l good to see you glad you guys
are coming on michelle i saw you too
everybody coming on um liz good to see
you lisa good to see you
uh green blue good to see you the thing
is what people don't realize is
we can talk a good game right do you
ever see that out there you're talking a
good game
people are talking a good game but do
they really know what they're talking
about
it's like helps immune system immune
boosts the immune system okay that's
kind of funny
because everywhere i go and anything
i've ever seen they didn't even know
about the epstein-barr taking our immune
systems down
they didn't even know how they didn't
know if the flu virus
took the immune system down people had
no idea
that the flu virus takes the immune
system down
tumbles it down to the ground and
important to know you guys i'm making a
healing broth i got some water in here
steven i'm going to add some more water
to it a little bit
um we're going to be doing that in a
moment so
and it's one thing to talk a good game
you see it out there
probiotics helps the immune system how
it does
how love to know okay but what
a new probiotic company that doesn't
even know why anybody's sick
no one knows why anybody's sick i'm just
saying just these are examples right
fish oil good for the immune system
good for the immune system and it's like
okay really
how right think about that one so look
we're talking about
building the immune system all this is
all this
is really really important i'm glad you
guys are coming on i'm excited
uh tara appleman good to see you it's
exciting
um on tick tock we're live on tick tock
we're live on youtube we're live on
facebook we're live on clubhouse
just want to remind everybody right
there and
so it's a funny thing right you got
chronic illness growing
at a rate we've never seen before in
history good ceo austin
never seen before in history you guys
okay
but everybody's an immune system expert
now
everybody's an immune system expert
chronic illness
like we've never seen in history but
everybody's an immune system expert
genius
genius nobody knows why anybody ever had
fibro multiple sclerosis
r.a because no one knew anybody has
lupus
right cfs chronic cfs nobody knows
anything about any of that but we're
immune system geniuses out there
everybody's oh this this fish oil this
probiotic this is going to be great for
your immune system
um so it's important to know like how to
protect yourself for what's to come
because we have some serious stuff
coming right
and i'm going to go into that a little
bit we're going to make a healing broth
hi from france good to see you it's so
great kimberly the papaya
mono cleanse is really helping repair
the damage
charcoal caused my intestinal tract
kimberly miller
um thanks for um telling everybody and
and telling us it's important because
the charcoal can really do damage and so
we're taught like do the charcoal do the
charcoal
internally right swallow the activated
but people don't realize that it
suffocates the lining of your gut
so you don't get absorption so you don't
absorb the things you need to absorb all
the nutrients
it it is so it's so evasive
to the intestinal lining charcoal
i've never recommended anybody to
swallow charcoal
never never never i've been consistent
not contradicting through the years
and you see that out there and i know
you guys right you heard me say this
before
but it's like all the podcast doctors
you should have seen what they were
doing
10 years ago seeing what they're doing
eight years ago six years ago it's like
a countdown let's change it up again
five years ago four years ago they
changed their tune no one knows how to
do anything no one knows how to fix
anybody
oh now we're down to three now they're
down to two years ago and now all of a
sudden they're picking up medical medium
information left and right
adding it to charcoal but you don't want
to do the charcoal it's really really
aggressive
on the system keep that in mind
so here's the thing we're coming to a
place where
there's going to be a lot of instigators
death by a thousand cuts and one of the
death
by a thousand cuts you guys is the flu
strains
right the plague strains all the
different flu strains
okay so we're up against that and
licking your hands after touching the
toilet seat is not a way to make us
ourselves stronger we don't become
stronger
by licking toilet seats okay we don't
become stronger by licking toilet seats
well hey you may as well just get more
exposure yeah touch the door
handles don't be afraid don't don't get
ocd about it
you can walk into a place and walk into
a gas station just grab the handle
sure no problem because you know oh let
me grab a package that was just
delivered
okay there's a package the delivery
person let me grab that package perfect
okay i'm holding this package with my
bare hands i'm gonna put it on my bed
let me do that let me also get a little
selfie camera on here and do a quick
little youtube on how my package just
arrived right
and i get it it's like we're excited
about packages when they arrive totally
understand but what happens is we're not
taught
we take the packages and we put it on
our kitchen counter
there's grease on the bottom of all the
packages there's
all kinds of pathogens on packages right
and it's not about being scared
it's not about being afraid
or in fear it's about having your back
the information counts wouldn't you love
to know the information
dr fawn md good to see you glad you're
coming on
and one of the death by a thousand cuts
is the flu viruses
okay there should not
technically be the flu it should not
exist
it would go through everybody and then
completely
die out if it wasn't brought back
and released again into the world
just so you know okay the flu virus
would not
exist it would just die out
we would never have the flu again no one
would be passing the flu around
no one would be passing around any kind
of flu variety
plague flu variety around no one would
be passing any of those around
they would run their course and die
that's all
that's it the bug would run its course
and die but
every single year well flu's back it's
back
it's back it's back because it's being
released
being released out there released it's
one of the death by a thousand cuts
it's there to knock you down so his life
is difficult
boom you get the flu too you get older
you get frail the flu is there to knock
you down
boom and take you out that's its job
right that's its job out there okay it's
put out there
so that when you get older you get
weaker it's there to knock you down take
you out
it's one of the cuts it's when the cuts
so it's like protecting ourselves is
important
it really is protecting our immune
systems building our immune systems
rebuilding our immune systems making
them strong
making those immune systems strong right
one of the ways to make your immune
system strong
is getting toxins out of the body or
less exposure to toxins
getting rid of the fragrances you guys
on clubhouse
the fragrances you know what they are
right there fresheners
scented candles okay you guys on
facebook youtube right
the scented candles right the chemical
abominations right okay
the colognes and perfumes on tiktok you
know about the clones right you know
about the perfumes on tiktok
you guys know you just came on we're
talking about rebuilding the immune
system
okay those things break your immune
down they break your immune system down
that's what those things do i'm going to
add eight cups of water in here
um chop up some carrots right here
let's do that you guys move these
tomatoes
um so
those perfumes those colognes they knock
our immune systems down those air
fresheners they knock our immune systems
down
right it's not you get stronger
by getting exposed you get weaker and
then the fungicides knock us down
the sprays next door that the neighbor
is spraying knock us down
okay right and
all the different fragrances that come
from either pesticides
herbicides fungicides
all the different fragrances that come
from clones perfumes
air fresheners right
they knock us down that's how it's done
i hear
cars have air fresheners and it's not
the one
that used to hang and dangle right
dangle by the rear view mirror up there
okay
that was toxic enough now there's air
fresheners you just plug them into your
vent in your car
talking about destructive it's like i'm
let me go hop in my car
and break down my immune system i'm in
my car now my immune system's breaking
down
all that air freshener is going in i'm
breathing it in this is great
smells like wildflowers
there's no wildflowers in that car air
freshener
there's no wildflowers in the car air
there's no there's no natural anything
in the car air freshener
right and but we're taught
we're being trained trained and trained
and trained
to drain our immune system we're being
trained to drain our immune system
that's what we're being taught chemical
companies
all of it and
people with the most toxins
and the most pathogens
become the sickest okay clubhouse you
guys
people with the most toxins and the most
pathogens
become the sickest lorraine al says the
cardio
fresheners yeah keep telling people but
they don't listen
yeah i know i know um
women already are struggling with
autoimmune at a rate that's unbelievable
unprecedented you guys
women already struggling with
so many different conditions and
symptoms worldwide
it's it's unbelievable you know
but let's teach women
to put air fresheners in the car let's
teach them that they have to constantly
be smelling some kind of chemical
that's that's the way it's rigged out
there
meanwhile what's happening whether you
believe it or not
you can just be like you know what he
this isn't true
i could breathe in my air fresheners all
i want in my car that's not going to
knock my immune system
down go think what you want it's
knocking your immune system down
okay and immune systems already function
they already fluctuate
for women they're already fluctuating
women have a reproductive system
different than men
so women's immune systems drop
dramatically
during menstruation ovulation being
pregnant too
the immune system is already dropping
well it doesn't happen for men like that
and so women alright are already
struggling
with immune system conditions symptoms
or immune systems are
already compromised because of the
reproductive system
but but how is that possible think about
this okay think about this
well anthony that's not how it works
think about it if it's
if it's natural if we're here on
earth why would women be given this
immune system drop during their
menstruation during their cycle where 80
percent of their immune system goes to
the reproductive system only 20 percent
of
their immune system is left to protect
them
why is it that this thing this wouldn't
happen
right if you don't believe that god put
us here
if you don't believe that god put human
beings that that
life is here because of god or if you
if you believe life is here because of
god anthony
god wouldn't do that why would god put
us here on this earth and put women on
this earth and have them have immune
system problems when they have their
cycle and ovulation and everything else
or say you don't believe god put human
beings here
you know say you believe that we we came
from
uh we came from a little sea creature
and we crawled out of the ocean as a
little sea creature
and we went and then another million
years went by and we started trying to
breathe
out of the water another million years
went by and we became like a badger and
now we're a different creature
another million years by we became a
monkey right and now we're a gorilla
right and now we're a human being say
you believe in evolution
right say you're somebody that believes
in evolution
why would we evolve in a way where
women's immune systems would
would tank during menstruation and
ovulation where 40
of their immune system goes down during
ovulation
you know or say you believe you don't
believe in having
evolution and you don't believe god put
us here
right and you believe an alien
spacecraft
okay bye and just put us all down here
dropped us down here gave us some food
supplies and said good luck
they believe in that too okay whatever
you believe in right
say we say we got here that way why
would that alien spacecraft
say hey women haha this is a cruel joke
their immune system
the aliens are up there saying your
immune systems are gonna drop
80 percent when they have their
menstruation it's like hahaha this is a
fun joke played on all those women down
there
watch how hard they have it
say you believe in that either way
here's how it works what we didn't have
millions of years ago were pathogens
that we have now what we didn't even
have
300 years ago are pathogens that we have
now what we didn't even have
a hundred years ago you guys 150 years
ago
are pathogens we have now
we got the epstein bars they've evolved
those epson words you know what has
evolved not
us not us
we didn't evolve no
maybe spiritually maybe you evolved
spiritually
maybe you took a yolk course in a
spiritual class and you know
went up on a mountaintop with a few
friends and camped out and
talked about the stars maybe you evolved
spiritually
maybe you did meditations every single
day you evolved spiritually
maybe you had i always say we evolve
spiritually
when something hits us and we're like on
our hands and knees
praying to god you know i've seen people
who don't they don't even believe in god
never believed in god and then they got
so sick they're down on their hands and
knees and they're like praying to god
it's like and whatever it is like maybe
we evolved spiritually
but we didn't evolve physically
we didn't let let me tell you what
evolved you guys
all the crap you're up against that's
what evolved
yeah and you know what's funny about
this conversation i know a lot of you
guys say
and i saw it in the comments you said
how does he do it how does he cook
how do you cook read comments and talk
about
this kind of stuff i got help spirit of
compassion is talking to me now and
giving me
much of this information right so i got
some carrots in here let's get some
carrots in there
let's put some mushrooms in here too but
we didn't evolve physically
but all the pathogens the epstein bars
the shingles the cytomegalovirus right
the hh v6 the hhv7 the hhv 10 through 16
that's undiscovered
all the different undiscovered varieties
of epstein-barr right
of hpv
right all the different bugs they
evolved around us
we stayed the same we stayed the same
is what we did
we stayed the same
we might evolve spiritually
we stayed the same christy g says i
followed the celery juice two years ago
and now
i'm off levothyroxine thank you the
doctor was shocked
he said he never took anyone off
medication before
congratulations congratulations on
putting mushrooms in this
broth i'm making the healing broth
congrats seriously i'm really proud of
you you did the work
you're doing the work right seaweed hero
it's a big pot today right
but the pots kind of up the pots up
forward
you know how it works on the camera you
guys when it's up close that's how they
get you on the mukbangs
what they do is they put all that food
they put all those cheeseburgers and
fries and
and they put all those nachos and all
that they put it up real close to the
camera
so whenever when they're eating them you
think wow they ate all that food
right and they put it way up there it's
a little trick
on youtube they do but i'm not trying to
do the trick i'm just putting a pot
right there and it just it's
yeah it's a big pot it is a bigger pot
so um let's go we got mushrooms in there
let's keep this going i'm gonna put some
onions i'm putting some of these
beautiful green onions in
because that's what i had in stock you
guys it calls for
you know a regular onion right but i'm
putting these onions in here two onions
right is what it calls for
i'm putting these in here
so this is really you guys on clubhouse
this is so important you should take
notes
seriously the most important one of
these important notes is
we didn't evolve physically we don't
evolve physically here
as time goes on
but everything around us that wants to
take us down
evolves the chemical companies evolve
how about that how about them
apples you guys how about them apples
chemical companies they evolve they make
a new batch of crap every single day
they got scientists right in their labs
playing around with chemicals we're
going to put this in this fabric
softener
who cares what it does to people's
brains who cares what does their
children
let's as long as they feel nice and safe
with their fabric softener and they like
the smell
then who cares what happens to their
family the chemical companies they
evolve
right what else evolves
okay not just the pesticide companies
they evolve
they'll come out with another 100
brews of skull and crossbones
skull and crossbones put some celery in
this
just put some onion in there it's going
skull and crossbones
that's what's on the pesticide
containers
herbicides herbicides are a big one
right there those herbicides
they evolve what else evolves
right nanotechnology that evolves
how about that right how about emf
that evolves we don't evolve physically
emf does okay
that's what evolves right chemical
company stuff evolves you know what else
evolves
gmo evolves gmo now they've got
a thousand varieties of gmo corn in
hawaii
in hawaii you know
a lot of my friends are like you need to
move to hawaii you got to move to the
island
you got i go really it's gmo central
they've destroyed hawaii no one's doing
anything about it
you know it's crazy it's like
i get some friends they're like big time
hippies and they're like which is
totally cool and they're like
they're like yeah we're doing we're
doing a protest against this and this
and this and this
and they're they're in hawaii and i'm
like really really why don't you guys
protest against
the fact that they've taken over hawaii
with gmo crops medical corn grain
crops big pharma owns hawaii
hawaii was sold to big pharma it was
sold to big pharma
they're just growing non-stop gmo crops
it's gmo central
it's like there's a watch it moved to
hawaii it's so great what are you
talking about the edge of the water it's
so great by the ocean
other than that they thought it's just
gmo
it because that's evolved so gmo evolves
you guys
clubhouse evolves and all this evolves
you know what else evolves the tech
companies
they evolve now you're now your tech
devices do this now your tech devices do
that now they radiate more radiation now
there's more radiation
they evolve so we get all the radiation
from our tech right
i'm not trying to say we got to be
afraid of our tech freight of the
chemical companies afraid of this
afraid of that afraid of gmo food if we
get exposed we get exposed but what i'm
saying
is we got to keep our immune system
strong we got to build our immune system
we got to make it happen
we got to take care of ourselves right
it's important
that's what i'm saying so i'm putting in
some carrots
i put in some celery right there i'm
going to chop up some parsley right now
for this soup
right
doing some finely chopped parsley right
here
nice parsley in this this is gonna be a
great broth this is the healing broth i
love it
let's put a bulb of garlic in here to
you guys
got it heating up so
what we have to do you know where we
have to evolve
we have to evolve in the fight
against all of that right
protect your immune systems get it ready
for battle
that's what we have to do but you know
what
how does this stuff break down your
immune system did you ever wonder
or is it interesting to know now did you
ever wonder
how how does a chemical how does a
fabric softener break down your immune
system
how does a perfume a clone break down
your immune system because it's
foreign chemicals untested
no long-term testing serious
ramifications
never discovered because it's not been
tested long enough
put some garlic in here let's chop the
garlic up
how does it break down the immune system
our body
is allergic even if you don't react to
all of these things
and our white count knows it so our
white count
gobbles it up you want to keep your you
want to keep your immune system busy
right oh exposure's good for you you
should get all that exposure it's so
healthy for you makes you stronger what
doesn't kill you makes you stronger
what bs that is
you know talking to a friend of mine
and
their uncle was in the gulf war
and got exposed to a lot of stuff
got injured did it make them stronger
no
when somebody strokes out from a
medication does it make them stronger
because i'm confused
someone someone i'm scratching my head
here i'm scratching my head
someone gets a blood blood clot someone
gets a blood clot from a medication
from the pill
note a lot of women they got a blood
clot from the pill um
did it make them stronger no they've
been
they've been knocked down from it
the rest of their life um
what else what else lots of lots of
harsh harsh antibiotics for lyme disease
treatment
did that make them what didn't kill him
made him stronger no
struggling the rest of their life
because of it so many people
right it's cute the saying is cute
the saying is cute i get it it's great
for
a song you're in the car
you know you're you're just feeling kind
of like down emotionally down it's like
look what doesn't kill you make stronger
you're whatever it is
and you're like yeah feel empowered
where you know you go see a healer you
go see a healer somewhere you recommend
it to go see a healer
healer says you know what it's okay you
know what doesn't
you know what doesn't knock what doesn't
finish us off just makes you get
stronger it's like whoa
so here's how it works your white count
let's give you a rundown you guys
got the white blood count here let's
just work on that one
let's work with some chemicals okay
let's work with some chemicals okay you
guys so see what else here
um now this works this works this works
okay got some perfume got some clone you
guys on
on uh clubhouse i'm holding some holding
a white blood cell in my hand right here
okay you breathe in that perfume
it's a toxic chemical guess who knows
that
you don't know that right nobody knew
that perfume was
a toxic chemical right about a barrage
of toxic chemicals
medical medium information was the first
to come out um exposing that right
but guess guess who knows about that
toxic chemical your white blood count
right there
put a name on your white blood cells
what do you want to name your white
blood cell
yeah and yeah well whatever
whatever you want to name your white
blood cell right
your white blood cell is aware has an
intelligence
and knows that that perfume that cologne
is highly toxic you breathe it in
your white cat has to eat it has to eat
it
see that's how it works
gobble it up every little
particle that goes in you your white
count has to gobble it up
right you get exposed to toxic heavy
metals
your white count has to gobble it up
right that's how it's done right
and then it weakens your white count
weakens your white count until it dies
isn't it interesting you're still alive
looking around you're
doing your thing and your one count is
dying poof one died
that's it no boom another one died
another one died okay over time it's
okay my bone marrow can produce a whole
ton of it
oh oh my bone marrow can produce tons
and tons of it keep on sending them out
boom die
boom die boom that one dies that one
dies
your white count gobbles these things up
it gobbles all those poisons and toxins
and all that stuff up the pesticides the
herbicides
the fungicides toxic heavy metals that
we get exposed to left and right too
every day you guys get exposed to it's
comments falling out of the sky
there's planes dropping it out of the
sky i told you about the medical medium
podcast at apple podcast you guys when
you get a chance
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
you know
elite maha says he is instilling fear
and sounds like an idiot oh
well elite majas
hey i'm glad you can make it on this
live
yeah fear mongering yeah
is that what it sounds like i'm sorry i
apologize
i i just saw it as i saw it as like
just education to protect yourself so
you you like getting exposed
so you eat maha's you like getting
exposed
you don't like living in fear so
what do you do you just you touch all
the door handles
okay that's good do you do you rub your
eye
you like living in denial oh elite majas
you like living in denial
such a great place to be wow let's just
all live in denial
that's great just like the medical
industry lives in denial when everybody
gets injured
by drugs and pharmaceuticals just like
everyone
let's just live in denial oh what if
what if we have an abuser
let's just live in denial if we're being
abused how about that would you tell
women who are being abused just to live
in denial
oh they're not being abused it's fear
it's fear
so let's just tell women to just be in
denial
while they're being abused does that
sound good elite applause
huh um what else should people just lick
toilet seats
why not they shouldn't be in fear yeah
don't wash your hands in a public
bathroom no why bother washing your
hands
shopping carts just touch shopping carts
who cares
shouldn't be in fear uh pesticides
herbicides
uh stuff falling what yeah just being
not
who cares if someone's got simplex just
doesn't matter just yeah don't question
it
so you can be safe with your partner
doesn't matter just be in denial
and then when you get your blister just
be in denial again
when you got your cold sore how's that
sound
i just think it sounds to me like to
live in denial
yeah let's let's coin it as fear i'm
just creating fear
and then you live in denial that sounds
great all right i'm gonna hang out
um i gotta cook this thing bulba garlic
went in there let's put an inch of fresh
ginger in there too
go pop that in there let's get some
ginger in here
on the medical beam podcast at apple
podcast i got the chemtrail episode okay
so every day they drop chemicals on us
right
every day all around all around the
planet
it's an unbelievable
unbelievable
private coup private mob
right it's just they're just dropping
this stuff
on us all day long on our children
on us and it's not about living in fear
it's just about how do we protect
ourselves right
so what do we do do we stay in denial
and never protect ourselves
do you you know what let's not i guess
we don't want to know the reality of
things we don't want to know the truth
right
is that what it is we want to be in
denial we don't want to want to know
what reality is
we just want to just pretend you know
everything's just fine
um let's put a chili in here you can put
chili flakes in here too but i'm gonna
put a chili in the soup
so what do we do pretend no one's
getting sicker
is that what we do um
yeah you know i'm really sick i'm
bedridden half the time
i don't feel good i got sore throats i
feel
incredible anxiety that's so it's
insurmountable
what are you doing dealing with oh your
leg hurts you can't even walk what else
is going on your
your back is killing you what you have
fatigue you have severe brain fog
let's just it's not happening right it's
not happening
it's not real right we're not really
sick you know what you know what i love
that whole denial thing
is the game that's thrown on the chronic
allele that's really its madness
you're not sick you're making it up
you're faking it you're making it up
you're faking it you're faking it till
you make it
whatever they say andrea says we can't
say no
and choose differently if we aren't
aware of what is really going on
we need to know how people are hurting
us so we can have
boundaries andrea wise words
wise words so your
white blood cells okay
they're there gobbling up left and right
everything we're exposed to
that's how it works everything we're
exposed to
our white blood cells are gobbling it up
and then the pathogens
right so we already have enough going on
in the pathogens we get exposed to
right we get exposed to the flu we get
exposed to the plague we get exposed to
those types of flus hybridized blues
we get exposed and
when we get exposed it knocks us down
another level so it's all this exposure
so our white blood cells are really busy
they're they're eating all this they're
they're feeding on all this
they're there eating it up but we lose
our
white count and when we lose our white
count to all these exposures
more is produced but there's a gap
you guys there's a gap everybody seems
to think
you lose your white blood cells after
they draw blood from you or something
like that like i talk about medical mean
podcast at apple podcast the blood draw
episode you've got to listen to some day
you guys
people think that when you remove blood
your bone marrow will just replenish it
all your
immune systems will be all back there
nice and happy everything's back and all
good
no there's a gap in between and when we
get our blood drawn that gap can run
three to six weeks
two to four months three to six months
for a lot of different people
and but even if we're up against poisons
and toxins
chemicals fabric softeners detergents
chemical household cleaners with
chemicals
in them right conventional ones even
natural ones some of them are really got
toxic things in it
so whatever we're up against not as much
toxic of course but when we're up
against these things
our immune system's dying when it gets
overloaded it when it gets overloaded it
dies
so the white blood cell gobbles another
toxic substance and it dies
it gobbles another another white blood
cell gobbles another toxic substance
another toxic substance until it's
overloaded and it dies and then there's
a gap
our bone marrow doesn't keep track at
those numbers
it only keeps track when you're hit hard
like slammed like your blood is drawn
from you
like getting your blood test at the
doctor's office and they take too many
vials four vials five vials six vials
eight vials 14 vials
that's when our bone marrow says whoa we
just
was something happened right there right
but all the little stuff the chemical
stuff falling out of the sky the toxic
heavy metals were exposed to
all the different little bugs were
exposed to everything that your white
town is
eating up your your your bone arrow is
not keeping track so easily of all that
and there's these gaps
and then we run around with this lowered
immune system
we run around with this immune system
that's lower
and then women women have a harder time
their immune system's already
fluctuating so much it's fluctuating
during the cycles it's fluctuating
during pregnancy it's fluctuating during
ovulation
and that fluctuation makes it so that
we're up women are up against
all these other chemical toxins and
poisons they're up against these
pathogens floating around
and then they're hit harder this is why
women are suffering with chronic illness
more than ever before more than men and
more than ever before in our history but
the tide's going to change the tide's
going to change
you're going to see more men sicker than
ever before in our history coming up
and the next from now today
to the next five years and this fall
coming up after the summer
okay we get towards the end of this year
right when we're towards the end this
year there's going to be a lot of
problems
there's going to be a lot of different
flu bugs going around there's going to
be a lot of different plate
hybridization flu plugs
bugs going around there's going to be a
lot of that
and there's also going to be weaker
immune systems than we've ever had
before
by the end of this year and we're going
to all have that too
and then media is not going to cover it
but people are going to be in sicker
and sicker and sicker and sicker
but we don't have to do that we don't
have to
be that way we can protect ourselves if
we can learn how to do it i'm making
medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothies every day for myself i'm
making a medical medium to celery juice
i'm drinking every day for myself right
what are you guys doing
i'm doing the vitamin c shock therapy
we're talking about the
zinc shock therapy right i'll talk about
that a little bit too and the vitamin c
shock therapy doing the medical medium
healing broth right now
the thyme tea right ginger water i'm
doing with
these things are giving us a chance
right these things give us a chance to
keep our immune system strong
so that the white blood cells don't die
easy
yeah when you give your white blood
cells things
they don't die as easy see
isn't that incredible white blood cells
are hungry
they need fuel so they need trace
mineral salts they need
zinc your white blood cells need zinc
right
and when they when your white blood
cells need vitamin c
who's feeding their white blood cells
enough
to battle what we're up against the
white blood cells
need the healing minerals that are in
the medical medium healing broth
so important
so elite maha says i was told that
giving blood
is healthy for us because it takes
toxicity out
look no disrespect seriously and i'm
glad you're here okay
i'm glad you're here elite my house i'm
really glad okay
because um that's a really good question
it's not how it works
because when we remove blood we remove a
large part of our immune system and that
part of our immune system is keeping us
stable and so what happens is if you're
somebody with cfs if you're somebody
with fibromyalgia if you're somebody
with
anything sibo if you're somebody with
plantar fasciitis
eczema psoriasis lupus r a
brain fog whatever you got going on
headaches migraines burning skin tingles
numbness
ringing the ears whatever it is the more
blood you remove
okay the more all these things can get
worse and they do get worse
that's why people with lyme disease get
bled to death
that's why people with cancer get bled
to death
people with cancer get bled to death
their immune system is taken out their
immune system's taken out
constantly with the blood draw and
that's how it works and i talked about
that many times right
that's how it works you're getting the
blood taken out you're getting the blood
taken out and too much blood
clubhouse i'm holding an arm in my hand
right now i got a blood vial
right in my other hand here and
that's what's happening they take too
much blood you got cancer
they want blood every three days they
want blood once a week
but they don't just take a little bit of
blood because that's all they need is a
little touch of blood they take a lot of
blood
is what they do they take a large amount
so much so a large amount that they
don't need
and that's how it works right and
um and then so but
you'll get told oh don't worry we'll
just get the old blood out
so new blood is created so now you're
you've got
healthy blood it's almost like that's
the bloodletting technique that killed a
lot of people that's the bloodletting
technique from the 1600 to 1700 to 1500s
you got sick they cut your vein they cut
your arm when you got sick they cut you
and they bled you
right big pan of blood and if you
survived that
cut while you were sick it's a miracle
so they did they basically just ended
your life bloodletting was a way to kill
people
it was just your everybody knew when
they were getting bloodletted
they knew they were done you know why
anybody sick back in that day
didn't come back from bloodletting they
didn't bounce back they didn't all of a
sudden he'll be a miracle if they
actually healed
and they survived the bloodletting
technique
so you're being told the same old thing
an
old way of doing something
that was basically devastating to
families
if a child got sick back in the the
1700s
in 1800s if a child got sick they would
bloodlet the child to death
the untold sorrow and pain
that has occurred from bloodletting but
no
hey let's just follow that same old lead
let's just know the more blood donate
blood the more blood that comes out of
you
hey fresh new blood will come back it's
a bloodletting
but here's the thing okay
it takes an unbelievable amount of
resources to rebuild
your blood so it's not just about
getting some water down
hey drink a lot of water make sure you
drink a lot of water you get all that
blood taken out of you drink a lot of
water
uh your blood will be back to normal by
that night no not at all you'll be
filled with more water
not blood eat eat a whole bunch of food
that'll build up your blood fast that
doesn't build up your blood fast your
blood is still
people who get who don't eat blood
they're sick for months many people
many people who donate blood it's the
last time they ever donate blood
because they couldn't even walk out of
there and they were sick for months
i'm not saying don't donate blood it's
just that women are trained to donate
blood guess who donates the blood it's
the women
and the sick women so that's who donates
that's that's the blood donors out here
did you guys know that
out there in the world so listen to the
blood uh the blood draw
podcast medical mean podcast at apple
podcast go there listen to the blood
draw
blood leading vampires episode if you
can
but so but that's another thing women
are trained
to be the blood givers on this planet
right so here's what happens you walk
into
you hop on to a blood donating
bus or you stand there at that bus
and you interview everybody coming on
okay
it's gonna be all women occasionally
this one guy
all women yep and all sick women
they all got thyroid problems they all
got fibro
they all got fatigued they all got brain
fog they all got all these different
symptoms
and they're filing in dumping their
blood giving their blood away
to the blood machine the blood monster
and that's what they're doing okay
that's a whole problem all on its own
no one's no one's like being held
accountable for the mistakes made in all
that
the irony is you only need a little bit
of blood that's the irony
i don't know if you call an irony or you
call it just the biggest screw-up on the
planet
you only need a little bit of blood
right so
and people people don't know that that
you only need that much blood
right there right there
that's it you can get probably
practically every test you ever dreamed
of out of that right there
okay you can get your dna figured out in
one shot
boom you can get your blood type figured
out one shot boom your a1c boom in a
a boom metabolic panel boom thyroid
pound boom
cbc boom all in that nutritional profile
boom bam done traditional profile just
in that right there
but they drain us to death and it is
it's like a slow death when you got lyme
disease it's a slow death when you got
bad case of lupus it's a slow death when
you got something
because they keep on pulling that blood
out pulling that blood out
and yeah we lose our immune system
right there we lose our immune cells and
one of the reasons why i'm even talking
about this right now isn't just because
elite maha
you know brought this up but it's good
to talk about this because this is one
of the death by a thousand cuts this is
one of the things we get exposed to we
have to be really cautious about
keep that in mind right there um
yeah so i'm making a healing bra right
now you guys
glad to be on we're live on youtube live
on facebook live and clubhouse live on
tick tock good to see you guys
incredible all right so talk about the
zinc shock therapy let's do that
zinc shock therapy is is is really an
awesome medical medium tool
okay and um
because what happens with your white
count is your white counts hungry for
zinc because we're all zinc deficient i
talked about this the other day we're
all
severely zinc deficient there's no zinc
in our food
okay if you're eating pumpkin seeds or
oysters you're not going to get the sink
you need
i mean i hate to break that to you right
because i
i hear that all the time just eat some
oysters are you kidding me
you can eat all the oysters you want the
only thing you can eventually get again
is hepatitis
which is basically a liver infection
neptune bar liver infection but the
reason why oysters will give you that
some bad oysters will give you that is
because they're so toxic they dropped
your immune system flat
boom they killed your immune system so
that epstein-barr can take off
that's how it works there so your white
your white count loves zinc
right and zinc shock therapy um
is a great way of getting it you know
what i've done with with family members
and friends and
you do what your doctor tells you guys
you know i'm just showing you what i do
nancy says how do we build our blood
back up after
they take too much nancy check out at
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
the blood draw
episode i got it all there like it's
it's packed with information right there
yeah lorraine oysters is pretty funny
and
yeah and then people say well pumpkin
seeds that's a great way to get sick
we'll do our pumpkin
seats it's like you need barrels of
pumpkin seeds
in order to get the zinc you need it's
just that and it's not that zinc is
it's not even pumpkin seeds or high in
zinc it's just that they're they
register enough in pumpkin seeds for
them to actually
say hey they're high in z they're not
high in zinc
there's no food high in zinc anymore
zinc shock therapy works every time
since
three years so incredible amazing on
tick-tock
so what i do with zinc shock therapy is
i feel a sore throat coming on
because i you know i i push the
limit myself that's what i do i work 20
hours a day
i'll work 22 hours for two straight days
right two hours of sleep for two
straight days right
i've done that you know i do four hours
at night right
i'm up at five in the morning went to
bed at two three hours a night right
writing the books doing all kinds of
stuff right dealing with life
like we all have to deal with life right
it all just keeps you busy
and you know if i feel a little scratchy
throat
at all you know because i'm around
people
there's flus going around and boom
if spirit of compassion says you got a
flu coming on there's one you
you you picked it up and you've been
burning the candle at four ends
i'm like zing shot therapy sneak shot
therapy
gone for me gone right
and you know and i tell family members
to do this but it's not just any zinc
there's a lot of zinc
out there they got the citric acid in
them they got the alcohol in them they
got
all kinds of um preservatives in there
fillers
so you know the one i use is the vimergy
that's the one i use
i'm not sponsored either it's just that
when something's good i talk about it
all the time
and if they ever go bad i never talk
about them again
you know and um but yeah so but right
now this is the one i'm using it's the
zinc it's the vimergy visa victor i
am as american ergy dot com but
so what i love about the zinc shock
therapy really it's so easy
it's like two dropper falls
every three hours right every waking
three hours so you wake up in the
morning like i don't feel good
or i was exposed to something or i think
i'm coming down with something
and i was talking about the other day
how people eat when they're
coming down with something they eat and
they'll just tank they'll start tanking
some pizza they'll start taking
something else they'll start eating
or they'll eat heavily or even if it's
healthier food but they're going to just
start eating
and when people start coming down with
something
if their stomach doesn't go too sick
when they're coming down with something
they just start eating it's like this
natural instinct of i need something i
don't know what it is
i know that my body's sick something's
going wrong
let me just gobble something down let me
just eat you guys in clubhouse glad
you're here
paula john good to see you lucy's on
there too
um amy glad you guys are on clubhouse
right now live we're on facebook we're
on youtube live we're on tick tock live
amazing talk about the immune system
talking about zinc shock therapy i got
the medical medium healing broth in the
works as we speak
you know i told a family member if
you're sensitive with zinc
you can always um do one tiny drop
like a pin drop but you do it every
three hours
you know talking to a doctor the other
day doctor said look
um can you do less can you do more i
said you're the doctor
you tell you you tell your patients what
what you want out of them or what they
want
what you want to do but yeah you can do
less you can do two tiny drops
right i do two dropper fulls that's what
i've always done
friends and family that's a spirit of
compassion is always giving me as
that that level but it doesn't mean
smaller amounts don't work
they do you know they do that's it's
incredible they
do and and you know however
but you know so let's go back to what
i'm preparing you guys for because
that's what it's about you guys on
clubhouse i'm preparing you
you guys on facebook youtube i'm
preparing you you guys on tick tock i'm
preparing you
that's what i do that's what i've always
done i've done that for years okay
but we're about to head to a place where
everybody's going to be kind of on cloud
nine this summer
okay everybody depending on where you
are on the planet okay
maybe somebody's winter somewhere on the
other side of the world right
and summer right on whatever side of the
world okay
but right now you know it's going to be
it's going to be for half the planet
it's going to be cloud 9
go you know we're in summer head in the
summer it's cloud 9.
things are going to be calming down
paul's going to be kind of hanging in
there
right and then this fall
we're just going to be getting sick okay
people out there are going to be getting
sick and we're already having chronic
illness just rise rise rise every year
every six months every two months it's
rising more people with extra psoriasis
more people with ra more people with
lyme more people whatever diagnosis you
want to throw
into the mix there's hundreds of
diagnoses
right and it's whatever doctor feels in
the moment feels what they're feeling
they'll be like you have autoimmune
disease and we're going to give you this
name
okay you got autoimmune disease and it
kind of looks like the textbook thing
but it doesn't so i'm going to give you
this name
and then you go home and you're like
well i got this
you know um i got ankylosing spondylitis
i got this or i got that or i got
sarcoidosis or i got
you know you go home with this this
diagnosis i got fibrosis so you just end
up with this diagnosis whatever it is
right but it's autoimmune
tagged onto it indefinitely anyway
even though it's not your body attacking
itself i talked about that if anybody
knows medical medium books and
if you guys have the book incredible if
you don't have the book you might want
to get it it's a new edition
medical medium new edition it's so
packed with information i don't i don't
even talk about what's in here there's
so much information in here and i should
or the cleanse the heel book or both of
these and this is cleansed to heal right
here
okay and there's over 200 symptoms and
conditions in cleansing heal how to
handle them
dosages supplementation different
dosages of what the causes are the true
causes are so these books are
critical for people pandemic info in
medical medium new edition you guys
pandemic info and i'll tell you pandemic
info
that will totally just keep your head
straight it'll it'll totally keep your
head straight we'd be like aha
okay i get it now i get it now because
there's so much confusion
right get it free the library if you
don't want to get it on sale on amazon
it's amazon on sale
important to know randy
so long so how do you heal
uh human gross uh
how do you how did you hold on a second
the steam from the pots blowing in my
face you guys
oh my god so how do you uh so how do you
heal from hemochromatosis
they drain blood to lower iron
in your body i need the soup to finish
so i could read comments
maybe if i take the lid off let me take
the lid off and see if i can get the
steam to go a different area
here we go okay
it's like a smoke screen going across
right now
so what they do okay here's here's the
first thing so they drain your blood
that's what they'll do right with that
condition
but they don't know why someone even has
it and
then i talk to doctors many times about
this condition
and because it's it's always a mystery
all these conditions are mysteries right
but but that's a viral condition
anything going
wrong with blood is a hundred percent
viral
and epsilon bars are the real those are
the real
viral stir the pot bugs right there
sometimes the hhv-6 and the hhv-7 will
stir the pot too
see an hhv-8 stir the pot i've seen
hhv-9s through the pot i've seen these
viruses the cytomegalovirus stir the pot
but i've seen bar is the big one for
anything blood related though
anything blood related so well how do we
work with that so what do we do you know
what i mean so
i would take the new addition to your
doctor
talk to him about epstein-barr or find a
that is open to understanding
epstein-barr
because once you do and you start
working
basically working helping your body
battle the upsteam bar
and start cleaning it up that condition
starts to go back to normal
where you start going back to normal
i've seen it on and on and off over the
years so many times
you know happening so when people start
doing the right thing
they start getting better um
okay you guys got the healing broth
going do the vitamin c
shock therapy let's do that
um i'm gonna get the tea kettle going
too so just give me a second you guys
let me get the tea kettle going i'm
gonna do some water over here
so all this information is really really
important
let's get the tea kettle going a little
bit
lorraine says ebv for blood related
makes sense it does it really does do
the vitamin c
shock therapy let's go into that a
little bit we're live on youtube
facebook clubhouse
so you're welcome to use any vitamin c
you want for this
i mean i use the vimergy one
it's so easy on the system there's a lot
of vitamin c's out there they're like
battery acid
they're just they're hard to get down
that ascorbic
acid is really difficult on a lot of
people
right chris you seem fine to me good to
see you you know it's that
it's that ascorbic acid nature
that type of vitamin c is really rough
right
but i like um
but i like the vitamin c shock therapy
with the micro c the vimergy micro c i'm
not sponsored by this guys you guys
so you know you guys know so
back to the immune system let's talk a
little bit more about how to build it
you can't rebuild your immune system if
you don't understand it
right even if someone tells you oh
vitamin c is good for your immune system
it doesn't mean you're going to do it
right or do it for the right time
or do it right time period or understand
it to keep it going
no like there's there's so much to know
okay
you might be somebody's oh vitamin c is
good for your immune system and then you
get given this vitamin
that has a little this multivitamin it
has a little bit of vitamin c in there
but it's worthless
multivitamins are one of probably one of
the most worthless
worthless alternative medicine tools
that are out there and i don't even know
if i could
call it even a tool because it shouldn't
even gain that much respect
it's it really falls short it's a money
making scheme
for the alternative therapy industries
so that's important that's a that's
worth the price of admission right here
if you wondered why you're even here
right now during this live watching me
make a pot of soup peeling broth
that that right there is just worth its
price of admission
even though this is free even though
this is all free
because the because what they do
is it's really just to rip off those
multivitamins are all
bulk low grade stock
from 10 years ago just so you know now
you're going to look at the date
you're going to look at the date on your
multivitamin say well
medical medium's wrong again always
trying to catch medical medium catch him
catch him while you can he never
contradicts himself it's always hard to
kick can't catch him ever
and he's wrong because the date on this
multivitamin is it's not due until
it's not expired until next year so once
again he's wrong
no once again medical means right
because this because they started the
new date
on the multivitamin when they
encapsulated it
when they actually encapsulated you guys
john on clubhouse that's what happens
okay they they start that date
process when they put it in the capsule
or the tablet john that's when they
started
just so you guys know that stuff
has sat around for years sometimes
10 to 15 years
just so you know and then when it
finally goes into the vitamin
you got your multivitamin and they use a
speck of everything
little speck of this and then you got
these vitamins now
and these powders out there and have a
speck of everything a speck of nettle
a speck of alfalfa a speck of some kind
of protein
a you know speck of choline a speck of
lysine a speck of whatever and it
doesn't do anything
at all because it's not enough
a speck of lemon balm because medical
means talks about lemon bomb now you got
a new supplement company around the
corner every single day
now speck of zinc because medical medium
brought zinc into the world
but pretty much not not entirely
obviously
but in the sense where it's it's on the
scene for viral stuff because of medical
medium information for 35 years it's
like okay let's put a little
little cat's claw in here a little this
a little that
and it's not enough and then we buy it
but here's how it works the company is
making all this money these companies
out there
are making all this money because they
think and they'll put
immune something on the bottle like good
for your immune system or whatever
right so hey i'm going to take this
immune system supplement
meanwhile there's so very little in that
bottle of each thing
that when it all adds up it's just one
big filler in a way your body can't do
anything with that there's two
little bits of it and they're usually
old
so it's important to know right there so
i'm making the vitamin c
shock therapy right now putting some
vitamin c in here
okay i'm gonna get a spoon to mix it up
do that two capsules
every two hours every two waking hours
every two waking hours two teaspoons of
raw honey let's get that in here
okay
two teaspoons of raw honey get that
going
let's get an orange going too
right chop it in orange right now
squeeze an orange in here could squeeze
a half i'm gonna
squeeze the rest of this orange in here
every two waking hours
you think something's coming on you
think you were exposed
you know um
i know somebody that works in a chemical
factory
they're in the warehouse department
the chemicals stink so bad in the
warehouse area
and this person i know a friend of a
doctor friend
is doing this every night does it every
night
gets home from work does this every
waking hour until bed
in the morning does it again until it
goes to work right
because his immune system
is getting eaten up by chemicals
nanotechnology it's a whole other thing
i mean that's chemical warfare right
there it's sprayed on everything you buy
now everything new we buy
has nanotechnology sprayed on it right
so many things have nanotechnology and
then wood
you buy a new piece of wood it's treated
you all that green stuff is on the wood
that's
treated so wood that's treated right
then of course
termite spray termite spray is around
all the buildings apartment buildings
you know these are other exposures too
all this stuff is exposures
we're up against every day right put the
orange in here put the raw honey
two capsules vitamin c
vitamin c shock therapy right there
um yeah so great
so great to have so this is coming along
this is simmering
let me get a
something here
just looking for
got this right here you guys i'm going
to move this around
making the broth
now if i was coming down with something
me personally i'd be making this broth
and i would be cautious to not dump a
whole bunch of fat into my system
i wouldn't do any avocado i like avocado
i like avocado
i have a little here and there i like it
it's a healthy fat
okay but if you're exposed you're coming
down with something
that fat will not protect your immune
system
it just doesn't do that okay so
it's something to know same thing i'm
not gonna eat a whole bunch of tahini if
i was exposed to something
so i'm exposed to some chemicals if i
was exposed to some pathogens if i was
exposed to something else
i wouldn't be downing a whole bunch of
nut butters and nuts
i wouldn't be downing and i wouldn't be
eating a steak
i mean i don't eat steak anyway but you
know and i support anybody who does eat
you know
if they do red meat i still support you
i still can help you heal
with the information that spirit of
compassion has has given us
but if if i was coming down with
something i wouldn't down a steak i
wouldn't down a piece of lamb i wouldn't
down
bacon i went down chicken i went down
turkey
i went down nuts and seeds nut butters
and oils
i wouldn't down any of that i wouldn't
down fish i wouldn't have a big fish
dinner i wouldn't have a lobster dinner
if i was coming down with something so i
wouldn't have well you know i wouldn't
be doing butter
and cheese and milk if i was coming down
something
like one way to get sick when you're
exposed to something
is down a whole bunch of cheese butter
or milk that's
or eggs right then you know
a whole bunch of eggs right there right
so let me make an omelet i feel sick i
feel like or i feel like i was exposed
to something
let me just crack a whole bunch of eggs
open and make an omelette right
that's the last thing i would do right
guess what people do
and then you know people down pizza they
down eggs
even if it's like a healthy version they
got vegetables on their pizza and the
whole bit
when they're getting sick or they're
exposed they're eating all this food
and what happens is this all that
digestive strength
your digestion all the strength it takes
to digest food
can lower your immune system all that
digestive strength
one of the greatest pieces of
information i can give you is if you
think you were exposed eat light that
night
let your immune system be just focused
on what's floating around that
bloodstream and keep the fats
out or keep them low keep them low
don't like don't have a big guacamole on
that day you think you were exposed on
that night you think you were exposed
you guys don't have a big old guacamole
because all that's going to do is fill
your bloodstream up with fat and then
your white count is going to be trying
to navigate through that fat to look for
any invaders
so if you think you're exposed by
pandemic stuff
right you don't want to be tanking the
fats you don't want to fat yourself to
death
because that's what everybody's doing
they're being taught to fat themselves
to death
if you were exposed to a flu someone's
got a sinus infection
which could be streptococcus someone's
got a stye
which could be streptococcus you don't
want to be
you don't want to be filling your gullet
with fat
you don't want to be filling your goat
with that no no no no
no pizza guacamole uh
tacos uh you know nachos um
milk cheese butter eggs nut butters
oatmeal with peanut butter on it you
don't you don't want a grilled cheese
sandwich grilled cheese sandwich you
don't want to do that if you were
exposed
so important enough right there that
that information alone is so
is so critical so let's run by this if
you guys just came on too
okay we're live on facebook youtube tick
tock live on clubhouse talk about the
immune system how to keep it safe and
strong
and prepare us for what's to come
do i want you guys up against something
with a weakened immune system or do i
want you guys
up against something with a strong
immune system you tell them you tell me
what what would you guys like right so
the goal is to be working on it now
doing things that help us help our
immune system
do the time tea when you can do the
ginger water when you can the medical
medium ginger water
the medical medium time t because you're
keeping your immune system strong in
between everything
that's all it's about being prepared do
you guys like being prepared
you guys don't like snow tires on
uh you you would rather have a big
snowstorm come
and then get your snow tires then right
after you've had to drive through it or
got stuck in it
so the whole point is is yeah we want to
be prepared
so this is this is a lot of information
here you guys even though this is
cooking
we're making the healing broth um i'm
going to instagram
i'm heading there there in a couple
minutes so i'll see you guys are you
coming over with instagram
and tick tock i'm bringing tick tock
back instagram
and uh i'm going to strain the broth
there so that's what i'm going to do so
i'm going to be still working on the
healing broth i'm going to strain it i'm
going to get it ready
i'm going to do that on ig i'm going to
bring tick-tock back and i'm going to
bring clubhouse back
i can't wait to see you guys looking
forward to it