lately what I've been doing is kind of
like a cocktail so I've been doing some
cat's claw so I'm just putting in a
couple of dropper FS of cats claw right
there two dropper
FS there right two dropper FS of the B12
in
there I'm going to put four dropper
fulls of the propolis in here right now
cannot say enough about this propolis
just want to show you what I'm doing for
my immune system during this time of
year I want to scream propolis I'm
putting four dropper fulls of golden
seal in here I can't say enough about
Golden seal as well now I'm going to put
a little bit of water in here let's get
an orange cut why am I putting a little
bit of orange in this one I'm increasing
the chances of making sure that all the
phytochemical compounds and nutrients
and coratin that's naturally like in the
propolis and all the different all the
different incredible nutrients that are
in these medicinals what I'm doing is
put a little orange in there because
that orange is glucose you know what
that means glucose delivers the nutrient
nutrient to the cell so that the
constituents so that the phytochemical
compound so that the anthocyan so that
the the polyphenols everything in here
and the enzymes and everything else
that's in there and the co-enzymes all
get delivered easily into the cells into
the organs they get pulled into the
cells and organs because you're driving
it in with the glucose you have to have
sugar in order to take a nutrient into a
cell you can take all the supplements
you want out there in the world all the
different things you want in the world
and if you don't have enough glucose in
your bloodstream you won't get all of it
in your cells mixing it up right now
just Naturally by doing this vimergy
check out their Black Friday sale right
now if you get over $200 worth of stuff
you get a free liquid B12 almost 4 oz
it's insane the crap that's in B12
bottles all across the land I don't care
who says what and they got the best
stuff going on they buy the lower
quality they buy the lower
tier I've seen it all out there that's
why I support Vin that's why I work with
them because of this fact that that's
what the companies do out
there