Anthony William the medical medium live
right here onto YouTube and I have
special guests right here Annika
Benjamin peace hi hi they're here from
Germany they flew all the way from
Germany we're here right now so this is
crazy we're here in LA as we speak and
this is amazing so we're gonna talk
about the healing stories that that
Annika has and cover some other things
too and this is just a great time for us
all to be together right here seriously
you guys took that flight all the way
here
flight ins was like being yes thank you
for having us you know your healing
stories are powerful because they can
help so many other people out there find
their way and you know when you can't
find answers and you know you're going
to doctor the doctor and you feel that
kind of hopelessness take over and you
realize that you know you're really sick
it's just it's so important to have a
way out or to have information that
makes sense and you know that's why I
mean you guys are warriors really you
are your health warriors you're here
you're fighting for the people and
that's what you're doing I mean I know
I've seen your work out there it's the
first time we've ever met which is
really exciting all on its own and but
I've watched your work on social media
and how much you care about people and
how invested you are about getting the
message out so people can heal and and
find the answers they need you guys
really care yeah us I've always noticed
I'm a big role model for us because you
care for for the humanity and this is so
important for us and we want to give the
light to other people that they can
actually heal because healing is is so
so it's possible with the right kind of
information yeah
you know it's about empowerment and
healing empowerment you know we get
disempowered and I talk about that a lot
lately is that you know when we're told
their body's attacking itself and we're
told that you know it's our genes and
we're it's whole or creating it that's a
whole nother thing do you ever hear that
is that just me talking about that all
the time but because I've always I heard
that out there where people are like you
know maybe I'm creating this with me you
know with my mic my sickness because I'm
thinking the wrong way did you go
through that that was exactly what
doctors told me so when I got to the
doctor's office my first diagnosis was
Hashimoto and emoto's and next psoriasis
psoriasis at writers and artists writers
came up well they always told me okay
Anika your body is destroying yourself
and you have to live with this and
probably you will not be you will not be
able to get an old age so you have to
learn to live with this and you're
servicing your mind has problem because
you know you are sick and you're getting
sicker because you think that you are
sick so it was it was weird so we get
told and that's what happens with women
right now where we think women are
empowered but yet they're disempowered
in the worst worst way we could ever
possibly imagine in our history right
now which is their bodies and their
health and so we it's like almost like a
joke being played on everybody out there
Alaura it's almost like no one wants to
talk about this and it's spirit of
compassion is is who gave me this
information all these years you guys
know I talk about that and and so and
spirit of compassion always said to me
women women this empowerment is going to
be at its all-time high where we are now
and that's unimaginable when you think
about it because how is that possible
how can we even think about that being
that way but when we're told our bodies
are too immense you when we're told our
bodies are destroying itself our body's
immune systems are attacking glands and
organs and that you know and then and
then it
that's it since they don't have an
answer for why you're sick they don't
have an answer research and science
doesn't have an answer it's not the
doctors fault doctors are great but
because they don't have the answer then
all of a sudden people try to figure out
well maybe it's a attraction maybe it's
how we're thinking maybe it's we're
manifesting it that is disastrous
because that might be great for other
things that aren't your body that might
be okay for like I want to attract a
good relationship I want to manifest a
good relationship I want to manifest
love I want to manifest this and what a
manifest a good job a good career I want
to manifest them that's great but when
it comes down to health so when it comes
down to why we're sick while we're going
through so much when we feel like we do
what we have all these symptoms it's
disasterous to think that we may be
manifest at that yeah and that's
happening right now I'm seeing that all
the time because research science
doesn't have the answers everybody's
running around sick and then you get
healthier people who haven't been sick
yet say to other women other young women
like no you're just you're not you're
not on your game right you're not you're
not like connecting up there you're not
spiritually connected because you're not
doing what you're supposed to do and
you're not like and that's disaster so
that's a whole nother form of
disempowerment I'm seeing growing
rapidly because once again nobody has
the answers to chronic illness
absolutely I think you desperately
empowered women so it's so important in
our work not just physical level also on
a mental mental level so Benjamin is
icon is a psychologist and we are
working a lot with some mental part of
healing recovering people because of the
wounds from your bodies destroying
itself the wounds of being siccola got a
loan of going through that because when
you feel hopeless and you're in that
place you get into a dark place people
get into a dark post I've been watching
that for 35 years and maybe even a
little longer than that and so when I
was little
and you know this is our place you can
go into and so I just knew you guys are
doing amazing work that's why I had a
you know I have to get them here it has
to be the first episode of this season
has to be you guys because you guys are
you guys are world changers and and and
that matters to me with the informations
tell me a little bit about your story
too and I know we're going a little bit
into - you're going to different doctors
and you're diagnosed with Hashimoto's
you're diagnosed with with us right so
this all started ten years ago when I
was a young college student Benjamin and
I were a young couple and we lived a
fully flat laugh we were very happy and
absolutely yeah
then out of a sudden symptoms started I
remember the date quite well went to the
bus station and out of a sudden I got
very dizzy and got something called
brain fog today I know it is brain fog
because you have a radio show about it
and you talking you books about it and
let me ask you for example here's all
the information in about brain fog and
this was such a hard symptom for me to
live this because when you have brain
fog you can't move through you your
normal daily life your normal business
I became awesome I also got a lot of
symptoms neurological symptoms nag
neurological fatigue tingling numbness
and fatigue is the whole thing with that
is that this medical meeting information
it's neurological fatigue because
doctors never put fatigue with
neurological together before that never
happened and either did research in
science it's either your fatigue and
that's it your fatigue but
neurologically fatigue means that
there's something going out the center
that your central nervous system is
having trouble and that's causing your
fatigue and there's so much information
I talk about that but so you have the
neurological fatigue going on the tables
and and and tiredness all day long
yeah you had you had to do the mattress
island thing I call it mattress island
where we're you know we spend more time
in bed than we want to that's right and
that's hard that's hard for women
because women and men too of course but
it's hard for anyone to who wants to
move and groove and they want to get
things done they want to like work hard
they want to survive they want and then
you start feeling then you start feeling
like well I'm not productive right my
studies yeah I had to stop it and other
symptoms man tinnitus how old are you 23
23 it's 10 years ago yes today so when
everything today I'm 33 and begins 10
years ago and I had tinnitus
and flowers in my eyes and problem was
my that was my vision so everything
around me was just in a like brain
focus and that's why why it's called
right yeah it was it was a hard time but
I am a lucky one because I have my my
husband and he was on my side every
every time on this on this journey and
there's a tough losing but it's I
learned so so much the last 10 years and
after seven years of chronic illness and
a bunch of symptoms I found your first
book medical medium and I think is it is
better than right it's a quite funny
story actually because I came home from
work and Anika was sitting on the couch
and reading this blue book and looking
with me looking to me was was tears in
her eyes and and I recognized
immediately that that aren't tears of
sadness but I couldn't find the onions
she mustered so as I was looking at all
the onions where was it
years came from but I couldn't find them
just tears of joy and then she looked at
me and said okay honey I finally found
the answer yeah and this was was like
and and I believe her immediately
and we went through so hard times and
and it was sometimes we were so
desperate of looking for answers looking
looking for solutions and but when when
you looked at me I like okay Wow yeah
give it a try when I read your book I
know this is the truth this is not just
an idea or opportunity in your
opportunity I tried so many diets and
lifestyle changes and therapies but I
never saw it okay this is the answer but
when I read your book everything makes
sense you you gave me so much relief so
from our heart for my entire being so
from my perspective it was like Anika
felt understood like finally someone
understood her and it's not saying I'll
you're you're making this with your mind
or or you're overreacting
your drama ring and stuff like that so
finally you had some feeling that that
you someone understood you yeah and
that's a great thing in our daily work
when we work with clients guiding them
through their illnesses with your
information the moment when they realize
that their body is not destroying itself
yeah yeah and that they are not that
they have not that they have not sorry
just have to find the right word that
the illnesses are not their fault
forward wasn't but then it is like magic
happens and this is part of empowerment
you're talking about this is so
important to realize it's not your fault
and you can do something against it you
know what happens is
but that was the plan that was the plan
for a spirit of compassion so when I was
writing that book you know it was it and
I was taking down the information I was
writing word-for-word with spirit of
mash it was telling me that's right now
in the words and you know it's like it
made sense to me
every Devery sentence was it made sense
and I was like so this is going to speak
to the ones that that need the answers
and spirit clash was like that's the
plan is that they see what they're
really going through and there is a way
out and that it that there I remember
writing that your body doesn't attack
itself and your immune system doesn't
attack itself in that first book I
remember writing sentence for me this
was so oh my gosh what this is crazy i
but in a good way
that's perfect it's so helpful and this
was so full of come compassion for me
part of me a big part of me wishes that
that I I had that book out years and
years earlier like I was supposed to do
and but the waiting lists in the
millions of people waiting for help I
had to help daily everyday I was hoping
you know 30 to 50 people a day and seven
days a week and had that was had a
24-hour service people can call me in
the middle of the night and I and I and
I was always always there for everybody
in that way and and then and so I hope
but I always wanted that book to be out
to the whole world so it wasn't just
about reaching me because people say oh
I have to get a hold of him I have to
reach him
now the books are there so you don't
have to reach me yeah also you can heal
and your make this you can do in Germany
and and other places around the world
and that's that's what it's for
yeah and absolutely and so great in
Germany when we went in also in Austria
and Switzerland when we went to the book
star stars there are all your books
there and people see them and buy them
and going to social media and looking
for more input and informations and it's
so so great so you are very well known
in Germany right now that well that's
incredible it truly is it's a it's a
it's a dream because that's what I want
I want I want people to have that
information so when you found that book
and you're reading and you're like oh my
god this is truth this is the answer
this is this is the information and then
Benjamin and you came home and you start
crying without on it so were you were
you like oh no now we got all this work
okay now we have this work to do to heal
and but you guys I mean you you jumped
into it yeah it's it's so nice to have a
little bit more control because when
someone is telling you your body is
attacking yourself you feel out of
control
and when when and you gave me my my
control back what's your information
know that for sure I have to be honest
healing and detoxing is not an easy way
it's not like starting and a few days
later you feeling like if you go on
taking after it's not like taking a pill
oh it is is this um you have work to do
and but when you have faith and trust is
in your body then you go for it and you
will heal and this is just the most
amazing thing I've ever done in my life
to start this healing healing journey
and to trust to trust you to just spirit
to trust myself in my body and I want I
want everybody to have their control
back over their health and I know that
when people aren't that sick and they
haven't been there yet and they haven't
been in the trenches where you were okay
and they only have a little bit of acne
which is no fun or they only have maybe
a little bit of Aksum on it kind of
comes and goes a little bit but they're
able to go and they're able to work out
every day and they're able to live their
life and run around and get their coffee
drinks and and they're able to get off a
gluten
and somebody gives them advice to do
this and somebody clears up a little war
they feel a little bit better here and
there and they're not in that place
they're not in that place they still
feel like they got control as they play
guessing games and and but when you get
when when that shifts and stuff starts
to catch up and and you start getting
sick and things that like pathogens that
people don't even know about or talk
about or in your system that are in the
medical medium book so people can learn
and you learn and all of a sudden you're
going to those doctors and you're really
getting appointments and you're really
and you're losing your in the fatigue
and you're getting the brain fog and
you're not able to do that workout in
the gym for an hour and a half every day
and you're not able to and you can't
really think and you can't see you feel
so fatigued once it goes then you just
you realize that no we don't have
control and I always tell people don't
let it get to that point learn the
information to where where you can heal
and come back from such difficult times
and struggles and what's what's
disheartening out there and what I see
is there's people that play around in
the whole guessing game land because
they're not really sick sick they really
haven't gone into the having been
through hell and back or anything
they're just playing around and they're
playing around and I understand that but
it's sad because there's so much noise
out there
to play around with yeah so much yeah
and people are realized this is the only
information it's ever been out there he
gets you out of the trenches was this
originally and it wasn't just oh try
this diet you can play around keto try
this go do this don't do this go do this
and it wasn't this get rid of processed
foods get rid of get rid of gluten try
this you know it wasn't that only that
this is this is the this is the heart of
wait a minute it's way worse than that
you know I I'm told my body is
destroying itself I can't get out of bed
I'm on mattress island i'm on couch
island and i don't have control and in
your you're somebody that fought your
way back you found information you
fought your way back
back in ensure okay sure the books are
there the information set but it takes
also somebody to be like you know I'm I
gotta I gotta do this
I'm tired this I don't want to live like
this anymore see so you're liking you're
a hero you need to use it you need to
use the information it's not enough that
the information is there you need to
read it and to reread it and to think
about it and to live with it and this is
what I did I not only read your books
once I read it I read them quite a few
times and sometimes I reread some some
pages because I always find another a
new thing
when a new and you think when I read
different places and you can actually
this is the magical trainer yes and I
think this is a magical thing about your
books I found answers for all my
symptoms and I had a list it was so long
just symptoms from literally from head
to toe nearly every part of my body had
at least one symptoms and I found
answers for every single symptom in your
book and the connection between them and
everything makes sense and this was so
Wow absolutely mind-blowing what's
important to have answers to all the
different symptoms to like why is the
symptom there what's causing the symptom
because that's not anywhere else and
it's just not there research and science
doesn't have it for anyone they just
don't have any answers it's your genes
are bad or your body's destroying itself
or if you go in kind of the new-age area
that all like and you're not spiritually
connected your your manifesting it wrong
and that's why that's why your sake we
can't accept that that's not acceptable
it's not supposed to be okay to be the
new normal for every single person have
a symptom or five symptoms your case
like 15 symptoms
maybe even more and it's not it's not
right to have to live like that
and so look you know what I love is I
love it that that you've you've come
this far okay
and I love that you're doing the work
you're doing and I love all of that and
I love how your you know your that that
spiritual power in a way that is the
guide for people and I see it that way
it's like well if I was ever sick if I
was ever sick if I was ever down and out
if I was ever struggling if I was just
if I was stuck in that place of not
having control and you are like Anthony
their third there are answers and you
put your hand out I would just be like
yeah just get me out of this and yes
you're doing for people I yeah I hope so
and I do this because it's so it's so
it's an important work and yeah so thank
you very much and what I realized is
when you live this way with a clean diet
who has a lot of fruits and veggies and
when you're detoxing your spiritual your
spirituality I saw before the
pronouncing I hope you guys understand
me
is is clear clearer so you have a better
contact to the spirituality I hope you
understand what I want you I need you
had all these books and everything bring
you spiritual and I'm like okay I'm
hearing a voice from up here giving me
advance medical information and also
other information I'm writing it down in
here I don't know if I'm spiritual I
don't know what you would call it what
do you mean because people say what how
are you really spiritual though and well
I'm getting the information from up here
I don't know if that accounts for being
spiritual because I'm not doing the
spiritual talk that's maybe trending so
much you know where everybody's doing
the spiritual vibe or a spiritual talk
that's trending so much and I'm not like
gee I'm not I'm always talking about
illness and sickness and people
struggling and and because I feel that
that's the most spiritual place you
could ever go is someone's struggle
there because you lose your spirit when
you're sick right so I don't know
anything more spiritual than that where
you're sick you're not feeling good
you're your there's a part of you you're
losing you're feeling like you're losing
you get the hopelessness for so many
people going through it your spirits
breaking down I've had people come to me
over the years when they get a chance to
talk to me all these years ago and they
would get a chance to talk to me and
they'd be like my spirits broken yeah my
spirit is broken and so I don't think
there's anything more spiritual than
getting somebody's life back because
it's not about a spiritual mumbo-jumbo
or still like it's not like spiritual
trending words or anything it's about
when you get your life back there's
nothing more spiritually powerful than
that yes because we all have souls well
we work we're spiritual beings here
doesn't matter how we kind of cookie cut
it or how we dress it up or how we gloss
it up or what's trending or how we talk
it's about worse more spiritual beings
and when we're losing our lives and
we're in that dark place and we're in
that dark hopelessness and we're
suffering and we're struggling and our
spirits are broken and I mean I people
tell me that over the years this is what
it feels like and you come back from
that that's spiritual empowerment that's
that's what that is and you know and and
I've had people come back from from the
depths of of despair from healing like
with you from from being sick and and
you become my spiritually
do you feel like do you feel it's that
tool away to you like it's almost like I
get a new chance yeah absolutely there's
something about that having that new
chance is a new chance and you wrote it
so so wonderful in one of your books you
said that we have a part of our soul so
upwards in the universe behind the Stars
and that even if we are so so broken and
feel so emotional tired and lost that we
can connect with this part of our soul
and when I read that I stood outside
looking to the Stars and cried now that
that we have the the heel part of our
soul to connect this yeah it gets me
choked up and because they remember when
spirit of compassion told me that and so
I put it in the book and and I remember
when spirit compassion told me that long
before I even put it in in the book
because I would tell people I would say
you if if you feel you're in that place
right now people would come to me so
sick and I'd say look I just want you to
look at the Stars
and I want you to know that there's a
there's a part of your soul that stays
protective up there in those stars
behind those stars and there's a part of
you that stays protected it's there for
a reason because we get broken down here
we go through betrayal we go through the
trust to breakage we grow when when
someone breaks your trust when someone
stabs you in the back when somebody
betrays you when someone hurts you and
someone if we go through so much
different kind of letdowns here from
emotional upsets and breakups and all
kinds of things that we have
relationship people that people go
through problems and all these things
kick just if you like it wrecks you
there's a part of your soul that stays
untouched and free from all of that way
up spirit of compassion told me and you
just have to look up you have to look up
behind those stars and you know it's
there
for you and connect with it and that's
gonna give you that extra power to start
that battery power in your soul and in
your spirit to start bringing you back
while you're working on your healing
process I remember this was a long time
before and we read your books was when I
was back in New Zealand and I had this
bad bad injury and I almost died was was
bleeding brain and I'm during this time
before that happened one of my greatest
fears was always death not dying but
death and then I got this experience and
I almost died and the doctors in Germany
couldn't understand how I survived and
it was so funny but and and but but what
happened was like that it was like I was
staying there in front of the door
knocking and and someone said no not
soon it's not your time and this really
changed my thinking about Wow and it was
amazing and this was was before we read
your books and then your books came and
it was again like wow yes it's right
what what you experienced this is real
yeah that's incredible that's a powerful
story going to near-death and doctors
wondering if you're gonna make it
exactly I you know what I wanted to ask
you guys like your foods and supplements
and you're doing things like that so
what are you doing for the foods I mean
I have a heavy metal detox ability of
course always in front of me juice is so
important for us because when we started
with celery juice it was three years ago
the first thing we realized was the
Benjamin get rid of his exit reflux so
the celery juice accelerate roses was
the first change in our diet the celery
juice and he had
bad exit reflux for his entire life
since childhood and in as a child you
saw it is quite normal to have such
burning in your throat right no I think
I I told my parents when I was 16 or so
and but I experienced I think the first
time I remember it was was 5 and since I
said okay we need to do something we
need to do a gastro and send I looked
and said today this yeah and and yeah
and I took pills so long and I always
had the feelings it's not right it's not
right and even when I was studying
nursing I it was like oh my god I can't
take such pills anymore cuz what am i
what am i doing I'm it's just trying my
whole guts was this pills and I didn't
want to do it anymore and finally it was
amazing you know your whole life
spending with having reflux or knowing
that you're doing something better your
body and was kind of a big relief
business celery juice and well how long
did you do the soul just before it start
easing up a few weeks I think I was so
fast and so it's very fast so we changed
a little bit more we cut off for no food
so everything that feed viruses and
bacteria we cut off so X and diary and
gluten and because I thought okay there
are these box viruses and bacteria and
they are making me sick and I don't want
to feed them one day longer so this was
my decision and so I cut off the no
foods you know the people say well how
can X be bad for you everybody's still
being told to eat eggs they're so like
you know it had some women are being
told every day young women just eat eggs
make sure you get your protein make sure
you get your healthy here healthy eggs
in you and all the stuff and it's really
sad because
eggs actually feed everything that makes
us sick the reason why were six these
pathogens and you know so when I did
with with the new cleanse the heal book
coming out i I really pushed spirit of
compassion really hard with the new
cleansing heal book so this is this is
actually that this isn't a book it's
simple this is mine did my copy which is
the manuscript I'm editing right here
this is and but it's it's on Amazon if
you want to find it um cleanse the heal
it's coming out soon
but anyway so what I did was I really
pushed spirit of compassion hard I said
I want all the information you can give
me on why eggs are hurting us and why we
need to stay away from them because you
know a shirt you told me it feeds
pathogens I want all of this information
so people can be armed and they can be
protected and they can have that shield
of protection to know that if they're
dealing with brain fog and you know
tinkles of numbness fibromyalgia
Hashimoto's and actually psoriasis
whatever it is that you don't want to do
eggs so it's really critical that you
don't do eggs and so spirit gave me so
much information about eggs and why we
shouldn't be eating them and it I love
eggs it's not even like it's not even
like I hate them or anything like that I
don't and people people are like way to
me you must have Lee system you just
don't like them or something no that's
not it they taste really really good
that's the whole problem and it's a
man-made thing right because we used
they used them in the last yes what
that's what that's that's what research
in science that's what the
pharmaceutical companies did they took
eggs a survival food that kept people
alive in so many situations around the
world because they were an important
food and they took that food and they
used it as a fuel source for pathogens
they raised in the lab back eighty years
ago ninety years ago like 80 years like
70 80 years ago all in that realm
and they still they still use them and
no one knows about it they don't talk
about it and no one gets that
information so what happens is when you
have the epstein-barr causing your
neurological fatigue your aches and
pains your eczema your psoriasis your
Hashimoto's your thyroid problems your
your fibromyalgia your your all these
different things are the shingles fires
causing your trigeminal neuralgia and
your neuropathy all these different
things that people are dealing with
every day then you eat eggs you're just
feeding that bug you're feeding that
epstein-barr you're feeding that
shingles virus and it's going to town
it's it's eating it's it's staying
strong and you stay sick and you know
it's amazing how you know the people are
so emotionally connected to eggs and I
read your books I ate just eggs and meat
and diary prologue says this was my diet
because bacon eggs and bacon and doctors
told me you have to stay away from fruit
so the fruit fear was going around and
this was the worst thing I think about
my diet no fruit no a lot of fat and no
very rare red veggies just meat eggs and
it was like it worked for for Buffett I
guess when we were just just diet like
some Munson's and my whole system
collapsed
well the reason why there what happens
is when you go off of processed foods
and and you just go on say eggs meat
dairy you're gonna feel a little better
you are because you're all for processed
foods it's just so just say somebody
wasn't as sick as you and they just had
a little bit of eczema a little bit of
brain fog once in a while maybe maybe
they just didn't feel like they had that
much energy or they had some acne and
there then then there they're told stay
off of processed foods but make sure you
keep your eggs in there soon as they get
off the processed foods you're gonna
start feeling better and they think they
found the Holy Grail they think that oh
wait a minute could still have some eggs
still have some of this don't have some
salmon still have you know lots of nuts
and sea
seeds still have some peanuts the seeds
are healthy but having a lot of them is
not really a good idea you can still
have all these different high-fat foods
or you can still have some cheese
healthy cheese some yogurt some he can
still have these things and then what
happens is what they don't realize
though is that they'll get a little bit
better they'll start feeling a little
bit better and then all of a sudden you
know things can take a turn down the
road or they'll just stay in that
guessing game area where they can get
away with just eating the trendy diet
keeping eggs and but when you're
somebody that really high and it can get
you in trouble go down a road you start
getting a little older and then it hits
and you start getting all your heart
palpitations and eat camp you know
office and live your life and you get
all these other things but with you you
were really at this place where you had
a lot of a lot of stuff going on like
millions of people do millions of women
do they have all these symptoms okay
and you you went off the processed food
and you just you kept your diet really
clean like doctors wanna you kept like
the eggs you kept the bacon in there you
kept right and you noticed a difference
you were feeling a little bit better yes
when everybody goes on their keto diet
there are Paleo diet and when you eat
such yes high-fat diets you produce so
much adrenaline and this is why you feel
a little bit better I think um yeah and
this was a first step for me cutting out
the no foods drinking celery juice and
the heavy-metal detox smoothie was was
very important because because I had so
so many heavy metals and my body
floating around they play a huge part in
this brain fog and so I started very
slowly with the heavy metal detox
smoothie on a daily base and yeah we
still drink it every day it was full
amounts of every ingredient and I think
that's the most important part yes you
started and I just followed yeah and
what we experienced was that I could
handle more than you could yeah you for
example was the celery juice as well as
heavy-metal detox smoothie and I just
followed and I had my own to be honest
my up and downs might a few transaction
costs because I I wasn't coming from
this bad situation as Annika was so and
this is a funny thing about your mind
cause because I just experienced that I
felt better quite fast and then this
little man in my head was like oh yeah
now you can try it again go back to your
own behavior and I needed some you asked
about supplements so I take a lot to be
honest I took a lot and I take a lot and
my favorite supplements lemon balm
because lemon born always grounded me on
an emotional level and it helps my
nervous system because when you have a
problem so this is just my opinion but
when you had a problem with your nervous
system for such a long period of time
then this is nothing that changed
overnight
so I'm three years on this journey right
now with your information and I healed a
lot so I never thought three years ago
that I will ever reach such a healthy
state for me in my body you know what's
amazing is you guys do just the medical
medium information you don't mix it up
you're not adding in the apple cider
vinegar you're not you know you're not
adding in the collagen you're not adding
in all these other things you're not
mixing it up we're we're including
changing up foods and doing this where
you're getting all this misinformation
on the Internet
you guys are sticking with this
information here that the the
information that's swapping the internet
that's both good and bad
is is a compilation of just guessing
games that are man-made and I always try
to tell people this because someone will
say to me why do I want medical medium
information why would I want your
information because it's not man-made
it's not manly right and and that means
it's not contaminated with guessing
games or interests money behind it or
investors behind it or trendsetters
behind it that have investment nesters
or whatever it is or research and
science where there's a thumb on the
scale so no one gets fired I'm in the in
the in I've had scientists tell me you
don't want if you want to keep your job
you better produce a result whether you
like it or not one thing whether you see
something bad you don't talk about what
you see bad you just scientists they
just gotta talk about a one little thing
that might have been positive because
you don't want to never work again in
the science field that I've heard that
from so many different scientists it's
like either scientists have they have
this this common saying which do you
want to work again or do you never want
to work again yeah and so so well this
isn't man-made information and the
information works so when I started with
your information and to change my diet
and so in my lifestyle at the time I got
my breast implants removed I had breast
implants for eight years of my life and
you have a radio show about breasts and
containers and breast implant illness is
a real thing it's not the cause of
chronic illness but it's a huge trigger
of course you have those influence in
your body and they are full of heavy
metals and other toxic stuff and you
wearing it under your skin and it's
always there and it's a big trigger and
a great place for bacteria to live in
and so I've got the breast implants
removed and I recovered so so quick with
your diet information from this surgery
it was a big surgery because the
implants were
everywhere my body literally and
connected to my bones so this was big
surgery and I recovered so so quick with
celery juice with mangoes they were
played at mangos like always a time and
this was so this was like hey that was
fruit you know it people have to
understand that some people like many
women can have the breast implants and
not experience any problems because in
that moment they don't have an Epstein
bar that's actually basically out of the
running out of the gate and and running
around through the body causing trouble
they don't have a shingles they don't
have multiple Epstein bars they don't
have an hhv-6 they don't have a
cytomegalovirus they don't have a
simplex one or two and or they don't
have a really bad bad mix of them all
you know what happens is that is that
but you can have the breast implants and
then they're creating toxins you're
creating toxins or discharging toxins
and there's nothing feeding on those
toxins until you end up picking up your
first step scene bar in a relationship
or you pick you up at the first Epstein
bar in a restaurant because you chefs
cut their finger or you pick up your
first step steam bar sharing some
glasses because someone would happen to
be really viral in that moment and
you're at a party and they're sharing
bottles or glasses and you get your
first EBV and you're at now your your
breast implants they become a trigger
because they're just like having saying
toxic heavy metals in your body it's
just like having something else in your
body and you know the toxins I talked
about in cleanse the heel which I cover
toxins like no one's ever known about
what's inside our body all the way to to
just luggage went in the airport on how
you have to throw away your your
carry-ons after you've gone through the
airports for a few trips cuz the amount
of radiation that's in the carry-on and
you don't want that near your child you
don't want that you know sitting by your
bed at night you don't want that you
want to throw away your carry-ons
eventually
so I tell people don't get real
expensive carry-ons because you're gonna
need to toss it after a couple of trip
few trips good to know radiation but the
point is is that all these toxins were
dealing with our triggers and breast
implants it's just it's like that it's
one of those triggers it's a big trigger
and I was so happy to get rid of them
and the surgery was was big I already
said that and I recovered so fast year
before that in 2016 I had appendicitis
and surgery as well and I need five
months to recover from that surgery ages
it took me so long it was before my my
breast surgery so the surgery for the
appendix was half a year before and I
had so many trouble to to recover from
that because I've got anti buttocks and
antibiotics after surgery and all
streptococcus and my body said hooray
let's have a party
in this girl so streptococcus is a big
big part and huge yeah doctor so know
it's a streptococcus they don't know
they don't know they don't know that
that's they know that yeah that you've
learned that from them that mean
information because that's the whole
thing in the strep groups are what
causes our our appendix to get inflamed
for so long that's those strep groups
and you know from sinuses the tonsils
to-to-to sore throats mystery mysterious
sore throats - - bloating reflux strep
is behind so I still have acne after
surgery it's amazing you know every time
every time a friend will be like you
know I was watching a YouTube or I was I
was on social media and there's another
person talking about their acne and how
you know
and they don't have a single clue their
acnes caused by streptococcus and
they're just getting information from
either some type of practitioner or
their doctor or a health coach and
they're just telling them oh it's your
hormones or use this cream or or change
this food but not know why it could help
or not help or might help but might not
and everybody's still running around and
you see it's just you know no matter how
many years I've been putting out the
truth that cystic acne and acne problems
are streptococcus and and how you have
to get rid of that strep to really get
rid of that no matter how many years it
puts it out you still see it every day
people tell me I still people tell me
like you know there's still a new person
on YouTube now open another ten more
people saying it's hormones or something
so may I ask you a question at symmetric
caucus is it is it about what is about
beans and lentils when it comes to
streptococcus well what it is what it is
this is is beans lentils they don't feed
viruses and pathogens so beans and
grains don't feed those those kinds of
beans like lentils and and dukey beans
black beans chickpeas garbanzo beans
they don't feed bugs and and grains like
millet okay
and even oats don't feed bugs but but
they still if you're eating too much of
it they don't offer Oh enough nutrition
so you're taking up so much space
because they don't offer that much
nutrition I mean compared to feed you
could meet it and that's one thing right
there it's really important no but but
gluten based grains are the ones that
feed viruses they feed pathogens and all
that it's just that when you're eating
too many grains too much rice you're
taking up a lot of space for what you
can you know and I talked about it all
and cleanse the heel - all about that
like all about beans and grains and
stuff and so but Anthony coos and I I
read that beans and vandals form mucus
in our body yeah just that this could be
a problem within some people because
they're not they're not
easily digestible because everybody's
digestion czar just there shot
everybody's hydrochloric acid stomach
lands are producing the HCL their
digestion is weakened their livers their
livers are weakened so when you're
putting you know you're putting in a lot
of beans and a lot of grains they're
they're they're harder to break down
they're harder to digest so it's not
that they're feeding pathogens it's just
they're really hard to digest so you
want to get your ACL your each CL better
you want your celery juice you want to
get your diet strong then you can bring
in could bring in a few things like that
you know you can bring you know so yeah
but I talk all about that Quincy heel
but I am I am blown away that I have you
guys here this has been an incredible
incredible time and I just want to say
I'm honored know you're helping so many
that are watching yeah definitely trying
out that I always say that - we just
hope - yeah and no you guys are you guys
I'm so okay I guess we're gonna be we're
gonna be signing off this was the first
episode of the second season YouTube
live Annika
Benjamin beast we're here so just want
to say bless your heart everybody take
care know that I love you much