we're live right now live on facebook
live on youtube live on tick tock live
on clubhouse
we're doing immune system building this
is a critical
critical live right here you might want
to take notes
because it's that important medical
medium information was always about
rebuilding the immune system medical
medium information
was the only that knew about all the
different viruses
of the epstein-barr sediment virus what
people were up against with shingles
what the symptoms are relating to these
viruses which was never known as far as
symptoms
and how to protect ourselves including
the flu viruses
and other bugs like that too so really
important also mm info
let everybody know how to protect their
immune system originally
before the plague and i talked about
and right actually during the place and
i talked about the new edition
medical medium new edition right here
revised and expanded
i talked about that information about
the plague we're up against now and how
it works and
how that instigates the epstein bar
and causes these epstein bars to come
out other viruses to come out too so
we're talking about rebuilding the
immune system
i'm making thyme tea time water
i'm doing the zinc shock therapy vitamin
c
shock therapy i'm also going to juice a
little celery juice because he can't
underestimate the power of
that humble herb so let's get going you
guys we're live on tick tock
we're live on youtube we're live on
facebook live on clubhouse right now
good to see you guys honored you're all
coming on and uh
incredible you know this is this is an
important and poor i mean i'm not saying
that the other lives aren't important
you guys
i'm not saying that they are they're
always packed with information right
and but this one right here is
you know i every now and then time
passes and i
too much time passes i feel and i don't
cover it with you guys again i'm like
wait a minute i think everybody's doing
their immune system building
i think they're doing their zing i think
they're doing their golden seal i think
they're doing
their lemon balm i think they're doing
their time t but they're not
not everybody right and just some people
and it's like okay well
when it comes down to immune system
that's how we can protect ourselves but
it's not just about
taking things to do that it's about
knowing why it happens you guys like on
tick tock i'm telling you now
it's important to know how zinc works in
your system
how it makes the bugs the pathogens the
viruses
docile that's important and then we lose
all our zinc
people don't have zinc in their bodies
they don't have it there it's a critical
trace mineral
and the reason why they don't have it
there it's not in your food
it's not in your food some will say
oysters oysters eat some oysters to get
your zinc are you kidding
me you're gonna get more mercury than
you are if anything
abby said this shock therapy really
works
uh oh my god you've done it so you've
done the zinc
one using vimergy's ink a few times
even when you feel a sore throat coming
on and it works that's that's the whole
point it's about
when you feel that sore throat coming on
and everything too um
the only one that i've ever used for
that i trust is the vimergi zinc right
there that's the one
so if you guys want to know i'm not
sponsored but it's the one
that i feel works for my family and for
my friends
um so yeah so it's really cool zinc
shock therapy i'm going to do in a
couple of minutes we're going to do a
little bit of that
do the vitamin c shock therapy too i'm
just waiting for
everybody to kind of come on right now
you know clubhouse two wait for you guys
to come on
so we can do this and doing the time
water so i'll get the time t
going that's an important one zinc shock
therapy is amazing yeah i just saw that
um
yeah it really is it's helped so many
people and where did i get that
information
like chris good to see you came on good
to see you on saturday you said you seem
fine to me good to see you too on
saturday
where did i get that where did this zinc
shock therapy come from
where did it come from am i a genius is
that where it came from
medical medium is a genius no
medium is not a genius i told you there
is medical medium a doctor
is a is he a doctor a genius doctor no
i'm not uh but doctors use medical meme
information they've
asked my help for many decades doing
this work
where does the information come from it
comes from above
where else does this information how
else would you
know about the fact that they're
literally
bleeding you to death that's not because
i'm a genius
no i've always said i'm not that smart
of a guy i'm not a smart guy
athena marie zinc shock therapy and
vitamin c shock therapy
saves us every time knocks anything out
fast
it just does right but
where would i get that information you
guys me
uh so mika says used to have sore throat
my whole childhood zinc helps it stop
throat pain
on the first day yeah it's just it's so
important right
so you know uh a genius lori says yes no
no not a genius no no no no no
definitely not
uh gozak says shock therapies are great
both
work vimergy has a great quality
absolutely because you're not going to
the vimorgy the vimergy zinc right and
the vitamin c
like with the zinc you're not going to
get those natural flavors not going to
get citric acid not going to get the
alcohol you're not going to get any of
that
jackie says my husband and i did zinc
and vitamin c shock therapy
and it worked within 24 hours we're
going to do we're going to show
everybody about the zinc shock therapy
in a minute too
um and so someone might say hey you know
there's other zincs out there there's
other things like
liquid sulfates right but what people
don't realize
is those aren't stabilized they're not
stabilized and that's the difference
between vimergy's
zinc versus somebody else's zinc the
other zincs aren't stable
and that's the problem um but where
would i get the information you guys
where would it come from right how would
i know
that they're just taking all your blood
and all they need is a tiny drop
right but no one's talked about it in
all of the medical fields no one's
talked about an alternative medicine no
one caught it
how would i know that people go
backwards and go backwards and go
backwards with their healing they don't
even heal
and that if you have lyme disease
they'll take so much blood from you if
you have lupus they'll take so much
blood for it the ms will take so much
blood cancer
and they'll send you backwards and
remove your immune system is am i a
genius
is that where it comes from no i'm not a
it comes from the information i told you
that it all comes from you guys it comes
from above since age four
right and if you can get past
the fact that i hear a voice since age
four
giving us advanced medical information
then you are open to the tools to heal
you are open to it you are free to heal
right you can you can just you can move
forward and heal
you know you have a friend of mine that
is a doctor you became a new friend of
mine pretty recently he says you know i
always wanted to talk to you it's been
years and years
been wanting to talk to you and and uh
never had the chance you know and
finally get a chance and
it took me a while to get past the whole
thing where you get your information
but you've saved so many lives and i've
heard it from so many doctors now all
around and i've heard
about also a lot of jealous doctors that
that don't like you because they're
tired of hearing your name from all
their patients bringing in the books and
stuff
and he said but it works and and i don't
care where the information comes from
eliza said got very bad allergic
reaction to supplement
yeah you did not recommend buying now
only the ones you are recommending i
mean
there are zincs out there that have all
the citric acid in there it's terrifying
just burn a hole in your throat right
there's there's tinctures out there and
all the alcohol right
you know back it still happens now
people like people like
do medical medium and do this other
person's stuff right they're all because
they're paid to say this stuff and the
other person's stuff
has all this alcohol and all the
tinctures their golden seal has alcohol
in it their tinctures all have alcohol
in it right
and then you got to be careful with the
in the herbal world because in the
herbal world what will happen
okay which works against your immune
system you guys
against your immune system what happens
in the herbal world
right is they got all these tinctures
and and someone just says let's just
throw 20 different herbs in this
tincture
you're getting that much herb like that
much herb
that's all you're getting that much herb
i mean not even a speck
and then it's an alcohol right it's an
alcohol it's not an immune system
builder
their immune system breakers you know so
it really matters supplementation it
matters like what kind you're doing it
matters about understanding it
all these things it just this this is
make or break
you know you get your blood draws you
guys but by the way have you heard the
blood draw
episode i know many of you guys have but
the blood draw okay bloodletting
vampirism medical medium podcast at
apple podcast just letting you guys know
being censored like crazy today on
facebook i could see that
so um but it really matters
having this information you know but is
it because
i'm smart does that work why why all
this information is that why millions
are healing around the world
nope it's not okay um the information in
the books come from the source since age
four
zinc shock therapy is one of those
incredible tools
that i've offered the people that have
come to me in the last 35 plus
years okay so we're doing the vitamin c
shock therapy zinc shock therapy it's in
this book right here this book right now
is
41 off
41 off the medical medium new
edition new edition on amazon us it's 41
off the new edition letting you guys
know of course you can get it free of
the library too i don't control
prices this is the price of amazon and
so forth so i'm letting you know that
there's
there's you know a deal on that which is
happening too
so let's start doing it let's start
making some tea sometime
tea gonna heat up some water right here
you guys don't mind right
got the little tea kettle going i'm
gonna do it this way with this tea
kettle
right uh paula on tick tock
these lives keep me on track incredible
i'm honored you're here paula thank you
for coming here
incredible and
so divine light says also the zinc shock
therapy
has saved me so many times it
immediately takes the sore throat away
nobody knew about that that could even
work that that can even be an option
you can go to a thousand doctors
in your lifetime with autoimmune and
everything
a thousand doctors and not
have that information think about how
valuable
that piece of information is i'm
teaching doctors that piece of
information but think about how valuable
that is
that it makes the sore throat go away
you know
and that's not all it does though too so
okay
um we're gonna do i got some tea right
here so i'm gonna take some sprigs of
thyme
right you can do two sprigs of time what
i really love about this okay and i'm
gonna
kind of bunch it up so the sprigs guys i
got fresh thyme right
here okay i'm gonna bunch it up a little
bit like that let me see here there you
go i want to turn this around
make a nice little what two sprigs this
is like
yeah this is more than two two sprigs
but i'm showing you that you can do
more than the two sprigs is a minimum
it's got to be minimum two sprigs right
so i'm putting these sprigs down in here
like that okay
so i'm gonna actually um i place the
fresh thyme in the mug
i'm gonna pour water in here now hot
water
okay we're gonna talk about this time
tea all right and i'm gonna steep it for
15 minutes
and as i'm steeping it we're going to
talk about how incredible it is
sound good and i'm going to answer
questions too possibly
yeah it's the vimorgy's ink on tick tock
that's the one right there
v is in victor i m as in mary ergy dot
com themorgy.com
um you used to suffer so
rena says i used to suffer from constant
strep throat
since doing zinc shock therapy no more
meds for four
years is that valuable
is that worth anything is it
the trolls to think it's not worth
anything you know people think it's not
worth anything that's worth
everything everything
i mean that's a lot of struggle and
suffering all the doctors visits give me
the antibiotics give me the antibiotics
that's what happens
it's like you got the strep throat
coming back boom doctor's office more
antibiotics and guess what
now it's utis boom utis
now it's chronic sinusitis more
antibiotics now it's boom back to the
sore throat strep throat more
antibiotics
now it's back to boom uti now strep
throat uti bladder infection strep
throat kidney infection chronic
sinusitis styes in the eyes
you know conjunctivitis back to back to
sore throat back to strep throat
back to bladder infections back this is
how it works right
and so and then more more antibiotics
and more antibiotics
right so we're going to talk about the
time in a second i just saw somebody ask
about that on tic tac
so we're going to also get some time
infused water going so i got the thyme
infused
tea which is a medical medium tool right
proud to say it is truly
because of how many people it has helped
and from where the information comes
from
i'm steeping it for 15 minutes so you
know we might not be on that exact 15
minute mark it could be a little after
whatever happens naturally
because we're live right here this is in
a studio recording where
everything's picture perfect right time
infused water but first of all i have to
infuse the time water that's number one
so i'm gonna put sprigs in here now
um and i'm gonna soak the sprigs in here
so that's what we're gonna do we're
gonna be putting fresh sprigs you soak
it overnight
in a pitcher of room temperature water
so we'll do that
let's get the i'm turning the sprigs
around a little bit
there we go got my sprigs ready right
here
okay sprigs go right in that water just
like this
okay i'm gonna add some lemon
let's cut a lemon i don't know why i
have to throw everything in the air
what i do put a little bit of lemon in
there
not yet though let me just hold off for
a second let me just get this thing
going
you know lemon slices is what we're
going to put in there how about that
we'll do lemon slices
so on the lemon slices i think
i'll slice them it's optional to do the
lemon slices let me do a couple of
slices of lemon how about that
let's drop those in there nice looks
amazing
all right let's get that going there
this is a great thing you know people
are worried right now they're worried
about something out there
all right and if you guys just came on
we're live on tick tock we're live on
clubhouse we're live on facebook or live
on um
youtube right and people are worried
right now they're worried
they're hearing some rumors hearing some
rumors about
exposure exposure right
and health with liz good to see you on
tick tock this time good to see you
and they're hearing something about
exposure that's what they're hearing
like what do i do for exposure what do i
do for exposure
okay and what i'll tell you what
i'm doing about
something about exposure so let me tell
you what i'm doing
okay i'm doing the time that's what i'm
doing
and if i get exposed to someone i might
even do a little zing shot therapy
or definitely some vitamin c shock
therapy right
that's what i'm doing just letting you
know and
i have i have two of these in my fridge
right now
right here soaking away so i drink the
time infused water
all day long for exposure time is more
powerful
than any other trendy idea
that's starting to come out about
exposure
and i'm not going to try to rip apart
that idea or anything or debunk it right
now or anything like that
but it doesn't work this is what i
prepared everybody for
all along that's the whole point and
it doesn't have to come out now it's
been out
i've been already ahead of the curve
making sure you were prepared
so you had that health with liz you love
the time t incredible
so um but everybody's in a panic right
now not everybody but a lot of people
are in a panic right now
yeah exactly on tick-tock and
they're in a panic right now what do i
do about exposure about something
and so the time is where
that viral exposure lies
that's where the anti-viral nature
for exposure is it's in the time water
it's in the time t i talked about
how the flues the plaguing flues
knock down everybody's immune system
causing
other things to come up which is the
epstein-barr the shingles the hhv-6 the
cytomegalovirus the simplex one to
simplex 2
hhv7 the hhv-8 okay
the hhv 10 through 16 undiscovered all
the different herpetic strains
and viruses and varieties right and so
and i have pandemic information in
medical media
new edition right here you can check it
out like i said it's 41
off on amazon.com or get a free
collaborate
health says you certainly did prepare us
liz
wasn't i right down from the get-go
over a year ago like well over a year
ago making sure you guys were prepared
for
that flu storm for that
whole plague for that pandemic right off
the running
and i did i did instagram lives
facebook lives in january
going all the way back not this january
the january before this january
that would just pass so but then you
know what happens is
then this kind of silly stuff occurs
right and people are like
all of a sudden they're they're chasing
once again the gay guessing game so
they're chasing the guessing games
because of exposure that's what's
happening right now
so once again guessing games right
that's how it works
meanwhile you don't have to have the
guessing game that's the whole point
you don't have to have it yes uh betty
says and given us a whole pdf
with healing tools exactly exactly
and that pdf by the way betty that pdf
went viral it completely
covered the planet viral i can't even
imagine
how many you guys how many people had
that pdf around the planet
and so medical media put the tools out
there
so the guessing games wouldn't have to
be there but then
all of a sudden let's get a new silly
trend
let's get a new guessing game out there
for people who are worried about
exposure
and meanwhile it's like what uh huh okay
all right use something that doesn't
work go ahead
keep on getting sick out there and you
know what you'll end up using medical
medium tools
so we're talking about the zinc shock
therapy talking about vitamin c shock
therapy we're doing the time infused
water we're doing the time
t that's what we have you guys we're
live right now as you know and tick tock
facebook we're live on youtube we're
live on clubhouse
let's talk about the benefits so so what
i love about time is
time okay time hangs in the bloodstream
it stays in the bloodstream okay because
you can take an herb it doesn't mean
it's going to stay in the bloodstream
it doesn't mean it's going to stay in
there long you have to
have something in the bloodstream
that's working for you that's the key
okay
and that's the most important place
right there it has to be
the bloodstream right so what time does
is it hangs
it doesn't go away it doesn't go way
easy
so what i like to do is i like to drink
it on and off all day
so that if i didn't drink it the next
day or didn't drink it the day after the
next day
it was still in my system so it stays in
your bloodstream
for a good couple days lucy good to see
you today
on saturday yeah can we do the time t
during the advanced 369 yes you can
you can do the time t good question
lissy definitely you can
right and so what i like about the time
is it has an everlasting like effect
is what it does right it's the gift that
keeps on giving so it's not like a lot
of herbs a lot of herbs you've got like
a half a day in there
that's what you have a lot of herbs you
got one day in there
and that's just naturally how it works
the herbs can still be amazing
still be incredible like goldenseal
goldenseal is a one-dayer
that's a one-dayer right still critical
still critical for the immune system
still really is really important that's
the bemidji golden seal right
um and so um and i'm not sponsored but
it's the stuff i use
all the time so i use gold and seal all
the time if i think i got a little
exposure boom i'm down in a bunch of
goldenseal
that's what i do i think i got a little
exposure boom get down again
so that's a one dayer well
the time which i love about it is it
hangs
it's got hang time it's got shelf life
inside your bloodstream
shelf life inside your body and then if
we can't if we don't keep up on it
it's still protecting us so two days
later
time is still floating around our
bloodstream
that's what i love about it now what
does time do
it basically what time does it's a
disinfectant
to pathogens pathogens hate
disinfectants
and that's what they despise one of the
things they despise the most right
so not just pathogens but pathogen
byproducts
viral byproducts viral star
dust okay because you know
viruses leave a path of all kinds of
debris and all kinds of crap
and all kinds of garbage not just
neurotoxins and dermatoxins
a byproduct of all kinds and so
all that stuff builds up in a lymphatic
system builds up in our liver it builds
up in our bloodstream
and time is this disinfectant that's
doing some cleaning in our system
that's what's so incredible about it
right and
yeah viral dust you like that one
michelle i mean that's what it is
okay see we hear hero time after time
good song
and so what i really love about it is
you have to just remember hey i'm doing
my time water i'm doing my time infused
tea
water what is it doing for me it's an
antiseptic
okay pathogens are allergic viruses
are allergic to the oil in time
okay so time has this really
um thin thin thin oil
is what time actually has so it's a va
there's fat in everything i told you
guys there's fat in every single herb
this is why i try to keep your fats down
with all your foods
your overt fats down i'm trying to keep
all your overt fats down
because we're we're hurting ourselves
with all that fat we do constantly over
and over and over again right
and that all that fat from overt fat
stops
things from working for you in other
ways and i've talked about that because
your bloodstream
and i'll go into that in a second though
what happens in your bloodstream with
all the fats
but time okay time oil
which is an omega-3 in time
itself right is an antiseptic too so
that right there it's
it's the one of the only fats
there are that propel viruses
it's in time so you can't just drink
some olive oil i'm going to repel some
viruses no your viruses will get worse
can't just eat some more chicken getting
all that chicken fat thinking that the
fat's going to repel viruses no your
virus is getting
worse can't just eat your eggs i'll just
feed the viruses straight out
you can't just do a whole bunch of
peanut butter well you know what there's
there's some omegas in peanut butter
there's a magazine walnuts there's a
mega
magazine in pumpkin seeds there's a
magazine you know and
chia seed so i use thyme essential oil
every day topically but i am going to
make the tea
too i mean if you want to use thyme
essential oil topically
right you can but it's it's not going to
stop exposure
so you can't use time for exposure well
the thing is with that is you might be
able to use it on your hand maybe
right and then if you were exposed to
something
in your hand like you grab the shopping
cart that could help a little bit so
that does help a little bit
but internally though it has to be like
the time t
time infused water that's where it
really kicks in inside the body
but it's that that it's that micro oil
micro omega oil that's in time but
it's not in anywhere else you eat a
bunch of hemp seeds you eat your peanut
butter you eat your walnuts you eat your
almonds
that fat doesn't repel any viruses or
bugs
you have your chicken you have your fish
you have your milk eggs cheese butter
that doesn't repel anything now just
just so you know
it's it's special for time it only
exists for time
and then there's an alkaloid in time too
so
time carries alkaloids okay
just like so many other plant foods do
they have a lot of alkaloids
and the alkaloid in time is another type
of antiseptic
so it repels viruses too so that's
another thing as well so the alkaloid
is a chemical compound in time right
it's in the leaf
okay the time oil is in the stem
so that's where the thyme oil is you see
where the stem is right here you guys
see that stem see the little leaves
that's where the alkaloid is that repels
viruses you see that stem
that's where the oil is that repels
viruses okay
i'm holding a piece of time you guys on
clubhouse right now
um so this is where the magic happens
right there
it's the antiviral alkaloid which is a
chemical compound
phytochemical compound and it's the
oil that's in the stem right
that micro oil that's in the stem and so
these are where the magic lies
okay and you remember when i told you
guys
remember when i told you guys that if
you eat fat
it stays in your bloodstream okay clogs
up the liver
stays in your bloodstream all right if
you're eating too much fat
it gets your bloodstream all clogged up
but those aren't anti-viral oils
they're not antiviral that's how it
works your avocado
oil in the avocado that fat's not
anti-viral
right and so it's it's about
what foods are the antiviral
antibacterial compounds you know so the
oil in time
and it's not an overt that's the whole
point no one would ever believe or
think by just looking at time like this
that there's fat in it
and it's on such a minute level
such of my my new level but that's
what's incredible and healthy fats are
great i mean if you're doing healthy
fats and that's the fats you use that's
that's great if you do your olive oil
you do your avocado you do your
sunflower seeds your hemp seeds your
nuts and seeds your pumpkin seeds
you do any of that those are the better
fats right
and if you're i would stay off a pork if
you're an animal protein person
that fat will make you sick that brings
down your immune system the more fat you
eat your immune system can drop
keep that in mind all right and
when you get sick or you're coming down
with something and you eat a heavy meal
and what constitutes a heavy meal
this is about immune system boosting
this is critical information guys just
take these notes down now if you're
getting sick
or you think you were exposed and you
think that sore throat's coming on
your body's starting to ache you're not
feeling good
you think you might have caught the
plague think you might have caught the
flu
right the last thing you want to do
is eat a big heavy meal do not eat a big
heavy meal if you did fine fine just
don't eat another big heavy meal
okay but the last thing you want to do
is eat a big heavy meal
that will take your immune system down
all that fat and that big heavy meal
will take your
immune system down and then whatever
you've been exposed to
the plague some virus you're exposed to
the flu
it's gonna get a chance to take off and
really
root that's what it's going to do take
off and really root
you see how it works trisha marie it's
valuable information right
okay and so one of the greatest tools i
can give you outside of the tools
themselves that i'm about to do the zinc
shock therapy the vitamin c shock
therapy right
we'll go into that next one of the
greatest tools i can give you
is making sure you don't eat that heavy
meal filled with fat
right when you got exposed right so if
you're around somebody
and you're around somebody and you're
like oh my god they just came down with
the plague oh my god i was around
somebody they just came down with the
flu oh my god they came down some kind
of sinus infection
someone just came down with something oh
my god someone just was dealing with
some kind of medical stuff
and and i'm getting exposed whatever it
is you don't want to go and tank
that's when you don't want to go in tank
and all of a sudden it's like let me go
tank let me go eat
all this food let me just you don't want
to eat that heavy stuff you don't want
to have that burger you don't want to
have those eggs you don't want to have
you don't want to have those um that
chicken you don't want to have that fish
you don't want to have those avocados
you don't want to
you can do some steamed potatoes in a
salad you can do some fruit you just
don't want to
actually tank that food down
you don't want to fat yourself to death
at that moment you don't want to choose
that moment to fat yourself to death
because that is how it happens someone
gets exposed
they're coming down with something and
they don't feel good so you know that's
what happens i got a phone call
coming through but it's like they're
coming down something they don't feel
good
and that's what happens that's what goes
wrong and
what happens with people is that the
minute they don't feel good
they're getting the scratchy throat
they're starting to not feel good it's
like i gotta eat
i gotta eat something i need to eat
something let me go eat something
like i need to find something and that's
what happens right there
you know that's what happens um and they
say you know what
they're looking for something and they
just start eating and things just start
eating
um and that's what happens it's like
oh yeah sore throat
uh-huh i think i feel i think i have a
fever
i got a bad taste in my mouth like when
i'm swallowing my throat feels swollen
and it feels like it feels like
it's starting in the corner of my throat
my sore throat starting in the corner of
my throat
uh-huh yeah
and i just feel sick
yeah i'm eating yeah i'm hungry
well i don't know if i'm hungry i feel
like i need to protect myself so i'm
eating
yeah i'm gonna have some pizza it's a
vegan pizza
it's gluten-free it's got a corn crust
and you know yeah the sore throat is
like it's sticky i got glue in my mouth
like glue
in my mouth i feel like i'm gluey yeah i
was around somebody with the plague
yep that was around a couple of friends
maybe we didn't have our masks on
yeah i don't know if it's that i just
know that
i don't know i just feel sick maybe it's
my strep throat coming back
could be my strep throat coming back i
already had
a pork chop yeah
i someone told me pork was good if you
start getting sick
i'm gonna have some vegan pizza too why
would i have vegan pizza if i had a pork
chop
i don't know this is live hey you know
look all i know is i'm gonna have a pea
slice of pizza and then i'm gonna have
an avocado yeah i'm gonna eat a bunch of
avocados
i got three or four avocados here i'm
gonna make a big guacamole
i just want to keep on swallowing like i
know i'm getting sick it's in my ears
now
yeah i'm gonna have more pizza more
pizza
okay is a good idea all right
and that's what you don't want to do you
don't want to do that
you and and that happens to almost
everybody
it happens to oh jack said oh my god
great i feel sick now
it happens to almost everybody you guys
yeah so keep that in mind let's do the
shock therapies let's go we got the t
going we talked about time a little bit
um let's go into the zinc shock therapy
right there there's his ink
okay you could do the zinc shock therapy
in different ways um
and i'm gonna what i'm gonna do is
remove these i'm gonna strain these
i'm gonna do in here remove the twigs
kind of strain this tee back this tea is
ready
let's put this over here
let's drain this in here let's see if we
can spill it everywhere wouldn't that be
great
let's do that
okay i'm gonna add some honey to this
you guys mind
all right here we go let's add some
honey add a little bit of honey in there
there we go add a little bit of lemon
right
let's mix that up
just made the zinc shock therapies honey
on tick tock amazing
that's the time t right there
it's so good i mean yeah it's strong
it's strong but you can taste
the medicine you know you can taste that
medicinal nature to it
and that's a smart thing to do right
there with exposure
exposure of any kind exposure pathogenic
of any kind just letting you know and
the tools always there let's see these
things talk therapy we got that
now the zinc shock therapy you can do it
in
um
and the zen shock therapy is something i
would do for me
my friends okay my family my loved ones
that's what i use you guys do what your
doctor tells you your doctor tells you
you know to do something you do your the
doctor likes right whatever you want to
do
um you can ask your doctor about this
can ask your doctor about it no problem
too
okay i'm just showing you what i do for
myself i do for my family right
now um now what i do is
you can do it a couple different ways
you can put put it right in your mouth
um that's one way then shock therapy
because i talk about that it's in the
book it's in the medical media new
edition right here
i like in the water too all right
i like it in water as well um
so and you can put in some water and
still let it sit in your mouth that's
something you can do you can also
swallow it down if you really want to do
it that way as well you can go
either way okay so one way to do it is
you do the two dropper holes
right put that in your throat
and two dropper folds this ink
okay every three hours just like that
that's in shock therapy okay you can
hold it in your mouth
30 seconds up to a minute whatever you
feel comfortable with
right and that's what i tell friends and
family you know you ask your doctor
you do what your doctor wants to but
that's what i tell friends and family
um and you can do that
every three hours so it's two dropper
fulls every three
hours and you can do it for one day you
can do it to two days
so two days is another thing you can do
renata says his in-shock therapy is
incredible saved me and my husband from
cove exposure multiple times
incredible incredible
so when it comes down to building our
immune system there's a couple ways you
guys can look at it
right right
you can build it short term you can
build it long term
right so i like building the immune
system short term
and long term i like them both so i'll
talk about that a little bit if you're
sensitive
you're welcome to try um a milder
version of the medical medium shock
therapy so you can do a milder version
that's just the version now for my
friends and family cold white spring
good see right now
awesome glad you're here today um elune
hell good to see you
glad you're here today so let's work on
let's talk about zing for a little bit
zinc is something that we don't
have in our food anymore so as i was
talking about before is like oysters
like someone's like you can get zing
from oysters make sure you eat a lot of
oysters
it's like are you kidding me you know i
mean you suck down all those oysters i
mean you're just gonna get
hepatitis possibly okay because
literally there's so much mercury in
that oyster
so much mercury in that oyster that
you're just going to feed every bug in
your body rapidly especially inside the
liver so oysters are like a bad idea for
the liver
because healthy lizards and oysters
you've got the smiley faces on that one
yeah because
there's so much mercury in oysters for
one
in dioxins and oysters it's just immune
system lower
so it breaks down the immune system and
people have to understand that that's
that's a problem all on its own right
and but mercury feeds
viruses to begin with so i'm gonna eat a
bunch of oysters is what i'm gonna do
eat a bunch of oysters meanwhile you're
feeding every virus in your body and
that's that's what goes wrong right
there
um and so you got the viruses everybody
is about
to say you just got exposure of any kind
say you're in a new relationship and you
just picked up one or two varieties of
epstein-barr by accident
because everybody's carrying around bugs
right and you can't carry a new epstein
bar
and it's floating in your system the
last thing you want to do is get a whole
bunch of oysters in your system too you
don't want to eat a whole bunch of those
because basically the mercury is going
to feed
the virus and it's going to take off so
that's something right there to consider
but
so it's important to get rid of these
ideas that are out there another thing
is pumpkin seeds
just eat a bunch of pumpkin seeds every
day
there's such a minute level of zinc and
pumpkin seeds
but the reason why pumpkin seeds are
heralded
as being the zinc holy grail
like pumpkin seeds is the zinc holy
grail right
the reason why is because there's
detectable zinc
in pumpkin seed detectable
zinc right detectable doesn't mean
it's enough zinc to get us by for five
seconds it doesn't mean it's enough zinc
to actually restore our zinc reserves it
doesn't mean it's enough zinc
to do anything for us pumpkin seeds are
great for you
it's the best the one of the best fats
if you're into fats
one of the healthiest fats right and
even with that said you just don't want
to be downing all this pumpkin seed
butter and eating all these pumpkin
seeds because too much fat still too
much fat because
that's what's happening out there yeah
oysters are the
ocean cleaners so yeah they're really
toxic for us because of that right there
so zing toxicity so sue says zing
toxicity question
mark um i mean you have to be doing a
lot of zinc
a lot of zinc for a zinc toxicity issue
so keep that in mind
and so that's important to know but what
you can get
with with supplementation is is copper
toxicity so you got to look out for that
because people like we got to take
copper
because you you know we need copper
you've got to take copper well copper is
the immune
immune system lower as well it lowers
the immune system
really takes it down a notch copper is
so abundant that we're loaded with
copper
all of us are saturated with copper
comes from our new clothes we buy from
the fungicides all the pesticides and
herbicides comes from that
it's dropped out of the sky it's in our
water comes out of our pipes it comes
out of you know everywhere comes out of
wells comes out of town city water right
so copper we're and then the earth is
saturated in copper
so organic organic farm
land is high in copper
so all the food we grow is high in
copper but not
supposed to be high in copper but it's
high in copper right
so we're coppered out that's why we have
the raging eczema psoriasis
we have all the issues with skin
problems copper is a big reason for all
of that
so okay so that's important to know um
so and and we'll just go we'll go a
little bit deeper into this for one
second here so
we're all worried about copper when
copper that's more abundant than
anything
but zinc isn't abundant so like i said
the zinc is detectable in a pumpkin seed
but still not enough to keep us going
you can sit there gobbling down pumpkin
seeds all day long till you're sick to
your guts
and you're not gonna get the zinc you
need to protect your immune system to
protect yourself so that's something
really important though because that
comes up all the time so i could just
eat some pumpkin seeds i don't need to
i don't need to worry about zinc ever i
don't need to take a few drops of zinc i
mean
even if you take like you know i told
the doctor the other day you could just
do
three tiny drops one two three four five
drops
you can take one two drops and
you know you can take a dropper full a
day depending on what's happening and
talk about protocols in the medical
medium books but
zinc keeps your immune system from
overreacting and under reacting so
here's what happens let me give you guys
this
okay so um
you got a virus right here and this is
medical medium information about sin
okay that doctors are actually using out
there and i saw something out there
plagiarized information wasn't cited
back to mm but
viruses when you get exposed to a flu
virus
or exposed to some kind of plague virus
right which is essentially really a flu
virus
when you get exposed to that that
hybridized flu virus
that's what the plague is hybridized
blue virus when you get exposed to that
your immune system can overreact
your immune system can also under react
and that's what takes a per that's why
that person there got real sick real
fast
that person there got sick kind of
slow and steady but
stayed sick too long that person
got sick too fast but
got better quicker doesn't mean that's a
good thing it either because they got
so sick so fast it shocked the system
that person got sick so slow but stayed
sick
longer would shock the system you see so
that right there
it's one thing or a bug is so bad a flu
virus is so bad
that your system gets shocked so bad
you're in trouble okay
so that's overreacting so what happens
is our immune system without zinc
overreacts under reacts overreacts
under reacts see how it works you guys
it's really important info
overreacts and under reacts zinc
in our body keeps your immune system
from
freaking out but keeps it also
from not going to sleep because your
immune system also can stay asleep
it's just staying asleep you're sick but
it's a sleep
it's a sleep and that can happen too
right
but you don't want one or the other you
especially don't want
your immune system overreacting that's
what you don't want
right darlene it's really interesting um
and so that's what i love about zinc
so it's that modular it's that modulator
it's what it is it's like modulating you
know
it's like that power box that's
modulating for a surge
a power surge and that's what it does so
that's what zinc does so that's
important um
and that's what i love about it so
anyway let's talk about vitamin c we did
some zinc shock therapy
we talked about that look you guys want
more info on that
zinc shark therapy in the medical medium
new edition boom it's right there
okay let's talk about vitamin c
therapy too we'll go into there now so
microc is the one that i use which is um
the vimergy microc
and what's what's tricky about vitamin c
is if you have a sensitive tummy
right get a sensitive tummy
a vitamin c is like battery acid to your
tummy
that's what it could feel like battery
acid to your tummy
so ascorbic acid straight ascorbic
acid and some people they're too
sensitive for that
they're sensitive they're either
inflamed they have no hcl
they're just sensitive so their lining
is sensitive
in their small intestinal tract they're
duodenum they're stomach lining
sensitive
so so when it comes to vitamin c this is
the only one that i feel confident now
that because we need vitamin c we need
vitamin c
so the only one that i feel really
confident about okay
and it's it's it's one that's buffered
enough and that's the whole key so
that's the one i recommend it's the
vimorgy you guys know
um so anyway there's the micro seat
right there
so maria says i almost didn't get fevers
before medical medium information
after starting i have had really high
temperatures
over 40.5 cell celsius
so i mean the thing is with that is it's
really important to know is like i want
you to be your own detective
and so were you starting medical medium
information
because you were feeling like you were
getting sick
or heading to a place of getting sick
happens to a lot of people
there's something inside of them that
just says i'm gonna go
start doing some medical medium
information because i need to
start getting better because i'm
something in me i'm not feeling better
i'm not feeling good
it's one thing's really important to
know um
the other thing is is were you exposed
to a new infection so ask your doctors
these things
you know you should talk to your doctors
about this like ask your doctor
you know because i've talked to doctors
about this stuff and it's like
some people get exposed to new
infections is it a new relationship did
they get
mono and now they have mono and strep
throat because they have a new infection
from a new relationship
did they get do they pick something up
from a public bathroom
in a restaurant they were eating food in
one of the things that i tell people
to really look out for is chefs cutting
their fingers
it happens every day in the restaurants
more
people eat chef's blood than anybody
could ever even know
it happens every single night a sous
chef
someone helping a kitchen hand cuts
their fingers in the kitchen
right a lot of people have thin skin on
their hands they're getting cut and
scratched while they're working
moving boxes then they're handling food
chefs are cutting their fingers they put
a band-aid on and put a rubber glove but
there's blood everywhere
so this is another thing too so one of
the biggest ways we actually transfer
viruses
pathogens around is through eating out
that's the that's like between
relationships
that's the second big one so it's
relationships the first bit
first one right there and then boom
eating out
that's the second one right there and so
um i mean that's important to know
and and when it comes down to
when it comes down to okay like
what i would do me personally if i was
getting fevers
i would be like okay good thing i'm
doing medical medium information
because if i wasn't how bad would all
that stuff be
because it's the whole point it's about
making sure you're so proactive and
taking care of yourself so at least
you've got that in your hands
i'm sure you get the support from your
doctors to do medical medium information
ask your doctors you know if you can do
mm info
um and and learn about it but there's a
couple things about being your own
detective
and what's happening in your foods is mm
info
minus the chocolate the caffeine the
apple cider vinegar nutritional yeast
the whey protein powder the protein
powders
the fish oil is it minus all that that's
just some things right there it's
medical medium information
minus all the fats is medical medium
information minus the eggs the chilled
milk cheese dairy butter
so it's one thing it's one thing we can
say
hey medical media information i'm doing
but are you doing medical medium
information
how much medical mean information are
you doing so these are things to
consider right there
like are you doing just celery juice or
a heavy metal detox smoothie
are you still eating eggs dairy
chocolate
matcha tea kombucha tea bone broth
apple cider vinegar vinegars what else
are you doing and then
are you still doing collagen the protein
powders
citric acid natural flavors alcohol all
these things matter
right there because if you're doing any
of that stuff
you means you're only dabbling in
medical medium information
so when you're dabbling it should be
like you know what i started dabbling in
medical medium information
i started playing around celery just a
little um
and and that's what i'm doing and oh my
god these fevers are so bad
because i started dabbling in medical
medium information
so just all i just want people to be
their own detective
so they know how to heal themselves they
know what to tell their doctors
to learn how to heal let's keep on going
you guys this is a great live this is
fun because i love talking about the
immune system what we can do i love
talking about
tools how to heal doing the medical
medium vitamin c
shock therapy is what we're going to do
so we're going to do one cup of water to
start with
all right so let's do that let's get
some water going on here
we're going to open up um
two 500 milligram capsules right here
vitamin c microc
get that going
um look you guys when it comes down to
essential oils i'm going to be straight
up
i don't recommend taking them internally
i know they get the essential oil crowd
really upset
you guys on clubhouse just letting you
know um you guys on tic-tac letting you
know
facebook youtube i don't like the
ingestion
of essential oils i think it was a bad
idea
i think it was a bad idea from the start
just letting you know
okay essential oils right i i do like i
do support
i support them when it comes down to on
the skin i support them on that level
infusions right infusers i support them
in that level too
you know vaporizers using them in those
like i support essential oils i'm fine
with it
but consuming them internally
i saw a lot of disasters happen right
so ingesting the ingesting them it was
never a medical medium recommendation it
was
to any of the people that came to me
personally for 35 years
for 30 years was never something i would
ever do in fact every time
someone would get into my office right
they'd get into my office
okay i got my appointment with you this
would be like 1995 or
1999 or whatever years all the years i
did this i'd have
people coming into my office and
i would be like you're not ingesting
those essential oils right because i
would hear it all the time like yeah
i'm told to drink the essential oils
that's going to help my lyme disease i
feel like oh my god dear lord
no it's not and sensitive people
they their nervous system can't handle
it it can really
really wig them out without their vagus
nerve
totally wigged out their bags their
stress their vagus nerve out stress
their
their their um phrenic nerves out
and and this is inhaling it too
essential oils
inhaling certain essential oils can be
too strong for people with nervous
system sensitivities
with tightness of chest tightness of
throat you know vagus phrenic nerve
issues anxiety depression
so i would always err in caution on
essential oils
say if you've got real sensitivities
where in the sense where you're
neurologically sensitive don't even
breathe them in
real don't breathe in strong amounts of
it
light and airy is fine little here and
there on your wrist and you're just not
covering
don't wipe your whole body down with
essential oil if you've got
nervous system issues that are really
sensitive i've always said this and
and and do not ingest them don't be
drinking essential oil concoctions i'm
just letting you know
that was never a recommendation here
andrea says i got sicker after ingesting
essential oils for a year
haven't since starting medical media yet
it's way too much on people way too much
on people so that's something that's
important that's worth
right now that alone that piece of
information is worth the price of
admission here
on this free medical medium life ali
said i was advised by a naturopath to
take 45 drops of
tea tea tree oil twice a day i got so
ill
i was dizzy for days could not get out
of bed
that's an epic that's an epic
piece of misinformation not what you're
saying your story is 100 correct it's an
it's an epic piece of misinformation
i've seen happen to so many people that
hurt people
lucy i got rid of all my plug-in smells
and my home and i haven't worn perfume
for a year
now thanks to you it's helped me with my
migraines thank you and that's what it
is you got
these fragrances in there back to like
we're building the immune system we're
talking about building the immune system
for all that's going on the plague and
the flu and everything else out there
right but you guys
we're also building the immune system
for things like that air fresheners
right and clones perfumes that lowers
your immune system
it does it does i think the phones i got
a friend calling
this is important right now because i i
i don't want to be late for this phone
call
come on
yeah yeah no i've been using it
yeah yeah you sent me this one
this smells so nice uh-huh
thank you for the present uh-huh
i love the smell yeah it smells so nice
i sprayed on myself a little squirt i
got this other one too thank you
well such a nice present yeah i love
perfumes and clones
yeah i love your cologne uh-huh i love
the cologne you wear
yeah i'm wearing perf yeah i love the
perfume sent me thank you
it's so good i know i know
did something's burning
how can you smell that you're on the
phone something's burning i can't smell
it all i smell is perfume
do i can i smell can i smell anything
else
oh you sent me something you want me
wait you want me to try to smell a lemon
let me smell lemon you can't smell it
no i just smell perfume uh-huh
yeah it's just all you smell is perfume
when you use perfume
okay i gotta go you know what's funny
you guys i was just thinking
people who actually wear perfume cologne
i'm not i'm not harping on them
not harping on them but they can't smell
anything
they say they can but they can't i'm
sorry but they can't they can't
i asked a friend who douses herself in
perfume
i asked her do me a favor it was years
ago i was like hey you're gonna be over
there
can you just check on something for me
check to see if
that place smells over there was a new
office like check to see if that office
smells going there
they went in there they doing their
sniff test around
came out place smells amazing the place
was saturated in mold smell
and chemical smell and all this stuff
because i've
run into this my whole life any of my
friends that have perfumes
colognes any of the guys i've known
colognes the doctor friends of mine that
have known colognes
they can't smell anything they can't
smell anything they can't smell anything
they say they're smelling something
in the kitchen they say they're smelling
something they're cooking but they can't
smell a
thing they can't smell anything they're
cooking they can't smell anything
they're doing it's
it's unbelievable let's keep on making
this right here
so we got the vimergy micro see right
here
the scented candles the clones of
perfumes
right the air fresheners lower the
immune system
back stay away from them
tick tock good to see you not tick tock
the app tick tock
on youtube uh laundry detergents
cleansers all of that fragrance that
stuff just lowers the immune system
and so your migraines will be there you
know a lot of people are dealing with
so many problems just from that alone
right there you know
m sky good to see you as well so let's
let's keep on making this
so i'm going to add some orange to this
if you guys don't mind
kind of nice orange here check out this
orange by the way
all right the red navels isn't that
great
squeeze an orange in here
so i put two f roughly 500 milligram
capsules
right two 500 milligram capsules a
microc in here and a cup of water
this is medical medium vitamin c shock
therapy i'm putting some orange in here
right
putting two teaspoons of raw honey in
here right
i'm gonna mix this up
you've got the vitamin c shock therapy
okay you can do it
every two hours
every two hours so what happens is that
you got exposed you got that sore throat
coming down
you don't feel good i mean ask your
doctor what's right for you but this is
this is what i would do if i had this if
i had my throat like
aching something was going wrong i had a
fever coming on
wasn't feeling good and so yeah
um that's that's it right there vitamin
c shock therapy
i would do it for days can we use
tangerines
yes 100 yep carry on tick tock you can
totally use tangerines you can use
oranges tangerines
definitely um
uh melton says i'm feeling sick from
perfumes
since childhood they're toxic highly
toxic
and they lower the immune system that's
why so um you guys
this has been incredible we got that
that's the vitamin c shock therapy so
easy
now what i like to do is i like to take
goldenseal
if i think i i've been exposed but i
tell people you know you can use
goldenseal for a lot of things a lot of
things i talked about that in the
medical medium books right there
that's one right there cat's claw is
another great one i told you how lyme
disease works
where the lyme disease community has
changed because of medical medium
information 35 years of the work
with medical meme info and how cat's
claws now accept it
in mainstream medicine for lyme disease
because of medical medium
that's an incredible one right there um
i talk about the protocols and cleanse
the heal
right there as well and that's 51
off at amazon.com um
yeah you guys are you coming with me
over to instagram because i'm going to
juice some celery along with do all
these over again but i'm also going to
do celery too
because that alone right there is a
healing tool
so with exposure
i was going to tell you guys i got the
omega mm 900 hds
there's a sale on that model may 24th
all the way through early june just
letting you know so i'm excited so if
you guys are looking for a juicer
that's when you get it um if you're up
for it anyway
got my celery
so i'm going to go on instagram i'm
going to turn tick tock back on i'm
going to
turn uh clubhouse back on and we're
do the medical medium zig shock therapy
vitamin c shock therapy
time water time tea we're going to juice
some celery i can't wait you'll be there
catherine
elizabeth incredible i can't wait to see
you i love you guys
see you soon
and um
you guys are incredible i saw some
meditate for love hey meditate for love
you know what
i saw a poem you wrote it's a really
really awesome poem
i was blown away it was on youtube
youtube comments man
you guys i read comments so letting you
know just that
things are going so crazy i don't have
time to respond too often
anyway take care of you guys i'll see
you soon going over the ig in a little
bit
tik tok i'm going to turn you guys right
back on
and clubhouse