can you William here I'm gonna scoot
over here this is an amazing moment
right here because I'm really happy I
got an incredible doctor right here an
amazing man that's helped so many people
throughout the years he's a cardiologist
and right here he's he's the man behind
clean and I want to show his books for a
second you remember the clean book right
here is came out years ago we're gonna
tell the story how we met we're gonna
talk about heavy metal detox we're gonna
talk about metals and people's live or
we've got so many things we're going to
talk about but these are the books right
here number one bestsellers if we're
talking about incredible books he's a
New York Times bestselling author an
amazing doctor clean gut is a great book
it's all about the gut it's all about
because you know that's where so much
stems from and hey the liver is part of
the gut you know so this is doctor
Alejandra younger I have here with me
amazing time he's got a recipe book that
came out a while back and he's got a
book coming out clean seven it's a
cleansing book incredible this is coming
out soon too so I'm really honored to
have him here we have a history together
it's an amazing time right here
hey you're in incredible cardiologist
amazing man I mean look when what hey
when I got family members or 30 you know
they have a problem because people they
they don't eat good right they get the
they get the hard problems to heart
conditions I make sure this is the man
right here he's incredible guy and so
here we are
he's a number one you know New York
Times bestselling author and he's an
incredible guy helps out so many people
and you know and you have an amazing
history with your practice to going back
everybody knows who you are you're
famous in my eyes and I have an amazing
with you and so it's great that you're
here it's on I'm honored to have you
here so thank you for coming on yeah
thank you for having me we're gonna talk
good stuff we got to celery juice right
here we're doing I think the bottom line
is is that you and I feel the same we
feel the same way chronic illness is
growing at an all-time high
okay all-time high science and research
can't keep up with it it just can't they
can't keep up with it and more than not
keeping up with it
it is
chronic diseases as if they were acute
problems
Yesi for acute problems like a broken
bone a burst appendix a heart attack an
ongoing heart attack there's nothing
better than modern science yeah I agree
but the problems that humanity is
suffering from are not mostly acute 90%
of the problems of humanity suffering
from a chronic product yeah and they do
not respond to surgery and medications
the way that acute problems yeah so we
are not really treating the the chronic
problems we were just killing the
symptoms yeah you know that's we you
know what's amazing about that is is
until somebody gets sick with a chronic
condition with symptoms they have and
they're not getting better and they're
going to neurologist right you've seen
this I mean come on how many times I've
something arrives I mean you're a doctor
I've seen myself yeah I got seven
prescription medications for health
issues that I was suffering from and it
didn't make sense for me so I've looked
for a different solution yeah and that
took me to discover the power of what we
eat and the power of herbs yeah and so
the whole thing is it's like you know
when people are dealing with exactly
there's chronic symptoms are going to
neurologist and they're going to another
doctor then go another doctor and then
they're going in all these different
places and the whole life is based on
doctor appointments and science and
research it's great for nuts and bolts
right I call it nuts and bolts you got a
gallbladder because we don't take care
of herself and we got an infection in
the gallbladder and it's got to come out
you want a good surgeon you want a good
doctor you get heart problems you want a
good heart doctor I mean that's what you
are a heart doctor and you know and in
an internist internal medicine doctor to
all of that and you know you want that
but but then what about all the other
people because that's why you became an
expert about chronic illness because
what about all the other people that
they can't get answers for all the
problems they have with modern medicine
is with chronic diseases in approaching
chronic diseases is that we do not look
for the root cause of the problem yeah
we just very concentrated in
cutting and and and pieces off and
giving medications just to calm the
symptoms right but the root problem
cause of the problems is not what modern
Western medicine is the best at yeah or
gives any attention to the reason there
is a big growing movement which is
called functional medicine that that
yeah that is what happens to modern
medicine doctors when they start
thinking like Ayurvedic or Chinese
medicine doctors right and these are the
doctors that are more interested in
growth then they're more open to what
could be wrong yeah what's happening
inside the body how deep is the problem
you know and that matters I mean back in
the day you know back in the day like
you know you've been a doctor for a long
time okay so you mean you got experience
and new doctors that come out of school
fresh out of school and they just don't
know a fraction of what you know because
it takes that history sick people
science and research doesn't have the
answers for aches and pains tangles and
numbness vertigo yeah eight you know
neck pain mysterious back pain sciatica
pain without back problems you know all
of this and all these different things
in the foggy head the brain fog right
and the floaters in the eyes and then
the fatigue and all that fatigue you
come out of school and then all that
what is what the hell is all that like
what is all that right I mean the doctor
said well you got the history you know
you got that long-standing history that
there needs to be more figured out to
help people you know and it's doctors
like you that you know they're rare
there's not a lot of doctors like you
out there that says you know what I'm
gonna you know what I'm an expert at
cardiology I'm an expert at these things
in the field but you know what people
are suffering you know he has compassion
you know when I met you you could tell
the story when I met you but he's a
compassionate man he's a compassionate
man about people suffering I don't see
that too often I know doctors are
compassionate they have to be but but it
takes it to a new level with him because
he actually really cares he said you
know he said I remember when I first met
you you said that science the research
doesn't have all the answers okay
because people are they're sick out
there
and we need to do something about it you
were just looking on this remember you
said I'm gonna dedicate my life that I
met Anthony at a party for one of my
book launch what in like 2009 2009 yeah
it doesn't not longer than eight or nine
okay and somebody brought in to me
because people that are that I that I
know intimately know that I am a healer
Ruby some people are rock star groupies
in there for a rock star I follow
either's true healers right so they
introduced me to him and they told me
his story and I you know always even
though I believe and I know that
miracles exist and the spirit exists and
and that it communicates with us I am
initially a skeptic until proven
otherwise
ya know you're you're a hard man but I
like this come from science that's the
whole point so if it's gotta convince
you it better be good because I like to
look in your eyes and I knew that at
least you believed what you told me you
were not faking stuff right now it was
then up to me to see if what you believe
had something to do with a few months
later I got a really big scare right I
was having labor pains like really
intense labor pains and I decided to
give the medical medium a try so I
called you and you said to me and I was
already scheduled for the next day for a
biopsy of my liver and I called you and
you said first of all your liver has no
problem you have an old cyst that you
were born with and the reason and the
reason that you are having pains has
nothing to do the cysts so when they
find the cyst
don't worry about it so so and he put me
on cats go if the cat's a cloth for the
liver powerful what else need live
around spirulina
abundance of spirulina I put you on Mull
and leaf because more than that wasn't
the immune system of your liver to get
stronger yeah and and and to be
protective because your livers have
immediately I ordered everything he put
me on and the next day I went to have a
biopsy and the results of the biopsy
were not a biopsy yeah yeah sonogram I
had about two of my lymph nodes and in a
sonogram and a cat scan of my liver and
basically they told me exactly that that
I had a cyst they didn't want to touch
it because they didn't think that was
part of the problem yeah and then I
received the next day all the things
that you ordered and then four days
later I had no more pain and then I
started sending my well I consulted you
about my kids I consulted you about my
family I love how many members and then
I started sending patients to you and
like everybody had some benefit if not
incredible benefit by seeing you want to
follow your advice one more you know and
and the thing is is is with you though
when you when you know when I tell you
hey Doc you gotta do this you gotta keep
that you just you just do it you just do
it you just said I'll go get what what
do you need me to do immediately
immediately you know and and because you
believe that herbs you believe that food
does heal and it does heal certain parts
of her body survive it because you have
that belief doctors didn't have that
years ago you know when I you know it's
a new thing now the doctors think food
helps yeah I mean I mean I'm thirty
years into this or more helping people
out all these years and I tooked a lot
of doctors over the years I've talked to
angry doctors because they didn't
believe no no garlic can't help with
anything you can't you know you can't
use garlic for the flu you can't use God
you can't use this and now they just
don't have any any faith my father was
from Hungary
used to tell me that garlic kept away
the bad spirits right ya know I always
knew that garlic was really it was
really believe that nature did not
design human body to get sick just like
it didn't design anybody to get sick any
animal animals in the wild don't get
sick I love animals that live in the way
that nature designed them to it in in
the places in which nature designed them
to live and eat what nature designed
them to eat do not get sick okay we are
the animals and and the cats and dogs
that live close to us yes we get sick no
yes no nature did not design humans or
anything to get sick the sicknesses are
just adaptation and survival mechanisms
right and when we discover what the
obstacles are and we remove the
obstacles and then we add whatever is
lacking everything corrects by itself
you know it falls into exactly what I've
been teaching from my information my
source that you got to get rid of toxins
you gotta get rid of toxins you got to
get rid of bugs bugs toxins I always say
that and and bugs feed off of toxins
like heavy metals we're going to talk
about heavy metals I got a little bit of
a heavy metal detox movie right here so
the medical medium heavy metal defense
movie right there and you know bugs like
the feed off of mercury they like the
feed off of aluminum land arsenic copper
and even more these heavy metals they
depress you a new system so bugs can
take over right otherwise sometimes we
have the ability to kill all this and
keep them away on these bugs by
ourselves with our immune system now
these heavy metals they tip the balance
and they allow give bugs an advantage
yeah and you know you know what's
amazing is that we're made out of trace
minerals you know we're making out of
minerals it's in their bones it's
everywhere trace minerals in our tissue
connective tissue or organs we've got
all these trace minerals you know we got
the zinc with selenium we've got all
these other trace minerals it's
unbelievable what we have what we're
made out of and metals toxic heavy
metals they're a metal they're a metal
out of the earth a toxic one
manufacturer metals trace minerals are
types of
in a way minerals have that connection
you have the metals they're reacting the
minerals and then they in a they would
they destroy our trace minerals metals
destroy the weaken our immune system
they break this down and then and they
and they also work energetically in a
negative for example don't talk about
astrology and in Mercury's in retrograde
so what has happened there's an
energetic influence cool of mercury yeah
that really puts your body in a pickle
yeah yeah no totally agreed 100% exactly
and and when you got the toxic heavy
metals you can have some brain fog can
have some anxiety could have migraines
aches and pains
well the main mechanism called mercury
is called the great mimicry because it
can mimic any disease it can mimic as a
psychiatric problem as a skin disease as
a gastroenterology problem as a heart
problem it can mimic any disease so it
is called a great mimicker and we need
to find out because now everybody's
exposed too much well you know we all
have mercury in us from year from from
generations past we tended earth yeah
it's in the foods that we eat it's in
the water that was showering with the
industries the industry's been using
mercury going all the way back hundreds
in hundreds of years
no no boys and it's oh it's innocent we
passed it on down the family line if we
don't get it out of us and the program
then we're gonna keep on passing it
around the process the problem is this I
am now a true believer that
detoxification is something that can
save the the big picture and really
bring chronic disease now well
detoxification is used in a weird way
too many people are using detox and this
and detox that that's why functional
medicine now changed the word and talks
about it as biotransformation
so basically is what the body already
knows what to do getting toxic chemicals
which 90% are lipophilic only dissolving
fat and then throwing it through certain
reactions in the liver first phase one
detoxification phase phase two
detoxification and turning them into a
non
toxic and water-soluble compound so that
it can be excludable it's like having
metals cannot yeah yes so so you can you
can create the conditions for your body
to detoxify by themselves by supporting
the liver nutritionally by by doing
certain things to reduce the workload of
the digestive system and and and heavy
metals with not so we can go might not
get clean we we can cleanse other
poisons and toxins out of us easy and
most of them yeah most of them all right
we can cleanse them out we do the right
things with foods we do the right things
with all the stuff but heavy metals
rolling heavy metals they're stubborn
they're really ineffective ways that we
do get rid of anybody anybody who just
came on dr. Alejandro younger right here
and the cardiologists internist
specialist give me a little history real
quick like you know we're graduated all
that it looked I was born in your away
and and life was very healthy by default
I went to medical school there then I
moved to New York to do my internship
and residency in internal medicine at
NYU downtown Hospital incredible then I
did my cardiology fellowship at Lenox
Hill Hospital the hard core the change
of lifestyle and especially with diet
had me find myself after six years with
irritable bowel syndrome severe
depression and severe allergies I went
to three specialists some of the top in
New York I ended up with three diagnoses
and seven prescription medications okay
and I had two shocks one of them is my
god I have to take seven prescription
medications in order to be able to
function for the rest of my life this is
what medicine was telling me and the
other shop was this is what I'm doing
with my patients yeah so I took off yeah
because you care about your patients I
just saw what you always did I went to
India to live in a monastery where I
learned a little bit about herbal
medicine Ayurvedic medicine and I
started getting better you know yeah it
was no processed foods yeah this thing
is love
you guys hear about you guys hear about
processed foods all the time I bet all
that in and we take it for granted we
think that information
always been out there it was never out
there it was never really out there
doctors are talking about stay away from
processed foods now it kind of stems
from basically sources like dr.
Alejandro younger that's what's
interesting I mean I'm going to talk
about no processed foods for a long time
I don't know processed foods yeah I call
them food like products yeah food like
products but we take that for everybody
everybody including on YouTube and other
places and then influence and stuff they
they automatically if you they hear
processed foods or they hear anything
like that that's it's a no-brainer stay
away from them it wasn't a no-brainer
years ago it's men like dr. nada under
younger that had a fight for it because
when you know when when you had a pavé
away its front earring and I had to pave
the way in frontier I mean that the
smack I got for trying to get people
gluten-free 35 years ago was
unbelievable untold agony I had to deal
with that really caught my attention
about you but still as a doctor though
it was this is new ground you you you as
a medical doctor you said you know what
and this is early on for medical doctors
with no processed food and no and none
of those no no you know bad foods and
all that I teach I teach my patients
live longer than the life shelf of any
product that you buy the shorter your
life yeah I mean and then you know look
and then you know you hear about doctors
out there and they they just they
graduated a few years ago they're in
gastroenterology they're in something
else they're doing something and they
don't like all the natural information
that's being spread out there about the
medical medium and other stuff they
don't like it
because they they haven't had the
experience of being like there's there
isn't answers out there there just isn't
answers there is but there is with a lot
of procedures there is with a lot of
medicine a good heart doctor priceless
all this but but but when it comes down
to broken bones and all kinds of
injuries you get into this you get into
there's all kinds of things but when it
comes down to what people are
the Crohn's colitis IBS got a
gastrointestinal disorders that are that
are not fixable by just cotton snip or a
medication that's when we get in trouble
it's all those things the chronic
diseases of the modern world cannot be
treated like the acute diseases surgery
and medications are great for the acute
diseases but humanity problems are only
ten percent are cubes ninety percent of
the problems you're suffering from are
the chronic problems in which you got to
go back to the where the root cause of
proteins and for most of them is in the
gut yeah exactly I want to ask for heavy
metals or bugs yeah and we're gonna talk
about heavy metals we know how to get
them out a little bit in all that to
we'll go into that a little bit but I
wanted to ask you about the science and
research part that's really interesting
like it's all interesting but the part
where you know what science thinks it
has it right for a little while and then
it changes its tune new years later it
changes it soon and then it's these are
people that are people that are
gravitating to studies here and then the
studies here but they they keep on
changing so no matter what scientific
study you got I'm even in heart
procedures heart surgeries they were
different back then they would cut the
whole chest wide open they would snip
all the ribs right down here I mean they
would cut them open at your spread your
whole ribcage out now they're doing
they're doing Valerie play some us an
under some of them still someone who's
still happy but but um for example look
at what happened with the war on food in
America yeah when I came to America in
the 90s early nineties there was a war
on fat everything was fat free from in
the supermarkets so they had to replace
the calories with carrots yeah right now
at carbide a few years later made
mistakes with that whole later
carbohydrates became the enemy yeah and
so we waged a war on carbohydrates and
then now we're in the honeymoon with fat
everybody who's loaded for any changes
and then it
and in so many studies that show
definitely results for certain
approaches that medic modern medicine
takes a few years later or 10 years
later shown to be wrong yeah cuz you
tell me the but they could find
something they're looking for yeah and
stay with that but then look and then
the rest falls apart a researcher and we
actually end up finding what they're
looking for yeah but they only look for
what they already know they already
exact so we don't know what they're
looking for it's like okay so celery
juice helping out a lot you've seen
celery juice help out a lot of people I
saw you prescribing to patients in front
of me that improved later by taking the
celery juice but science research they
don't know anything about celery juice
because they don't even know what
they're looking for yet they don't look
for so people be out there oh it's got
this vitamin and it's got this mineral
it's got a little bit of this set but
that's not why people are getting better
because all the fruits and vegetables
and other foods and even animal products
have vitamins and minerals in it and
that's not this gets people better the
thing is this you can you cannot argue
with success and you can see and you see
the results all over the world in how
many thousand hundreds of thousands of
people that are because of you taking
celery juice right yeah so now senator
juice doesn't need a study well maybe
yes but but what are the downsides of
taking Saturday juice there's a downside
in taking medications there's a risk but
there's no risk in taking senator so why
not try exactly why not try and the
thing is is I always find the organic
studies organic studies are lots of
people drinking celery juice their skin
is clearing up their eczema psoriasis is
clearing up the brain fog is going away
their their anxieties dropping down
there's third there bloating goes down
their digestive system gets strong you
kind of argue would success all these
things are happening neurological
disorders are reversing celery juice
when you're drinking it right at the
right dosages and you're doing all that
all the stuffs happening and that's the
study see that's the study that's not
paid for that's what I love about that
that's the study that's not paid for
that's the organic study that
those truth and that who's gonna waste
money for research
instead you know because there's mainly
money maybe it's innate maybe the so
many juices a nice or because basically
what it does it hurts the pockets of the
industries
you can't bankroll off of it you can't
bet you can't make like billions of
dollars off it unless every fun acting
Center is so yeah but they get like one
penny one penny I talked to a couple
selling farmers and they said listen
there's no money in this you're making
us do all this work we have to feed this
so we have to get the all the natural
organic fertilizers we got to get all
these things and when you have the
equipment you're making us
that's what you know a farmer said to me
you're making us lease 20 more tractors
and and we're not making any money off I
think it's the middleman I think it's
not the farmers a new supermarket that
are delivering it to probably to a
supermarket it's good you know it's
funny because they remember you know you
know and by the way it's going for
somebody to make money yeah on something
that's good yeah yeah that's you know
that's a reward from from the universe
you know I mean people would say hey
what's your history where do you come
from a little bit like with me and stuff
I don't talk about myself ever it's
always about people it's about people
making sure they get the right things
yeah but spending a lifetime in Maine
and in that state and then the fisherman
out there with the lobstering and all
that stuff and I got that history in my
family and everything that family my
family line and and what happens is that
you don't make the money
catching the lobster of the fish the guy
that takes it to wherever he thinks it
next to he picks it up and he takes a
store he's a guy making money so I think
in the celery world's probably some
other place that's the same thing you
actually you're making the money
actually you know transporting it and
then the supermarket probably make some
money to the farmers they're not making
money I've had farmers tell me we're
killing ourselves to keep up with the
celery juice at that you know but they
know it's healing people
because they're drinking it too farmers
are like I'm gonna drink this and it's
healing people and everything and that's
the results you know the results are
what that is it's about this the organic
study in that organic study I mean you
have to remember that so if you're doing
something that's helping you in your
life that's that's what where it counts
that's where it counts I remember you
know visiting a doctor friend of mine
years and years years ago he said we'll
come to my office for I have lunch right
it's a long time it I think was like the
mid 90s or early nineties that come to
my office we'll have some lunch you just
gotta wait for a little while I have to
finish up with a couple patients so I
was waiting around out there and he had
a television inside his waiting room
area in a television in there and it was
saying garlic was bad for you bad for
you meanwhile there was a there was a
report on mainstream media I think a
couple of years before that in like 1989
1990 that garlic was good for you and
then but garlic's bad for you so
something was found out in science of
garlic's bad for you and then garlic
became good for you again and now it
then became bad for you it's just this
is is it on purpose why is this done you
know what I mean it's like I mean you
you know better than I as a physician
you know but I mean you're an expert
cardiologists you're an expert doctor
you you know why why is it like that
because because first of all first of
all there's in there's economic
interests in many of the studies but
also there's there's mistakes there's
the way that you design a study and then
the way that you interpret a study will
have a huge difference between the you
know one result or or another okay so so
you know research it's very important
but you gotta be careful when when you
interpret it yeah so that's that's what
happens you know it's incredible I mean
I know there's a lot of people and they
stand behind science and research but I
think that I noticed that when they
haven't seen twenty doctors and I
haven't seen five neurologists and I
haven't seen all these other people
right and they haven't been through what
all you guys have been through because I
mean you know dr. Junger I mean the
people in the audience here I mean they
there they got the aches and pains they
get the Hashimoto's thyroiditis and now
they get the fatigue then they get the
lime diagnosis then they get something
else and they they've been doctor now
they've been doctor it out you know and
in and it's like and put the people in
notice too haven't gotten sick yet but
just by chance by chance in a lot of
ways it just weren't the toxins didn't
overflow yet or something didn't go
wrong yet and by chance or they didn't
pick up a new pathogen or a new bug or
something or or an old bug in their
system didn't flourish and take over
something something you know Medes made
it so they're just still okay enough
they'll get sick later but they're still
okay enough those are the people I
notice that are like Oh hogwash rubbish
hogwash on this hogwash on that they're
not critics they become haters instead
because they believed so strongly the
science has figured everything out you
know and everything else the body is the
house we've been given right but it's
not their body we're renting it and and
it's not until people get the eviction
notice right the diagnosis then they
start looking for different solutions so
yeah I know I know the people that are
watching because I deal with them and
I've helped many of them reach restore
their natural ability to heal themselves
by detoxifying by choosing the right
foods by by using our Vedic medicine
principles functional medicine
principles intermittent fasting mixing
all these things to to really help
remove the obstacles and provide
whatever is lacking so the body can heal
itself
you know in a doctor youngers a really
humble guy you know what's it's it's
funniest thing cuz you know I I look to
him to keep my I try to check myself
thing a little bit in the sense where
you know he says you gotta be humble and
he tells me you gotta be humble you
gotta he knows I get I get I get upset
about things I get passionate about
things and he's always like look you
gotta you gotta check check that out the
door a little bit and you gotta stay
compassionate you gotta stay humble
you're always reminding me why don't you
know I I don't think I have to remind
you to stay compassionate
who are you are kind of the embodiment
of compassion yourself but what I what I
what I am saying is that we we cannot
forget that there is a space for science
right yeah yeah and there is a huge
space also for what science doesn't know
yeah and and and we have to take the
best out of everything
yeah and sure we're gonna deny one way
or not exactly and that I love because
there's things in science that offers is
amazing I talk about that all the time I
talk about my books you talk about it in
your books and you know there's there
it's a powerful nugget science does have
so much to offer and but but
compassionate doctors like dr. Junger
that no there's you guys have suffered
and struggled you know that's the whole
thing that you guys have really been
through a lot that's what counts because
that's the only way we're ever gonna
move forward that's the only way we're
ever gonna move forward is if if
professionals you know that that have
the degrees like you do and have the
training that you do and then the
experience and expertise know that you
guys are really struggling and that all
the answers are on out there and then
that our bodies the temple we got to get
the foods we've got to get the right
things we've got to get the herbs we get
all these things in all matters and that
that's what's incredible I want to talk
about the metals because the metals are
such the metals are such in the way
they're sent in such a toxic a toxic
element that's in the way of people's
healings and I want to talk about that
to get them out but before we before we
tell them how to make take them out tell
them how they get in yeah right well
what's your and what's your perception
of hag what's your opinion and
everything and we use them in so many
things I mean do you remember or write
about my Hatter's disease these to use
mercury in shaping hats so when you put
the hat on and you absorb mercury into
your system yeah and here's the thing I
put it on cosmetics okay the Mad
Hatter's disease I want to talk about
that a little bit
you guys don't wear a hat laced in
mercury you know but your forefathers
did and it's passed on through utero and
you know from sperm and egg it's passed
on that's how it's done
mercury gets passed on down the line
every generation until you get it out so
yeah yeah someone wore a hat back
19:20 with mercury and oh you know but
even if you were from your environment
the furniture that we buy is treated
with having met with LED and sure yeah
then the lacquer lacquer metals in it so
yes recently lipstick had mercury and
lead and so some some the cosmetics we
use the air we breathe the water we
drink and showered with but mostly the
the foods that we are loaded with
chemicals that a loner in communication
would cause some kind of learning
problem exam and the heavy metals are a
big part of it and the thing is this if
you don't help the body get rid of the
heavy metals it won't catch up with it
so that's why I love that you came up
with with the ingredients here I used to
recommend them separately but what
better than get them all together yeah
you get them all together you guys you
guys know about the heavy metal detox
smoothie of medical medium it's that you
got the cilantro you need that you got
the barley grass cheese powder you need
that you got the spirulina you need that
the wild blueberries you go get your
frozen wild blueberries it's critical
because people be like well how do I get
the metals out how do I get them out
frozen wild blueberries not the regular
blueberries they can't pull them out but
the frozen wild ones do the wild sea
wild food has different things going on
especially those blueberries so you got
that to get the wild blueberries you got
the cilantro
you got the broody grass you've got that
yeah and then adults do exactly adults
the seaweed you need the dulse in there
and then you blend it up with bananas if
you want to blend it up with a nut you
know you can check out the medical
meeting recipes if you want but you can
what you can blend them up with the
bananas another fruit you can pick you
can pick some papaya any if you really
want to or some other kind of fruit you
want to do I like me I'm kind of easy
it's like bananas and in the frozen wild
blueberries and get the other things in
if you got a thing that I detox movie
the thing that I teach my patients is to
eat all the different colors as I
learned from a colleague of mine called
you're gonna get something good in you
that way
no matter what is it what's been
happening this is the variability of
colors in your diet the bigger the
variability of your gut flora which is
now known to be really important part of
your body system so especially for
detoxification yeah the good intestinal
flora will detoxify half of the toxins
that you're exposed to if it's if it's a
healthy yeah bio yeah and it gets beaten
down by the toxins too so it gets beaten
down and that's a whole other thing and
we get inflamed the thing is with the
gut and she's got the pathogens in there
you got the streptococcus which will end
up giving you a SIBO diagnosis you got
bacteria in there that could you know
it's hiding behind rancid proteins that
are up on the linings of the intestinal
tract you know you got those things and
you end up feeding it with gluten and
you end up feeding it with eggs you
gotta be careful you guys don't do and
you do chicken eggs you'll feed
everything you know I always tell
everybody all the bugs were raised in
labs a long time ago and eggs were used
as the food eggs are a food for these
bugs and if they have eggs and you know
to feed the food you know feed the bugs
so what is it that the bugs love love
the eggs they love the eggs we train
train the scrambled eggs yeah we train
you know and in people if you don't have
a lot of bugs in you in the moment
you're young you feel indestructible
sure hey just say you're doing eggs it
might be okay but you get older you get
older and things hit and I you just have
to get you into your 30s and you start
getting more problems and you start
getting acne and you start getting you
know it's so the metals are one thing
the bugs wheat the bad foods we've got
to know what foods to stay away from
you're an expert at what foods to stay
away from you've been teaching at all
these years I'm it's incredible I can't
believe I have dr. l/100 younger here
for people that just came on we're live
right now and that's how we like to do
what we like to do with live I don't
like to edit things I like it alive you
know and hey if I make a mistake I make
a mistake if I you know if I fall off my
chair I fall off my chair
I'm just glad we're here this is
incredible and I just want to talk about
his folks for a quick second and he did
a book called clean gut you guys could
always check that out incredible clean
the original that's the original book
that's when you were like you know what
I'm gonna just I'm gonna do this I'm
gonna get the word out to the world
right there the thing is that that I was
discovering you have when you support
the detoxification systems that we
already have yeah and are trying to do
their work but they can't because our
foods are devoid of nutrients and
because our digestive systems are
working all the time therefore stealing
energy from the detoxification systems
then then when you create the conditions
and you support the liver and the other
organs to do the work of detoxification
it was just incredible what people who
are getting better off from right and I
got still called because the book he's
known as many languages as yours but
it's in a 20-something language you know
it's in a lot of and I get and I get
messages from all over the world ten
years later telling me I did the 21-day
program and I got better from this and
that and I still surprised to learn to
hear about how many different chronic
problems people get better and then my
new one yeah that's the new one coming
out the new one coming out how to look
out for that one to applying principles
from function you know there's something
else I want to tell you guys too is is
that uh dr. Junger
he wrote the foreword to the first
medical medium book so I was honored
when he did this this was a big deal for
me it meant all the world to me because
he's a famous doctor he's a famous
cardiologist and you know and he said
you know what I'm gonna do the foreword
for your book
well and it was yeah that really helped
me it really really helped to me because
it helped me get the information out to
you guys and help me get the information
out to the world me I don't I don't he
called me one day and say hey listen I
know that you have a lot to risk you're
a medical doctor maybe you shouldn't be
talking about these things but I wrote a
book and I want to see if you would be
willing to write because I I said well
let me check it out cuz I didn't want to
write a foreword for for anything just
because I like you
I read the book and I was blown away and
that's why I wrote and by the way people
call me from all over the world because
of that of that forward and at many
times even royalty from Europe call me
to see if they can get all of you and
when you did that forward you know and I
I couldn't thank you enough because
because I talk about controversial
things in that book and we you know we
talk about controversial things and
that's what it is about mystery illness
about chronic illness about why you're
sick about why you have the symptoms and
by the way he's a gentleman and he
returned the favor no not the favorite
how you gave me the book and I said I
only want you to write a foreword if you
really like it and he did right and so I
just want to tell you guys that there is
hope for healing that mean that's what
that's what it's about that's what we're
doing here you know you gotta pull the
medals out get your gut better talk
about that but it's an honor having me
here man I I don't even know what to say
and I really appreciate it and I really
feel like this is gonna help a lot of
people because they're hearing about the
gun that you Haley they're hearing about
their body being this temple and we rent
it we rent out this body we can get an
eviction notice if we're not you know
that's how I know this is an eviction
notice that's the only time when people
get serious and start making changes
right that's true but the problem is
this we know now that the chronic
diseases that we're suffering from all
over the world start years before in a
silent mode and they start by turning on
the inflammatory system by the way which
80% is around the gut within and around
the guys so your inflammation can be
turned on for 15 years before the real
disease is diagnosed absolutely so start
don't don't wait for symptoms even even
if even if they're minor symptoms don't
wait for them to get worse or other
symptoms to appear or chronic diseases
to be diagnosed start now
powerful powerful exactly it's what
happens with Hashimoto's thyroiditis it
started out with Epstein Barr in your
system and then percolated in their
proliferated over the years and also now
you're 32 you're 35 you're 42 you get
your you gave your hypothyroid diagnosis
the doctors worried about your thyroid
and that's because he had the viral
infection the Epstein Barr deep down in
there in your system a long time ago and
if we knew if we just know that we can
we can really avoid things and of course
if we get a problem we could work on
healing it reversing it make sure you
drink your celery juice make sure you do
all the good stuff we're talking about
and remember and remember your body has
the ability to heal each I love that
that gets me kind of choked up right now
well that's right that's what that's how
nature design nature did not design
diseases right disease is what we known
as diseases are just adaptation and
survival mechanisms that your body put
on in order to defend itself in and
survive right and they've been there for
too long
for example heart disease which affects
everybody what is it
it's the blockage of arteries right by
cholesterol yeah but at the beginning in
the beginning it starts because there's
a little fissure in the artery in the
body it patches it up good cholesterol
now if if the fissure is healed and you
know the smoking and the bad fats and
then the stress and the high blood
pressure are taken away from the from
the picture the the the body we
reabsorbed that lack of cholesterol and
then everything will be fine
but because the irritating factors the
toxins the heavy metals them let's just
keep on there the body keeps on patching
keeps on patching keeps on patching as a
survival mechanism
eventually the patching will block the
flow of blood and that's when heart
disease is diagnosed right so so this is
our survival mechanism and if you get to
understand how to remove the obstacles
bugs heavy metals stress bad thoughts
bad company you remove the obstacles and
you add what is lacking which is usually
a nutrient yeah
good nutrients
then everything results by itself and
the body is able to regain its ability
its natural ability to heal itself you
know in remember and that's coming from
you know an expert cardiologist right
here an expert cardiologists right here
means powerful piece of information and
it's just it's it's you know they have
that right here is amazing you know just
remember it's like exactly the doctor
your eyes are saying is your body can
heal there's so many of you that have
been sick for a long time and you forget
what it's like to feel good and some of
you have never felt good and it breaks
my heart you never had that moment in
your life where you felt good and then
and because you've started out sick you
started out with symptoms you know there
weren't it's or it's rare times you
remember you felt good and and and and
don't get lost in that I know it's it's
it's easy for me to say and when you're
going through it it's hard it's hard but
they hear it from me it probably easy
it's easy for me to say hey just hang in
there but no it's more than that know
that I care and I really want you to
hang in there because I want you to know
that you can heal and you will it's just
you're gonna you're gonna learn from the
medical medium serious books you learn
from dr. younger suppose you just learn
and we're gonna make sure we help you in
any way we can I mean I would go even
further and it's this I see the planet
as a living organism as an animal as it
were right and the rivers are like the
arteries and the forests are like the
lungs and and and the cells that are
running around right are you and me
so people are the cells of this organism
right and and if you look at this
organism this the planet it has a fever
global warming is not anything else but
a symptom it's you know so so where is
this symptom coming from and in in my
opinion the majority of the problem is
the toxicity of our breath yeah it's
excessively not only the toxins the air
we breathe the water we drink and shower
with the cosmetics we use the
medications we take right but most of
the foods that way that food a lot of
yeah you know I didn't have to worry
about you coming
with clone on cuz cologne cologne just
it's just it's so strong you know when
people work alone it's they stay away
from it's toxic and and and if you know
and some people don't like the smell I
don't think too many people like the
smell Cologne I didn't even have to say
anything because you're not gonna come
here to doused with Cologne you're not
gonna come here not gonna come here
doubts with all that and because it's
you know it's toxic and so it it's an
example you know you know where I was
when I was going at is that when when
healing ourselves we have to be healing
the planet yeah because yeah eyes above
so below right everything goes together
the more the more we learn how to create
the conditions for our bodies to you the
more we're heating the planet you know
it's incredible and it's true I mean
there's a tremendous amount of toxicity
here it's falling out of the sky I talk
about it all the time we breathe it in
or it's any we can't we can't hide from
it we can't run from it we can protect
ourselves the best we can but we got to
do it for the food so we got to protect
your stuff some way we're doing it I
just love this and it's incredible time
to be here this is amazing thank you for
coming on thank you you know and I am so
happy and proud of you because when I
met you you didn't need to have an
Instagram account nobody you don't know
what you really are you was working on
people you were doing yours your thing
at a small scale with people and you had
amazing results right but now this
ability to scale and to have your your
your knowledge expose people all over
the world what's the book is amazing you
said instead it used to be a jelly I had
to work on 50 people a day seven days a
week and I'd be on the phone with him
and talking to him I be up on and off
all night moms had bring their babies to
the front door and two o'clock in the
morning and but it but I didn't I didn't
have the books out I just the waiting
list got big and I had I knew I had to
get the books out I know Lori I gotta
get the books because I had people
waiting for so long and I had to call
unit please squeeze them
the books are did that's what's getting
out there in anyway I'm just honored to
be here and can't tell you subscribe you
know subscribe so you can be there for
these lives because these aren't edited
where you can just take your time and go
find one sure you can find either look
at all my other lives that we just did
but the point is is these that these are
not edited so subscribe and make sure
you click that notification Bell make
sure you like you know do the likes and
all that I'm not tech savvy but that's
what you do right and the bottom line is
you don't want to miss these lives
because this live right here so powerful
and so helpful I'm honored to have you
here and and just incredible so I love
you man and you guys know I love you and
look take care of yourself I'll see you
next time and we're gonna keep on doing
this but today it's a big day and I'm
gonna be nice to be with out of you I'm
not even gonna be able to sleep tonight
I'm gonna be buzzing all night long
because this and anyway I'm gonna I
guess what I'll do is I'll pick this off
because that's that's how we do it