a pizza
sausage pepperoni the sausages on there
it's the pepperoni right
there's a red onion on there that's too
healthy though right but I got a nice
Pizza going don't worry this is a vegan
pizza I'm craving a vegan pizza now
right
vegan pizza
hungry oh
your legs are back I'm bringing them
back in
I hear everybody's got chickens now
everybody's got chickens because the
price of eggs went up it's like okay
everybody's got chickens now everybody's
laying their own eggs
pretty funny I'm gonna make some eggs
some fried eggs scrambled eggs got a
hankering got a craving is what I got
right
you guys this is day 11 talking I'm
talking about Cravings creating shifter
we're talking about the moderation trap
took some reading straight out of here
brain saver just so you know I'm gonna
read a little bit which is kind of
exciting let's find the craving shifter
of what we're going to be working on
we're doing the craving shifter today
mind blowing it is so powerful it is not
a joke man when you do that craving
shifter
that thing shuts down Cravings like it
just shuts them down it's really
incredible it's a miracle
I'm reading page 147 of the moderation
trap inside brain saver if you guys want
to hang out while I read a little bit
it's pizza smells really good These
Wings smell really good right here
Heidi Inman said saving so much money
not buying so you're not buying all the
chocolate and all the coffee because I
see some emojis there
all right
you guys know that why it's not good to
eat eggs right
you know vegans don't eat eggs
for the moment when they're 100 vegan
because they don't want to eat an animal
product but they don't know why eggs are
bad nobody knew why eggs were bad nobody
in any health realm vegan or anywhere
else eggs are bad because the medical
medium information about eggs feeding
pathogens inside the body dormant
shingles virus dormant Epstein-Barr
Dorman hhv6 dormant CMV all the
different viruses especially
Epstein-Barr feed on eggs we eat the
eggs the viruses feed on the eggs and
then release neurotoxins and the
neurotoxins give everybody symptoms
neurological symptoms which is all
medical medium information nobody knew
that either it's incredible really the
contribution of spirit of compassion to
the Alternative Health world and
conventional Health world with this
information that's why you don't eat
eggs it's not because of other reasons
like hey I'm vegan and I won't eat eggs
even though vegans go back to eating
eggs after they get sick eating vegan
because they're not doing vegan the
right way or whatever people just go
back to eating eggs
all right moderation trap right here in
brain saver good to see you guys we're
day at 11 brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge moderation never works for
anyone
what what
are you serious there's an IG comment
here I'm about to read
uh Madeline says oh and the craving
shifter worked
yeah it does work thank you for saying
that because it really does it's
powerful it's a powerful tool it's
incredible it's unmatched for busting
Cravings it's an instant craving Crusher
is what it is it's incredible
moderation never works for anyone what
it's permission to do things that aren't
great for us
am I wrong or am I right
is this wrong or is this right is SOC
wrong or is SOC right
it's permission to do things that aren't
great for us
right because that's what moderation is
moderation the whole concept the whole
understanding of it is to make sure we
have permission to do things that just
aren't good for us
our physical body does not like
moderation
it doesn't I'm just gonna do these
shrooms man and put in moderation I'm
going to micro dose these this Ayahuasca
just in moderation I'm gonna eat this
chocolate bar in moderation man
I'm on page Jane I'm on page 147
in brain saver right here
I'm gonna do these recreational drugs in
moderation I'm gonna eat this chocolate
cake in moderation
yet our body is governed by our
subconsciousness and Consciousness our
body is under the control of our
subconsciousness and Consciousness that
part of that piece right there is just
incredible when you think about it our
body is under the control
of our subconsciousness and
consciousness
that means if our Consciousness wants to
eat in moderation or party in moderation
then our body has to shut up
sit down and take it
that's what our body has to do
if our Consciousness and
subconsciousness wants to partake in
moderation in any way it wants to
partake in any kind of moderation
whether it's wreck drugs
prescription Pharmaceuticals whatever or
Pizza
chocolate cake whatever cacao
our body
has to just be like
gotta do it got no choice
your body has to shut up
and take it
so our body is governed by our
subconsciousness and Consciousness our
mind which can be injured or persuaded
to want something our physical body
doesn't want
our Free Will is part of how we step
outside the box in life we use our free
will to step out of the box
it's how we embark on trying to heal
when we aren't being given any true
answers so we don't have any answers go
to the doctor we're sick we have no
answers
we go to a functional doctor and he says
oh stay away from processed foods
you do it you stay away from processed
foods and you're still sick
don't know why but you're still sick and
don't have an answer
and because of that our Free Will has
this desire to be like we we use our
free will
our soul has this desire to get a free
will to be like we need help we need
help we need answers I don't want to be
sick I need answers
we can make two kinds of mistakes I'm
interested in reading that I want to
know what these mistakes are
hm sounds 88 says yes what is wrong with
cacao just really kills the adrenals it
gives women hard
childbirths like
it because you're adrenals
get clobbered when you're doing cacao
clobbered so you're using them like a
credit card you're using them you're
using all your credit card power out of
your adrenals so if you're if you're
someone that's dealing with adrenal
fatigue or any kind of adrenal issues
you don't even know you're dealing with
or kidney issues on any level that you
don't even know you're dealing with
or brain problems you don't know you're
dealing with like nervous system issues
cacao kills your nervous system because
it jacks up the adrenaline the
adrenaline floods into the brain and
destroys nerve sheaths because
adrenaline's so corrosis it's like
corrosive you're taking adrenaline that
you shouldn't be using you're creating a
stimulation you're not supposed to be
creating
so it's a drug
it's a cacao really prevents healing
okay fine if you're not so sick and we
just did a big talk about people who are
not so sick they can play in any land
they want I'm going to eat a whole
ton of eggs I'm gonna eat all the cacao
I want I could do what I want right when
you're not so sick but when you get
really sick and the scale tips
and you start doing that cacao you you
can't heal the chocolate industry the
caffeine industry has has a lot of money
behind it they will tell you that it has
antioxidants and Cacao is good for you
and caffeine products are good for you
but they're not
and they really really rip apart the
nervous system they damage the brain
over time and they they cause the
adrenals to just flood what the cacao
does for women is it makes it so many
women have to have a C-section when they
weren't planning on a C-section
that's what cacao can do years of cacao
and chocolate coffee right all of it
they have think tanks that are designed
to really keep people addicted for a
lifetime so the caffeine industry
has think tanks that are designed to
make sure that you stay on caffeine for
the rest of your life and that your baby
becomes addicted to caffeine and all
that carries it on carries it up
we can make two kinds of mistakes I'm
reading page 147 in brain saver these
are incredible books that protocols
right friend saver protocols
anybody who's interested
we can make two kinds of mistakes in the
first kind of mistake we can have a test
in front of us in school and get several
true true or false questions wrong
we can make a mistake crossing our T's
and dotting our eyes
we can make a mathematical mistake
in this type of mistake there's no free
will
or rather not your free will
the Free Will behind that test was the
Free Will of an institution or the
person who designed it
so you're in school and you take a test
you're not using your free will
it's an institution
that's making you take that test
the institution
is in control of your free will you
don't have free will
you take you're taking the test in
school because an institution has you
taking that test
Free Will behind that test was not the
free will
of your own
it was an institution
or the person who designed it so the
person who designed your test in school
your mathematic medical test or whatever
remember I'm not a college grad I never
went to college
whatever
the point is
the point is is that
if you go to school which is fine I want
people to go to school I want them to go
to college I want them to do
what's right for them of course right
not telling people don't go to school
it's just that we don't use our free
will when we're in school
our Free Will is taken over by an
institution or a person who designed
that test
we only used our free will when we
decided to sit down
this so you walked into class and you
sat down that's your when you use your
free will
and when you filled out the test
and you tried to answer questions that
was your free will
then we can make mistakes that affect
our soul mistakes through decision
processes using our conscious mind that
aren't about exact calculations so
there's one form of mistake you make
where you fill out the wrong
answer on your test in school that's a
mistake you made you made a mistake
but there's other mistakes mistakes that
decision processing happened where you
used your Consciousness it's not about
exact calculations formulations or word
choices
we can make mistakes that are outside
the realm of punching numbers and
answering questions that we've studied
and prepared for and memorized
so when you study for a test you can
still make a mistake oh
I remembered the answer I can't remember
it right now so I'm going to choose this
little spot I'll check this box and oh I
made a mistake
but there's another form of mistake we
make with our consciousness
while making these other kinds of
decisions our soul can be impacted these
are the mistakes we make with our own
free will so what I'm trying to say is
we can make mistakes in moderation
that hinder Us in other ways
Health with Liz said this is
mind-blowing that's why I didn't
continue using my free will now to
create myself it's incredible
when we're sick
the diagnostic testing process is
similar to being in school
you guys follow me on that
when we are sick the diagnostic testing
process when we're sick is similar to
being in school here's a physical test
that the doctor prescribed
here's a drug that the doctor prescribed
it's kind of like school
here's another test here's another drug
we use our free will only
to try all these tests and these
treatments
we're using our free will to do the test
and try the drug
just like we use our free will to sit
down and take a test in school
we go through the MRIS
the CAT scans
the blood panels
and more
we're still not better
a lot of people that go through all that
and they're not better yet right
that leaves us in the realm of not
finding answers how many people have
gone through
a battery of tests
taking a battery of drugs
and they're not better
it leads them to search for answers
correct
we find ourselves sitting at home one
night telling ourselves we really need
to heal we have to find an answer
how many people have been left sitting
home at night
after they tried a battery test in a
battery of drugs
and a battery of doctors and they're
sitting home at night
and they see to themselves
I have to get out of this
I have to find a way
I have to find an answer
I have to heal
now we have to use our free will like
never before to find answers for our
physical body you see where I'm going
here
anyone who found medical medium
information
they went above and beyond using their
free will
they really ignited their free will to
find an answer
now we have to use our free will like
never before to find answers for our
physical body it's not about black and
white
we discover
it's about taking a it's not about
taking a test
in an institution on a memorized set of
answers
it's not about being indoctrinated to a
place
all our egos oh sorry
must be the ego shifter I'm still
remembering there it's not about being
indoctrinated to place all our eggs in
their basket
instead finding Health answers becomes a
journey
when I think about this getting a little
bit a little bit emotional right now in
this moment because I'm getting
flashbacks over and over again of how
many people I've seen throughout the
years
and how many people that are out there
now
they're searching for answers
their free will only went as far
as sitting down and taking getting
through a battery of tests and doing a
battery of drugs but then they found I'm
not better yet
I need to do more
l r Rose says I can relate and then they
sat down
one night
maybe in their Darkest Hour
and they thought about all the symptoms
they have
and how they've tried everything they
can think of
and they're stuck
spiritual path to true love says all
those tests really had me fooled that
they knew what they were doing so glad
you told us what's really going on
it's a powerful uh comment by the way
that means you're experienced that means
you've seen how things are you know
what's going on out there
so what I'm what I'm reading to you guys
right now is I'm talking about how
our free will
really ignites and takes off when we're
in that dark hour
and we've used our Free Will instead for
the institutions
and then all of a sudden
there's this moment in time where like I
need an answer
I need to heal I need to find something
and that's when your Consciousness and
subconsciousness
really
hunker down
attach itself to the Free Will that you
have
and then you search for something else
now you're not putting all your eggs in
the institutions basket
instead you're finding Health answers it
becomes a journey
kind of like when we're looking for love
we're lonely
we want a partner to share our lives
with
and there can almost be a desperation
of our Consciousness in some situations
that brings the soul into a different
Realm
just like in the search for love when we
reach when we reach this point in our
search for healing
it's not about what looks perfect on
paper anymore or even what makes sense
anymore
we end up taking risks
that's where the soul has no choice but
to go along for the ride with whatever
we're being pushed into and whatever our
Consciousness is pushing our soul into
even if it's not the best for our soul
and physical brain and body this is
where we can make mistakes
if our Consciousness is peer pressured
convinced persuaded or conditioned into
using information or practices that
don't align with healing or that even
interfere with healing I'm on page 148 a
brain saver
you know when I read that what do I
understand
this means that after we leave that
institutional understanding
you go through a battery of tests
you do a battery of drugs
you're stuck
and now
you go on a journey
you use your free will and go on a
journey
but we can still make mistakes using our
free will on a journey but we're still
we still have to search
we may search for love
it may not work out
but we
need it
to find somebody else
and maybe it did work out
or searching for health answers
we take a whole bunch of stuff that
isn't good and eat a whole bunch of
cacao and we do all this other stuff
whatever I'm just saying
and we don't get what we need
but then we stumble across something we
do find and it works out
foreign
spiritual said it made many many
mistakes because of that
Korean passion says this is amazing I
had no idea how deep you were
and that's your service and
wait a minute don't you listen to my
podcast at Medical meme podcast at Apple
podcast
and don't you read all the medical
medium books
serious deep stuff big time
ah you thought I was just a celery juice
guy no I don't know
foreign
to go against our instincts check this
section out you guys this is incredible
page 148 a brain saver
moderation
is one of those practices
there's nothing wrong with having that
I'm not saying
I tell people they can eat what they
want they can eat pizzas they could eat
this and this but just try to do some
medical medium Tools in between it all
try to get started somehow start with 16
ounces of celery juice on an empty
stomach I don't tell people if they have
to give up everything in their life
that's not it it depends how sick they
are and what they need accomplished how
they need to heal how far they need to
go someone's really sick they're
bedridden they're on mattress Island
there's a way out and it may be where
we're not doing certain things to get
out of that
moderation is one of those practices
I've always said start bringing in the
good and crowd out the bad that's the
medical medium talk for years now
decades bring in the good slowly and
it'll crowd out the bad
moderation is one of those practices
there's nothing wrong with having that
you should have what you want
you need to balance it
we're told that if we only engage in
reasonable amounts questionable Foods
and certain practices such as micro
dosing caffeine and even alcohol could
benefit us
if it's in small reasonable dosages it
could benefit you that's what we're
taught
so we give them a try and we end up set
back even more in our healing
absolutely so many people are set back
in their healing constantly
whether we know it or not we're set back
in our healing
because our conditioning is so strong
that's what happens on planet Earth
we're up against an immense amount of
conditioning here and brainwashing
we blame ourselves for these practices
not working out instead of blaming the
substances themselves
we don't know how to blame the
substances
we're conditioned to think the
substances are fine like cacao
coffee
so many other things
and this isn't just the cacao and coffee
thing I'm talking about those two little
examples
because of our conditioning is so strong
we blame ourselves for those for these
practices not working out instead of
blaming the substances themselves we may
even become so attached that we guard
these practices with our lives
Kombucha tea can turn your blood into
acid
mm info for over 30 years now out there
it literally can turn the blood into a
straight acidosis condition
but people love their Kombucha Tea it's
most Kombucha tea has caffeine in it
we've been pushed so often into finding
fault with ourselves with their brains
and bodies that we self-blame ourselves
and it becomes our default setting it's
my fault it's my fault it's my problem
I'm the blame my body's faulty I caused
the problem I'm why I'm sick I'm why I'm
mental I have a problem because of me
it's me it's me it's my fault
it's not the conditioning out there
yes it is it's not the brainwashing out
there yes it is
it's not all the traps out there yes it
is the traps out there people just blame
themselves it's got to be me I'm faulty
I'm broken down I'm a bad person
Warehouse one says my health crashed in
early 2020.
lived with an ostomy bag 10 months
they had no answer I asked what caused
my colon disease they had no answer two
years on medical media my life is better
than ever now
Warehouse one on YouTube thank you for
leaving that comment bless your heart
moderation cannot be defined
even though you'll see a definition of
the word moderation
if you look it up in the dictionary
we should see it as undefinable
because moderation is not measurable
it's a ruleless definition because it's
different for everyone
isn't that interesting moderation can't
be defined
that's incredible
number one Spirit of compassion gave me
those words and I wrote them as I heard
them
I was kind of blown away because I
didn't think about that what do you mean
moderation the definition can't like you
can't have a definition for moderation
how's that possible
I cover kombucha and brain saver
protocols for those that are asking if
kombucha is actually healthier enough
I would love to do a Kombucha Tea
episode I would love to do a Kombucha
Tea podcast right now and I would love
to talk about it but we've got to talk
about moderation for a little bit
this is mind-blowing right here is it
just me
no I know you guys think this is cool
too right the info
moderation cannot be defined what
even though you'll see a definition of
the word moderation if you look it up in
the dictionary it still can't be defined
we should see it as undefinable because
moderation is not measurable
it's a ruleless definition because it's
different for everyone
foreign
each individual's limitations are
different one person's moderation can
kill another person
see why it's not definable
one person's moderation can kill another
person
someone else is drinking in moderation
can kill another person
who can't drink like that
that's true whether we're talking about
alcohol psychedelics or even food even
food
someone who's allergic to nuts could die
from someone else's level of nuts in
moderation someone else could have a nut
allergy but still be able to eat nuts in
moderation another person with a nut
allergy can't even eat a speck of nut in
moderation
it'll kill them
it can't be defined it's not measurable
when sort of compassion told me that and
I put it in here what's this like what
we hear moderation talked about a lot
with food choosing to eat a food in
moderation is born out of knowing
somewhere deep inside that the food
you're choosing may not be safe to eat a
lot of or to eat constantly is that true
like is that true
I hear moderation all the time out there
I hear people talk about it all the time
I'm eating in moderation I'm doing what
I want in moderation do you guys hear it
out there choosing to eat of food in
moderation is born out of knowing
somewhere deep inside deep inside
everybody
that it may not be a good thing to eat
too much of
instinctually you may feel that way I'm
just gonna have a slice of that
pepperoni sausage pizza
I gotta be I gotta just do moderation
right now and I only have to have to
slice of that because deep inside I know
I'm not supposed to be tanking one of
these every night
Ros Angela says lived way too many years
feeling like I was inadequate as a woman
since age 10 being made to believe my
body was flawed out and I'd never get
better thank God I found you three years
ago
thank you for being here truly vegan
mommy V's life
all the books are truly amazing with
life-changing information I must say I'm
really loving the brain saver books
though I've learned so much I feel like
the brain saver books are the best books
ever
ever out of all time I mean in history
of Health when you crack into these
the information is just
so mind-blowing so incredible
I mean all the medical meaning books
so we're talking about moderation right
now
deep inside of us innately
we're using the term moderation because
we know that we have to be careful and
that what we're eating might not be good
and what we're doing might not be good
we use the term moderation to give
ourselves permission to consume that
food something inside us knows we're not
supposed to be eating fried greasy food
every day
is there something inside of you that
tells you you should probably not be
eating fried greasy food every single
day
because I talk about moderation all
these years
I've had a lot of people both like
outside of the communities and every now
and then someone inside the community it
just doesn't like
you know doesn't like doing their celery
juice doesn't like whatever and they'll
be like
he's he's anti-moderation moderation is
is the best thing in life
are we
foreign
are we okay to eat cakes and cookies and
donuts all day long
we know it's not good
so maybe we'll just have one cake one
cookie one donut
see Rising Phoenix said it would be very
very very helpful to hear more about
what is helpful for the normal person
and not everything but grass and celery
are acceptable to eat
what's really interesting about that
comment
Rising Phoenix
is that medical medium information is
the only out there in all the health
world that allows people to be a vegan
if they want
or an animal protein person if they want
and all walks of life come here and if
you want to eat what you want to eat you
can the tools are here for when you're
ready that's all so hang out have some
fun the tools are here for when you're
ready
pick up a medical medium book at the
library for free if you don't want to
pay 22 dollars
you know at Amazon whatever and
they're there for you so if you're
really sick someday Rising Phoenix you
can take the books to your doctor or
whatever meaning like looking into the
books getting the information
and
check out the medical game podcasts at
Apple podcast so you know like what I
talk about because it's not about just
grass and celery
that's not here so I don't know where
that information came from I don't know
if someone said that out there you must
not be reading the books or this or
hearing the podcasts or seeing
everything on social media with all the
amazing foods and the recipes and the
herbs and the wild foods and you can eat
meat if you want you can be plant-based
if you want that's how incredibly vast
it is so I just want you to know Rising
Phoenix that it's not just grass and
celery and it's it's so much the recipes
you can be eating all the potatoes you
want you can do whatever you can be
plant-based you could be animal protein
it's really there's a tremendous amount
of information so I wonder if someone
just said something to you and
and you just didn't know
but thank you for being here and thank
you for that comment
see we learn along the way that it's not
the best choice and could lead to some
kind of Health complication if we want
to just go crazy and eat donuts every
day all day long we know that
something's going to go wrong we can
sense it we can feel it we know it
moderation is permission to self-indulge
or self-sabotage so it's a permission to
self-sabotage when you hear hey I can do
it in moderation we're actually giving
ourselves permission or someone's giving
us permission that moderation is totally
fine
and maybe it is fine if you've never
been sick
and you're not sick and you want to play
reindeer games and you want to partake
in whatever maybe it is fine if that's
what you want to do but if you're sick
and you're struggling you've got the
migraines and the aches and pains and
the jaw pain the back pain and you've
got R.A you're at the rheumatologist
you're you're going everywhere you're at
the autoimmune doctor you don't know
what's wrong with you you got brain fog
you've got anxiety you've got depression
you got Tremors ticks and spasms
whatever's going on then moderation only
is out to get you not protect you
maytal said on YouTube I question a lot
of the foods my health nutritionist says
for my sibo
no pears and apples but cookies and one
serving of alcohol okay
are you trying to make me laugh
[Music]
Hall
are you trying to cheer me up and make
me laugh or something give me a giggle I
don't agree
the FODMAP list is very outdated
first of all
FODMAP or any place else
they were always outdated mm info was
always far advanced
but now they're actually taking medical
medium information
and they're incorporating them in all to
those outdated programs and diet belief
systems they're just stealing and
poaching so much mm info and they're
plugging it into all those outdated
there was all those outdated crappy
belief systems that never got people
better when they were sick anyway you
made me laugh right there
okay
a little bit of alcohol is fine don't
eat a pear
don't eat an apple but you can have a
cookie
oh man
I'm cracking up over here
drinking in moderation is also a term
though often here that's because they
were allowing drinking in moderation we
happen to be talking about that right
there maybe you even use the term
drinking in moderation I'm drinking in
moderation
you guys want to come over my house
later have some drinks
um we'll do it in moderation medical
medium will have just half a shot of
vodka Maybe
do you want a Long Island Iced Tea
do you want a Bloody Mary do you want
some do you want do you want a rum and
coke right we'll do it all in moderation
I'll have a drink
kidding
maybe you even use the term moderation
as with any other substance using the
term moderation around alcohol gives us
a fuzzy safe warm feeling inside I'm
doing it in moderation I can have this
beer in this glass of wine right now
it's in moderation
it's permission to drink in any capacity
we feel is appropriate yeah my
moderation happens to be three glasses
of wine a night I'm not doing six
glasses of wine at night I'm doing just
three glasses of wine a night that's my
moderation ah it's warm and fuzzy
that's a slippery slope one person may
drink every single day and still call
this moderation heck yeah another person
may drink in the afternoons and feel
that's moderation because they're not
drinking in the morning I don't drink in
the morning so my moderation is pretty
good it's pretty solid pretty untapped
it's right there I mean my moderation is
don't drink in the morning I could drink
from the afternoon on as long as it's
after 12 o'clock in the afternoon I can
definitely drink that's my moderation
everybody's moderation when it comes to
alcohol is different for some it may be
on weekends only I only drink on the
weekend
that's my moderation I got it totally
under control
for others it may be one glass of wine
at night all week
one glass of wine a week
and for others moderation may be getting
straight out drunk once a month I get
plastered and shit-faced once a month
that's my moderation I don't drink for
the whole month
and then I totally
get plastered
we hide our alcohol addiction behind the
word moderation of it as if it's a
shield keeping us from harm moderation
is my shield
I got a shield right here that's my
moderation Shield right here and I'm in
battle
I'm really getting hungry though oh I
think I'm gonna have a pizza but it's
only in moderation
meanwhile we make those who recognize
themselves as addicts feel different or
faulty when that's far from the case
yeah no you're an addict
when you're you're doing the
20-step program
you're an addict totally you're an
alcohol you've got alcoholic you got a
disease me I'm just drinking in
moderation I don't have a disease and
I'm not an alcoholic I drink one glass
of wine a night I'm not an alcoholic I
don't have a disease but you you got a
disease and you're an alcoholic you
better do your 12-step program
that's right you better be micromanaged
because you're not safe with yourself me
I drink in moderation
I drink on the weekends yeah I get drunk
on Saturday night but I got control over
it I drink in moderation you you better
be doing your 12-step program man
because you're an alcoholic
Jacob Johnson said it's amazing how we
rationalize our self-sabotage indeed it
is
all right let's talk about moderation
Origins for a little bit if you guys
hanging in there with me we're gonna
make a craving shifter today Gene says I
was told to eat fruits in moderation but
I could have eggs dairy sugar
Free Stuff Etc
better be careful with fruit better eat
fruit in moderation but you can have
lots of these
could have plenty of eggs six eggs a day
just
be careful with the fruit
gotta watch out don't eat more than one
orange a week but you can have lots of
eggs all week long it's unbelievable
Nicholas Russell I've been following mm
closely really
what did you find
I've been following mm closely for about
seven and a half years boom Nicholas
Russell that's a long time always spot
on and never once contradicted info
uh I love knowing you're keeping a
record Nicholas that makes me happy mm
info truly is a game changer it works if
you work it with a I think a heart there
thank you Nicholas appreciate it
it's good to know you've been
uh watching over me
waiting for me to screw up someday
and you know the thing is Spirit of
compassion it's hard to contradict
that's the that's the problem like
that's not the problem that's a good
problem to have Spirit of compassion
makes it so I don't contradict because
it's not my information if I was if it
was my information from a human I'm a
human
I think I am right I'm human and so
if it was coming from me I probably
would have contradicted myself a billion
times over like all the other people do
in health they contradict themselves
yearly weekly daily
and it seems like on social no one
really sees it it's just here today gone
tomorrow they contradicted themselves
six months ago and nobody remembers and
then they start fresh with some other
bull crap and then they contradict
themselves on that right but medical
medium
info
hasn't we don't contradict Spirit
compassion and we don't contradict and
we stay consistent and it's always been
like that for years with eight huge
Bibles I mean it's it's really
incredible
so that's important to know too
exactly never contradict itself Lucas
says
we don't do trends
we don't do Trends this is timeless
information on how to heal
medical medium info
is not Trend this trend that Trends
don't heal people this is incredible
Timeless classic unique information from
above
all right moderation Origins if you guys
don't mind I would
I want to proceed if that's okay
even when we know better
when we know not to consume something
that isn't best for our health and
well-being someone around us or
something we see in the media tells us
we can do it in moderation
even when we know better
someone is going to say you can do that
in moderation in the media or somebody
you know or whoever a practitioner a
doctor but always listen to your doctors
do what your doctor tells you of course
but I'm just saying someone's gonna tell
you
even when you know better and it's not
good someone's going to tell you to do
it
sometimes it's stated
and sometimes the modern the moderation
message is subliminal
sometimes it's just straight out in
front
sometimes it's subtle
the suggestion is always in our face
whenever we turn
and wherever we turn moderation is
nothing new it goes back hundreds and
hundreds of years in human civilization
this is cool just check this out if you
guys got a second this piece of
information always blows my mind
it just does
Katrin says Anthony what's going on with
people
who do everything opposite every day
that food smoke caffeine drink on the
weekends no fruits no grains no water
age 45 and no problems why talk about
that through all the medical medium
books their scale will tip Katrin
it will tip
and they'll be in a bad place no one's
escaping sickness
everybody's sick out there now just
about
and there are a few scragglers left that
are 45 and they're still doing what they
want and then when they're 48
it hits sometimes it just hits in
different ways maybe they won't get a
chronic illness where it's all this
neurological stuff
and instead they get their first heart
attack
moderation is nothing new it goes back
hundreds and hundreds of years in human
civilization
for as long as it's been human
conditioning
to eat ourselves sick
the concept of everything in moderation
arose in ancient times
the con the concept of everything in
moderation
it's not now it's not in modern day
world modern day Health modern day
medicine modern day reality
the concept of everything in moderation
arose in ancient times
people are always like oh oh in ancient
times they knew about this herb oh no
in ancient times they knew about celery
no celery root is not celery celery root
was a soup
in the 1800s had nothing to do with
people dude juices orange juice the
industries push it hard they push
moderation really hard and they run with
it because that's how they keep you
conditioned and train you but check this
out
everything in moderation arose in
ancient times when people first started
to have the type of access that allowed
them to indulge in excessive consumption
of all times the minute
civilization was able to indulge
they weren't starving to death
they had resources and access
that's when moderation started
hand in hand
with this newfound instant gratification
the concept of moderation developed as a
way to rain it all in because the minute
civilizations had enough to eat
they would burst their stomachs
they would eat themselves sick
and so they had to learn how to rein it
in and the minute they learned how to
rein it in that's when moderation
started
this moderation knowledge has now been
in our Consciousness for centuries
that's insane it's unbelievable really
if we're not taught to be careful and
put limitations on what how when why or
how much we consume we can kill
ourselves in one capacity or another
today
we can kill ourselves today in one
capacity or another
boom
even though the word moderation emerged
concept emerged as a way to protect
ourselves
now moderation is being used to
unprotect ourselves did you know that
moderation is being used in the reverse
way right now you guys to unprotect
ourselves
that's what we're being brainwashed to
do constantly now unprotect ourselves
we're using it moderation as a
permission to poison ourselves
we're actually using moderation now to
give us permission to poison ourselves
whatever we want to indulge in or harm
ourselves with we can do it so in good
Consciousness right by saying
in good conscious we're doing it in
moderation we're meant to have the tools
and knowledge and resources to not go
down this road though and that's another
point we're meant not to have to go down
this road
but
what's happened now is it's being used
to control us
to control what we purchase out there
now and
to eat now
it's hard to break away from the status
quo of moderation because it's so built
in society it is weaved into society now
as
a weapon moderation has been weaponized
right now
so much so that if you start eating
to heal someone's gonna call you
orthorexic
if you start eating to heal this is
incredible kale right here this kale is
insanely good
if you start eating to take care of
yourself and heal
and you you're sticking with your celery
juice every single morning you can be
called orthorexic or that the medical
medium protocols or create orthorexia or
something that's how weaved in
moderation has been it's weaponized
right now it's actually weaponized so
you're not allowed to have your spinage
and your heavy metal detox smoothies and
your incredible celery juice
and your protocols to heal and eat as
much fruit as you want or whatever it is
you're not allowed to because the minute
you start doing the right things to take
your healing further and further they
weaponized moderation
to actually use against anyone in that
moment to totally screw with their head
you can feel like you're on top of the
world you're taking care of yourself
you're actually juicing you're you're
working on healing and then someone will
turn around on social or somewhere and
be like oh you're just orthorexic now
and it scares the crap out of somebody
and they'll be like what I am what do
you mean oh like you can you can eat
healthy in moderation but you should be
able to do everything you want to do but
I was sick
oh it doesn't matter you should still
just do moderation like it's weaponized
now
it's hard to break away from the status
quo of moderation because it's so
weaponized in society if you choose to
fight the brainwashing of moderation you
get your wrists smacked if you want to
fight moderation someone's going to
smack your wrists with a ruler
you get punished by others who don't
want to break their own habits and
lifestyle of using moderation to consume
foods and substances that aren't
benefiting them what happens is you're a
threat
when you take care of yourself
you're a threat in the medical medium
Community if you do it right
because you're a threat to somebody else
outside of the community
that doesn't want to be told
they should eat better they want to do
it their way
they want to have all their chocolate
bars they want to eat their eggs even
though they're sick and it's making them
sick they want to do whatever they're
doing their apple cider vinegar or
whatever they want they want to do what
they're doing and they don't want to be
they don't want to be shown
that it probably isn't a good idea so
then they'll turn around and bite the
person and be like no you're orthorexic
you shouldn't be taking care of yourself
they weaponize it people get bullied and
that's what we're talking about now
bullying they get bullied big time for
it even in families in society and
Friends
by strangers it's so hard for people to
heal when they're being bullied and
moderation is being weaponized against
people
and so is the whole term orthorexia
which means that was a term did you know
that was a conventional term created to
stop somebody from taking care of
themselves did you guys know that
orthorexia was a conventional term
created to stop someone from starting a
journey of eating healthier
that is a sick
what's sicker than that
what's sicker than just the dumbass
guy or professional that created that
term back in the 80s because he didn't
like to see somebody actually eating
better what's sicker than that if
somebody
in the health communities or even the
medical medium Community that's trying
to sabotage other people and they use
that term
that's actually even sicker
if you choose to fight the brainwashing
of moderation you get your risks back to
get punished by others you get bullied
punished by others and bullied by people
who don't want to break their own habits
or lifestyle so they lean on moderation
so they can consume foods and substances
that aren't benefiting them
they're delusional
Aquarian passion says
so refreshing to find you with three
explanation points
Laura says I have been called orthorexic
and believed it until medical medium and
learning the truth
medical uh meaning France says I've
bullied in my been bullied in my family
for five years for doing medical medium
those who give themselves permission to
indulge in what they know deep down
isn't good for them
find it unsettling and even threatening
when you decide to go in your own
Direction and heal
including people that dabble in the
medical medium community that sell
programs and all kinds of stuff they
they don't want to be told
that you're doing it
they want to be able to just roll you
and tell you how to do it there's that I
see that too it's really sad
they want to even kind of shake you up
and shift your brain you're taking care
of yourself you're doing the medical
meeting protocols you're doing a great
job you've already done some healing and
then they try to shake you up and be
like
why are you doing it that way should do
it my way and then when you look my way
which is you not orthorexic it's
moderation meanwhile it's normal to be
sick though
as you age you gotta you can get on a
ton of medications and be in the
hospital all the time that's great
well that's a great place to be
don't do it right so you're in you know
so you're in the hospital all the time
down the road when you age and
everything else and
it's just unbelievable
it makes people uncomfortable when you
start to find empowerment and take
control over your health and become
aware that certain foods and substances
even in moderation aren't doing you
justice
instead of questioning their own
practices these moderation champions
and orthorexic champions tend to point
to you as if you're out of balance
the more uncomfortable they feel the
higher and the more
insistently they start waiving the
moderation and orthorexic flag
they're watching you do your thing and
they're like trying to throw shade in it
orthorexic moderation
Tamara Jones says that's gaslighting gas
lighting indeed it sure is to trigger
somebody to doubt themselves well that's
what a whole bunch of people do out
there
and volca says my mom was not sick like
ever and hit her 70s and Wham chronic
illness is popping up
and more after C triggering more issues
sure there are people that skate by to
their 70 but that's rare that's rare
that that's that's not happening anymore
I'm letting you know that that's there's
only gonna be a few of those
and then not even a few of those anymore
people aren't going to be 70 and then
they get sick when they're 70. they're
all going to be getting sick in their
20s
everyone's going to be getting sick of
their 20s coming up
that's where it's going
yes there's people in the community that
used to be in the community
and they wanted to sell programs and do
and and all that off of medical medium
information or whatever they're doing
and then they go and they try to put
down other people's heads in hopes that
they gain more followers and stuff to
sell more programs to that's happened
over the years it's kind of like a thing
and then they throw words like
orthorexic out where they throw other
stuff with moderation because they try
to screw up the person's thinking in
heads and just mess them up and in the
end the whole thing's sad because it
just doesn't get anybody anywhere
a chance to grow free
we are smart our souls are wise do you
hear that
you know what I love about Spirit of
compassion
it's like I remember writing that
and something Felt So Good In the Moment
I was sitting at my desk
and SOC said we are smart and I wrote We
are smart
and then Spirit of compassion said our
souls are wise and I wrote our souls
were wise
and then I wrote
from SOC when we're finally given the
knowledge
the correct knowledge
about how to heal
we have the potential to recognize it
when I wrote that like my hair was
standing up
back of my neck I was just like
Goosebumps everywhere and I feel like
that now
if we have struggled enough with our
health
that the blindfold of Health Dogma has
come off
we can see the information here for what
it is
and spirit of compassion gave me those
words to write
like
who would ever know that
the truth
then it's like recognizing a soul mate
after years of relationships gone awry
whether suddenly or slowly we realize
that those past relationships we
contorted ourselves into in desperation
didn't go wrong because of some flaw in
Who We Are
just like a healthy relationship the
truth about healing may push us to grow
if we give ourselves that chance to grow
we give ourselves the chance to heal
there's so much depth in this right here
if you even read into it and really read
what that is it
is more even there than even your
reading
when on the other hand we take
moderation and apply it to the world of
poisons and toxins we push it too far
now we're taking the basic
problematic standard of moderation and
exalting it
to a place recklessly
that's what you'll read about in the
coming chapters of brain saver
you've already discovered this in this
chapter it says something in 7 chapter 8
your addictive brain oh my God that's a
whole other chapter your addicted brain
why it's so easy to get hooked on
certain substances and activities this
is an amazing book right here
you guys
I'm on page 150 of brain saver I think
we're gonna make the shop the craving
shifter that's what I think we're gonna
do let's go find the craving shifter
right now inside the book craving
shifter it is
we are here
when Cravings we need a half time then
we're going to read about this and move
into the shot that's what we need we
need a half time there's a lot of
intense information right there you guys
want to do the robot
I have no choice when the music comes on
the robot takes over
[Music]
a little bit of robot going on
all right hey that was a quick halftime
craving shifter when cravings
when Cravings were addictive impulses
are disrupting your life this shot is a
great tool
and by the way I hold my breath when I
do the robot that's how you get the best
robot
don't breathe but here's the thing I
don't recommend that so breathe when you
do the robot
no you to get a best robot you got to
kind of like hold your breath a little
bit or a lot
when craving someone asked me that the
other day that's why I'm saying that
they're like how come my robot doesn't
look good I said
well it doesn't look like you're a robot
not saying my robot's any good because
it's really not either all right for
Hunger that feels insatiable or
Unstoppable
do the craving shifter if your hunger
feels insatiable and Unstoppable do you
have that does that hit you because
emotional stuff coming your way you've
got all kinds of shade being thrown your
way because you're on the phone with the
phone company and they hang up on you
whatever happens it's like get the
craving instead of going for something
like a chocolate bar instead of going
for something you want to go with
the craving shifter get the craving
shifter out if that's the case really
important
all right
when Cravings or addictive impulses are
just disrupting your life the shot is
great A great tool as a craving buster
it's about busting that craving
as a hunger suppressant when you're
trying to shift your diet
if you're trying to like if you're
having a hard time you're like I know
what foods I need to heal with
because medical medium
has endless amounts of free information
on that including the books like I know
what food that's going to help me but
how do I do that when I'm craving the
bad stuff get the craving shifter out
do the craving shifter if your diet is
too high in fat
and you're trying to reduce the amount
of fat you're consuming and there's a
lot of confusion with that people don't
realize
how that works with the diet hide fat
and everything they're like wait aren't
fats good and they're all confused you
got to know the mm info because you
could fat yourself to death you can fat
yourself to death with good fats too
people don't realize this and then
you'll always have insulin resistance
you'll always be craving off the charts
you'll always have fat addiction and
when you have fat addiction you can
never Escape so that's a problem all on
its own right there so there's a way to
to kind of bring that down it doesn't
mean you have to stop fats if you know
all together if you're somebody that
doesn't want to stop them but you can
take it further and you can lower the
fats it's really a great way to
to shift gears
medical meme information is all about
that insulin resistance and and what
happens the fats are to cause not to
sugar all that
if your diet is too high in fat and
you're trying to reduce the amount of
fat you're consuming bring out the
craving shifter here's another one too
to help break overeating patterns
we get into patterns habits because
we're under stress we're under stress
we're under a lot of stuff and we tend
to overeat
easy to do overeating is easy to do it
just is
so to help break overeating patterns
food addictions or even caffeine and
salt addictions the craving shifter is
important for that let's get into it now
by the way this is day 11.
of the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge I want everybody to
know
that
worse
this is day 11.
no is it day 11.
yeah 10
10 plus one
we have nine days left so you can still
join and join for free because it was
free to begin with so download your
grocery shopping list you can see the
other all the details about it and all
the other
um brain shot therapies we're doing we
still have nine more days to go please
go to medicalmedium.com get on the email
list get the information download the
free grocery shopping list seriously
also check out the cold and flu tool kit
by the way because guess what all I hear
out there is people getting their butts
whooped from RSV flu and C right now
check it out for seven herbs and
supplements to keep on hand right here
which are critical download this amazing
resource right there you got the Bemidji
stuff I endorse these guys because this
stuff is freaking incredible and it's
unmatched and it's like the zinc and the
micro C the golden seal you got the
propolis pure check that out when you
can don't miss out have it in Your
Arsenal you know to actually we battle
the darkness out there really important
all right so I just want everybody to
know about that so let's get into it
let's make this
looking forward to it
I need a craving shifter right now I'm
craving a glass of wine where's my glass
of wine here
I don't know
I think that
I have a white wine today
no craving the last one
let me see
hmm
smells so good it's a dry wine
don't sip it that's the rule here at my
Vineyard that I just purchased for 50
million dollars
don't sip the wine just smell the wine
does that smell dry to you
I smell uh a bouquet of rosettes from my
Vineyard when the flowers are in bloom
it's a kind of soil I have in my
Vineyard too it's the soil that makes a
wine the best am I a wine stop I might
be I don't know
oh no you can't have a free glass of
wine
yes it's a thousand dollars per sip
hmm don't let the wine touch your tips
don't know where to touch tips on your
lips no no
okay you guys that's real wine no it's
not all right
let's go
meet all says did time shock therapy
twice
no wait did time shock therapy two weeks
ago for my dad
and when we caught a cold amazing
shortest cold ever I love that that's in
the brain saver book
incredible tools in the cold and flu
tips
that you can download
okay
reluka says my butt was whooped as we
speak with the flu my kids have ear
infections and pink eye I'm drained I
talk about the flu lowering the immune
system in everybody knocks everybody
back all the stuff starts coming up all
the streptococcus and everything else
starts coming up I talk about
it's critical to have the right things
on hand right so that's the seven herbs
and supplements to keep on hand right
there I'm just letting you know I don't
know if you guys can see this right but
it's the Bemidji ones you guys know I
endorsed them I'm saying this because
I'm watching people get their butts
whooped I'm watching it all the time out
there and it's just like I don't know
what to say I can't be in a billion
places at once I can't remind people
about tools and resources every minute I
want to but it's hard to do and people
say oh
what's so good about these oh my God I
talk about that about the four reasons
why this company is the greatest that
I've ever found yet it's why I fully
endorsed them but anyway
they show you the zinc right there the
cat's claw the propolis critical stuff
anyway and check out shock therapies and
the Brain saver books okay so the
medical medium shock therapies there's
so much information in a cold and flu
protocols like seriously I just feel bad
what I'm saying is I actually feel bad
I feel bad for people you know when a
friend reaches out to me and says aw I
hate to bother you but right now I got
the worst flu and I'm like okay can you
use this stuff that you're supposed to
have on hand they're like I never got it
I'm like what do you want me to do about
it you want me to magically snap my like
my finger and all of a sudden it all
appears you should have gotten it you
should have had it in your toolkit I
don't understand cold and flu toolkit
you can download at medicalmedium.com
seriously like it's just it's powerful
information
it's just that I feel bad and the thing
is we're not done with cold and flu and
RSV everybody is going to be up for the
possibility of getting their butts
whooped again in a month because a whole
nother round is rolling through
and just when you think that's done
there's the spring one that's going to
roll through and just be whooping
everybody's butt all right
half piece of Ginger fresh ginger here
let's get a little bit of a blade
let's get some ginger
got a nice little piece right there
gonna drop it in next thing quarter cup
tightly packed fresh basil
I got my basil quarter cup we're looking
at don't need all of this
get my basil in there
big hunk
half cup tightly packed spinach
dropped some nice spinach in here I'm
excited
I'm really looking forward to this one a
Cravings Buster I don't mind having a
Cravings busted right and they busted
right now it might stop me from drinking
the rest of this is it okay to actually
to drink my wine before I do the craving
Buster
no it's a bad idea
white wine
there's no wine there it's apple juice
for God's sake
okay we should have just about a half
cup in there because spinach packs down
real tight
like that all right good
it really turns into nothing once you
pack that down
okay half cup chopped kale
yep
nice
half cup chopped kale put this big old
kale leaf in here right now
and maybe I'll put the rest of that stem
in there too
all right what else do we need
half cup of chopped cabbage
cabbage coming right up
we need our cabbage
let's get it going here
you guys wasn't that an amazing amount
of information about moderation and all
that wasn't that incredible
like I feel like it's so empowered
having that data having those details
having that information and what a great
way to empower
the mind
I mean truly it really kind of blows my
mind in so many ways
what else do we have on the list here
we have a half orange peeled everybody
we just get that spinach down in there a
little bit
I peeled it
here
that's a nice size orange though so
you get some orange sound in there
nice
cut this orange up
foreign
there we go pushing that orange down in
there
and just when you think you're done we
got a little bit more to go
the thing is with the mm-1500
it's like my favorite
people don't realize what you can do
with the 1500 you can do so much stuff
with it it's incredible let's get a
to have stock but that's a small stock I
usually have bigger stocks so I'm using
that as my half stock right there
we go
when you put
Carissa says this whole challenge has
been amazing
incredible you just cheered me up
I go to bed at night and I'm like does
everybody even like the challenge Spirit
like Spirit does anybody even like the
challenge
all right you guys
let's SOC like spirit is like is anybody
even really like it
are they having fun
all right let's get a shot going right
here
incredible
this is the Cravings shifter
you don't think it'll work
[Music]
you'll see
it does
[Music]
this one I noticed
it hits me
immediately I'm not even talking about
when the Sip Goes Down the Hatch I'm
talking like when the Sip is in my mouth
it starts to work
[Music]
whew
incredible
I'm not even halfway through you can
send your shot down one shot if that's
what you want to do
I'm nursing this one a little bit
craving shifter
bartender
[Music]
that's when you really feel it you're
halfway through
did anybody doesn't know about the brain
cell Therapies
synergistically combined just right in a
way people would never know here on
planet Earth humans can't figure this
out this isn't just a tasty concoction
thrown together that's not it at all
information from above to create these
shifter shots I mean brain shot
Therapies
this is to actually give you quick
instant relief in so many areas of
Health while you're rebuilding yourself
with other medical medium tools
foreign bartender
give me another
say Ian says love the challenge
on YouTube
incredible
Saint Sue says loving the challenge you
guys are loving the challenge
our Rose is yes I love the challenge
accounts bookkeeper says challenge is
wonderful exclamation point
amazing Diana Eva says I'd love to see
you every day doing your thing
and then the list goes on my God this is
unbelievable and I was all bummed out
last night talking to Spirit Sherry Anna
says yes we do like the challenge Tina
babe says I love the challenge Divine
Light says I love this challenge oh
McCallie this challenge has been so
uplifting best way to start the year
boom incredible you guys
aisling says we love the challenge
amazing even though right now all you
guys empty bajira says this challenge is
the best start to the best new to the
New Year I've ever had an amazing
incredible you guys
I you know I went to bed last night it's
like I hope people even like the spirit
does anybody even like the challenge
um I gotta argue with the bartender
right now you guys I'm really mad at the
Bartender Bartender I asked you to give
me another
coming right up
coming right up Mr William
and at this bar we shall provide you
with another
yes we should but miss really I'm gonna
hold it back for now you're getting a
little tipsy bartender give me that next
shot I'm not tipsy I'm okay I really am
I'm okay
we think you're a little tipsy come
excuse me of
um Can the butler get Mr Williams car
keys we don't want him driving today he
said we're gonna hold this shot back
what do you need my car keys bartender
I'm not even drunk give me another shot
okay we're gonna give you another shot
thank you give me that nice nice nice I
got it from the bartender I'm good hmm
bartender
give me another you guys this has been
amazing incredible
and fun this was day 11. say lady cath 7
says absolutely love the challenge I
make them for my parents too and they
can really see a difference that's so
incredible this is such a precious tool
Lynn Meyer says if not for this
challenge I wouldn't have done all these
shots 20 days in a row I needed to kick
in the pants
the kick in the pants it is
Frenchie League says the robot and
challenge make my day
the robot
let's do a good one after and The Cold
Light spring says how could I not love
it
thank you may
amazing
hey guys I'm just blown away
wait a minute what's this on Rumble best
part of my day for sure Deborah says on
Rumble incredible living food on Rumble
says this challenge is the best ever
with the smiley face you're the kind
that have the two eyes and the comma for
the nose and the right
intellectual Integrity says what shot do
we do day 21 when we miss you we'll come
up with something on day 21 you never
know there might be an encore
or not we'll see let's get to day 20.
we'll get to day 20 but there'll be a
shot to do for 21 possibly I will call
that shot out
when it comes down to day 20.
amazing guys
do the 10 days
maybe through the 10 days we did in
October go to medicalmedium.com and you
see the 10 days that we did in October
so after this 20-day challenge go to
that one and do those 10 days just
re-watch for free at medicalmedium.com
you guys sign up to my telegram if you
can that would be great make sure you do
that if you can because I'm leaving
um exclusive messages on there make sure
you check out this video when I post it
today on Instagram too you could always
re-watch it or watch it on medicalme.com
that would be actually the best place to
see it streamed
um I'm posting
so make sure you check out the video I
posted today
on Instagram I talk about the heart what
goes wrong seeing so many hard problems
out there which is not funny and I go
into more depth into blood clots and
More in brain saver so you can read
about blood clots and brain saver
protocols check this out you guys
um a lot of people are having heart
problems right now
big time out there like insanely crazy
and it's really sad
check out the video I did I talk about
the heart I posted it today on IG
all right guys check out my telegrams
um subscribe to that for the exclusive
messages check out medical meme podcast
at Apple podcast I did a swelling uh
podcast episode recently but not too far
ago and some other ones intermittent
fasting check out the blood draw one
that's so incredible and you'll notice
on my podcasts no advertisements
and no commercials fancy that
anyway you guys love you
and take care I'll see you tomorrow