things to talk about episode 17
has been released i'm going to talk
about these for a little bit too um
all kinds of other stuff as well so look
you guys bottom line is
the episode has been released today i
want you to take a look at it
it's stargazing so it's a stargazing
meditation
so i hope you guys check it out when you
can link is in the description
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
um
this is this is a meditation that is
really really powerful
and it takes you on a journey in the
stars
good to see you guys glad everybody's
here um so answer questions too any
questions you guys have
have you checked out the potato show
that's one thing right there the potato
show
i got some really nice russets in my
hand right now so the potato episode
and i want you guys to like get the
information because it's packed with
information in these episodes
so uh jackie says telling the worldwide
telling everybody about me incredible
like look
spread the information spread share the
information
um more meditation somebody said more
meditations
and the check check out that meditation
if you get a chance okay it's stargazing
it's a stargazing michelle michelle said
i started eating skins now you started
eating the
potato skins now michelle michelle i'm
gonna do a show on strep
okay so i'm just letting you know
because i saw that i saw you mention
that in a comment
and uh so i am gonna work on that so
just hang in there hang in there
yeah you're doing the skin it's
incredible it's incredible really is
i'm glad people are coming on because
there's so much to talk about i'm
talking about a few different foods too
i'm going to talk about the orange the
lowly orange because
people are like well i don't want to eat
an orange don't want to eat an orange
you know like what
these things are packed okay and i got
other foods with me too
people ask me what foods do i eat that
happens all the time people are always
asking me like what foods do you eat
the whole bit and i have a papaya right
here and i'm gonna cut it open
so right there got a nice big papaya i'm
gonna cut open um
you know while we're on talking and all
that so
even you guys and i got other foods with
me too but did you check out the potato
episode
link is in the description medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast don't
miss the episodes
seriously like subscribe so you get
notified when the episodes come out
and the stargazing episode came out
today
it's a powerful meditation and i mean
just wait till you do this meditation
wait till you do it have any have you
guys tried the meditation yet
because it is incredible um
so comments are going up they're flying
up today um
tina says thank you anthony you
literally saved my life that
matters to me because that's the whole
point that's the whole point
since i was four years old spirit of
compassion came to me
spoke to me and said that i was going to
be bringing out
information about chronic illness that's
ahead of re-science research head of the
times out there and that's what we've
done
we spent 35 years putting information
out that you guys see
now and you don't even know it came from
medical medium in the 35 years the work
that we've done so it's incredible
really we've we've
we're trying to save as many lives as we
can and uh and you're saving lives
because
you're when you're live when you get
your life back you tell somebody else
it helps them heal so you're saving
their life um
all of that so link is in the
description you guys i'm holding
potatoes because
recently i did the potato episode you
should listen to that
because it's really packed with
information there's not a line wasted in
these they're
it's incredible lorraine l hey lorraine
i'm so thrilled that my sister started
celery juice today whoa i'm proud of her
incredible
incredible it really is i saw that you
liked spicy food in a comment a while
back i think
i think i read that i think i read that
somewhere that you like spicy food
you know look you guys um i gotta tell
you about the star gazing episode
i really do that's the episode today
link is in the description it's a star
gazing meditation
you don't want to miss the stargazing
meditation whatever you do and elia says
thank you so much for the podcast and
all your work the potato show was
amazing and so much information
you guys have you this is this is a free
resource it's a free resource the potato
episode it's a docu-series episode it's
not
coffee talk and a podcast where it just
gets thrown away and another guest comes
on it's like cotton candy and cotton
candy and cotton candy
and it's not like that so this is like a
docusi docu-series
free podcast episodes
whatever you want to call it catherine
elizabeth hi anthony was so happy to see
this meditation
i was thinking about you the other day
catherine because
now i know that you're you're doing the
meditations too and i'm so glad that you
that you um so that you're happy about
the meditation so link is in the
description for anybody coming on and
doesn't know about it
ardent says thank you love from new
zealand yeah that's a great place so
many more people
following your advice down here in the
southern hemisphere now whoa
share the information share the podcast
um all of the
dr fan md medical doctor papaya helps
you go
it does it does and he's a medical
expert
he's a medical expert he's a brilliant
doctor and
papaya does yeah it helps you go it's a
pusher pushes
all down that track whoa whoa whoa
pushes all down that track
uh and gets right through you um sonia
says the stargazing meditation is so
beautiful it felt like
home i hope everybody gets a chance to
do the scar
this stargazing meditation that's funny
you know i got to tell you i'm going to
cut this papaya open right now right
here as we speak
doing a little cutting probably opened
up
i don't know thousands of these over the
last whatever years
i mean a few decades for sure open that
sucker right there that's a papaya
that's a healing food
and i'm always asked like what do i eat
what do i eat and i never talk about it
it's like i never talk about it and i'm
like
well i don't know like i thought that
everybody knew that
i'm probably eating the foods that i
have in the books that i talk about in
the books and everything like that you
know
uh reena says thank you you're amazing
i'm healing my trigeminal neuralgia
whoa you're better than doctors potatoes
are my friend
whoa got potatoes right here
you know trigeminal neuralgia brutal
brutal brutal people suffer with that i
guess
some of you guys know um i mean look
if you want to know more about different
things for how to heal and all that
here's cleanse the heal on my hand right
now but anyway link is in the
description
okay just so you know the medical medium
podcast apple podcast
link is in the description so i'm
talking about a couple different
episodes i'm talking about this
the stargazing episode meditation okay
it's episode 17.
it's a powerful episode it'll take you
on a journey
so it'll help heal your soul i wanted to
want to talk about that a little bit
and there's a special surprise behind
the stars
that i talk about in this meditation so
you don't want to miss this
don't want to miss this my comments seem
to stop so
can't read anymore right now because for
some reason it's just stuck
um but anyway you guys this the
stargazing meditation is something you
don't want to miss
the link is in the description and you
don't want to miss it
it's really really powerful i hope you
guys try it
it you know lorraine says can't wait to
listen
incredible whoa eop i planted 20 papaya
trees are you kidding me
20 papaya trees i don't have one papaya
tree
you playing at 20 maddie says i love
papaya incredible
love papaya but it's a really healing
food it's it's incredible for the
nervous system
it's an amazing food for the central
so that's something to think about right
there really really helps
it helps heal neurological issues and it
helps to support the
nerves and it helps to support the
nerves in the intestinal lining too
and that's a big deal it's a soothing
food
to soothing food melanie says i'm
excited can't wait to do the meditation
tonight
incredible i hope you do that and
i don't know if you guys stargaze do you
guys stargaze do you look at the stars
up there
do you guys ever get a chance to you
know on a clear night
um moon rain says what about mango love
mango and i was gonna actually have one
here with me
today but i don't um so yeah
how do you know if the papaya is too
ripe
holly if it gets really soft and squishy
if it gets to too many kind of like
holes going through it
all of that could be it you know could
be a problem right there
so see guys link is in the description
please share the medical medium podcast
so people can get free
information to turn their life around
free information it's the medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast
that's the uncensored platform right
there of choice
if you hear it on another platform it's
sent through okay i'm just letting you
know even if you think it's not
it is little pieces are missing and all
kinds of other stuff
so hey loon lunell's here uh
whoa how did you make it i think it's
aren't you like
on the other side of the world and it's
uh it's like nighttime now or something
and you missed the missed notification
or something
um anyway and look you guys
the stargazing meditation you definitely
want to try it
if you can because it's powerful for
healing the soul
powerful to heal anxiety
depersonalization
depression even ocd it's really a power
packed kind of thing that turns our
lives around
the reason why is because our souls they
get
injured down here you know when someone
betrays you
when someone you know you know uh messes
with you okay
when they mess with you you know
emotional struggles i call them
emotional bullets when emotional bullets
are being
you know shot at you in the whole bit
when those emotional bullets are flying
at you and stuff
and so we get hurt along the way here
and our soul gets kind of like a little
beat up from it and you know that what
i'm talking about
broken relationships broken friendships
over the years or something happens and
the next thing you know it you're like
i don't really feel like meeting
somebody i don't feel like moving
forward with my life
you know i'm scared i got fear you know
you're just you're feeling beaten down
well the whole point um maddie says
love these episodes incredible
incredible so glad you're listening to
these episodes it matters to me that you
are
but our soul gets tattered and beaten
out beaten down
and broken down a little bit we get you
know to our last tether we get kind of
frayed down here
and the star gazing meditation
is a meditation to help truly restore
that because
when nobody knows there's a surprise in
the stargazing meditation the link is in
the description
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
and
there's you have to know what's going on
there because
up behind the stars i talk about it
there's a sanctuary special little place
that has the essence of your soul and i
connect that essence to your soul down
here
you can't miss this link is in the
description seriously
um link is in the description so
really you have to you have to so amanda
says amanda jones says
are you having the meditation today well
link is amanda link is in the
description
so it's right there you can listen to it
now you can listen to it tonight
and it's a guided meditation for free
that's the whole thing it's it's there
medical media podcast at apple podcast
okay missy says thank you for all the
information
this is always great incredible jasmine
said
i just ate ripe papaya this morning you
did incredible look at this
look at this baby look at how beautiful
this papaya is
but you know what you guys i got these
oranges here too which i'm really pumped
up about look at the color
of this orange right here i mean is that
insane or what
and i'm going to cut this orange open
now here right
so i've got another one
look at look at the color of that i
don't know if you can see it
seriously i mean honestly
incredible so link is in description for
the stargazing meditation
don't miss it you should you should
really try it when you get a chance
um so i'm learning my conditions from
the episodes
awesome see your neurological episode
the brain fog episode right
these are really healing powerful power
packed
episodes um is there anything that you
could do with the papaya seeds you could
dry them
you could try them and um put them you
know you can dry them and chop them up
if you want they're spicy
you know you could eat them right out of
the papaya but remember they're spicy so
if you eat too many of them they're like
whoa
she's good you just can start with a
little you can start with a little
um you guys link is in description
i don't want you to miss out on this
next meditation that i just
that i just unleashed it today released
right it's a powerful one and you don't
want to miss out on it so
it's it's um stargazing meditation
do you guys ever stargaze do you look at
the stars at night if you look up there
do you wonder what's going on up there
do you are you looking for things to see
up there are you looking for falling
stars and all that
um so this is a meditation you don't
want to miss you just don't link is in
the description
letting you guys know so i got foods in
front of me healing foods everybody's
always saying
you know anthony what do you eat a w
what do you eat i hear it all the time
all that stuff
peter says aw listening to all the
podcasts awesome
awesome and you're listening to the
podcast did you did you hear the
caffeine one
coffee matcha tea chocolate episode
that's like one of my favorites
have you heard that episode then there's
the neurological symptoms
episode the brain fog and then there's
the air fresheners
scented candles episode i mean you just
don't want us
and that one right there is incredible
all on its own um so you don't want to
miss these really you know
potatoes what about the potato episode
that was the last one before the
meditation was released
today vicky says i love stargazing thank
you for the meditation
incredible that's amazing uh trisha
maurice here whoa hi anthony this is a
beautiful way to start the day so you
tried the meditation trisha
incredible i know you did all of them so
far you did the brain meditation
you did the moon meditation you did the
freezer bird meditation
i know that the fruit picking meditation
ashley applesauce loves potatoes
yeah right right maddie says
the caffeine one is my favorite
mind-blowing
maddie do you remember in the caffeine
episode
by the way if you guys just came on here
link is in description share
the link share these episodes right so
the caffeine
episode maddie do you remember in there
when i was whispering
i was like whispering i was like you
guys aren't supposed to know this okay
you're not supposed to know what happens
when you
pick coffee all day
and you get that neurotoxin covered all
over your clothes
all on your body while you're sweating
and then
something could happen because of it you
got to listen to the episode and i was
whispering it because yeah
i'm not supposed to talk about it no
one's supposed to know that that's
classified information just letting you
know they're okay
so um you know and really if you
if you michelle l says caffeine monster
never got me
that's awesome that's cool that's cool
that's cool it's cool
whoa juan says chemtrails great episode
chemtrail episode you guys
have you listened to all the episodes
like i know a lot of you a lot of you
guys are new and you're coming on here
have you listened to other ones
catherine says your voice was different
on the
stargazing episode so my voice was
different
it was softer i think so you guys want
to hear it the link is in the
description right here
so dr faun md coffee pickers
end up in trouble yeah they end up in
trouble
yep they do lorraine says cloud cover
that was cool
you know you guys i just want you guys
to heal i want you guys to have the
information i want it there for you
you know so i put out the books right
the new york times was selling books
just cleanse the heel do you have this
because
there's 75 recipes in here over 200
symptoms and conditions
and different dosages of supplements of
what to do you could take it to your
doctor if you want it's a medical book
and i mean it's on sale right now
amazon.com i mean
pick up one for somebody else or get it
free at the library just get it for free
um linda says yes it was a comforting
voice
i try my best because i try my best okay
i probably sound annoying now though
sarah says i'm not new but i'm doing
what i can brain meditation was awesome
incredible incredible michelle says she
keeps the book by her bed always
hey i do too i keep a copy by my bed as
well
and i grab it and i open it up and i go
well what
did i forget about that's in here like
what did i forget about that's in here
and i look in here and there's all kinds
of stuff i mean
god gout i'm looking at right now
glaucoma what you can do for gout
glaucoma
fatty liver fibromyalgia gallbladder
problems
fibroids eye floaters i mean you guys
the list goes on i mean edema and
swelling
endometriosis if you have reproductive
issues like endometriosis
fibroids pcos i mean you got answers
here in the book
i i mean right wouldn't that be great
because they're in here
actual answers to what's wrong with
people um
and nellie says yes i have the book it's
amazing everybody should get it thank
you for telling everybody that
um susan says love the stargazing
meditation yay
say different things to discard
stargazing meditation incredible
shell says i go back to reread all the
time and always see new things right
yeah yeah totally trisha marie
i have i i have so much to say about the
end of the potato podcast
okay the end of the potato podcast
since you brought it up um that that's
got a lot of prophecy in there
okay that is a lot of prophecy in there
that has a lot of information
in there and it's it's it's in there i
you have to know what you're hearing or
decode it
or basically you know you've got to read
the between the lines but the
information's in that the potato ending
a lot of the endings too
the potato ending i talked about the
alarm
okay so yeah so check that one out so
honestly if you haven't seen the potato
episode or heard the potato episode you
should you should you should
and um but listen um hey trisha murray
said exactly
prophetically exactly i mean thank you
thank you for knowing that that means
you know what you're
hearing you know all of it and it's a
big deal here's the podcast right here
you guys
okay that's the medical medium podcast
at apple podcast it's uncensored
you guys just so you know i'm censored
with everything
i didn't know if you guys knew that i'm
censored on these platforms
i'm not censored on the apple podcast
platform letting you know all right
so very important to know and
but i'm censored everywhere else that's
the podcast right there
and there it is finding yourself all
right start
gazing episode 17
stargazing meditation finding yourself
reconnecting with your soul the power of
that
is huge it's a big deal peter says
the caffeine episode awesome yeah
no one knows what happens did you know
that that whole thing in the middle of
the caffeine episode that i whispered
about
right that little spot do you know how
many lives were lost
because of because of that oh what about
the reverse polarity
what about that you're on your treadmill
you're 25 years old you're on your
treadmill
and and you die you just die nobody
knows why they said oh it's a fluke we
don't know if they had a hole in their
heart
we don't know what happened we don't
know if it was a medication they were on
we just don't know
and it was the caffeine it jumps the
heart
did you hear in the episode the caffeine
episode where i said the caffeine jumps
to hearts
reverse polarity like syndrome where all
these young people and older people die
out of nowhere
on their treadmills they never had a
health problem in their life never had
anything wrong
they're exercising they're runners
all of that and then they're just
running on the treadmill and then
they're gone they're down it's crazy
it's crazy you know i talked about that
it's in the episode
it really is so um but you guys
like there's so much information in
these episodes check out stargazing okay
it's the meditation check out the potato
episode
all right when you get a chance um all
right
you guys great being on here bless your
heart love you much