yo I have some good news to pass on I
have come across something that I think
is a real life-changer it's a book by
Anthony wale he's the medical medium let
me just put it this way
Kenny muscles you can do that no problem
it's just work diligence perseverance
but if you don't take care of the engine
there's little part in here that you
never pay attention to do you uh it's in
the dark I don't look at it well it's
not the guard this is what runs this
system it keeps it all growing I'm not
getting anything out of this I just want
to pass on something I wish I had come
across when I was younger I mean yeah
I'm still strong I feel fit I feel
aggressive it but you could feel better
and as you get older you get better keep
punching