a lot of people get dark spots they get
black spots they get all kinds of
different stuff on their face um on
their body on their arms on their chest
on their back and so forth a lot of
people get a lot of different skin
lesions people are up against a
tremendous amount of skin toxins that
are surfacing like I said if you guys
just got on here this is the product I
endorse right here this is the company I
endorsed because of the quality and like
I said if you were here a little earlier
it's really incredible
um about how it works with this product
and I was just showing you the one thing
right there that helps the skin alone is
the fact that there's no anti-caking
agents in this this product right here
which is a miracle all on its
own um so anyway you guys I'm going to
talk a little bit I have I have a tech
issue going on really but right now but
I'm just going to wait and see if it
kind of Remedies and then I'm going to
focus on
uh some other stuff too
what you see is some oranges right
here okay these oranges are going to be
part of the Skin
Potion all right so back to that whole
micro needling or however it would is
that that what it's called you guys
micro needling it's the thing with the
roller and all the prickly things on the
roller right and you do this on your
skin and you do your face like this when
that started getting popular I was
like ah
a nightmare
nightmare it's if you're not healing
your skin from underneath from
internally you'll just add to more
problems doing things like that add to
more Scar Tissue more issues around your
skin but that's how it works Trends can
be really bad just like the collagen
Trend it's really bad it's a waste of
money in the whole bit so when it comes
down to skin like I said before if
you're toxic inside and unfortunately
yes pretty much everybody's toxic
internally the toxins are going to get
pushed to the skin the skin is going to
get
problematic and no lymphatic drainage is
going to fix that you're just going to
be chasing your tail looking for ways of
fixing that and so forth so I want to
make the Skin Potion now let me go get
working on it now too so I got a glass
right
here little bit of a mug okay and this
is really simple
I'm just taking a
scoop
of this right here it's taking a scoop
putting that
scoop right in here just like that all
right taking two
capsules of the MSM that's part of the
Skin Potion okay so make sure you get
the MSM make sure you do that that's
important
okay you can get this as well and just
get that but the Skin Potion you really
want both you just do now it's important
to have this for so many other
reasons right here so many other ways
it's important to have
it but the MSM you want okay so you want
with the skin aspect of it so I'm going
to open up two
capsules of the MSM powder right
here so we had a tech problem I think we
probably lost
YouTube so right now but
[Music]
hey could have
been
anything all right so then I'm going
to doing kind of like moving things
around right here are you
guys I got the MSM two capsules in there
I got a scoop of the micro C powder the
immune
power now I'm going to put some orange
in here I'm going to cut a fresh
orange now if you really want you can
put a little honey in here you don't
have to with this so I'm putting orange
in here now some orange might
accidentally go in there when you're
squeezing it and that's fine I'm seeing
some pieces of orange go in there I
don't
mind there we go I squeezed it
orange all
right you can add honey in here if you
want I have some
honey but it doesn't have to be in this
one and then we're going to get some
warm water so just bear with me really
quick aw's here we're going to add some
warm water in here here we go we're
going to stir
[Music]
this easy to make a medical medium Skin
Potion easy to make that's a big
deal it's the easiness to it that's
really really helpful as well it's
something you can do every single day so
you can be somebody that's doing
facials you know facial ma masks on your
face uh
right exfoliations and think about all
the time you're putting in there how
many people do you know spend a lot of
time on their skin on their face
alone this took what I don't know if I
do if I recreate it how how long does it
take so let me recreate it really quick
okay I'm going to have that there okay
you
ready okay so if you're somebody going
to get an appointment for a facial or
you're trying to prepare yourself for an
exfoliation how long does that
take two hours you have to get in the
car you going to do at home did you
start your exfoliation
yet all
right okay there we
go all right
okay just made another if you were here
right now in my kitchen I would make
that one for
you okay there you
go now that's how easy it can be but you
get
results you get results and that's what
matters it's not a game that's problem
in the health World it all became a game
I really believe that at this point I
know there's some good intentions out
there and people with good intentions
but honestly the stuff they use or the
stuff they sell or promote every day is
not the best stuff it just isn't and
it's not going to help the
person but this is so simple and so easy
you can't go wrong with that when you
want to restore your
skin
now I'm going to sip this I got two of
them here let sip this original one
it's so good knowing I'm doing this for
myself you
know with me with my work schedule and
everything like that I got a lot going
on it's hard to keep up with everything
and so if I can do something that's
really simple and easy but yet help move
like me so far so with the immune system
and everything so I want to talk about
why this is so good too so I'm going to
give you that so the viy micro C has
grape seed extract in it grape seed
extract whole another form of
antioxidant right there grape seed
extract power of that alone in here so
that's in here along with the vitamin C
that's buffered that's not ascorbic acid
now here's the thing if you're going to
take a vitamin C every single day
thinking that it's going to do the same
thing it's not because a it's going to
be ascorbic acid that's number one on
you don't want vitamin C that's made
from ascorbic acid that becomes ascorbic
acid it's too harsh on your gastric
glands too harsh on your stomach lining
too harsh on your dadum too harsh on
your intestinal tract way too
harsh and when it so when it comes down
to vitamin C you want something that's
so buffered where it doesn't cause a
problem where you can use a lot of it
you can take it every single day for
your immune system you can take it to
help restore your immune system and your
liver and throughout your body and
everything that's the kind of vitamin C
you want it's a kind that's not ascorbic
acid I have to say this because people
just don't know and they're not going to
know like I said I'm not going to be on
here talking about skin uh every every
other day or something like that like
say an influencer would do or something
when they're trying to sell a product I
may never talk about this until a year
from now I don't know I wish I can talk
about it every day but I don't have the
time but you need to know what you can
do to move your skin forward help heal
your skin help get somewhere with your
skin it's important to have that it is
especially if you're somebody worried
you're worried about skin problems of
all kinds and maybe you were told being
in the sun too much maybe you told
something else cause skin problems maybe
you were told you got some kind of issue
there's people out there that are like I
got Celiac and it gives me skin problems
I got Celiac well then let your doctor
know about the medical medium skin post
I let them know about these two things
combined right along with a squeeze of
orange ask your doctor if you can do it
take that to your doctor the information
and ask them if you can do it so you can
work on your skin in your healing
process and see what your doctor
says but I can tell you right now when
you do the right things for your skin
and for your body your skin changes and
turns
around it's not about gimmicky crap and
biohack crap which is flooded right now
on the channels it's flooded it's all
bioh hack and gimmick crap and when it
comes down to Medical medium information
it's only about what works that's it
that's it whether you like me or don't
like me or don't like the way I look or
don't whatever it is it's all about what
works that's what counts and starting
with medical Med information from the
beginning when I was younger all the way
to when social media started all the way
to all of it to right now to where I am
now people get results because it
works no matter how you feel about me or
whatever it is like me you like my voice
some people like I don't like his voice
well that's fine just heal work on your
healing process feed your immune system
what it needs get your immune system
what it needs to heal and repair and
when it comes down to skin your largest
organ on your body so science of
research says as far as far as organs go
it's your largest organ as far as your
skin that large organ that you have you
have to take care of it you have to feed
it and feed the immune system so it can
repair itself and repair the collagen
and repair damage cuz Planet stress
planet Earth skin gets ripped apart
fight ORF flight sends adrenaline
through people's skin all the time time
the skin has to deal with all that
adrenaline which is like battery acid
all the free radicals all the poisons
and garbage that's floating out of the
sky that's in our drinking water all the
old Pharmaceuticals we took all the way
going back that everybody took you know
when they were young and maybe still
taking now there's things you can do to
help repair and reverse skin damage help
get that skin to glow and
recover I'm letting you guys
know what works that's it what
works you
know and that's really important so the
MSM has really amazing stuff right here
if you look at the MSM you'll see silica
right there so it's MSM with silica and
when you combin MSM with
silica with the right kind of vitamin C
with grape seed extract and you combine
all of those
together you got
yourself a unique skin healing power
house yeah it's really really
wonderful I think in the next coming
just 5 years from now you're going to
see turbos skin problems
happening
everywhere you're going to see more
eczema more psoriasis more dermatitis
more
bigo more skin problems of all different
kinds more skin lesions more brown spots
more dark spots on skin more patches
more lupus
rashes so-called lupus rashes you know
you're going to be you're going to be
having so many different things so if
you're somebody
that's if you're somebody that's looking
for help to understand anything at all
with this with health get cleanse to
heal that's a great book to start with
right there so you can learn all about
things that you've never even knew in
the health world there's cleanse to heal
you can get it at Amazon there's that
there's the brainsaver books that will
knock your socks off if you're somebody
that knows Health you read this you're
never going to be able to go back and
you're never going to think the same
you're just not if you actually read
this book and go through this book your
life will change you will be so confused
you'll you'll be so confused about what
happened out there and what they did in
the health movement that has just
spoiled everything basically for
everybody to really get a good chance to
heal when you read this you'll know
really what's going on you'll just be so
confused about as far as like why the
world goes the way it goes and people
get sick the way they get sick you'll
just be like it's it's a red
pill your mind will be blown so blown
and then you'll be like have an
Awakening when you read that book and so
these books are here for for you if you
need to learn if you need to grow if
you're somebody that's in that's
saturated in the health movement you've
been sick a long time get these books
get cleanse to heal get cleanse to heal
start with that right there and that's
important all on its own but anyway you
know what I'm looking forward to I'm
looking forward to you having results
with your skin even if I don't see you
or something on here and you don't come
on here and leave a comment or something
I know you're going to get results and
I'm looking forward to that and so when
you wake up one morning and you're like
son of a
gun my skin is actually
changing my acne is Shifting my because
of your immune system my skin is healing
something's changing my skin is less
thin something's going on
here I'm looking forward to that
like that's what I live for right there
I live for that I live for you waking up
one morning and being like I can't
believe it but my Skin's turning
around and then long gone the days of
the exfoliations all the time and the
constant skin ointments and skin stuff
you're putting on your face those creams
are like Mega Buck out there all the
different skin stuff and skin skin skin
creams and everything they're like Mega
Bucks out there people have like a whole
bathroom filled with that stuff but if
they did the right
thing I mean Game Changer right there
guys know I endorse viy I'm not an owner
I don't own the
company you know I don't have stocks and
shares in the company or anything like
that I don't have a stake in the company
but I endorse them I stand behind them I
work with them I support them because
I've never seen anything like it the
stuff they put out there it's just
mindblowing nothing compares I don't
care about all the [ __ ] ads out
there that people do on products nothing
compares to this there's no anti-caking
agents in here I said that before that
alone if you guys only knew what
supplement companies did out there and
the crap that they give people if you
guys only knew it's
disgusting loving healing over there in
IG medical medium information makes your
skin
glow whoa I always hear there's no way
you're
44 no there's no way I'm
44 what me or you're you're
44 I'm trying to get that last one right
there or was it 144 there you
go I wish I was 44 all
right it's hard when the comments go
flying up and keep trying to catch them
in time well listen you guys amazing so
you guys got the information about the
Skin Potion medical means Skin Potion
you know about the immune system a
little bit about how crit critical it is
to keep your immune system strong catch
us free
radicals you need the right antioxidants
that's what we're talking about you need
the repair skin damage all of that
matters you
guys I'm going to have mine I hope you
guys have years later and um good to see
you guys hope to talk
soon that's so good