helping people heal what does it do
what's in
celery juice so that's the whole thing
they're going to talk about
and everybody's always asking and ever
since the video
the dream on video ever since all of
that people are wondering like what you
sir what juicer are you using
what do i do uh do i need a juicer do i
not need a juicer so i got the
juicer right here the omega juicer i'm
going to talk about that a little bit
too why i like it why i
use it so that's really cool so we got
lots of cover but maybe juicing celery
right here talking about the benefits
like
how come it's getting people better like
what's up with that
and you know like you can be doing all
this stuff for yourself
all this great stuff you're on this best
diet out there
you're trying all these supplements
everybody keeps on throwing at you
in different places you're doing all the
things you're doing you're seeing your
10 doctors you're seeing your five
doctors
but all of a sudden you bring celery
juice in
therapeutically properly bring it in
and the needle starts moving you start
getting better
things start just disappear why is that
why is that happening and you know
what's really funny
but by the way if you guys are just
getting on here i'm juicing celery
so that's one thing right there so i'm
doing that um
and i'm going to be talking about the
benefits of celery juice
by the way there's a black friday sale
this juicer's on sale i'll talk about
that as well
it's a juicer i use um you know
in my opinion it's the best one saves
people money i'm going to talk all about
that
so but you guys like the bottom line is
why are people getting better
when they're bringing celery juice in
therapeutically
and just all this crap's going away acid
reflux
bloating everything like skin's getting
better in people
on just like different eczema psoriasis
vitiligo
rosacea why does it move the needle
how come there's so many thousands and
thousands of testimonials thousands of
testimonials out there
of people moving the needle and getting
their lives back
why is that someone has this juicer i
just saw that i have the juicer chris
chris uh amazing i'm so glad you have
this is the mm
900 hds that's the one
you guys know i licensed my name to this
one i tell you all the time
because the company contacted me they
said look we want to make the best
juicer for celery plus this is the best
juicer for anything you could put apples
in here
you could put whatever else you want in
here you can juice spinach you can juice
greens you can juice other things you
like
but anyway the point is though
is that this juicer here is the one i'm
using it's the one i like i'll tell you
why
it's black friday blackfoot there's a
sale on it but
the the here's the most important part
of it right here okay
and listen if you got any juicer use
your juicer if you got a juicer
you like use your juicer you like juice
celery with that the link is in the
description for this model though the
mm-900 hds
but i'm going to just be straight out
here
you know nothing in our history of
trends
or history of popular health
things that we've done it just years and
decades
nothing has moved the needle like
celery juice has and you got to think
about that for a little bit like what is
up with that
it's not just water because it's not
water
you know what you know what i hear all
the time this is really funny
i hear this all the time okay it's like
when i just did that tick tock video
and of of juicing celery and all that i
hear this all the time
it's just water you can get better just
on water
the the celery juices that's all it is
that's funny because if you fill a fish
tank with celery juice all the fish are
gonna die
you know why do you know why all the
fish are gonna die in a fish tank when
you just make it all celery juice and
you have all your fish swimming in there
and they're swimming in just celery
juice
do you know why because it's not water
that's why
celery juice is not water
that's why okay and it's something more
special something more powerful for that
than that nancy says i feel much better
when i drink celery juice incredible
sharon says celery juice for sure moved
my needle
for the win right
i mean and there's thousands and tens of
thousands of testimonials
and you got to think about that like
you know i mean nothing has done that
out there
in the world nothing has done that
collagen hasn't you can be you can have
lupus
and collagen doesn't change that uh
doesn't help you with your lupus
symptoms you can have multiple sclerosis
and collagen doesn't that's just one
thing
there's so many different things out
there that are popular
but they don't move the needle and
yet celery juice has like nothing
has and it's one of the medical medium
tools it's the whole thing it's so
incredible when you think about it so if
you guys just got on here i'm juicing
celery
um this is the juicer i use letting you
know
you don't have to use this juicer you
can use a juicer you already have that
you like and love
just use it i don't care just use it but
if you don't have a juicer
it's black friday this is the black
friday sale at omega the link is in the
description
letting you know i've licensed my name
to this model so you guys know what's up
they knocked on my door a while back and
they said look we want
we want to use your name because
we want to make this thing into
something that actually
changes people's lives and there's
there's a little adapter on here which
is incredible
that squeezes almost every last drop
out of out of um out of celery you know
the whole bit
so so the bottom line is
you guys you need to know something that
when it comes down
to healing what are the tools we can use
out there
where are they you know what's going on
and you got people out there that they
don't know about celery juice yet
and they're sitting there and they're
the needle's not moving for them they
can't get out of that rut
they're trying all these different
things they're seeing all these
different people
and they can't get to where they need to
be
and you know when it comes down to it
it matters it matters when we
find something that works it matters
when we find something that
changes our lives and celery juice has
done that
just for so many people you know my
favorite thing is you guys
and i'm going to juice some celery right
now and talk about you know my favorite
thing is which is really funny is
people will be like oh that's just a
crock
celery juice is just where's the where's
the data
it's you know that that's it's placebo
first of all i got to tell you something
if placebo worked
then no one would be sick not one of you
no one no one you know would ever be
sick in a million years all they would
have to do
is go see their doctor and their doctor
give them a sugar pill
and say this will fix you here's a sugar
pill and all the problems will go away
their ms their ra their autoimmune their
hashimoto's direct some other psoriasis
their vital
vitiligo would all go away all you have
to do is just give somebody a sugar pill
and tell them it's gonna fix their
vitiligo and it should all disappear
so when you hear that that really silly
placebo talk
you gotta kind of like you gotta think
about that one for a little bit
okay placebo doesn't work it never did
what works are things that work
so the only thing that works are things
that can actually work
and look darcy lee um drinking celery
juice for four years now
ibs is gone so grateful well
that's incredible sarah dredge my sister
lorraine
l put me on to you and celery juice i'm
loving it
and feeling a great boost i find i'm
craving it now
incredible you know it's so that's so
amazing
so incredible when i think about it and
so
it really has changed people's lives you
guys know
you're seeing it and so i mean so when
you hear out there somebody say oh it's
all water
um that's funny because it's not all
water
or someone says it's just placebo that's
another funny one too
because placebo doesn't fix anybody it
never did
um so we know that right but
what's amazing is people i've known
35 plus years they're stick when they
get stuck
and they need to move forward man i've
seen people out there
they're doing everything everything
under the sun
they're eating roots they're eating
roots they're eating
dirt they're drinking grass juice
they're doing everything
they're in clinics all the way across
the board europe
to united states to south america to
just everywhere under the sun
and spending thousands and thousands of
dollars
and all of a sudden they stumble across
hey what would medical medium um juice
some celery
let me try that and then the needle
starts moving they're like why am i
starting to improve when i was just
stuck
and and that's what's incredible about
it when you have
healing tools that actually work that
actually really help people
it it's really amazing and you can you
can have two groups of people right you
could have a couple of groups of people
you can have one group of
one person that doesn't do anything for
their health
at all nothing and they drink celery
juice
and it helps move the needle and you can
have somebody who does everything for
their health
everything they're doing just they're
doing
all kinds of stuff for their health and
not moving the needle and they bring in
celery juice and it changes it so it's
really incredible
what happens you guys i'll try to answer
a couple questions too while i'm here
and if you do it right
that's when it counts that's when it
counts
and i've talked about that in the celery
juice book that i put out a while back i
talk about that cleanse the heal
but you guys know the celery juice book
right there the medical medium celery
juice book and
i talk about all the information in
there on on how celery juice helps us
why it helps us why it changes our lives
and what's in it and i'll talk about
that a little bit so let's
let's do a little juicing i'm excited
so um
[Applause]
the bottom line is
what is this doing this herb first of
all it's an herb
so it's herbal medicine herbal
medicine's a whole
nother game okay
and this is herbal medicine
that you can drink a lot of
so it's not like this
root from the amazon that
you got to be cautious to how much you
consume
in hopes that you're going to do some
healing
right this is
herbal medicine and herb that you can
consume
a lot of and use it therapeutically
that's what's incredible all on its own
[Applause]
manjula says can you use this juicer for
other vegetables besides celery juice
absolutely of course you can and it
juices those
incredibly that's the whole point it's a
juicer for
other things any kind of vegetables any
kind of fruits
it's a juicer for that and that's what's
amazing
it's just that this model also has this
incredible
device on the end of it that
makes it so you can squeeze as much
juice
as you possibly can out of celery and
that's what i love about it in my
opinion
it's the best one you know i've like
gotten every juicer out there i've like
and for the price point it's incredible
so
right now it's 60 off it's black friday
sale the link is in the description for
this juicer
um it's a great time to take advantage
of a healing tool
that will pay for itself this one's the
mm 900
hds so i'm all about well
something that i buy pay for itself
that's what i'm about or is something
that i'm gonna buy gonna cost me money
am i gonna buy a car
right am i gonna buy a car that i gotta
keep on
fixing all the time and i'm dumping
money
in all the time now i got to get a new
set of tires
now i got to get now i got to get a new
set of brakes
right off the running and all of a
sudden you're spending all this money
with this juicer it's like you're buying
celery
okay and celery gets pricey at certain
times of the year
it can get a little pricey right it
could cost a little bit more
and people say well it's expensive to
juice that much celery
it's actually not um because of what it
does for you
it's incredible on that level but here's
the thing if you're one of those
if you're concerned about it costing
like more
like you're saying well that's a head of
celery is 99 cents or a head of celery
is 1.99 or
whatever it is in whatever grocery store
or wherever you are in the world
the point is is that when you're
squeezing the juice out of it you're
saving money
and that's the key like for me i've used
celery for
30 plus years right and
what i noticed when i use this juicer so
far because i'm doing a little
experiment
with that like how much money can i save
and
when i'm juicing celery with this
machine every day because i juice a lot
so i do 32 ounces minimum every single
day
i got a pile of celery right here you
guys see that right there
um but i do 32 ounces minimum each day
that's what i do right so i want to know
am i
saving money and it turns out i am
that's what's incredible i'm squeezing
more juice
out of the celery that goes through this
machine
that i've done in any machine i got a
garage
filled with machines like every company
out there
and this is the one i use
so this is the one i back this is the
one i back
but the point is is when you're
buying half the celery that you would
normally buy
or a fraction of what you would normally
buy
for your juice that alone pays for the
juicer
so by the end of the year you're like
well i just saved all that money
that could buy a whole bunch of juicers
you know
and it's kind of like that it's really
cool
can use this juicer for other veggies
that question i answered earlier
yeah you can and that's what's that's
what's amazing
um so let's talk about something really
cool here if you see it
this is what i wanted to show you guys
about this juicer i really love
okay i almost have a full container here
and the amount of pulp is a lot less
it's like dry too it's like
it's it's it's compressed and it's dry
so that's what's really cool and i'll
show you how that works
and look if you guys got a juicer at
home i know people that got a blender
they blend it and they strain it through
a cheesecloth i'm all for that
totally do that you don't have to get to
get the shoe stretch not
it use the juicer that you have totally
you can totally do that so i'm going to
give you a couple of tips that are
really good i'm going to shut this off
for a second
and i'm going to grab
a myself right here so when i look at
how much pulp is in here okay
this is this is unbelievable that's
it a little string okay
and i wanted to show you this it's dry
i mean it's dry you can't find celery
juice
the bottom of this you can't look
look how dry it's so dry it's like a
little piece of rope
and it's not like all this pulp
and all this all this you know pulp and
fiber and leftover
it's a little stringy rope that's dry to
the bone
and where did all the juice go
right i hardly used any celery
and the money saved in my opinion
it's insane so that's what i really love
about this model
but it's this model though you know it's
not like another model
though you know it's this model and
omega says the mm-900 hds
and but i want to show you guys because
i feel kind of like guilty knowing
knowing that i'm getting so much celery
juice
and a lot of you guys are and i feel bad
so i have to at least let you know in
case you ever do down the road
maybe next year two years from now six
months from now
you actually you know get the juicer or
something
but you can use the juicer you have you
can use it forever it's fine the juicer
you have
but i feel like if i don't tell you that
you can have this experience where i
just have this this is so dry
it's it's unbelievable and this
experience of
only having this much in your container
that's dry to the bone
and then have all this juice it's like
it's just something to think about you
know what i mean it's like that kind of
thing don't add water so let's talk
about this a little bit
if you juice your celery juice celery
look i have this big container and that
is all i have for pulp left over and
it's
dry to the bone it's in my fingertips
it's like what the heck when you think
about that
you know and at the same time you can
juice any vegetable and anything you
want in this juicer that's just really
cool
so don't add water to your celery juice
if you blend
it in a blender if you if this is how
you do it right if you juice your celery
juice in a blender
um don't add water okay
just blend it and let it mush up there
and blend and let it get shredded up in
there and then until you're ready
and then dump that into a cheesecloth
and squeeze it out
and do it that way but don't add water
if you add water
it doesn't work celery juice won't work
you can't use it
therapeutically it'll still give you
some nutrition for sure
like you'll see your celery juice if you
add water to it or ice cubes or
lemon to it will still give you
nutrition but it won't
do the magic that's changing the lives
of millions around the world right now i
mean i would
i would estimate over 300 million people
in the world right now and more
are drinking it therapeutically but and
i know a lot they kind of miss the boat
on it they'll throw lemon in there
they'll put water in there they'll put
ice cubes in there
they'll juice other things in there but
they'll still call it their celery juice
but it's not gonna work like
really therapeutically like move the
needle like it needs to move
debra cole um is it on sale for black
friday yes
totally on or i think i originally used
a different juicer for about four months
but then bought this one
when my old one broke in the end i saved
money because
one bag or 2.5 pounds of celery makes
around 32 ounces but would have to use
1.5 bags
which might with my old juicer to make
32 ounces so so you're saying you're
doing less you're using less
so that's amazing okay and that's
incredible i mean
i can tell you with the mm-900 it's less
so i'm just making sure i got that right
so you save money incredible
with the new juicer
amazing amazing that's the way and you
know what
it's happening for me it's just
happening for me too
but i like i said i feel like if i don't
tell you guys
especially when there's a sale it's like
you know i want you to be able to take
advantage of this down the road and
and be able to or anytime be able to get
that experience like this is dry
so dry it's ridiculous like and that's
that's what's incredible so i have all
this juice
right here so i'm gonna
pour it in
i still got leftover this is a
i'm gonna put this over here still got
left over in the container but
i didn't have my celery juice yet today
so i'm really excited about this
but this is a cold pressed juicer too a
lot of people be like
okay there's a question nina what about
celery powder um no
terrible terrible that's that celery
powder is a scam
for sure and it just can't do anything
and i talk about it in the celery juice
book
so the medical medium celery juice book
i talk about it in here
so just letting you know that's a
medical medium celery juice book and the
subtitle
is incredible because it says the most
powerful medicine of our time healing
millions worldwide and guess what
fact fact already happened
all these years so it's a great thing to
see when people are getting their lives
back
it's a beautiful thing um
and celery powder it doesn't do anything
so you're putting just
dead powder you know right in
some water which you're not supposed to
do
so you're not supposed to add water to
celery
juice well if you're going to rehydrate
celery juice from a powder and you add
water
it's not going to be the same thing and
i'll tell you why this is in its
living fresh form and
the water is connected to the sodium
cluster salts
right now in it alive and it's in here
doing its thing it's all connected
it's all attached to itself the sodium
cluster salts are suspended
in the living water but you can't kill
it
you can't just kill it like that and
turn it into powder
and then expect to add water to it and
think
the same thing is going to happen that's
like
throwing something in the blender that's
like throwing something in a food
processor
and expecting to put it back together
after it's been chopped up and diced up
it's just it doesn't work um
so i'm glad you guys are here yeah
strain it so robert
definitely strain it that's what i do
you you want to strain it you want to
take a strainer
even though you're juicing it here it's
already being juiced you still want to
strain it so when i was pouring it in
here
i was straining it that's what i was
doing right here
of course i just spilled a little but
yeah there you go
um
molina vimergi's celery force
has no celery in it no that's actually
that's actually for an incredible
that's an incredible supplement for all
kinds of stuff that's not
it's called celery forest but there's no
celery in there you can look you can
actually look into it
at vimrgy.com it's a wonderful
supplement that's not celery powder
that's not what that is
anyway you guys so i'll talk a little
bit more about this
and let's talk about benefits celery
juice benefits
what happens when you're
drinking this why does it even work
why is it helping people what's going on
with that that's that's the question
there
so here's what happens with celery juice
there's something in here called
sodium cluster salts that's not salt
it's not the same thing salt can't do
what this does this is a subgroup of
sodium
and it's suspended in living water but
it's a subgroup of sodium
that actually interferes
with pathogens so if you have
epstein-barr if you have
streptococcus in your system if you have
if you have anything if you have
hashimoto's ms lupus
ra chronic fatigue syndrome tingles
numbness aches and pains that are all
mysterious jaw
pain neck pain back pain if you have
restless leg syndrome insomnia
depression anxiety eczema psoriasis skin
problems
ticks and spasms twitches dizziness
ringing in the ears
floaters in the eyes all these viral
symptoms if you have all these different
viral symptoms
and toxic heavy metal symptoms the
reason why
people start to get their lives back
when they're bringing this
in as one of the tools as one of them
and i
never said this is the only thing to do
this is just one of the powerful medical
medium tools right
but when this enters your body
something magical happens to begin with
inside of us
we have a big mess going on inside of us
okay we got
rancid fats clinging to our intestinal
tract
we got putrified proteins clinging to
the walls of our intestinal tract lining
it's harboring all kinds of bacteria
it's harboring all kinds of toxins
and when the celery juice enters and
goes in
it goes into that first it
starts to knock out bugs bugs that get
behind sibo
small intestinal bacterial overgrowth
bugs that get behind
acid reflux bugs that cause all kinds of
stomach bloating stomach pain
if you're somebody that's worried about
worms of any kind in your gut
it even goes after those and that's the
thing when it's going down in
it's starting to dismantle the bad
things and it's starting to clean things
up if you were told
you got parasites in your gut and that's
why you're sick whether it's right
or wrong or whatever the celery juice
starts to work on it if you were told
you got bacteria in your gut and your
microbiomes off
and your guts all in balance
and you got bad bacteria and mold and
yeast
and fungus in your gut the celery juice
starts to work on that and
one ounce of celery juice isn't going to
do that much
it's still good it's still good but it's
not going to do as much
like melody says what can i do for sibo
i'm talking about sibo right here and
the celery juice goes down in there and
it starts to shock
those bugs starts to basically electrify
those bugs starts to move them
out starts to weaken them starts to
break
down their membrane that keeps them
strong
and then the celery juice goes down in
and it finds its way
into the liver it goes into the hepatic
portal vein
it finds its way into the liver up into
the liver and then
it starts to go after little buggies in
there and starts to
dismantle toxins neutralize them
so one of my favorite benefits of celery
juice
one of my favorite benefits is it
neutralizes
poisons that have energy to them
meaning they're on a charge because
poisons and toxins
from toxic heavy metals and pesticides
and herbicides and plastics
and petroleum chemicals and
nanotechnology that we breathe in
everything that we get exposed to
has a charge to it and the celery juice
starts to neutralize that charge turn it
around
and that's what's amazing about it right
there it's one of the things
it it basically diffuses poisons and
toxins and at the same time
starts to break down the bugs the bugs
that are behind acne
so when you start drinking celery juice
and your acne
is starting to get better that's because
the streptococcus the bacteria behind
all the cystic acne that everybody has
is getting cleaned up from the celery
juice
and so when celery juice
gives somebody the runs or gives
somebody a little bit of
of diarrhea or give somebody
something like that where it's loose
stools when celery juice does that
it's killing bacteria is what it's doing
so i always recommend
you can reduce the dosage you can do
eight ounces you can do six ounces
you can do a little less but eventually
it goes away
that the runs or diarrhea or anything
like that goes away eventually
and that's what happens because
the celery juice ends up killing and
cleaning up the very bacteria and any
kind of yeast any kind of mold any kind
of fungus that's in the way
cleans it up shocks it out gets it out
of the system so you can do a lower
amount of celery juice if you guys just
got on here this is the mm-900 hds
um and it's on sale right now because of
black friday just letting you guys know
i juiced all this like i used hardly any
celery
and i made all this celery juice and i
just showed you guys
the pulp is dry to the bone
and it's just a little look at that
that's all it is
that's the pulp this is unbelievable
when i think about that i laugh
every time i see that because i'm like i
don't i mean i'm blown away really how
that works
um gabriel celery juice helped all my
family like nothing else
drinking around 16 to 32 ounces every
day since 2018
i wished i found it earlier to save my
mom too
thanks anthony gabriel thanks for being
here i'm honored you're here
amazing 16 to 32 ounces
that is a beautiful thing this is about
24 ounces close to 25 ounces right here
and do it on an empty stomach in the
morning
that's my favorite time to really help
move the needle
don't do coffee with it don't mix
anything in it don't have breakfast
right with it try to keep a distance
between it i've talked about that many
times
um you got you guys i think someone
asked about the juicer i saw
go up there in the comments this is it
right here the omega om ega
link is in the description but this
model is the mm
900 hds um
this has got the you can use this for
anything you can juice anything with
this thing
you know like all the vegetables and all
the fruits and greens you could juice
all of that
but it's got a special attachment a
device
that makes it so the juice gets really
squeezed out for celery and other things
um
so this quest says we're live by the way
you guys we're live right now
vasquez surfing says i got horrible
long-term gastritis
and acid reflux from anti-inflammatories
from my back
i tried everything to heal it and
nothing worked
celery juice healed it quickly i mean
that's incredible
that's incredible i mean it is it's
incredible
and there's tens of thousands of
testimonials for celery juice changing
things
um sandra says how much time in between
what as i talk about in cleanse to heal
and i talk about in the celery juice
book
the distance i like is 20 minutes to 30
minutes
15 minutes the minimum would be the
minimum
i would do like like what i do in the
morning is i do lemon water
in the morning and then lemon water
i i did it first give it a little time
i do 16 to 32 ounces of lemon of water
in the morning first thing is what i do
right
but i keep that separate from the celery
juice the celery juice
comes later i wait a half an hour so i
wait 30 minutes but you could wait
15 to 30 minutes after you had your
lemon water
and then you can do your celery juice
okay so that's that's it right there
so you guys this is incredible got my
celery juice right here i had to share
that with you
it's a black friday sale link is in the
description if you already have a juicer
and you like it
keep it do your juicing i just want you
to know maybe in the future this is
something down the road when your juicer
breaks or something
happens at least you know there's this
option that will save you money and
like really squeeze the juice out links
in the description
mm-900 hds i'm going to instagram
now so heading to instagram live right
from here
and i'm going to tell everybody about
this juice and more celery
and all that you guys then after that
i'm going to tic tac anyway
you guys are incredible love it deb says
feeling amazing
incredible that's good news i love you
guys take care