blast very excited
so I have what's in front of me the
ingredients for the healing broth
which I can show you right here
now I really like the healing broth
after a light blast day because it's
really important for me and I hope you
guys feel the same when you have the
healing broth of course you can eat
whatever you'd like
doesn't matter I mean whatever you feel
like you have are the foods you have or
whatever you're doing if you know of the
healing broth it's an amazing recipe
very very
beneficial for people with chronic
illness it has a history and a street
cred of like helping people with almost
anything as far as what they're going
through from colds flus all that stuff
good to see you guys coming on little
light blast discussion I got some water
in here it's just about to take a boil
let's just get some stuff chopped up
really quick
to begin with four carrots
get some carrots cubed we're gonna pop
this in
good to see you guys
do you feel like a different person
after that light blast
incredible
truly I can't even tell you
what was your experience
like what was your experience listen you
guys just so you know
if you post your experience on the light
blast if you post a real or do a post
I'm not going to be able to see it
the algorithm has been changed on IG so
I can't see it so what you have to do is
you have to hashtag medical medium on
that post and tag at Medical medium but
you have to then put it on your insta
story
and hashtag medical medium and tag
medical medium on your insta story
then I can see it
I'm chopping up some carrots right now
let's get this going
we're making the healing broth because
it's an incredible tool medical medium
tool
to help with emotional healing emotional
cleansing
now I don't I mean
just talking to a family member
and a friend who was at the light blast
and they experience
the light that came down some people saw
the light
as clear as day it's all they saw was
the white light
and then some people saw it way up there
behind the Stars
and then some people saw a flash in
their eyes some people after it was done
saw white light when it was finished
some people didn't
felt it through their
body and they felt it in their hands
they felt it in their legs
I'm getting some carrots in here
I still have Goosebumps
it was really intense
really intense
right so I got my carrots going let's
let's keep this up
um I don't have celery stalks but I got
the tops of celery I had the celery
greens right very little stock but I'm
gonna use it
from broth
ceiling broth is helpful because it
helps with emotions
a little bit cleansed what happens is
there's space now inside of us after the
light blast I don't know if you feel it
do you feel like like a refresh do you
feel like a fresh start
it's an incredible feeling I don't know
what to say I mean it's really
incredible I've been trying to put words
to it for hours now since it happened
let's get some shiitake mushrooms in
here
shiitake mushrooms
all right
do you have the ingredients if you don't
just hang out with me first you can have
what you would like and
you have in your kitchen
if you're gonna eat it all
right now or just hang out let's talk
about the late blast let's talk about
your experience
let's get these shiitake mushrooms in
here
I want this healing broth cooking right
away so we can talk
I might put one more shiitake mushroom
in there if that's okay by you guys I
have an electric mushrooms
boom
let's get that in there incredible
all right guys
we're having a post discussion about the
light blast
let's get some tomatoes in there too
yeah let's get some tomatoes in here
Tomatoes that's what it calls
for right
have you made the healing broth before
you have
get a couple of tomatoes in there
trying to do it as quick as I can
without chopping my hand
this knife happens to be a little extra
sharp
so I want to be careful
right sweet potato
let's throw some sweet potato in there
[Music]
all right
does anyone know what book it's from the
healing broth is in brain saver
protocols
all right I have to tell you guys
I know I know we're talking about the
light blast
but I have to tell you about the
surprise I've had blue light blast is
kind of part of the surprise right
but I got this other surprise
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
it's an event
and guess what it's free it's free but
it's gonna blow your mind just like the
light blast it's gonna blow your mind
like transformational stuff
seriously
July 12th registration opens for it
to not miss it it's a seven day Journey
I'm taking you on
come on it's going to be so fun I swear
we have a very tough sweet potato here
and I'm just gonna be careful
be very careful
[Music]
don't want to mess around with these
sweet potatoes you don't want to cut
them wrong you don't want to mess up
you know what happened was after the
light blast
I was calm
I just stayed in my chair
I stayed in my chair
and then stayed in my chair and stayed
in my chair I didn't get up but I didn't
get up for a long time
I just soaked it in and I just sat there
and
it was a feeling I Can't Describe I'm
still trying to actually describe it
which leads me to this what's going to
happen with a lot of you guys
is things are going to unravel after the
light blast and I've seen this happen so
many times where
it a week later you start feeling all
these results from it two weeks later
you start feeling all these results from
it a month later it's still carrying on
or things start happening a month later
it works different in every single
person because we're not all the same no
one is the same as another person we're
not all the same some people are going
to see the light some people are
actually going to feel it in their hands
some people are going to feel it
instantly in their neck they're going to
feel it run through them
they're gonna sleep better tonight
they're going to have deeper Dreams
they're gonna have vivid dreams they're
going to have experiences everybody's
different it's going to be like that so
just remember as each day goes on how
things are going to be different along
the way
for each person no one is the same
you have emotional experiences someone
else
doesn't have someone else has emotional
experiences and wounds and they're soul
that someone else doesn't have
and that's how it works
someone asks what is the light blast we
just did the light blast
we just did it
this morning Eastern Time afternoon
Pacific time
and it's something you want to
experience get on the newsletter so you
can learn about it because I want to do
another one
a hundred and ten thousand people
we're on the light blast today a hundred
and ten thousand people
33 000 people signed up registered for
the light blast
33 000 people
and what happened was
over a hundred and ten thousand people
ended up at the life blast
because people gave out the link
remember when I remember when I said
something about that try not to give out
the link I'm trying to say it in a
really nice way please don't give out
the link
because if you give out the link you're
probably gonna crash our technology
because we only have technology enough
for
with technology not from technology
experts telling us that 33 000 people 30
000 people was Max on this one that
signed up but we let it go to 33 000
people for the sign up
but what happened was lots of people
shared the link gave the link out and it
ended up ended up over a hundred and ten
thousand people were on
but what happens when that happened is
it ends up starting to break down the
system a little bit and then some people
they lose a connection or something it
can happen
[Music]
all right so we still have some turmeric
to put in and I I apologize
I apologize to anyone who could not get
on and we're going to do another light
blast and we're gonna do one fairly soon
not a long time from now but fairly soon
so I apologize my greatest apology to
anyone that that couldn't get on that
registered and couldn't get on or
registered and just it couldn't happen
for them like my greatest apology
seriously I feel really awful about that
if they if they couldn't get on
we're working on improving the
technology so people can actually get on
and not have that problem I'm just
letting you know it's good to see you
guys I'm making the healing broth right
now I'm making it out of the brain saver
protocols book I'm not going to talk
about the brain saver protocol book
we're talking about the light blast but
if you don't have this book you're
missing out get this book from Amazon or
from the library whatever Library
just get the book okay when you can
you'll be mind blown about that but it's
not about that it's about
would happen today with the light blast
often maxner says I cried like a baby
but I feel like I have a fresh start I
feel like I have a fresh shirt too when
you said there was 10 people left I felt
like I'm getting I'm getting chills and
I'm getting emotional right now with you
saying that when you feel like there's
10 people left
10 people left what what you're saying
if if no one understands what that means
is that as the light was going through
everybody
there were a lot of scragglers there
were people that were they were
how should I say it tough cookies
lots of heartbreak old heartbreak lots
of emotional wounds lots of soul wounds
lots of Soul injuries
lots of Confrontation things in their
life look even abuse all kinds of
different things that have been
happening in their life maybe they were
gaslit forever in their life all these
years whatever it is broken trust issues
betrayal
relationship breakups relationship
problems whether it's divorces or
breakups or friendships
or business partners whatever it is so
many people had so many wounds and the
world is getting tougher and what
happened was when that light went
through people and it hit the crown of
their head and it ran through them it
just it blew up that stuff to get it out
of them it literally sent shrapnel out
it sent debris out of their body and
that's why I was saying you got to kind
of like shake the air a little bit
because it was blowing that much out of
people
and it was that intense and the 10
people left were the toughest cookies
the ones with a lot of injuries a lot of
Heartache a lot of betrayal that
happened in their life a lot of broken
trust and those 10 people
they it all blew out of them by the end
it was just boom that debris came out
that hurt that wound all of it came out
right at the end there that was the last
10 people there were a few people that
went through close to the beginning went
right through them where the light goes
right through the crown of their head
runs through the body runs out of their
feet into the ground there was a bunch
of those but not a lot everybody had a
blockage everybody had a blockage
and some people as they were blocked
here they're blocked here are some
people didn't even get through their
head right at the beginning
yes I feel lighter and so calm
I just read that comment
okay I felt
Zen veteran says I felt stop in the
chest and you felt the light stop in
your chest then you felt it stop in the
heart then you felt it stop in the
stomach and then it went all the way
through
that's what it was doing that's the kind
of that's the kind of experiences that
was happening and spirit of compassion
was telling me that light was getting
locked up in people the third one was
starting to really get through people
then it was Amplified then the fourth
one then it was Amplified and the more
people were freed
Cricket says on IG yes first light blast
my heart feels light I am warm and still
somewhat tingly I'm finding that my body
is not registering negative emotions so
amazing
it's incredible
I'm gonna put a hot hot pepper in this
just bear with me for a second I had
chili pepper flakes here but I'm gonna
take this Garden pepper right here
Robert said on Facebook I saw red and
orange and purple and violet when I
closed my eyes during the blast a lot of
people saw a lot of different colors too
that's really interesting
foreign
guys don't mind if I put a little hot
pepper in here
I'm not going to put the whole Cayenne
in there because I don't want this broth
too bitey too hot so I'm going to do
that I still got garlic to put in I
still have some ginger to put in let me
put an inch of ginger in there
I would like to put some ginger in there
is that okay with you guys I have to
tell you though I'm really actually
feeling really good after the white
blood
I feel okay so Rory says I feel so much
better since the light blast incredible
and then I am Freddy I think said I felt
it in my hands
I felt it in my hands and legs
I couldn't get off my seat afterwards I
just sat there I was kind of in shop
I read some people saw rainbow colors I
see that coming in IG amazing I feel so
much better Julian says in IG
it's just it's such a miracle
windwild says I had a hard time getting
online so I got the end of it I want to
do it again I will try to make sure we
do it again soon not later but soon I
feel really bad for a lot of people that
could not get in to the light blast
Laura says I feel infused over there on
Facebook
you did cry after the first blast
well if you if you're you were there for
a oh my God at the first blast you'd be
the very first that came down
you got a little parsley in here if you
guys don't mind
loan says over there on Facebook why do
we cry during the light blast
so much is Letting Go
we bury we bury we stuff inside we hide
we put aside we put deep
deep the emotional wounds because you
have to move forward
you can't live in the hurt in the moment
so we have to pick up our our feet we
got to move forward
but what happens is over the years
it builds up inside of us
some people might not feel much at first
but then they'll feel it and see the
changes in the coming days weeks and
months
let's get some garlic in here
we stuff it inside
my anatomy's over there
Madeline says it was intense for me I
was dizzy nauseated and felt a little
weak afterward it was only later that I
got my energy back I feel good though it
is real
Thank you Madeline for being here thank
you for being at the light blast
truly I'm so glad you were able to get
in
I feel sad about people that people that
registered and and they say they
couldn't get in I'm 110 000 people there
the system was was barely hanging in
there by a thread because it wasn't
designed for a hundred and ten thousand
people
dear Lord
Patricia Santana over there on YouTube I
felt the light blast especially in my
legs I have a peaceful feeling let's see
how we sleep tonight too some of us
might sleep a lot better some of us
might just be buzzing because of the
amount of healing that occurred it's
almost like you don't know what to do
with yourself when you get that much
healing emotionally Cynthia C says is it
normal that we feel tired afterwards yes
yes
for a bunch of people that's definitely
gonna happen
doing some garlic here
[Music]
guys remember what it was I always say
about garlic when you see me crush it by
hand like that or you see a chef out
there crush it by hand like that
you have to have the blade facing out
you can't have a blade facing in When
you crush garlic like that
burning around town says there was less
Tech issues than last time though laugh
out loud indeed you're right in fact you
are a hundred percent correct
actually a thousand percent correct how
about a hundred thousand percent correct
we improved
not because of me I can't take the
credit the credit goes to my team
my team worked there butts off for this
late blast you guys they work their
butts off for it like I can't even tell
you so much so
so much so
and for free because we want people to
get the healing
is it normal I feel tired
and couldn't get it
I'm not sure what that means couldn't
get it all right let's get some garlic
in here this is cooking healing Frost is
already being made
nice
mmm garlic
hmm
what a smell garlic has isn't it
something else
I Saw The Light Deanna says
incredible I get tingles
I get goosebumps
I had chills
when I just read that just now I Saw the
Light
we stuffed the stuff down we stuff it
deep inside hello I'm living my life oh
you just betrayed me crap I'm hurting
for a few weeks or months but I have to
move forward with my life so I'll pick
up my feet and I'll keep on moving
forward and I'm gonna have to stuff that
betrayal injury down deep inside walking
around and going on meet somebody else
or something happens hello how are you
oh you just broke my trust what the heck
it hurts hurts really bad but I have to
move forward I'm going to stuff it down
deep inside let me bury it down hello I
keep on moving on with my life I come
across something else like what why did
that happen hey that's unfair I'm not
validated you misunderstood me I stuff
it down deep inside because you got to
move forward
and then it sits there and it sits there
and it percolates and it percolates and
it grows and it turns it and it festers
and festers over time and then
we're running around doing self-help
I'm trying this I'm trying that I'm
trying that I'm trying this but it keeps
on coming back the patterns keep on
coming back I try to do this I do this
meditation I go here I go to yoga class
I go wherever I'm doing well that's
great but it still comes back I still
have all the patterns coming back
and so what I love about the light blast
is it's different than anything else
because it's not man-made down here it's
not controlled by man it's not
controlled by time or space it's not
controlled by law it's not controlled by
Nature it's not controlled by physics
nature can be cruel nature can control
stuff
physics nature
controls things
we need light that's on the Angelic
realm there's no control
there's no earthly control
and what the light blast is it's not
about that the light blast is separate
from that it's out of the Earthly chaos
it's not involved with the Earthly chaos
that's entirely different
and so we need that kind of light when
we're all built up inside with
everything stuffed down in us to hurt
the Betrayal the broken trust all the
pain and suffering all the losses the
heartache all the different things we go
through the validation issues because
we've been not validated because we've
had trust broken because we're we're
taking advantage of or we're mistreated
or we're Gaslight or whatever you want
to call it there's so much hurt and then
we need a light that's not controlled by
law
govern here on planet mess we need a
light that's away from that comes from
above and you believe in God if you
believe in God that's where the light
comes from way up there if you believe
in the universe then it comes from there
if you believe in a Creator if you
believe in everybody has different
beliefs but the light is there
Alicia M this was my second light blast
that I felt so clear this second time
around I didn't feel like getting stuck
like I did last time which I want to say
to people once you've had a light blast
before
once you've had one
things can be different when you get
another light blast
and that's all incredible all in its own
things can be so much different when you
get another late blast
cold white spring said are you tired
cold white spring mayor you asking me if
I'm tired
the mm who burns a candle at five
different ends
okay we're making the healing broth
right now
foreign
yeah I'm tired
because the light blast is not easy on
me
all right but I still
feel
a lot of the incredible effects
what happens is that
it is tiring on me
but
in a good way because I know I'm being
used as a conduit and that's the that's
what's tiring
right because I'm being used as the
conduit
the messenger
facilitated right so because of that
it's tiring yes
but I have no complaints
because
on the flip side
I get some light
which is incredible
and I feel so good because of it and on
the flip side the most important
which isn't about me anymore like the
most important is you guys getting
what you need a mattress service I want
to be at your service and that's the
critical part is you guys getting what
you need and that's the part that
matters to me because I'm at your
service that's the whole point
if I have to be the conductor if I have
to be the conduit and the conductor so
be it that's fine if it tires me out a
little bit fine if it targets me out a
lot fine
if it puts me in shock for a little bit
fine
but it's well worth it when I know you
guys get what you need and I'm at your
service
and then I bounce back after being the
conduit in the conductor I bounce back
after being the messenger
and I feel the effects
of the light
this is coming out incredible by the way
got hot pepper in here I got parsley in
here I got celery in here I got Tomatoes
I got carrots and I forgot the onions
I have an onion right here
oh
gonna get tears in the eyes
[Music]
we don't edit these These are live right
here I'm live in the moment I just want
you to know what's happening inside our
bodies mm sugar plum masks
hurt
takes up space
hurt from betrayal and broken trust in
Old Wounds going all the way back from
relationships to just different things
that have happened in life take up space
and then we've run around trying to
actually soothe ourselves and we get in
trouble we get into addictions we get
into self-destructive patterns we get
into everything we jump into self-help
we look for help we get we do all these
things we say we see we seek out therapy
everything we do right psychiatrists
therapists
we seek out therapy
because we're trying to fix it right
but those wounds take up space
they take up brain space they take up
Soul Space they take up
Spirit heart soul space
Mind Body however you want to call it it
takes up space so if you want to ask the
question what is happening
in our bodies mm start with
what the light blast does is it opens up
new space
inside of us inside our soul inside of
our body inside of our spirit inside of
us
it it actually
is extracting that Venom and that poison
right that old hurt and then when that
leaves
you got space
do you ever have a really cluttered
house did you ever have a cluttered
apartment do you ever have a cluttered
closet because you ever have anything
that was so cluttered right
your car is cluttered what about your
car is your car cluttered
you ever you ever drive a car that's
filled with so much stuff there's
garbage on the floors did you ever do
that you're like maybe you're somebody
that never happened to you there there
isn't a bunch of garbage on the floor
you don't have boxes you don't have
stuff I know people they have to live
out of their cars practically and
their cars are just taking up there's no
space in their car
what happens when you clean that car up
and you get rid of all that stuff and
you organize it and you get it out and
you throw out a lot of bunch of stuff
whether it's in a house an apartment
whether it's in a dwelling whether it's
in a car
it makes room for something else
makes room for something else
when you actually
are experiencing the removal of wounds
that shouldn't sit there and fester
forever year after year of 20 years 30
years when you remove those
what happens you guys
space opens up
and then things are possible an ignition
igniting the healing process
you guys I just want to tell you real
quick
I got to tell you about the collecting
Stones meditation journey I just have to
let you know
I beg of you I beg I'm begging a Metro
service but I'm also begging
that you don't miss out I say that
because it's going to be that
life-changing
that you don't mess that you don't
miss out
on this opportunity
because then you're going to say
yourself oh my god did I mess up how did
I miss that
so collecting Stones is one of the
meditations inside medical medium New
Edition
New Edition
if you don't have the book go to the
library and get the book or go to Amazon
it's on sale at Amazon right now so it's
a medical medium new edition book
there is a meditation in the back of
this book called collecting Stones I
just want to give you guys the rundown
on how insane this is
okay
so I'm going to find it collecting
stones
it's that's surrounded by trees that
meditation that's free is a bird
meditate here it is collecting Stones
right here
when you want to cleanse yourself of
challenging emotions take a walk in
nature and keep your eye out for small
stones
okay here's the collecting Stones
meditation
I'm going to be guiding personally
registration starts July 12th
that's registration the meditation is
going to start July 19th
keep this in mind it's coming up
it is a seven day
meditation Journey
that I'm guiding you personally
and you're wondering how much is it
going to cost
everybody else's stuff out there costs a
whole bunch of money he's certainly aw
for a seven day guided Journey it's
gonna cost a lot it's free
it's free
and your life is going to change because
not only if you did the light blasting
if you didn't do the light blast fine
still do the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
you will be blown away
medical medium make sure you have that
if you're going to do it Mary C on
YouTube I'm getting the chills now again
thinking about it I saw light through my
eyelids and my eyes were moving like an
REM mode surreal very healing thank you
aw and SOC
every time I read a comment like that
like because I understand
Gabriel over there on Facebook
thank you Anthony I felt energy on my
head
and got very emotional
then started crying thanks to Spirit of
compassion
gonna get me uh emotional for sure
like I am emotional about just reading
that
and uh kind of gets me choked up because
okay so got a comment here
um the light blast I signed up used a
link
I signed up before nine o'clock CST this
morning and nothing
I had check telegram for updates and the
final update was not clear that you were
starting
and no indication that it had finished I
finally logged off after 10 20. this is
breaking my heart as we as as I'm
speaking
this was a waste of my time and you seem
to have no consideration for others
look I know you're upset I I really do
feel bad that something went wrong there
I appreciate you having this service but
if you can't consistently deliver you
need to Pivot and find a new method
Instagram live allows way more people
why don't you just go live instead of
whatever you are using that I didn't get
to take part in my partner will be
throwing your books out
since he is so disappointed this late
blast was a joke and apparently it's on
me and everyone else that didn't get to
join okay
please I just want to say something all
right first of all it kills me that
you're upset and that's your that your
partner is upset first of all okay and
here's what happened okay
it takes a lot of technology to harness
this what we're doing
and a hundred and ten thousand people
got on because people share the link
and they're not supposed to share the
link and a lot of people share the link
and so glitches happen with the
technology
right and
Instagram
lives they have a cap on me
and they usually only let me have five
six seven hundred people when I used to
have six to ten thousand people
um per live I used to get six seven
eight ten thousand people every time I
went live on Instagram but they they
tapped me
and so they did that and they usually
keep me around six seven hundred or if
I'm lucky they'll let me have like
fourteen hundred like out of nowhere one
day but they won't let anybody else go
on they get kicked off
so I can't use IG
right so I'm just letting you know I'm
just you know so you understand
but
I feel for you I'm sorry if you're gonna
throw the books out
and I'm sorry that like you're really
upset and I and
if I were you I would be mad too
and that's how I feel and there are a
lot of people that couldn't log on and
something went wrong it was either on
their system or it was because of of our
system but people share the link and we
had 110 000 people on when there was
only supposed to be 33 000 people and it
is a free event and I'm not trying to
cry or anything about stuff but to put
this event on it costs me thousands and
thousands of dollars
and so I don't charge like a hundred
dollars for a sign up a hundred dollars
for a ticket for each person
I don't do that there's no charge
and it but yet it cost me tens of
thousands of dollars to actually run and
and put on and pay my team and we work
on it for weeks
um including the Technologies were
expensive to use for that anyway
so I just want to be of service so what
I do is is
what I like to like what I love to do is
give to the community
and not empty their pockets
that's what I've always done all these
years
I'm the only one out there to whatever
they call it my caliber that's what PR
people will say my caliber up there in
the health and healing world
then I hate hearing that and when they
say I'm the only one that doesn't do
subscription fees for the website
programs and classes and courses and
certifications all these things that
just make tons and tons of money to make
me a billionaire
also did you turn on the audio button on
the bottom left if you did not that is
another reason you have no sound for
people who didn't have sound so
onions are there are cooking
oh
so anyway
but I wanted to re I saw that comment
come up and I said look I want to
address it we put instructions on the
screen and above the video by the way
[Music]
I'm hoping Dr Nesbitt stops by
do you guys remember Dr Nesbitt
does anybody remember Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbitt signed up for the light blast
and he got in
I get a beating no matter what I do by
the way you guys I get a beating
I get whipping I get a beating
I get the crap beat out of me no matter
what I do
and then of course you know
there are enough hate groups out there
that don't like me
I'm grateful too for you guys I just saw
that you're so grateful I'm grateful for
you too
all storms pass coaching I see that
right there
over there on YouTube
I also felt the light stop in my chest
the first blast with the first blast
after that one I felt really
uncomfortable in my body can't explain
it
but felt a full release after the last
blast
and and you guys remember
it was like
the intensity was getting increased
so SSC would say increasing
and then I would get kind of like
they get kind of a little scared right
because I know that so much is going to
be flying out of people so much hurt and
so many things that have been trapped
there for so long and print it
like imprinted within us like imprint it
within us so much gets imprinted and
trapped
and so on Spirit of compassion Spirit of
compassion doesn't start out on the
first blast is the most powerful
because
it's
graduate
because it has to be that way
because there are people with a lot less
wounds
but there are a lot of people with so
much going on that it can't be full
power on the very first
blast
because that's like
pavement you know like for real it's
hitting the road real hard
with the second length glass Janet says
with the second light blast I had
tingles in my arms and legs but it was
Technology's going crazy today but it
was the release of tears that surprised
me and I have just woken up from a
two-hour nap something I never do
I am feeling mellow and so thankful for
this opportunity and Janet what's going
to happen is that's not where it stops
the healing with the light blast it
Carries On
it Carries On
I just want to let you guys know I can't
wait to taste this broth I hope you hang
around while I actually put it in a bowl
and I have a little bit for myself I'm
actually gonna put some in a mug
I'm gonna put some in a mug
okay
you don't want to miss the collecting
Stones meditation Journey registration
opens up July 12th please be on my
newsletter so you know so you're on my
newsletter list so you know it's a free
seven day guided journey by me
get the medical medium New Edition make
sure you have it you won't be sorry
the book is loaded with healing
information but I'm not even going to
talk about that I'm talking about the
collecting Stones meditation in here
you don't want to miss this go to the
library get the book out for free I
don't care that's fine just get the book
okay Amazon has it Dirt Cheap right now
but yes make sure you have this you
don't want to miss the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
foreign
healing broth is done
now listen you I'm gonna strain it if
that's okay
EQ com says I couldn't get in at first
but refresh the page and wait it again
and it worked I followed the email
instructions and telegram updates and
found it really helpful so telegram be
on the medical medium Telegram
so you can get the updates be on the
medical medium telegram so you can get
the updates
very important
this is very hot let's hope
everything goes okay
[Music]
let's hope this glass bowl can withstand
very hot
very hot very hot
course you can keep all of the different
herbs
and rhizomes and mushrooms and
everything else
and you can actually save
which I do I save all that but I'm
having the broth in the moment
this is live so anything could go wrong
right now
like a huge mess can occur
medical medium does make Messes in the
kitchen I just want to give you that
disclaimer
so if something happens don't be
surprised
putting that over here you guys don't
mind
okay I have the healing broth
also if you don't mind I'm gonna put a
couple of little pieces of parsley
inside or on on top of the broth fresh
pieces
if you're okay with that
I am also going to make a mug of the
healing broth
I don't know if that makes sense make a
mug of the healing broth I'm going to
fill the mug with a healing broth
there we go
this is the way I like to do it now keep
in mind this is really hot
that's the way I like
right there
putting away
knives for a second here
got some healing broth
thank you Anthony for the amazing light
blast I felt the light
stacked in the stuck in the chest
and then the stomach and then after many
tries it went through thank you so much
you're welcome
fantastic
foreign
so
I'm reading the comments you guys
this has just been an incredible day I
can't say enough about it about how
incredible of a day it is
truing
you guys
Dr Nesbitt
got a label ass today
Dr Elizabeth what did you think about
the lay blast
Dr Nesbitt says that he got the late
blast when he was in surgery
he was doing an open heart surgery
and
he said it was his best day in surgery
in years
I need people to know that
if for some reason you couldn't log on
or anything
I will do everything I can
in Technology power and my team to try
to make sure the next light Blast has
the least amount of glitches but like
somebody said it was a lot better than
the last time
[Music]
um
um Dr nessman Dr Nesbitt said that he
said that his surgery went better today
than any other surgery he's done because
he had the light blast during his
surgery
and he said he had less alcohol to drink
after the surgery so he
he sent down less shots of
of vodka
and whiskey
um
you guys
I'm gonna have some healing broth just
know I'm proud of all of you
and let's do the light blast again in
the next coming month or so I'm going to
try to get one done sooner than later
Katie flake said something and it just
went up I can't catch these comments
fast enough
okay
all right guys
love you greatly
and looking forward to hearing how
things go one last thing really quick
remember I can't see your posts or reels
so when you hashtag hashtag of course
medical medium on your posted reels and
tag at Medical medium but I still can't
see them so that means you have to then
put them under insta stories
you have to put your Post-it reels on
your insta story and hashtag medical
medium tag medical meme on your insta
story
for me to be able to see them and if you
can share your experience it would be
helpful for other people in the
community that also have experi at that
experience so many different emotions
and feelings and different Sensations
during the light blast and so please
share your stories
so that others can also see how you know
how you felt during your making sure
their stories too it's a community
a very powerful community
interaction because so many of you guys
have really have released so many
emotions
and so much old hurt
it's just it's very important to all
stick together
many blessings
mirabai says light blast
lay blast was super helpful
there was
and then it's gone
anyway I love you guys
and I will see you guys next time
you want some healing bro sure