recipe that's really awesome recipe that
is really exciting
because um I've been doing recipes
lately I've been it's been fun so I'm
excited about that want you guys eating
healthy want you guys eating good I want
to answer some questions too so I'm
going to do that as well um for anybody
that doesn't know the new release right
here medical medium okay Secrets behind
chronic mystery illness and how to
finally heal revised and Expanded
Edition new Edition uh you can get it on
Amazon right now so it's mind-blowing
I'll talk about that in a little bit too
about what this has in here how
incredible it is that's exciting so I'm
glad we're here going to make this
potato salad this is a recipe that's out
of cleanse to heal so if you want to
know it's out of cleanse to heal so I'm
making a recipe right here the potato
salad right here out of cleanse to heal
so I'm excited about this um
anyway how's everybody doing hello from
Missouri great glad you're here awesome
um it's one of your favorite recipes
Margarita wow cool the potato salad
incredible I'm excited about making it
then um you love the recipes Julie
awesome cool cool this is great so uh
it's a healing potato salad definitely
potatoes got their high in lysine reason
why so many people are sick because of
all the herpetic viruses got the upstein
bar in the the shingles the hhv6 the
cyega virus the simplexes and that's why
people get the trigeminal neuralgia the
body aches and pains chronic fatigue and
potatoes are really healing for that and
that's what's incredible medical medium
information and um so the healing potato
salad that's what it is going to put
some good stuff in here too some great
stuff that's so great so let's do it
let's start working on it so I'm going
to take the potatoes the potato halves
and I'm going to this your first time
here Lindsay hey I'm honored I'm glad
you're here incredible so uh Abby says
saved her life
amazing um hello from North Dakota great
glad you're here you love the uh
Angelique says she loves the potato
salad wonderful wonderful glad you guys
are coming on yeah so I'm going to cut
the I'm going to dice the potatoes okay
I already have them cut in half so I'm
just going to dice them
up and like inch to 2 in slices are fine
these are steamed potato potatoes just
so you know so I'm putting some steamed
potatoes in here just like that hope you
guys can see it so I'm slicing it up
right
now hope everybody's doing great on this
day so these are cubes that are this
size right here
see
and first time watching from Australia
Ashley thanks for being here amazing so
glad dicing these up right here so this
is the healing potato
salad so red potatoes are okay Barbara
totally you can use red potatoes I love
red potatoes um it's a great potato and
you certainly can use it why steamed
Lori because it preserves the nutrients
like no other and it's the the makes it
easy to digest a potato is easiest to
digest when you steam them that's the
critic key right there so you have to
steam them not boil them you don't want
to boil them cuz you'll boil that flavor
right out of them too and it'll be in
the water unless you're making a soup
right unless you're making a soup but
we're not making a soup and you want the
steamed
potatoes not not any other way for this
for sure
um so I'm dicing this up don't add oil
don't add butter don't add cheese don't
add any products that's not in the
recipe plus you don't want those in
there if you're actually struggling with
any kind of
condition you certainly don't want those
in there um you love potatoes I saw that
Shelly says she loves potatoes
incredible I do too I do
too Tama says she loves steamed
potatoes incredible so I'm dicing these
up hi from the
Netherlands great place in Netherlands
thanks for being here um what gives
potatoes a bad
wrap is what people do to potatoes okay
it's not potatoes that give anybody any
issues or problems potatoes are actually
a healing food really healing what the
problem is it's the milk cheese butter
oil the Mayo right the egg it's all that
that causes problems with potato cuz
it's not the potato causing the problem
it's all the dairy products the oil the
the that's drenched in them frying
potatoes that's another thing right
there that causes problems so that's
what really goes on that's what gives
potatoes a bad wrap right
there so I'm dicing these up making the
potato salad as we speak here you can
use 2 lbs of
potatoes you can roughly peel them I'm
roughly dicing
them okay you don't have to peel
them so I'm getting my potatoes in this
dish right here I want to answer some
questions for you
too but potato is a great food Corn's
not so I'm just letting you know corn is
not a good thing to do cuz cuz I saw
somebody say starch solution it say you
know what happens is that is that you
don't want corn and I know that in the
old days the starch solution stuff was
all about corn disaster there's problems
and holes in everybody's ideas out there
it's really sad how it works because
nobody knows that the corn feeds viruses
so when people are sick with chronic
fatigue and fibro and they're eating
corn in their starch meals lots of corn
they don't know that contributing to
feeding the very bugs that's making them
sick and and really hurting them and but
potato that's not the case of potato so
potato's antiviral antibacterial NAA
says hi from Sweden great to be here um
hi from South Africa incredible I'm so
glad you guys are here so I'm making the
healing potato salad and I'm going to
put a clove of garlic in there you can
do um I like one clove in here if you
guys really love garlic of course you're
welcome to put a little bit more but one
one garlic clove minced so I'm going to
do that right now just going
to get this garlic clove
prepared so
um these recipes are really helpful
especially if you have problems with
digestion especially if you Pro have
different problems um with your health
this this is an amazing recipe for that
very helpful very healing so I'm just
dicing these up just kind of like little
tiny pieces for this garlic is what I'm
doing you can use a mincer I just like
chopping it really fine cuz that's
mincing it too but I'm mincing it on the
board is what I'm
doing saw somebody said she uh you eat
potatoes every day there's Michelle L um
she's here today everybody's coming on
so I'm putting a little garlic in
here so I got that going
on 1/4 cup of roughly freshed parsley
I'm going to grab some back
here about a/4 cups worth right
there going to chop that
up hi from
Brazil la
Trisha says she loves
garlic I love garlic too I really do
so it's getting this parsley ready right
here so I'm roughly chopping
[Music]
it pop popping that in it's a/4 cup
um got some other good stuff coming in
here too and green onion is the next
thing I'm going to
do get a little bit of green onion in
here two tablespoons of finely chopped
green onion that's what I'm going to do
roughly around two tablespoons right
there finely green onion there we
go got that in
there um lemon going in here too so
letting you guys
know me get my lemons ready as well so
there's different options you can put in
here so um you can put you can put
radish in this dish so I have radishes
so I'm going to thinly slice those
cucumber I got the English cucumbers
right here can thinly slice
[Music]
those Caroline says love your chopping
skills do you recommend digestive
enzymes not really I recommend fixing
the digestion that's what I do recommend
so medical meum information is about
give needed tools to fix things like the
celery juice to fix the hydrochloric
acid to fix your stomach gland so your
digestion gets strong All These Years
everybody was doing the digestive
enzymes out there it was a big thing and
they were just pumping them everywhere
they still do but what people don't
understand is it's a Band-Aid or you're
trying to do this Band-Aid so you're
doing dig digestive enzymes it's like a
Band-Aid to things versus actually
fixing a digestive problem fixing the
the liver and its bile strength fixing
the hydrochloric a
in the stomach glands that that produce
the gastric acid the stomach glands
fixing things and then get Ri getting
rid of bad bacteria through using foods
and and also understanding how
everything works like can cleanse the
heel and the new medical medium book
that's coming out um so you can learn I
got a gut chapter in here that's
mind-blowing so inside the medical
medium uh revised and
expanded so it's really about fixing
things that's what I like to do
um see how do I know different between
cultivated and wild blueberries okay
cultivated blueberries are bigger
they're larger and wild blueberries will
say Wild on the packaging like the
Frozen wild blueberries that'll say Wild
on the packaging it's in the freezer
section Frozen wild blueberries so
that's really important right there
cultivated blueberries are in those clam
shell pint siiz clam shells that you see
in the grocery store where they're all
stacked up and they're bigger they're
their larger blueberries those are still
good for you but they won't do that
healing they won't do that healing that
you need they won't get the toxic heavy
metals out they don't even have the
antioxidant level that the wild
blueberries do or the phytochemical
compounds wild blueberries are antiviral
cultivated blueberries are not antiviral
antibacterial so all those things matter
um they really
do so so let's do some like additions
with this potato salad that I'm making
you guys steing potato Sal I got the
diced up Cub potatoes these are steamed
potatoes just so you know I got a 1/4
cup of parsley thrown in there I got a
couple tablespoons of green onion diced
in there and I have a clove of garlic
diced too really finely and thrown in
there just so you know so let's keep on
going let's go into some radish land I
don't know if you guys like
radishes but I do sulfur comp compounds
and radishes are really healing can
thinly slice these rad es it's what I'm
doing right
now you don't need a whole lot of
them so you don't need a lot of them
like this is an option right here you
can do a half a cup of radish put in
here so I'm thinly slicing these
radishes right
now okay Lisa says I make potatoes and
eggs together is that
bad well it all depends you know if you
have any symptoms going on if there's
any kind of symptom you know when people
have um skin conditions eczema psoriasis
if they have sibo intestinal tract
disorders if they have Celiac if they
have Crohn's colitis chronic fatigue
syndrome thyroid problems and anything
like this eggs aren't a good thing for
any of these symptoms or conditions
because what's behind everybody's
sickness and behind autoimmune so if
you're somebody with any kind of
autoimmune what's behind it is viruses
so Epstein bar virus shingles virus um
all the different viruses that's what's
behind autoimmune and they sit inside of
us and we get all these symptoms skin
conditions and everything so with all
that said eggs will feed the bugs so
eggs are a bad idea so um I'd keep them
out of your diet if I I would listen to
the medical medium podcast at Apple
podcast and listen to the egg episode
your mind will be blown the information
in that episode so it's a docy series
style podcast it's uh at Apple podcast
medical medium so you can check that out
so um got a half cup of thinly sliced
radishes right here I'm going to pop
these
in that's what I'm going to
do it's one of the options in this
recipe see guys I'm making the healing
potato salad so I just threw the
radishes in there take a look right
partially flat or curly you can use
Either Ore so I use the flat leaf
parsley but you can use um either one
perfectly
fine so anyway all right so I'm going to
do some cucumber too that's that's the
next option inside this so thinly half
cup of thinly slice cucumber all right
what I'm going to do is cut the cucumber
in half this is an English cucumber I'm
leaving the skin on this one too here's
a question from Janette by the way this
is an English cucumber I just wanted to
show you and I just cut it in half just
so you know that's that's it right there
um why are so many people sensitive to
onions the people who need them stop
eating them
um so what happens is that a lot of
people they'll have a lot of
sensitivities because they're dealing
with so many different levels of
bacteria in their intestinal tract
that's one reason too so in their
intestinal tract they'll have bacteria
strepto octus is one of the bacteria the
main bacteria in people's intestinal
tract the other one is other ones E coli
and if you got a lot of that in there
including fungus yeast mold if you got a
lot of this inside your intestinal tract
you're going to rock the boat because
when you put something like onions in
onions is like an antiseptic against
these very bugs and these microorganisms
that aren't great so when you're eating
a little bit of that onion some people
can get a reaction the reaction is um
they feel a little funny in their tummy
maybe or they feel like they got got
some extra gas that kind of sensitivity
um but but really that's that's that's
what happens there it feels too
strong does radish give Jacqueline says
does radish give nutrition I heard
radish is a
condiment radishes are an incredible
food I mean I think I talk about
it here in life-changing Foods I think I
talk about it in some of the other books
too radish is really power ful because
it's it's got a high sulfur Rich
phytochemical compound in it and that
high sulfur Rich pH phytochemical
compound is is anti-bug and you got to
think about here's the thing okay
everybody's sick because they got these
little bugs inside of them and they got
toxic heavy metals too and other toxins
in them and foods have to be detoxifying
but they also have to be anti-bug
anti-pathogen antiviral antibacterial
anti- mold anti- geese anti fungus and
some foods are stronger than others for
helping us to heal and radishes that's
the food right there so I just put some
radishes in there thinly sliced okay I
got that so I'm doing the Cucumber now
thinly slicing some cucumber I'm using
an English cucumber right here so I'm
thinly slicing some cucumber going to
try to do about a half a cup of this I
like having the Cucumber inside here I
like the cucumber inside this healing
potato salad I like the
radishes and I even have some asparagus
in front of me too I'm going to put in
here so I'm trying to get about a half a
cup I think I got it thinly sliced
cucumber right here so I'm going to
sprinkle that about inside this healing
potato
salad thanks for being here you guys and
in my kitchen today this is
awesome so I got that in there and then
asparagus steamed or raw I'm going to
use steamed asparagus in this healing
potato salad so I got some nice um
steamed asparagus right here so that's
this Julianne asks IBS any suggestions
of what to eat so in cleanse the heel I
talk about Mono eating so mono eating
cleanses and cleanse the heel so that's
what I talk about in here and it's for
people with gastroparesis IBS Crohn's
colitis Celiac intestinal bloating
cramping intal intestinal sensitivities
and so it's the mono eating cleanse
inside cleanse to heal it's one of the
cleanses it's healing people all around
the world right now with
gastrointestinal problems so um so an
IBS is inflammation that is a mystery to
medical research and science so it's a
mystery to the doctor it's a mystery to
medical research and science they don't
know what IBS is irritable bowel
syndrome so with all the science and
technology in the world and all the
trillions of dollars that went into
medicine so far all they can come up
with with three words irritable bowel
syndrome which means out of all the all
the medical technology we have they came
up with the fact that your bow is
irritable that's all they came out with
like that's it it's like trillions of
dollars they can send a rocket ship into
space um we got the best stereo systems
in our cars now but all they can come up
with with IBS is it's irritable so
you're irritable that's it so you got an
irritable problem in your gut that's all
they can come up with it when you really
size it up and see how stupid it is and
see how actually crazy it is and when
you actually look at the truth of things
and see where technology is and and the
medical world is it's it's remedial it's
really sad sure you get into a car
accident they try to piece you back
together in the hospital and and keep
you alive and try to put your broken
bones together but you know and Sur too
your gallbladder is about to pop they'll
take it out for you but when it comes
down to so many things when it comes
down to all these mystery illnesses and
autoimmune and and hundreds of
autoimmune conditions they've labeled
now they don't know the cause and they
don't know the cause of celiac they
don't know the cause of anything
gastroparesis they just don't know the
cause so it so with IBS it's
inflammation yeah but it's inflammation
from Little buggies that are inside the
intestinal tract so and little buggies
cause a lot of problems and then what
happens is when you eat gluten and when
you eat dairy products it could make IBS
worse even if it doesn't make it worse
that day it could make it worse a week
later and then then you kind of don't
know what did it you kind of don't know
what's going on so if I had IBS I'd be
off gluten I'd be off dairy products I'd
be off um milk cheese butter I wouldn't
be doing that I'd be off eggs I would be
off all that that's what I would do and
and then then I would learn hey what's
the cause of IBS so I would try to find
out the cause of IBS and then learn how
to heal it so that's cleanse the heel
right there if you see it I know it's
kind of shiny on the screen so that's
cleanse the heel I have IBS in the book
you could take it to your doctor if you
want have them look at it um so I got
some asparagus right here so half cup of
chopped asparagus now I'm just going to
chop this asparagus
up and and pieces not not just roughly
diced I'm not going
to like overdo it with chopping them up
just letting you know when you guys make
yours tonight you can kind of remember
that so I'm putting the
asparagus on this there we
go Marissa where can I find the recipe
for the potato salad cleanse the
heel that's where the recipe is it's in
cleanse the heel right here um on sale
at Amazon us $16.99 or get it free at
the library you want you can go you know
a lot of people they don't they don't
have the means to think $16 right now
it's tough times for a lot of people to
go to the library get it for free I just
want you to have it so there it
is um so this potato salad's coming out
really good so far so I got a half a cup
of steamed asparagus I got a half a cup
of thinly sliced cucumber got a half a
cup of radishes that's a healing food
all on its own you guys
I got some parsley in here 1/4 cup of
parsley I got a little bit of garlic in
here and then now I'm going to put 2
tablespoons of um lemon is what I'm
going to put in here you can put less
you you could put
more so um but I'm going to put a couple
other things let let's put some mustard
powder in here a half teaspoon of
mustard powder is what I'm going to do
so just want to show you see if you can
even see that there so I got some
mustard powder so I'm going to do about
a half teaspoon of mustard powder over
here there we
go I'm going to do some uh some other
stuff so two teaspoons of lemon is what
I'm going to do so about two teaspoons
so you can do a couple things you can
use the measuring I'm going to squeeze
the
lemon and gauge it that way for me I've
done it so many times over the years I'm
going to get about 2 tpoon of lemon
lemon juice on here is what I'm going to
do there we
go a lemon seed went in and I'm going to
grab that lemon seed real quick get it
out don't you hate what that
happens what if you have a sulfur
allergy sulfur allergy is different than
what's in a radish so that's not the
same sulfur so the sulfur um for for
sulfur allergy is a whole different
chemical a whole different element it's
a whole different compound it's a
different chemical compound um this is
this we're made out of sulfur we're made
out of sulfur from plant material like
we're made out of sulf that's what's in
all vegetables that's what's in all
fruit all herbs I'm drinking some
traditional medicinal tea right now so
I'm drinking some tea I got some nettle
leaf tea in the moment okay and um
there's sulfur in the nettle Leaf so
whatever herb you've ever had you know
have you had lemon bomb nettle Leaf
peppermint Peppermint's got sulfur in it
it's it's it's the fundamental basis of
life so that's not the same sulfur
chemical compounds that you'd be
allergic to um that's a whole different
that's a whole different kind of thing
this is something that's in food
entirely
different um so if you've been told that
you're allergic to a vegetable or a
radish
that can happen out there well they'll
tell you you know you get testing for
food testing it's totally messed up it's
totally backwards in so many ways and
the problem is with all those tests is
whoever created them doesn't know why
anybody's sick so here we go we're going
to tell somebody don't eat the radish
don't eat this don't eat a strawberry
don't eat an apple don't eat cilantro
don't eat this this this don't have
asparagus you know you're sensitive to
asparagus they'll say on the test don't
have cucumber knock that off the test
don't have lemon that's bad you and
they'll do this thing where now you're
just stuck with some meat and some
chicken and then they'll give you
something odd to eat like you'll be able
to eat like uh you'll be able to eat
like a zucchini or something they'll
give you like a few things to eat and
now you're totally stuck you're like you
have 50 things they say you're you know
you're sensitive to and meanwhile these
foods are the foods that are helping you
heal a problem that they're not
detecting and that happens with food
allergy testing
food sensitivity testing now it's
different if you're really allergic
where you eat an asparagus and now you
can't breathe or something and your
throat closes well then you're allergic
to an asparagus pressing Prince hey good
to see you um you love to eat radishes
and you love eating their leaves too in
salads incredible incredible yeah I the
radish leaves are really healing in
salads too you put those in your salads
that's an amazing thing to do so I got
the lemon in there so I want to put a
little garlic
powder um but here's the thing you know
what what people don't realize is that
people don't realize is that you don't
when you don't know why someone's sick
it's easy to just mess things up so you
tell somebody hey you're allergic to
these 20 Foods you're allergic to celery
you're allergic to Strawberry you're
allergic to Apple and you tell and it's
like what you don't even know why
they're sick you don't even know what's
wrong with them um you know it's it's
it's when it's a rash they don't even
know what causes a r here's the thing if
you eat a food that you're really
allergic to and you get a rash right
that second or your stomach gets really
crazyer funnier T right in that second
then you might have a sensitivity to
that food you know but like if it's like
really really Intense or something but
other than that you know nothing happens
you eat a piece of radish and nothing
happens you know you eat an asparagus
and nothing happens and even
then and even then what you know what
people don't realize is that you know
rashes like from eczema rashes from
psoriasis vitiligo rosacea they're viral
so these are viral things and IBS is
strepto coctus it's bacterial
and sometimes you'll eat some foods and
you're cleaning all that up and you
might see some rashes come and go but
that's different that's different than
eating a strawberry and then your throat
swells up or something and you break out
in hives or something that's that's
different you know it's an entirely
different thing that's when someone
actually has a real food allergy or
something you know when they experience
it in that very second their throat
swells up or something and you know like
with peanuts like with peanuts something
like that so um other than that I know
that so many people they don't have food
allergies to their foods and they're
just they're just told got to eat them
so they don't eat a radish they never
try it they don't eat a piece of
eggplant they don't have a cucumber they
don't have anything and um and people
get hives all the time but it's not from
the healthy foods they're eating so
anyway I want to mix this
up is what I'm going to do so I'm going
to mix this potato salad
[Music]
up lot of people have chemical
sensitivities out there a lot of people
have chemical sensitivity because
they're they got the Epstein bar virus
they're they got lots of metals in their
system and between the Epstein bar virus
and metals that alone can give somebody
so many chemical sensitivities they
become sensitive to everything as far as
chemical wise so that's important to
know they'll get hives because of
chemical sensitivities that's really
important there I just mixed up this
dish it's incredible dish it's the
healing potato salad can you guys see it
at all how good can you see it I'm not
sure
but that's it right there Lena says my
stomach hurt every time I ate and I
thought it was normal eating this way I
don't experience any pain or bloating
incredible I'm so proud of you that
you're eating so good you're eating this
way um Barbara says love this show made
made mine made ma your Saturday
incredible makes my Saturday that you
guys are all here
um how do we get your book of recipes
well 45 recipes I put in this revised
and Expanded Edition you guys I put a
book in this book this is at amazon.com
this is the medical medium Secrets
behind chronic and mystery illness and
how to finally heal now this isn't the
there there this isn't the original book
this is the new edition so you have to
look and you'll see revised and expanded
this is the new edition on Amazon link
is in profile link is in description so
just so you know and you'll see the gold
emblem on there that tells you I don't
know if you see it there I'm not sure
what the lights like today but this is
the book right here 45 recipes basically
it's a recipe book I mean it's 45
recipes in here but it's so much more
than that there's conditions there's
symptoms there's supplements dosages
there's an angel chapter I added
additional essential Angels additional
meditations in here um there's the meal
plan expanded on that EXP B on the
28-day cleanse so seriously this is such
a powerful book and I talk about the
pandemic I talk about the plague up like
updated This Book Like No Other so this
is really great I put a book inside this
book so that's awesome and then look
cleanse the heel 75 recipes in cleanse
the heel it's a medical textbook so you
got these options so they're there for
you that's that's the whole point but
I'm excited about the potato salad it's
going to be delicious
so Karen says what book do you recommend
for chemical sensitivities I recommend
cleanse the heel so if I open up cleanse
the
heel right
here
um so if I open up cleanse the heel I
don't know if you can see this but it's
going to say chemical and food
sensitivities for some reason the
lighting is doing something weird
today um chemical and food sensitivities
and I talk about the true cause of
chemical sensitivities the true cause of
food sensitivities and I talk about what
to do for it everything I mean this book
right here just has that right in here
it's over 200 symptoms and conditions in
this book so I'm excited about
this um so this is a recipe that's
helpful for the digestion it's it's easy
on the system there's no fat in this
recipe so it's important to know not to
put oil in your potato salad in this
recipe don't put oil in there there
don't put nut Butters in there don't
throw Chicken in there has nothing to do
whether if I like animal protein or I
like vegan diets or animal protein diets
has nothing to do with that it's just
this recipe is meant to help heal the
liver help you gently cleanse out toxins
and poisons keep you strong so it's a
really good powerful recipe right there
I'm reading some questions right here do
you like mustard powder better than
using
mustard well when you use mustard you
got to remember there's vinegar in there
so keep that in mind and vinegar is a
problem so vinegar can really be a
problem it's it's it's highly agitating
to the liver it's irritating to the
liver um and that's a whole another
story so and mustard pow unless it's a
mustard recipe for medical medium maybe
my blog medical mem.com at the blog and
it's a mustard recipe that's another
story but mustards out there in the
little squeezy bottles it's got vinegar
in there so you got to look out for that
and that's a big issue I see a question
here Karen my Eczema is flaring up after
eight months of 369 is that part of the
healing process are you doing eight
months of 369 the whole time is you
taking breaks what are you eating in
between
369 is it the 369 Advanced or 369
uh simplified 369 original 369 Advanced
are you doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie at all because eczema is caused
by two things it's caused by the epine
bar in combination with copper inside
the liver so that's copper inside the
liver so are you doing anything to get
the copper out of the liver because
until the copper completely comes out of
the liver then you're free so are you
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie um
are you doing any of the antio antiviral
protocols so when I look at cleanse to
heel and I look at
eczema and you can take this to your
doctor and you can ALS or healthc care
provider or health coach or whoever's in
whoever's in charge of your health care
um you can take this to them but when I
look into eczema I'm going to find it
here
um so exoman psoriasis including rosacea
lupus style rashes and some other things
too some in here right now okay um and
I'm looking I'm seeing supplements and
dosages
so some people can get rid of their
eczema by just doing the 369 after a
week or two right and their eczema
starts to clear up some people can get
rid of their eczema doing the mono
eating cleanse some people get rid of
their eczema by just you doing the 28
day cleanse like like in the medical
medium book here but it all depends some
people have more copper inside their
liver causing the eczema some people end
up having two or three varieties of
Epstein bar inside their liver so or
they'll get exposed and get another
epsteam bar three years after they got
their eczema better and then three years
later they pick up another viral uh a
viral load and then they're you know
they they end up getting something else
but you have to have copper inside the
liver in order to have eczema and So
when you buy new clothing brand new
clothing there's copper in the fungus
side
and you know they sell copper clothing
now right you know copper clothing type
stuff where they got copper weaved into
clothing now and stuff like that socks
and other things and all that highly
toxic because that's copper that gets in
our system they um and then fungicides
pesticides everything scented candles
have copper in it um air fresheners it
all depends on your exposures too so I
talked about so I talked this about a
doctor recently about ezim and psoriasis
and people get new exposures too they'll
get scented candle exposure and then a
month later they end up getting a flare
or they'll get air freshener exposure
and they'll get a flare or cologne
exposure so perfume in Cologne exposure
I've seen people order new clothes the
new clothes come they try them on and
they got perfume on them from somebody
else trying them on and all of a sudden
it flares things up because perfume
cologne have copper in them copper is a
heavy metal toxic heavy metal used in
perfume clones scented candles
pesticides herbicides fungicides air
fresheners and everybody should be
complaining to all these companies
because we're just they just they're
just contaminating everybody but so
there's a couple things you could do you
can go to your practitioner doctor and
you can look at the supplements too for
examon orasis you could be like well am
I doing all these am I doing some of
these and so and that's what's in here
so I don't know if you guys could see
that it's kind of Whiting out on there
um but the whole thing is that when you
look here when you look here you can
start out with you read the supplement
chapter in cleans the heel and you can
read like the information you can try a
few different supplements for it you can
go to your practitioner and see if your
practitioner wants you to try more and
then it and then you're doing the heavy
metal detox smoothie too so when you go
in here there's a heavy metal
detox um smoothie in here the reason for
that is to get the copper out so when
that when it comes down to that you got
like the vimergy spirulina the barley
grass cheese powder in the heavy metal
detox smoothie I talked about that the
other day and when you get out when you
get out the copper then you get you get
you know you move forward you move
forward and then the supplementations
for the ant that's the whole antiviral
thing too but also if you're doing the
369 or you doing it how's how's the
process going like are you doing
caffeine at all in between it did you
have chocolate in between chocolate is
the eczema instigator so if you had
chocolate a month ago you can end up
with a cycle of eczema a month later cuz
it's an instigator because it jacks up
the adrenals and the adrenals push out
copper everywhere that's in your liver
so any kind of caffeine any kind of
chocolate any kind of tea any kind of
coffee drinks um these are just some of
the things are you staying away from
vinegar are you staying away from
nutritional yeast uh make sure no eggs
get in the diet between the 369 and
maybe you're doing a 369 8 months
straight and nothing's getting in so you
got to try some of those other things
I'm talking about um you can talk to
your practitioner but I'm trying to give
you any
insight um to make sure that you know
you get every chance to recover like so
many millions have with exim mons orias
um or you under a lot of stress stress
triggers the adrenals when the adrenals
are flooding the heart rate goes up the
adrenaline pushes out old storage bins
of copper deeper out of the liver and
now you got a little bit of a flare up
that's how it works so um it just
happens anyway um but you're in the
healing process you're doing all the
right things and you just keep you can
go further you can go a little bit
further and that's how it's set up so
you can go as far farther as you need to
go guys I'm going to be on Tik Tok
around
5:30 uh 2:30 Pacific Time 5:30 East
Coast time I'm going to be on Tik Tok
and I'm going to make a new
recipe that's the recipe I'm going to
make right there and it's the potato
cauliflower mash and I'm going to be on
Tik tock
exactly 2:30 Pacific
5:30 East Coast time okay um at Medical
medium on Tik Tok just letting you know
and I'm going to make the potato
cauliflower mash a a recipe I've never
made for you guys a recipe you haven't
seen it's a recipe in the new edition
revised and expanded medical medium book
so I'm letting you guys
know but before I go to Tik Tok I'm
heading to ig and I'm going to make the
potato dish all over again on IG maybe
talk and answer different questions so
that's what I'm going to do so there's
potato salad I'm excited I'm actually
going to eat this later um but I'm going
to head to ig pretty soon just going to
straighten up and I'll see you there if
you guys want to come with me um take
care and hope I see you on Tik Tok if I
don't see you on IG because I'm making
that new recipe on Tik Tok can't wait
bye guys love you