it's real medical medium heavy metal
detox launch party at Iran in La at
Culver City I'm going to be there
signing books bring your book bring your
book your favorite book medical medium
book and I'm going to sign it right
there going to say hi to everybody all
of that there going to be like meet and
greet people are going to be coming from
all over the world to come there it's
going to be insane it's going to be
incredible it's going to be June 15th
June 15th that's right this year I'm G
to be there in per person and there's
going to even be like some free gifts
and stuff we're going to do that we
might be able to do some other stuff too
who knows it's going to be crazy I'm
excited register go to medicalmedium.com
medicalmedium.com
register and guess what it's free yep my
favorite words are coming out of my
mouth right now free free free for free
free free for free free free for free
free totally free that's what's
incredible okay that means you don't
have to buy a ticket you don't have to
buy a 200 300 $400 ticket to enter it's
going to be the medical medium heavy
metal detox launch party collaboration
with irwan and irwan is putting the
heavy metal detox smoothie on the menu
right there in their stores made fresh
and I can't wait cuz I want to be the
first one to get get one and Maybe not
maybe I'll be the last one to get one
either way you guys I'm excited it's
real it's happening it all came together
it's just when things come together when
they just come together right and it
just falls in the place when things just
fall into the place and it feels really
good when it all just falls in the place
you know that feeling do you ever have
that well it happened it happened this
time with this so I'm excited you're
excited too incredible also
just so you know though you know
register register go to you know
medicalmedium.com and register okay link
is in the profile link is in the
description so make sure you do that
that would be awesome I am excited I
hope you guys are just excited seriously
I'm going to be there in person in
person first time in almost a decade how
crazy is that people can now
conveniently get their heavy metal detox
smoothie at Iran when this happens start
ing June
15th unbelievable and like I said I'm
going to be there in person going to say
hi the whole bit okay bring your book
your favorite book bring your family
bring whoever you want to bring I'm
excited give me some free gifts and I
might even do something else there
something else that happens we just take
one day at a time but right now it's
solidified it's solid we're doing it
June 15th you guys today I'm talking
about freeing your brain and body of
toxins and one of my my favorite topics
of all time Mercury aluminum copper
heavy metals toxic heavy metals all of
it I want to cut into this a little bit
so I'm excited seriously though you guys
I mean aren't you excited as well cuz
this is going to be really fun check it
out but go to medicalmedium.com if you
can all right go to medical medium.com
and check it out there because you can
you can uh
register so I'm excited let's get down
to it let's get into the information a
little bit I want to talk about some
metals never before in our history and
I'm reading right here at a new edition
right here at a new bring the new
addition bring this
one never before in our history have we
been exposed to so many poisonous
substances and that's true never before
in our history have we been exposed like
this this includes the toxic heavy
metals Mercury aluminum copper lead
nickel cadan arsenic
that's right and more air pollution such
as Chemtrails pharmaceutical narot
technology chemical sprayed on almost
everything manufactured pesticides
herbicides fungicides blah blah blah you
know the drill you know how many poisons
and toxins there are you guys know it's
serious it's real out there people are
getting exposed every single day and
metals get passed down from generation
to generation so I'm going to talk about
the Mercury man and a little bit more in
here too these poisons saturate our
water or reservoirs they find their way
in from the coffee you get at the coffee
shop they find their way in they fall
out of the sky the majority of these
substances are so new that it'll take
decades before science recognizes how
dangerous they are to our health that's
way when you hear people go glycate gate
or they go you know and they go from
alide from Malahide or they go you know
something else right and they think
they're onto the like the the the scary
chemical the scariest poison and they
think they're on to it and then it
becomes the buzz word whatever it is
there's way more than that and the
industry knows this and knows it and
they're like you guys worry about yeah
you worry about those yeah you guys keep
your eyes on that and the decoys you
know they're bad the decoys don't get me
wrong but you guys keep a little watch
on the
decoys and then the real scary stuff
nobody knows about they keep that stuff
top secret
classified seriously people have no idea
there's chemicals that are in things
that just AR you don't know because it's
in it and no one's talking about it and
no one's going to like look at that
chemical analiz it they don't even know
it exists because if you don't know it
exists you can't test for it then you
can't find it you see how it
works that's how it works they can take
new chemicals a whole batch of them but
if they don't know what that new
chemical is
they can't find it test for it and find
it how crazy is that how crazy is that
it's only if they know what they're
looking for like the chemical was
registered the chemical was put out
there and if it was registered put out
there and then they took samples of it
and they brought it to the agencies and
everybody knew what that thing was and
they knew it and they can actually tag
it and understand it so then they can
look for it but that's the whole thing
you guys don't know there's all these
chemicals that research and Science and
all that environmentalists don't know
about nobody knows about but instead
they focus on DET
decoy chemicals to give them a detour
that's how it is and even the decoy ones
are bad but the point is is there's so
many other ones out there so I just
wanted to mention that because I haven't
mentioned that yet I don't think in a
long
time the majority of these substances
are so new that it'll take decades
before science recognizes them that's
the whole point you can't recognize them
until someone registers it they know
what it is it's got its patent number
rigged it's ready they get a test sample
they can say well who I've never seen
that let's actually Mark that one and
now we know we can look for it in the
water system we can look for it in
somebody's coffee we can look for it in
somebody's drug we can look for it
somewhere but you can't look for it if
you don't know where it is and what it
is you don't know what it is and can't
identify and that's how many thousands
of these chemicals are out there that's
how much exposure people
have I took my celery force
today and those risks will only be
discovered if funding in common sense go
in the right direction we know how that
works which is unlikely most Industries
M Mo their MO is to put chemicals into
our environment and deal with the
consequences down the road you put the
bad stuff out 50 years down the road
something gets discovered somehow
someway or talked about and then boom
most of us are carrying around toxins
that have been with us for almost their
whole lives and have burrowed deep
inside of us I just saw somebody it's
this one right here just so you know
it's medical medium New Edition right in
my hands Incredible Book it's saved so
many lives around the world so many
people people getting out of wheelchairs
because they got answers to why they
were suffering their pain and all of the
all the hell they've been through Chris
over there um I'm bringing my friend
that's a doctor and he drinks celery
juice now too thank you you just
reminded me to sip some of my celery
juice Amanda Stefani says I registered
just now I'm so excited whoa I can't
wait I'll see you there whoa mhm I'm
excited to see you there that's
amazing toxic heavy metals for example
can oxidize overtime and kill cells
around them so I want to give you guys a
little bit of that de
demonstration let's bring this out for a
minute let's look for some markers
really quick let's
go all
right so you got your brain
right okay got your brain right
here got a little bit of the midline
canal right there see the midline
canal little bit of art happening
okay all right and then you got your
Metals you got your metal deposits that
got in here from birth from both the
parents passed on down from exposures
antibiotics loaded with toxic heavy
metals of all kinds right so we got the
metal deposits right here okay let's
make a nice big metal deposit right
there let's get it to Glow a little bit
maybe we could use some paint maybe you
can see it maybe not there we go and
then let's do another deposit somewhere
else cuz I want to show you guys this is
a
brain yep that's a
brain all
right okay here's what happens okay over
time in everybody's head some faster
some slower in everybody's head over
time oxidation happen happens to the
toxic heavy metals Mercury aluminum
copper mainly those three and oxidation
occurs and when oxidation occurs
it leeches and that leeching comes out
of those deposits you see this right
here and there's a lot of things that
make the metals leech fast really really
high fat diet makes the metals leech
more okay that's just an example right
there and I I'll cover some other things
that make it leech more as well
adrenaline doesn't help that's for sure
and a lot of people are jacked up all
the time they're high on their caffeine
and everything else I'm not blaming
anybody or judging anybody so these
metal deposits right here are
leeching and guess what happens when
they leech when they leech we end up
getting
dementia over time we end up losing our
memory okay our memory we end up getting
episodes and
spells we get a lot of symptoms even if
it's not diagnosed as
dementia
okay so as these leech these metal
deposits right here some Mercury
leeching there's some aluminum oxidizing
there's some Alloys of mercury aluminum
and copper there's some copper oxidizing
right here okay you see this here
right there we
go so it's leeching now here's what
happens when it leeches it leeches into
adjacent tissue when it starts to leech
into adjacent T tissue we start getting
in big trouble because then it's
spreading it's spreading into neuron to
neuron to neuron and that's what toxic
heavy metals do over time as we live our
life the metals move they oxidize and
they move and they start to spread and
as they're spreading right as they're
spreading they're leech they're leeching
they're oxidizing they're out gassing
that's what's happening they're out
gassing and we end up getting in trouble
so now tissue is actually being
destroyed brain cells gal cells neurons
are being affected metals are leeching
they're oxidizing and they're branching
over into gleo cells into other brain
tissue exactly and into neurons when
that happens our OCD heightens even our
PTSD heightens our bipolar heightens our
depersonalization heightens our anxiety
heightens our depression heightens those
are just some okay our schizophrenia
heightens yes everything our Neurosis
our psychosis anything else starts to
advance itself right and so that's an
example right there also other symptoms
too we're going to go into autoimmune a
little bit all kinds of other stuff
around that how that works
Christine I've been drinking you're over
there on Facebook I've been drinking the
heavy metal detox smoothie for 3 years
every day it has been a game Cher as my
thinking is so much more clear that is
the most powerful metal remover there is
safely and effectively gently without
the side effects that's what that is
from Spirit of compassion
that heavy metal detox smoothie is
saving lives around the world it has
been for a very very long time I'm so
glad you're using it the heavy metal
detox is powerful and you don't have to
have it in a smoothie just so you know
you can have it in a bowl you can have
it on your salad you can have it many
different ways as long as you're getting
three out of the five ingredients that
are key but try to do five because
that's the most powerful way of doing it
you can separate the ingredients through
throughout the day and you can have the
five ingredients starting from the
beginning of the day all the way to the
end of the day you can do it that way
but that's the heavy metal detox it's
powerful it's lifechanging it's saving
lives out there so let's talk about
Metals a little bit longer and so glad
you mention that if you guys just got
here I made an announcement at the very
beginning it's real get ready I'm going
to be live June 15th in La at irwan with
a collaboration that the heavy metal
detox movie that's going to be there
made fresh it's going to be the heavy
metal detox launch party you don't want
to miss it it's going to be some free
gifts there and stuff like that I'm
going to say hi to everybody it's going
to be incredible and I'm going to be
doing the book signing bring your book
I'd love to sign it I'd love to meet you
in person I don't know if I'm ever going
to do an official book signing again
it's the first official medical medium
book signing ever ever in the medical
medium book series or any books that
I've ever put out um like I never did a
book signing ever crispy perspective
says drinking my hmds now awesome over
there on YouTube so what happens with
metals like Mercury aluminum copper they
corrode they outgas they leech they out
poock and they damage and destroy brain
cells like Leal cells and neurons and
they spread they actually spread to
other tissue two other neurons and as
they're doing it you're wondering why
you're sad you're wondering why you're
forgetting fulness is kicking in you
wonder why you can't explain this deep
deep sadness you can't explain these
feelings of depression you're getting a
a a serious depression like a serious
serious debilitating depression so many
people get that that's really terrible
the heavy metals do that and then you're
getting other problems too OCD bipolar
anxiety right depersonalization Sherry
over there on YouTube says hmds got rid
of my
migraines just that alone just that
alone here you are Sherry suffering with
migraines okay and I'm sure you've been
here and there and tried that and this
and that I'm sure you have and that line
alone heavy metal detox smoothie got rid
of my migraines that is everything if
you're suffering from migraines there
I've seen a lot of people throughout the
years suffer from migraines and metals
can create migraines toxic heavy metals
can create the worst debilitating
migraines keeping people held back so
they can't move forward with their lives
they can't do anything with their lives
because they're stuck they're stuck in
migraine hell and that right there I
love hearing that Sherry seriously over
there on YouTube got rid of my migraines
if you have been helped by the heavy
metal detox smoothie okay or the medical
medium heavy metal detox or the medical
medium heavy metal detox cleanse share
your stories tag medical medium in your
stories okay and your posts all right #
and tag medical medium so that I can see
it I would love to see your stories how
has the hmds helped you how has the
heavy metal detox helped you how has
even parts of the heavy metal detox
helped you like just three parts of it
like say the barley grass juice powder
and this incredible spirina and the
cilantro even if it's three out of five
how has it helped you I would love to
hear your stories about the heavy metal
detox the original heavy metal detox
John deas over there on YouTube I put
all my hmds ingredients and a melon or
papaya smart I love that and so do I I
do the same thing I put all my hmds
ingredients heavy metal detox
ingredients right I put them all in a
papaya a lot of times I put them in a
melon a lot of times I love it John spot
on and I'm so so glad you're doing that
incredible out there in this world right
now there's somebody waking up somewhere
from a nap or a miserable night's sleep
or any kind of night's sleep and they're
suffering and struggling when they wake
up they got debilitating brain fog they
got OCD they got depersonalization they
got depression they got anxiety they're
on anxiety meds they're on depression
meds and they're struggling they've been
to a lot of doctors they spent a lot of
money thousands upon thousands of
dollars they bought a lot of courses
from coaches and and different
chiropractors and doctors and different
doctors of chiropractor Dr dos and and
naturopaths and MDS and all kinds of
different people in in the world of
medicine they bought programs they
bought they did classes they didn't get
the answers they needed they still wake
up the next morning and they're
suffering suffering all over again and
then they're back to it again and then
they do more they they get courses from
herbalists courses from other health
coaches and they're back to suffering
again back all over again they wake up
in the morning they got their depression
their anxiety their depersonalization
their bipolar their OCD their
nervousness their sadness their pain
their migraines their debilitating
fatigue and so forth they're just
hurting every day it happens every
morning someone wakes up or wakes up
from their nap struggling and the
madness and the sickness is not gone
it's still there and they spent a lot of
money they've gone to 20 doctors and
they're still struggling every single
day there are millions of these people
around the world and only if they knew
only if they knew how it works that
toxic heavy metals are interfering with
their quality of life how they sit in
the brain how they turn into an outy how
they outp poet and actually spread and
out and out get G and leech and then
spread tell their tissue and create
their symptoms if they only knew this
and they only knew how to get those
Metals out so they can heal and recover
and move forward if they only knew
Lindsay says over there on YouTube hmds
freed me from severe dep
personalization PTSD and depression
saved my life that alone is just
incredible truly incredible okay um Kath
over there an IG Twitches are gone after
doing it every single day why because
toxic heavy metals are responsible for
tourettes Twitches spasms mysterious
spasms and twitches and
ticks yep okay golden seal over there
hmds got rid of my anxiety boom got
rid of my depression boom gone among
many other symptoms it is a life sa
savior Lifesaver incredible all right
over there on IG just drank my smoothie
it's clearing up my rosacea over there
on IG these things matter these things
matter okay over there strength over
there by Jennifer on IG heavy metal
detox smoothie cleared my son's eczema
and my chronic GI issues my whole family
does the morning cleanse and have been
doing it for five years five years five
years five years incredible it blows my
mind blows my
mind Alex over there on IG the brain
saver heavy metal detox cleanse is a
game Cher when it comes to clearing
heads space from OCD repetitive thoughts
dark thoughts in other headspace issues
I'll tell you I want to go into that a
little bit because that's a big deal so
many people suffer from dark thoughts
negative thoughts dark thoughts they're
suffering and struggling Heavy Metal the
heavy metal detox helps to get rid of
these symptoms helps to clear these
symptoms I remember many years helping
people right one on-one okay for many
years thousands of people throughout the
decades right many times people came to
me and they were like well I've been to
every doctor I don't know why I have
these dark thoughts I've been to every
single practitioner I don't know why I'm
so sick and I'm suffering this way and I
have these repetitive thoughts and I've
been to spiritual healers and I tried
the
iasa and it didn't work I went to
another spiritual healer and I tried the
toad poison and it didn't work I went to
another spiritual healer and they told
me it was because I have like some past
life problem okay and so it didn't fix
it I went to another healer and they
told me that it's my fault and it's cuz
I'm not a happy person and it didn't fix
it and I'm suffering with the OCD the
dark thoughts repetitive thoughts I'm
struggling and I'd be like you know why
you know
why the medals we got to get the medals
out we got to get the medals out that is
the key right there okay Jen over there
on IG hmds say healed anxiety panic
attacks panic attacks are brutal Vegas
nerve
issues and
Optical
and optical nerve over stimulation optic
nerve over stimulation while driving
okay one thing that happens with a lot
of people okay the cranial nerves get
affected with toxic heavy metals really
easy I'm they can't drive they got panic
attacks their nerves are overs
stimulated that's hell to live like that
it's really difficult so sorry you
actually have gone through that I'm
really sorry because that is brutal and
people don't realize it unless they were
there unless they experienced that then
if they experienced it they would be
like oh my God and then you find out
that no one understands you're
misunderstood No One Believes you
happens all the time out there very
difficult life when you're living with
those symptoms so I'm just really proud
of you you're working on it you're
healing you healed it all incredible
Jess sang Hey Jess thanks for always
leaving a comment on YouTube you're on
YouTube right now hmds saved me in so
many ways OCD depression anxiety and
more am I going to see you over there in
LA June
15th all right so Dian says yes my
migraine stopped immediately after 50
years what as soon as I started celery
juice in the heavy metal detox smoothie
did several 369
too for 50 years you were
suffering and I'm sure you tried things
in 50 years I'm sure you tried this and
I'm sure you tried that I'm sure you
tried things and then you do the celery
juice and the heavy metal detox and boom
you got relief exactly that's how s so
wanted it that that's why this is the
original that's why the heavy metal
detox is incredible the one that Iran is
going to be making fresh every single
day starting June 15th at the launch
party I will be there I'm excited I
can't believe it I actually can't
believe it can't believe it I haven't
done anything like this in in like
almost a decade I haven't done a book
signing ever thousands have already
registered for the event I hear I hear
some out there thousands have registered
already to the event and guess what my
favorite word favorite word okay you
don't have to buy a ticket for $100 or
$200 to get
in so I can sign your book you don't
have to because it's free free free it's
free and I'm going to be there and I'm
excited to say hi I actually can't
believe it I am pumped all right let's
move in into this a little bit we know
what we know how it works Metals get
passed down from generation to
generation they sit inside of us in
older Metals mm info all this metal info
is MM info I mean just going back like
even six years
ago six years ago podcast doctors
weren't talking about metals they were
talking about eating better processed
foods I don't know if you guys remember
but back in 2018 17 16 15 all you would
here is just about eating better and
stay away from processed foods I don't
know if you guys remember that right
nobody knew that mercury caused anxiety
and depression nobody knew that copper
and aluminum caused you know all kinds
of different issues nobody knew that
ecem was caused by copper in the liver
all medical medium information and what
happened was the books got out and this
book right here millions of this book
got out around the world and this
chapter right here blew people away and
they learned how to do the heavy metal
detox and when they learned how to do it
they healed
and when they healed they spread the
word and guess what someone else got the
book and healed and someone else got the
book and healed right and then it got
around and everybody was like ho ho ho
all the health coaches and the podcast
doctors and everybody they were all like
wait a minute wait a minute I keep on
hearing heavy metal detox everywhere I
keep on hearing heavy metal and
everybody want hop on the bandwagon they
all want to sell their heavy metal
detoxes and create all kinds of stuff
and that's what's happened now but the
one that works is the one with the
street cred the one that actually has
healed people around the world kids do
the heavy metal detox popsicles they get
it in that way and it changes lives and
Family's lives it's incredible hey guys
you know how it works I'm going to give
you more information too I want to talk
about with
this powerful information over there in
IG at
35 two pregnancies hmds helped with
anxiety eye twitches floaters eye
floaters oh yeah restless leg syndrome
oh that's brutal right pains in the body
depersonalization and help me find
purpose in life feel like a baby now
incredible when you get the heavy metal
detox in medical medium heavy metal
detox and you pull that stuff out and
you drive that stuff out and it comes
out of the body life changes over there
in IG freedom is your hands that's
that's your handle that's a cool handle
hmd has healed me emotionally Made Me
Stronger I using all ingredients for
three and a half years every day never
stopping thank you mm heart heart heart
heart back to you okay incredible
another one right here Soul Purpose with
Sarah over here in IG heavy metal detox
saved me from OCD anxiety and forgetting
you got guys know if you've ever
suffered from OCD brutal anxiety Vertigo
Vertigo is awful I'm registered in and
hotel booked to travel from Michigan to
California Culver City see you there see
you there I'll sign your book bring your
book bring your book and I'll sign
it bring your favorite medical medium
book anyway what does this
mean what does this
mean it means people heal and they get
through it and they get out of their
vertigo and they get out of their
anxiety and their depersonalization and
their OCD and their depression and their
pain and suffering migraines and their
eczema that's everything that's why I
wake up in the morning medical medium
mommy best thing in the world was
Finding mm info 6 years with my son on
MM autism protocol for my
son I bow to you I bow to you
truly truly a
hero
incredible all right we're going into
some metal talk let's talk a little bit
more I'm talking about how the metals
move and how they contaminate more
tissue gleo cells neurons and they
contaminate as they move the metals move
and they cause problems that's what
happens to people it's really difficult
and then guess what your symptoms crank
up everything cranks up it gets very
difficult gets very hard and that's what
people go through and that is not easy
not easy at all all right let's move a
little bit through the
information all right let's go Mercury
for close to 2 200 years wait got
another comment check this out on IG
Barry gvy girl cool handle the hmds has
helped relieve me of anxiety and panic
attacks
now I use it to protect me against the
fragrances I'm exposed to every day
that's acting as pathogenic fuel well
here's what happens when you know
information by the way um that's really
powerful okay really powerful so um
Julia check this out when you're using
metals like that in those when you're
using heavy metal detox smoothie like
that and metals are getting into your
system
from that exposure those fragrances and
so forth those fragrances become fresh
they become fresh in the bloodstream and
the heavy metal detox smoothie is doing
two things at that point it's removing
the fresh exposure the metals that come
with the fragrance fragrances and
everything it's removing the fresh
Metals out of the bloodstream so they
don't enter and stay and make homes
right you guys and then the other aspect
of the heavy metal detox is removing old
stuff old stuff passed down from
generation to generation to generation
and it's grabbing onto that and pulling
that out but it's doing two things it's
eating up exposure so that's what
happens so here's our brain right
here and then here's brand new exposure
okay so now you're somebody you're
exposed you're breathing in fragrances
and that exposure and that fragrance is
is just floating around okay that's a
good color for fragrances by the way
it's a very good color
all
right and then we're breathing in right
here those fragrances those fragrances
are entering in the sinus cavities the
bloodstream they're entering
in and they're getting into the brain
and body when you're doing the heavy
metal detox every day you're
absorbing and sucking all that up out of
the bloodstream new exposure and you're
getting rid of the new exposure because
here's what happens to everybody the new
exposure adds to the old
exposure so let's talk about
that the new exposure adds to the old
exposure any new exposure from
pesticides herbicides fungicides from
fire okay retardant from all kinds of
stuff that people are up against every
single day from formal theid to
chemicals that are pumping out of the
walls of houses and apartments to Lawns
being treated and sprayed to
insecticides falling out of the sky when
they do mosquito spraying all of it is
entering into our bodies because that's
life here on planet Earth we can't
change that planet Earth but that's
what's happening and as we're breathing
all that in it's going into our
bloodstream and if we're not being
proactive if we're not doing the heavy
metal detox and we're not taking care of
ourselves that enters into our organs
like the brain and then it joins in with
metal pre previously there metal finds
metal metal looks for Metal By the way
metal loves metal that's what it does
Pockets get bigger and bigger and bigger
they expand more more more more exposure
Comes In Pockets get bigger more
exposure Comes In Pockets get bigger
over time you don't know where you are
you don't know who you are there's a
rise of all kinds of things is happening
not just brain fog but a rise of like
memory loss and everything else where
people are having episodes they don't
even know people are walking down the
street their underwear now they have no
idea what they're doing that's happening
because of years of this expansion of
pockets getting bigger metals never
coming out nobody's doing the heavy
metal detox in that situation and
they're not getting the stuff out
cristelle over there on YouTube had CT
scan today and picking up ingredients
for radiation exposure brain shot I love
that brain shot it's an incredible brain
shot it's reassuring and empowering
beyond words to know what to do with
things that come up in life thank you aw
thank you for being here truly you guys
I'm excited Melanie good to see you hmds
helps us to survive on this dark planet
indeed I agree for for close to 2500
years man tried to claim that mercury
was the Fountain of Youth did you guys
know that Mercury was the Fountain of
Youth it was called the ultimate cure
for all disease you felt sick drink
Mercury eat
Mercury it's pretty crazy okay the
secret to living forever that was the
longevity secret it was Mercury did you
know that and the source for Eternal
wisdom was Mercury oh yeah that's right
source for the Eternal wisdom in ancient
Chinese medicine Mercury was so revered
that countless Emperors died for mercury
Elixir that healers vowed would end all
their problems which I guess you could
say they did if you take a morbid view
of
things but they've been using mercury
worldwide everywhere Mercury wasn't only
favored medicine in East Asia all
throughout England England that's
right and the rest of Europe Mercury
Elixir were celebrated Big Time Mercury
was the thing Mercury concoctions were
celebrated Max Max vond over there on
YouTube it really is
empowering I love that it really is
empowering right Matt Hatters Anna Matt
Hatter yep Sherry my dad who is 86 just
started hmds and loves the taste it is
protecting his memory it's incredible
that it tastes so good too it's
incredible I know people are throwing
all kinds of different heavy metal detox
Elixir out there now everybody wants
their own brandom one and they're
throwing a bunch of stuff in there so
they want you know they want to put
their own crap in there and you taste it
and you're just like you just vomit it
out meanwhile it's not even getting
Metals out of people okay Debbie Gail
coaching over there on YouTube the
advanced hmds has been game changer for
my rosi here's what I love about it
here's what I love about the medical
medium heavy metal detox cleanse and
heavy metal detox here's what I love
about it it works you know what else I
love about it it works I love one more
thing about it by the way it works and
has and it has street cred and it has a
track record and that right there says
everything Nancy over there on YouTube
hmds Every Single Day save my life so
grateful explanation point just taught
another friend all mm yesterday so
wonderful to share thank you thank you
thank you for actually telling a friend
and helping them that's why I'm here so
they get help Shen 777 that's a really
good number right there 777 that's a
good one 144
777 hmds got rid of my panic attacks and
debilitating anxiety thank you aw and so
people don't understand debilitating
anxiety unless they experienced it it's
another level I don't understand how
like a pin drops and on the ground and
you're literally suffering people don't
get it Loop is free with celery
333 the beginning 333 hmds rid me of
fear and
insecurities I can speak my mind and be
free of the negative inside voice wow
incredible
okay and then Facebook Stephanie fera
hmds got rid of of my ticks and foggy
thinking been drinking it for over three
years ticks and
spasms
Tremors Tremors you know when people
have the Tremors how many people out
there have seen that where people
actually have the Tremors where
everything is just tremoring on them
right where it's like this okay like
this so many people and then Parkinson's
it's tox toxic heavy metals Parkinson's
there's like so many varieties of
Parkinson's like toxic heavy metals
and then the Tremors and then the
shakes right and the shakes worsen
different times for all kinds of reasons
like if their blood sugar drops the
shakes worsen but somebody else's blood
sugar drops they don't have any shakes
at all they have no shakes at all
because they got because that's somebody
with blood sugar problems and toxic
heavy metals see so many things to talk
about so much vast information from
Spirit of compassion I'm just blessed to
have learned it and and I'm able to
actually message it to you guys be a
messenger Marissa spiritual hmds has
saved my life and continues to nourish
protect and cleanse and heal healing
severe digestive distress from childhood
for decades migraines brain fog add M
nausea UTI and so much more that's
that's just
incredible some celery juice all right
yeah Culver City June 15 are you going
to be there I'm going to be
there and I I mean I don't know if I'm
ever going to do book signing again I've
never done one that's the whole point
this isn't like a book signing tour I'm
only doing it once with the book signing
and so I'll be there June
15th um check it out link is in the
profile link is in the description go to
medical medium.com and register and it's
a it's free but
register Alexander Lang over there on
YouTube yes can't wait to meet you aw
can't wait man I can't wait all right
you talk a little bit more about this
for a time in the 1800s medical
universities in the US and England were
turning out doctors fast stamping them
out they were stamping doctors out right
in the 1800s and the number one protocol
they taught students was to give a glass
of mercury water to any patient who was
Ill regardless of age gender or
symptoms and they always gave it the
same Mount no matter if you were a
little toddler they gave you the same
old big old glass of mercury
drink and if you were somebody if you're
were a dude was 6'6 6' 7 right 250 lb
they give you the same glass of mercury
Elixir and you give this petite woman 94
lbs maybe frail you because you're sick
and you're just in your your
411 and you go to the doctor they give
you the same Elixir they give the 250 lb
male who's
6'7 just it's just
crazy over there on Facebook Vicky
Russell can't wait to meet you after 10
years of reading your books and
following your protocols whoa you're
going to be there Vicki all right now
like now I'm just like whoa um YouTube
Wendy thanks to the heavy metal detox
smoothie and CJ I am exema
free yeah exema really really brutal so
many people Cheyenne over there what is
his website please medical
medium.com medicalmedium.com
register be there I'm going to be there
I'm going to give out some free
gifts I'm actually really excited about
this
let's see piley Ren planning on flying
from
Europe we were booking an Airbnb already
and the cost was 144 per night
144 if that's not a sign
144 per night
144 Jessica toric over there on YouTube
will there be a talk by you Anthony or
just book signing would love to come I'm
going to be there in person I'm going be
signing the
books I'm sure I'm going be saying hi to
everybody and you never know you never
know what I'll do because you know how I
am you just know how I
am many of you guys you've seen the
pirate you've seen samanth
you seen the
doctor Dr jobi you seen right you've
seen Dr
Nesbit you never know what I'm going to
do you just don't know Joanna over there
on YouTube coming to meet you from
Ireland
whoa YouTube Leslie O'Donnell been
working on medical medum prot for 5
years now healing from severe
ra you have helped me helped more than
anything else thank you thank you is
thank you back Leslie thank you
back all right okay I want to talk a
little bit about Mercury for a couple
more minutes because I know some people
they love Mercury info love it okay all
right the treatment was especially
common method to force a miscarriage
Mercury to force a miscarriage and to
treat what was labeled as female
hysteria a lot of reasons for
miscarriages every single day is mercury
every single day women have storage bins
of mercury storage bins of metals from
generation to generation to generation
and metals move can have one baby and
then now you have a miscarriage because
Metals move and they gravitate they
actually move and spread
okay the 19th century wasn't exactly the
Stone Age it had been established that
mercury was a dangerous toxin that
destroyed life they didn't know really
what it did besides it killed you if you
had too much of it if you played with it
and ate a big hunk of it for centuries
already people had born witnessed to the
millions who died from Mercury exposure
so why was it still favored still
favored one factor was the great
industrial demon that sat behind Mercury
did you hear that a great demon yes a
great big demon that sat behind the
Mercury
industry that alone was enough for it to
be pushed as the top cure all
Trend there were interest groups pushing
it Forward interest groups that had evil
and darkness behind them that would push
Mercury and the use of mercury and push
it into guess what
Pharmaceuticals and push it into other
things it's
crazy
yep the Mercury movement finally hit a
speed bump in the mid
1800s doctors had become more accessible
than ever before in history to people
from all walks of life which seemed like
a good thing yet in increasing numbers
of people went to visit these new
medical graduates Observers caught on
that more and more of these patients
were coming down with uncontrollable
shaking fevers Madness rage body ticks
jerking gibberish talk gibberish talk it
became obvious that a visit to the
doctor could result in poisoning so in
the 1800s it was figured out yeah it was
figured out that mercury was causing so
many problems in the Pharmaceuticals in
the drugs in the Mercury Elixir Mercury
was causing so much trouble back in that
day in the
1800s for example a wife and mother of
five might have sent her husband to the
doctor to help the husband with his gout
upon arriving home her husband would be
delusional yelling out children's Rhymes
as his eyes twitched after just one
experience like this a family would say
we have had enough following this
widespread realization there was a
25-year ghost town period for medical
businesses did you guys know that in the
late
1800s there was a
25e
absence of no one going to the medical
doctors anymore 25 years a medical
doctor barely saw a patient in their
tenure whatever you call
it they knew that a visit to the doctor
would lead into mercury poisoning
medical universities hit their all-time
low funding and were broken by busted by
the late
1800s this is this is sick
information right Michael Charles on
YouTube right there CJ and heavy metal
detox smoothie got me back on my feet
symptom
free you're awesome bro you're awesome
okay this was exactly the break that
natural practitioners and healers needed
to gain some credibility for the first
brief time in history practically in
modern history or early forms of Home
Homeopathy chiropractic treatment and
other varieties of alternative medicine
exploded in popularity by 1900 finally
traditional doctors offices caught on
and started advertising that they were
no longer carrying Quicksilver
Quicks that's what they called it
Quicksilver liquid mercury drinks and
traditional medicine gained back some
credibility because they dropped the
Mercury so medical schools were starting
to get students once more again in there
and patients were starting to go back to
doctors
again finally traditional doctor offices
caught on and started advertising that
they no longer offered Mercury Elixir
anymore Mercury Quicksilver Elixir and
traditional medicine gained back that
credibility like I said yet the demon
behind mercury still wanted the
population to get plenty of exposure the
demon behind mercury still wanted to use
to get Mercury so inventive ways were
created and figured out so you got
mercury in you not only were Industries
dumping mercury into every river lake
and Waterway possible but other forms of
mercury containing medicine were born by
the turn of the 20th century plus
dentists were still using mercury malum
fillings and that's just the start baby
that's just the start over there on
YouTube glow ly said I can't wait to be
one of the luckiest to have your
signature in my favorite books of yours
um many blessings I can't wait to sign
your book serious Susan hey aw I've
signed up to I signed up to see you in
La I can't wait I'm going to be there
I'm going to be there I
am you guys this information is there's
so much I'm skipping through a little I
got to skip through a little I'm going
to give you a little bit more Mercury
information if you just got here you
have to watch this video from the
beginning watch it wherever you want to
but yes watch it from the beginning
right
okay cold White Springs says can we
follow this event live you mean if
you're not
there no May I'm really sorry but no no
it's only there it's only there the
dirty secret what does this have to do
with
you um dep personalization depression
panic attacks anxiety eczema
psoriasis rosacea all kinds of different
other conditions tick spasms Tremors
shakes memory loss brain fog
bipolar ups and
downs I'm just naming a
few over there on IG Anthony changed my
life I'm now symptom free from high
blood pressure cholesterol and thyroid
the hmds and celery juice changed my
life forever that's incredible that's
incredible that's incredible even got
your cholesterol back to where it should
be it's
amazing because it's the dirty
secret why am I going to tell you why am
I going on like this about Mercury
Mercury Mercury
because it's the dirty secret we're not
supposed to talk about and we have
mercury in our brains and bodies from
generations of ancestors who are exposed
to it you're not supposed to know about
what mercury has done to shape history
and you're certainly certainly not
supposed to know what mercury has done
to you on any level right up to this
present moment Mercury can be toxic even
in tiny dosages you can't see you can't
see it and there's no hazard sign saying
beware
Mercury if it were up to the Mercury
demon he would think Mercury was
harmless even good for us better yet
Mercury would be entirely
hidden and we wouldn't even know it
existed Mercury never goes away unless
you take specific steps to detoxify it
and get it out Mercury casts an evil in
soulless shadow that has engulfed so
many and destroyed so many lives
this toxic heavy metal becomes a part of
us and that reflects itself in our
health greed carelessness darkness and
ignorance are the major factors that
have allowed Mercury to prey on the
population a Mercury mind owner of the
past likely didn't care if workers only
live 6 months to 3 years after starting
at the mine the Mercury mine because
there was money to be made money to be
had what good has mercury ever done none
it's said nothing good for us absolutely
nothing it's an unnecessary dangerous
neurotoxin it could have been replaced
in its medical and Industrial uses with
something safer but no and I'll tell you
why because the Mercury demon for some
reason has a grip on the hierarchy on
this planet
especially the hierarchy that loves
pharmaceutical world and that hierarchy
wants Mercury sprinkled about in it it
wants mercury in a
desperately sick World Lisa hi Anthony I
just started listening to your podcast
you are new here I'm going to tell you
right here I am at your
service and I am honored you are here I
got some some really killer podcast
episodes from
information and when you come here
you'll find information that has leeched
out and been
poached and now you're going to know
that oop it was here check it out learn
it it would be incredible did you hear
yesterday's medical medium podcast
episode coffee Animas did you guys hear
that the coffee enema podcast
episode coffee enemas make sure you go
to Medical beam podcast at Apple podcast
and listen to it it's mind-blowing
information e there was even a YouTube
influencer um at the beginning of the
episode that actually said to me
aw I want to start that coffee anima
show off with a bang and so this YouTube
influencer for the first minute um got
on there and talked about how much she
likes coffee enas you don't want to miss
this episode seriously you don't want to
miss
this all right
I got so much information listen before
I forget sign up to the newsletter so
you know what's up so you can get the
announcements seriously please sign up
to it so you know go to Medical
medium.com register to the June 15th
event where I'm going to be signing
books updates too are going to be
coming yeah collaboration between
irwan and medical medium collaboration
putting the heavy metal detox smoothie
in the store The Heavy Metal detox made
fresh I can't wait I hope I'm the first
to get one chances are I will just be of
service to everybody and I will get the
last
one and I'll be sitting somewhere in a
corner somewhere with the last
one but that will be a dream come true
follow medical medium on telegram for
updates telegram definitely I said I was
going to leave a telegram
I was very busy and I'm going to leave
one overshore soon so please get to
t.me slmed medium that's my telegram get
on there okay check out the PMP like
audios you know the P&P audios Pride and
Prejudice the 1994 version of Pride and
Prejudice you know how I talk about how
the only film one of the only films rare
films that was filmed with dark
out not in the filming of it which
happens in all of filming industry for
the most part most of it check out on IG
medical medium inside scoop where I'm
sending you personal
messages
uh-huh that's right you
guys
incredible
incredible I am going to sip some more
celery that that's what I
want but I got a
hankering for some grapefruit juice
That's freshly
squeezed but I'm going to finish my
celery juice cuz it got a lot more to
drink all right
guys one day at a
time all
right anyway that's some metal talk but
I'm going to be talking more about
metals because there's so much more
information we
oh Dental amalgams right um
Seafood um interesting information in
here okay
Amanda spanin over there on YouTube I'm
so excited 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 17 18 explanation
points that's exciting that's
exciting and I'm excited too wait there
they are 1 2 3 I 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 is it
18 you guys incredible buying my books
today Annette over there on YouTube you
won't be disappointed you'll be blown
away can I suggest a few things the
medical medium New Edition is
mindblowing the information for chronic
illness is mind-blowing it's helped so
many people and K so many people
right and if I could walk you over here
cleanse the heal just unbelievable book
saves so many lives and then of course
brain saver brains saver protocols and
brain saver just really
incredible all right you guys I love you
guys