we're live anthony william the medical
medium
did you catch the mold episode mold
you got to check it out um looking
forward to you guys checking this
episode out mold the crazy maker it's
the reason why i call it that because it
has really
caused a lot of trouble with a lot of
people and it could make us go crazy in
such a
in such an intense way i've actually
talked to a friend recently had intense
mold exposure
and it really triggered everything
in this friend as far as fatigue and
aches and pains
and just oh my god the brain fog that
my friend deal has dealt with with it
has just been off the charts so
i i kind of think that the mold issues
that we deal today
should get more attention it's like
everybody kind of sweeps it under the
carpet
nobody really wants to know about it
unless you're living with it and then if
you're living with it nobody else really
cares
there's really like not a lot of help
for people out there when you're dealing
with mold exposure
people go through hell and back with
mold exposure so
this is an important episode medical
medium podcast said
at apple podcast check it out there when
you get a chance
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
the link is in the description
uh mold the crazy maker check out this
podcast episode now
just giving you a forewarning about it
it's it's a docky series style
um podcast it's not a podcast where it's
coffee talk and you just throw it away
and then you get another guest
on and throw it away another gets done
and throw it away and you get a little
tidbit if you
if you can or a little nugget wherever
you can this is filled with
tons of information it's packed with
wall-to-wall with information
about mold about all the different
things we go through so check it out
it's a medical medium podcast at apple
podcast that's the official
platform for the medical media podcast
where it's uncensored the other
platforms
they're censored in different ways uh
michelle's there great good to see you
everybody's coming on um you know you
guys the thing is about
mold is it's devastating it's not the
same old as
yesterday it's not cindy says thanks for
these podcasts
thanks for listening to him and um
cindy dunn says hi anthony the mold
episode was spot on and also the
neurological one so many things you hit
spot on thank you i now have supplements
to follow
it's critical to know what supplements
to use with neurological symptoms
critical to know what supplements are
used with mold exposure these are
important things that
you know and i talked to people all the
time i talked to a doctor last week
about mold and everything and
he was telling me that his patients who
get mold exposure
they just they just their their symptoms
get 10 times worse than they should
normally be
and by the way we're live right here
just so you know if you're on here we're
live streaming we're live right now
um and so i like doing these live and
you know i don't want to pre-record them
and then put them up i just
want you guys to know that i'm here and
there's good stuff to talk about and i
want to answer questions
i want to see how you guys are doing
what's happening in your life
what's happening with in your life with
mold what's happening in your life with
neurological symptoms
all these things are so important are
you dealing with brain fog i have a
brain fog episode
so these episodes at medical medium
podcast at apple podcast these episodes
are docu-series style
filled with information they're not
coffee talk where you throw it away
and then another guest comes on you you
know toss it aside another
the end and they just you just you know
whatever it's not like that
these are informative powerful packed
information
some of these episodes really got
wrenching with information so much
because there's so much
truth when you hear that much truth in
some of these episodes it's really
intense like the egg episode the
chemtrail episode right
all of them um christie silva says thank
you so much for doing
the the modeling podcast so many
people with mold ish illness needed this
thank you thank you for listening
anyway you know people with mold really
do
need help they not only need help in the
situation they're in
but they need help as far as support
because
people don't get mold support out there
it's like the minute it hits
you become the unlucky one you know what
i mean guys it's like the minute the
mold hits you become the unlucky one
it's like
okay that's your tough luck so you're
you're dealing with mold in in your
house or your apartment or your living
space that's your tough luck
or you know your building that's your
tough luck it's like
and anybody else who's not going through
it they're like oh that's so
sad really mold how what does that mean
is it really bad and
it's you know a lot of people don't get
support now i've had friends
that have had mold you know mold
problems devastate their lives and hit
them really hard you guys
and then they tell their other friends
and other friends like really
uh what does that mean mold um you mean
like
something got moldy and they're like no
it's devastating a pipe broke in the
house the basement mold came up
there's mold all over the house there's
molding around the apartment
and they kind of don't get it and they
don't get what that means so what does
that mean you got to move out
does that mean you have to find a new
place to live like what does that mean
and so the support for mold all on its
own and that's not even getting sick
and then when you get sick where you're
like yeah mold
made me sick and then friends are like
well did mold really make you sick i've
seen it where friends
question friends you know even family
members question family members but
friends question friends i've seen that
out there
seen doctors question patients and say
uh
this isn't from mold this isn't mold
didn't kind of cause this
this isn't probably a mold issue so i've
seen that over the years too now there's
more doctors that actually believe in
mold
that's good but as i talk about in the
episode they still don't know why
someone really
gets triggered in a way they do buy mold
and what's going on deep inside of them
you know
while wireless says hi anthony the mold
podcast is great great
um great you take the fear out of mold
we can overcome it you can
it's important to actually have the
ability to be empowered and have that
information
um messaging with angels good to see you
catching up on the podcast the egg
podcast is amazing oh my god
the egg podcast is one of my favorites
messaging with angels it's one of my
favorites and
it's really intense really tons of truth
in there tons of information in there
check these out at medical medium
podcasts at apple podcast if you haven't
heard these the mold one is what i'm
talking about today i might cover
neurological symptoms in a little bit
too
we're live right now if you guys just
came on um
totally live that's right it's the way
to do it
and so the mold today is not the same
mold as
yesterday the the mold in the years here
aren't the same as yesteryear
important to know the reason why is we
have thousands of super molds now
and they've gotten really strong because
fungicides are everywhere fungicides are
created by
you know the chemical giants they make
fungicides to try to kill the mold
and when they do that they make mold
stronger and then make a new mold and
mold adapts the minute you try to
exterminate it
with a fungicide it just adapts and it
gets stronger and that's what happens
and i talk about how
fungicide is sprayed on the highways
every single
highway at least in the u.s and probably
globally too
and i've heard it's in in other places
around the world they spray the sides of
every highway it's sprayed with
fungicides
um you know rest stops on highways
are sprayed with fungicides in inside
the rest stops it's just fungicides
everywhere
and it's always like this and new
clothes when you buy new clothes brand
new clothes
sprayed with fungicides got to wash them
and everything so
you know and people don't realize that
they try on new clothes all the
fungicides in there
and they get the air fresheners sent to
candles those got fungicides in them
clones and perfumes have
fungicides in them i talk about it in
the episode you guys
about how you can have an old bottle of
of cologne that's 50 years old
and there's no jellyfish in the middle
of it how come
there's a fungicide in it to stop from
from a fun
fungus forming in your bottle of clone
it's unbelievable really
lewis uh louise says what is the name of
the podcast
it's a medical medium podcast so medical
medium podcast
at apple podcast that's the platform if
you don't
have an apple device um go to
medicalmedium.com
you'll see the menu podcast in the menu
you can listen to that way it's a free
podcast
but it's really informative really power
packed i'm just forewarning you it's
not a throwaway these are docuseries
style episodes they're not coffee talk
and people coming on and you just next
and next
throw it away next it's not it's not
cotton candy it's actually informative
it's powerful
it's um a tremendous amount of
information in there to heal
there's healing tools in this podcast so
the mold one is the one up now
that's what's going on here the link is
in the description so please know that
the link is in the description so you're
going to want to check these out
mold exposure is really serious it can
trigger off a lot of symptoms in people
it's a major trigger for illness and
that's what it does you know
uh gina says high anthony mold exposure
symptoms sound similar to my lyme
disease symptoms yes
they do that because lyme disease
symptoms are neurological
mold exposure can trigger any
okay just say you never had a diagnosis
of lyme disease say you never had a
diagnosis of some disease or illness or
symptoms
and what happens is when you get mold
exposure it can
trigger something inside of you and then
you can end up with a lyme disease
diagnosis for a lot of people that
happens too so it's not like
it's not like they they get lyme
symptoms they get diagnosed with the
lyme
you know diagnoses and never see mold
there's people out there that
get the mold first it becomes the
trigger and then they have the lyme
symptoms then they have the neurological
symptoms
absolutely so that's how it works um
so kelly says i'm new to this where do i
find the apple podcast so medical medium
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
the link is in the description kelly
so check that out the link is in the
description and you can find it that way
you won't be disappointed the the
episodes are
packed i have three meditations so you
can heal
using the meditations i have a brain
meditation i have a moon meditation i
have a free the free is a bird
meditation it's a free
resource no commercials no infomercials
no advertisements and it's just
jam-packed with healing information
including all the tools to use and stuff
like that
trisha tricia marie says fungicides good
to see you trisha glad you're here
and it's a free resource and there's
healing tools in this podcast so people
can heal
so you know that sydney says how do i
listen to the podcast
um you don't have apple then if you
don't have an apple device just go to
medicalmedium.com
and you'll see the menu and podcasts in
the menu and you can listen to it that
way right there it's free
that's the whole point i try to offer as
much uh
information as i possibly can so you
have the ability to heal
move forward that's what it's always
been about mandy says your podcasts are
incredible
and are in the meditations too so the
meditations too you're doing those doing
the brain meditation the moon meditation
freeze the bird meditation incredible um
yeah it's about making sure you guys
have that knowledge so let's talk about
mold for a little bit
it's important um i talk about how
fungicides are dropped everywhere
they're even dropped out of helicopters
they're dropped all over the place
they're they're
literally they're dropping fungicides on
us like yearly they
did side the highways parking lots
schools yeah schools they just
they just just they they they coat
playgrounds with fungicide in schools
and this is what they do and it's to
stop mold from growing
the chemical companies sell it to
everybody as a package deal
and then you just you just spray it
everywhere so everybody's spraying it
everywhere that's how it works
um all the institutions spraying it
everywhere this is how it's done
hospitals they spray it everywhere
fungicides everywhere
and then it creates super molds over
time molds that get a little crazy that
get
out of control and that's what we're up
against out there so information
very important information but i want to
talk about this
what mold does is mold lowers the immune
system
that's what it does mold lowers the
immune system
so that when it lowers the immune system
it triggers something inside of us
something that's already happening in
there
and that's why you can have a family of
five you can have a family of seven you
could have a family of three
a family of four and only one person
gets sick uh one person gets sick
and that's it so it's like well why is
mom sick
why is mom in bed suffering with fatigue
aches and pains
tingles and numbness ticks and spasms or
just
body pain and why is mom suffering like
that from mold exposure
and dad's not you know dad can eat the
mold it could be in the air
it could be do living in it all
breathing in it the kids are fine doing
the same thing and that that's how it
works
uh kim is this greeting from germany
thank you and spirit so much we are
healing
germany is amazing so glad you're here
so lorraine ellis here too
trish marie's here everybody seems to be
here today it's great um
see uh tanya says are the podcasts
related to the information in your books
yeah they are they're related to
information in the books but what i
always have done
i've always put i always like to put out
more information
and more and more and more so that if
you have the medical medium books like
cleanse the heel which is
the most comprehensive medical textbook
out there for healing over 200 symptoms
and conditions if you're interested
get it free at the library or amazon's
on sale right now 51
off us so what i like to do is offer as
much information as i can in
all the resources all the resources so i
put out this docu-series podcast for you
guys
and keep in mind like this is something
you'd have to pay for
and you don't have to that's what's
incredible this is a high production
um and and uh really really quality high
production
and it's a docu-series style podcast so
it's not like
well am i just going to listen to
anthony shoot the crap
is that what this is going to be let's
just go to his podcast let's just hear
him shoot
shoot you know shoot the stuff and you
know and just and go off and talking
that's not what this is this is
packed with information docuseries style
it's so you have this other resource to
heal and move your life forward
that's what the medical mean podcast is
about and so every resource i put out
like the book
um it's a resource packed with
information so you don't
have missing missing pieces so it's like
you listen to the podcast you got the
book too
it's you know look and if you're not
sick and you haven't struggled and
you're not dealing with anything really
like problematic like that
then you know i get it maybe you don't
need this stuff right now but if you
ever get really sick or know somebody's
really sick
they want the cleanse to heal book i
mean they're going to need it they're
going to want the medical medium podcast
um alexandra where did you find them
um so
well the link is in the description
that's where you find the the medical
mean podcast at apple podcast link is in
the description
and this week you can find it there
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
you know so catherine elizabeth good to
see you
hi anthony thank you for this episode
blown away super molds
scary that mold loves emf let's talk
about that for a little bit
so i can only scratch the surface you
guys of what
is in there but let's talk about the the
emf
and all that so molds they jive on a
frequency is what they do
they thrive on a frequency that's what
molds like to do so
and there's a reason for this because
molds
were tested in labs where there were
tremendous amounts of
frequency electricity emf
radio signals all of it so mold has
adapted to that it
it loves cell towers so mold loves
cell towers that doesn't mean throw away
your devices because that doesn't matter
cell tower is still sending signals
regardless if you have a device in your
hand or not
still a signal that's going everywhere
and molds love
these types of frequencies they love it
they love emf
they love radio frequencies they love
cell tower frequencies they love it all
so with that mold thrives on that so
when you break that frequency you got a
chance of actually breaking mold and i
talked about that in the episode
so important nina says what's the book
called the book right there
that the book is cleanse the heel so
medical medium cleanse the heel
it's 51 off at amazon.com us
200 symptoms conditions it's got 75
recipes in there it's packed with
information
supplements supplement dosages what to
do for different symptoms and conditions
get it free at the library if you don't
want to get it at amazon
so and then the medical media podcast so
there you go medical meeting podcast
the thing is with medical medium
information is you always have the
option of getting it for free
that's that's the whole point it's like
get the book at the library if you want
hear the podcast for free no commercials
in the podcast
that's what it's about so you know i
know we're live stream right now so i
just want to convey this information out
to you guys
and just so you know because someone
might come on here and be like what's he
selling
what kind of stuff is is anthony
williams selling you know and it's like
well not selling anything
i want you guys to have free information
be able to heal all the whole bit
so talk about neurological symptoms a
little bit
so um aches and pains tingles and
numbness anxiety
depression those are all neurological
tics and spasms
that's neurological okay so you know
migraines headaches that's neurological
brain fog
you know focus and concentration issues
that's neurological
so i'm talking about all these different
neurological symptoms
that we that people have burning skin
jaw
pain burning gums burning tongue
tremoring shaking vibrating ear popping
ringing in the ears
right eye floaters all of that
neurological symptoms you guys should
check
out the neurological episode at medical
media podcast at apple podcast check out
the neurological episode
uh it's packed with information so
important
and um ashley's doing the moon
meditations that's awesome there
so we're live right now just everybody
know that that's that's what's happening
here i'm talking about mold the crazy
maker talk about neurological symptoms
too check out that episode
but anyway you guys check them out if
you can
um so much healing information in there
so much to learn
so much to know you know i got your back
you know i love you guys
and just keep the hard work all the hard
work you're doing healing
do your celery juice do all the things
you need to do to heal
keep on learning about the information
just know that i care
and i'll just keep on doing this i'll
keep on putting out these powerful
episodes
subscribe if you can please subscribe to
the medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
so you can be the first to get the
notification so you don't miss out on
when the next episode comes out you know
why
because there's no definitive time it's
not on a schedule
it could come any day any hour so make
sure you subscribe
and then share the episodes with other
people please share the episodes link is
in the description
i love you guys okay take care