[Music]
hello everyone welcome back to on
purpose the number one health podcast in
the world thanks to each and every one
of you for learning listening and
growing with us thank you so much for
prioritizing your growth in work self
and love and like you know every week
I'm trying to find guests that are gonna
give you really raw authentic genuine
advice people are coming at this from
new angles new ideas fresh perspectives
that can genuinely help you transform
your life and move it forward and
today's guest will not disappoint I'm
genuinely so grateful and excited for
this person for making time making space
in their life for coming on and being on
the podcast his name is Anthony William
and he's the originator of the global
celery juice movement
he's a four times number one New York
Times bestselling author and today's the
launch of his new book which is called
celery juice the most powerful medicine
of our time healing millions worldwide
Anthony thank you so much for being here
incredible introduction I'm honored I
can't even believe it it's it's so
awesome being here right so you have to
do it well so it's so true hey I'm just
I'm so happy to be here happy to talk to
your audience so much to talk about lots
of cover on health things that are
life-changing things that move the
needle and that's what matters you know
when you're sick with chronic illness
and you're trying to get better and you
can't move that needle forward and you
know and you're stuck in it and you're
just in the trenches of it all and then
something takes you further along and
you finally start experiencing a benefit
you start getting better let's say the
celery juice is one of the most powerful
healing tools out there and when you
start moving forward it's life-changing
like no other when people are stuck when
they're actually really stuck in the
trenches of what I call hell basically
chronic illness and they finally see the
light and that matters that's why I'm
here absolutely and I love that energy
man because I think you're so right that
so many of us today are so stuck and a
lot of the time we've tried everything
or I hear that a lot with my lens I've
tried everything let up into my doctor
I've been to this person like I tried my
weird thing that my aunt comes up with
like you know I've tried all of these
things and the thing is it's not like
those are bad those are all good things
because everybody's got a piece
the puzzle you got the best doctors out
there you got functional medicine
doctors you got alternative guys you got
conventional guys girls all of them
they're all working hard on their
patients and people people have
compassion doctors are the most
incredible people the compassion to wake
up in the morning go to the office and
work on person after person after person
like they do and hear their stories and
hear their cries doctors are
unbelievable and the tool there's a lot
of good tools out there right but what
happens is there's some things people
don't even know about yet that that plug
into what they're doing say they're
doing a keto diet say they're doing a
paleo diet say they're doing a vegan
diet say they're doing a plant-based
diet and they're not getting all the
results they need and they're all
confused and everybody's flip-flopping
from vegan to paleo to paleo to vegan
and everybody is all upset but when you
plug in something like the celery juice
and you know how to use it you can move
forward wherever you are you can plug
this into what you're doing it's tools
like that that literally move the needle
and change the lives of millions and
right now hundreds of millions are
drinking celery juice it's the most
powerful healing movement of our time
and day and I want everybody to actually
be part of it because why miss out what
are you gonna do you're not gonna do it
you're not gonna part taking something
that could change your life so I want
everybody to know this isn't one of
those scams or forces this is that
powerful when you use this herbal
medicine something changes inside of us
I love that I can't wait to uncover that
with you in this podcast and in the life
that we're about to do I can't wait to
get into all the details but I want to
take it backwards slightly short because
I want people to understand where you're
coming from absolutely and and I want
people to understand your background
your journey and just behind the mind
you know inside the mind of Anthony so I
want to go back to you being four years
old yeah and you're four years old and
you literally without any help any
support whatever it is you literally let
your grandmother know she's Chik lung
cancer she had lung cancer yeah she was
symptom free like no one knew it yeah
not at all no and then they checked yeah
and you were spot on
yeah woke up one morning and heard a
voice perfectly clear you know people
say wait a minute how does he get this
advanced medical information
that's decades ahead of research in
science you know I know scientists
I know I know incredible doctors lab
technicians and they say his information
is advanced whether anybody likes it or
not whether the source he hears it from
you don't agree with or you're not happy
about this voice he hears that he heard
it four years old that diagnosed his
grandmother a lung cancer and from there
on this is all he's ever done and people
are like hey you know what I don't know
do I trust this and I totally understand
I totally get it a guy that hears a
voice when you really know the origin of
it you know it's hard but when lab
technicians and scientists and doctors
that are elevated in the field of
medicine say his advanced information
like epstein-barr causing Hashimoto's
thyroiditis he was the first to actually
bring that out before they even knew
that's what was happening and when they
say hey he's advanced with this
information and it's about getting
people better we got to kick back a
little bit we got to calm down and say
okay let's listen to this because this
is different this is actually really
helping people and at four years old
that's what happened it was information
coming through perfectly clear I heard
heard it straight in a voice write to me
and it's I've been using that ever since
not just my grandmother with that what
happened was in 1975 in the fall of 1975
had another family and member with a
back problem a back problem that
wouldn't it wouldn't ease off if the
doctors didn't know what was really
causing the back problem it wasn't an
injury it was an inflammatory condition
a mystery back injury or a mystery back
inflamed problem where they're suffering
they couldn't walk right in late 1975
spirit which I call spirit the voice
said celery juice this is when it
started celery juice for this family
member we didn't have really any kind of
juicer look look what year it is look
what's going on we weren't prepared they
had the blender the beat-up old blender
we ground up that celery right and we
strained it with a cheesecloth and we
just strained it out and and a family
member was a skeptic about celery juice
well what do you mean celery juice drank
it and started recovering that night
slowly recovering and then
the end of the week out of the woods
with his back from walking and it's that
kind of thing right there and yes the
voice tells me what to do so that's what
I've done
dedicated my life helping people but
giving them information that even
doctors want to know there are thousands
of doctors in this country alone with
the medical medium series books in their
offices patients have brought them in
and they and the doctors art they're
smart they read it and say wait a minute
this is different
whoa wait he's talking about viruses
he's talking about pathogens he's
talking about things we don't know about
viruses and pathogens that's not
anywhere and also what to do which is
one of the tools the celery juice I love
selling stuff online but shipping out
takes so much time and cost so much
money that it can make the process
extremely frustrating but then I found
out about shipstation now I can save
money on shipping and get my orders done
quickly so I can focus on more
productive things I need to get done
that day regardless of what website
you're selling from whether it's Amazon
Etsy or your own website shipstation
brings all your orders into one simple
interface and it's so convenient because
you can do it all from your phone which
is great for someone like me who's
always on the go ship station works with
all of the major carriers including USPS
FedEx UPS even Amazon Fulfillment so you
can compare and choose the best shipping
solution for you and your customers and
you always know that you're getting the
best deal possible and right now on
purpose listeners can try ship station
free for 60 days when you use the promo
code purpose there's absolutely no risk
you can start with your free trial
without even entering your credit card
information just visit ship station comm
click on the microphone at the top of
the homepage and type in purpose
that's ship station comm then enter
promo code purpose I have a huge sweet
tooth and a couple of weeks ago my wife
made me this amazing hot chocolate I
thought it would actually count as my
dessert for the day I couldn't believe
it when she told me it was actually hot
cacao with reishi from for sig Matic and
it was actually good for me now I have
it all the time because the
actually supports relaxation and
actually supports restful sleep it
tastes exactly like hot chocolate and is
made with pure Peruvian cacao but is
guilt free and just 25 calories per
serving for stigmatic is a natural
superfood company that specializes in
mushroom based drinks that benefit our
immunity energy and longevity and help
us live healthier more enhanced lives
for sig Matic makes a wide variety of
blends including mushroom coffee
mushroom elixirs haka cows matcha and
superfood blends for sig Matic works
with my always on the go lifestyle
because it's so quick and easy just tear
the packet and mix with hot water this
also makes it great for travel which is
so so helpful for me I have a special
offer just for my audience right now you
can receive 15% of your for cig matic
purchase just go to four sigma decom
forward slash purpose or use the
discount code purpose a check out that's
for sig Matic fo you are s IG ma TI c
comm forward slash purpose and what I'm
more interested in because I've seen all
of that research have seen people say of
all of your incredible background and
the studies and the research and the
fact that it's worked for people how did
you start to trust that voice because I
almost feel like that's sometimes harder
it's like trust you know oh yeah
trusting a voice that's coming too how
is that process for you you know what it
is is when you when you see it working
in front of your own results you know
when I was 13 years old and a stock boy
in a little grocery store and that voice
is telling me you know why someone has
diabetes or what's going on or what's
happening with them or or the brain
tumor that they have or something that's
going on and the voice is telling me
what's happening inside their bodies and
what they need you just you just it you
can't avoid it you can't ignore it it's
not one of those things you should say
well I don't I don't want to do this
anymore
you know it's not what you're you're in
it and you just you go with it and you
keep on working you know forward to help
people and change and change your lives
it's so critical absolutely so let's get
on to the cellar do you start
discovering the secret behind this like
how did you start seeing that it had
such a powerful effect how did you first
uncover because I think there are just
so many vegetables out there you can
make so many Juice
people have drank probably the wrong
juices for such a long time yeah then
where did it start all juices are great
that's the thing all juicers are great
they offer benefits and a lot of people
they get confused they say well why
would celery juice by itself do anything
for you and one of the reasons is it's
an herb it's not a vegetable it's an
actual herb and herbal medicine is
powerful I mean if anybody is listening
out here do you like herbs on any level
what herbs are your favorite there's so
many people that are into any cut
they're into herbs that's the whole
thing you got Chinese medicine you got
air Vedic you got all this herbs are
powerful and there's herbalist out there
there's doctors out there natural
doctors you know and in herbs are a big
part of our lives so well why do they do
things for us they because they're very
healing well celery has been its it no
one knew and that's the thing I mean
even when I heard it from the voice
originally perfectly clear Sellars used
the celery it's an herb I was even like
wait a minute no it's a celery stick
what do you mean this is this is a
vegetable that no one cares about and
never really cared about and spirits
like it's not a vegetable it's an herb
it's herbal medicine you extract it in a
large quantity and when you do that
that's when the miracles happen and then
you know someone might say wait a minute
you know you have to leave the fiber you
have to leave the pulp the juice things
not good you're leaving like nutrition
behind the fiber and the pulp but what
they don't understand is chamomile tea
right do you eat the teabag after you've
like had camp you go out with a friend
right do you cut open that teabag and
say wait a minute I got to get this
fiber I got to get this pulp here cuz
that's where the nutrition is no the
medicine comes from the chamomile and
that's what you're getting that medicine
to relax you to calm you the things that
people like same thing with other herbs
in herbal teas and so forth of course
you can eat some of the herbs but
they're better extract at the medicine
so it's the power of that this is an
herbal tonic and herbal elixir and what
you'll see out there's dietitians who
are amazing people are nutritionist who
are amazing people what they'll do is
they'll be confused and be like no no no
leave the pulp and fiber
Anthony William doesn't know what he's
talking about you don't you don't want
to just have that
they don't know this is herbal medicine
you're extracting a large quantity of
this incredible mysterious tonic why is
it mysterious science the research
hasn't looked into what is in celery yet
barely any information out there another
reason why people don't know but we're
getting there
we're actually getting there we are
getting there and you're leading that
movement which I absolutely love like
it's incredible like you're really
pushing that out there and I think it's
so important that we do live in a time
where we are allowing unique voices to
come to the fore yeah you know maybe in
1975 and years after that people would
have been close to these things but now
people are seeing also the lack of
certain research in certain studies and
recognizing that there are alternatives
tell me when you started uncoming celery
juice what are the key issues that
you're seeing celery juice benefit what
are the key challenges the people
experiencing ottowa mean I know there's
a big leap oh my god big Liz big list
people dealing with chronic illness what
I call chronic illness symptoms that
won't alleviate more come constantly or
on and off intermittently but they don't
go away technically what could that be
chronic fatigue syndrome
Emme chronic fatigue syndrome right lyme
disease multiple sclerosis Hashimoto's
thyroiditis lupus these are just some
things eczema and psoriasis rosacea
different conditions people suffer from
and all this acne
there's SIBO all of these things you
could just keep on going on things that
people are plagued with you know and the
fatigue is one of them that's a big one
when moms can't get out and they can't
get out of the house and and run the
house and run their careers and take
care of their children because they
become barely function because a severe
brain fog chronic fatigue syndrome and
and not have real answers in the
fibromyalgia and the rheumatoid
arthritis and all these things people
suffer with these are the things celery
juice starts to move the needle with
it's these these things it's different
when someone's exercising every day two
hours day they feel good they're young
they're strong in the moment they
haven't gotten sick yet in their lives
they haven't been there and they're
trying celery juice for a week and
they're like I'm not sure what I'm
noticing I think there might have been
energy I
don't know but then you take someone
who's been to 50 doctors okay
been through hell and back struggled
suffered been told they're crazy
okay or given three four different
diagnoses and then you take somebody
like that and they tried everything
they've been on every diet they've been
to every functional medicine doctor
they've been to every single
conventional doctor everybody they can
under the Sun and then they try celery
juice for two weeks three weeks for two
months for thirty days for anything for
five days and they're like oh my god I'm
getting relief for the first time and
I've tried everything I have fifty
supplements piled up in my house in my
cupboards I got all this food I buy
everyday from all these different diet
plans I talked to all these different
doctors I'm online looking for
information and celery juice is moving
the needle and it's getting me better
and that's why it's here there's
something really important to understand
here health trends are not propelled
like this this is propelled because
people are actually healing that's the
difference this is this is an organic
movement this is a trend or something
more powerful above a trend and people
don't realize this yet they through they
sayers are too late for the party they
can complain and cry and say oh there's
no science behind it
they well what what else in there's so
many things there's no someone said
recently
well forget celery juice you have to eat
all the rainbow of the colors where's
the science proving that if you eat
every rainbow and the color that you're
gonna be you're gonna fix your chronic
illness where's that science there's no
science on that about what someone
actually healing a chronic illness
moving forward because they're eating
all the rainbows and the colors of
course you want all the colors in the
foods and you want all the different
foods I never said you know that would
be bad or good or not I said that's
great but celery juice is a medicine
that you can bring in to everything
you're doing and it's really changing
lives it's incredible I know I keep on
saying it's only because it's only
because it actually is working other
health trends are propelled by other
things there's tremendous monetary
behind it like monetary involvement
pushing that trend so you take all that
college and of course you
take all of that whatever it is so you
take all that apple cider vinegar so you
take it all there's there's money which
hey that's just how the world works we
know that and there's money propelling
that well you're the only thing
propelling celery juice is millions of
people getting benefits and telling
their story without being prompted or
paid to do it it's never happened in
history before and if you don't like
that idea I don't know what to tell you
if you don't like the idea of there's no
science behind celery juice yet you know
what tell people tell that to someone
who suffered and struggled push through
their day and they and they realize see
when you get sick you realize science
and research doesn't have the answers
for chronic illness sure there's
life-saving medicine out there sure if
you get into a car accident there's
life-saving medicine I know incredible
ER doctors I know amazing surgeons
actually that do procedures that save
our lives in different do all kinds of
different problems we have but let me
tell you this right here Jay okay when
you're sick and you're struggling and
you're suffering and you've been to 20
doctors okay you realize fast science
and research dropped the ball somewhere
where maybe people don't know but they
dropped it and they dropped it hard
because people have they people have
been suffering and struggling there's
over 250 million Americans in the u.s.
that have a symptom that won't go away
getting worse and that's where we're
heading we're heading into the land of
the lost getting worse with chronic
illness and so you've quickly learn
especially young you're 20 years old 22
years old you get sick you're 25 years
old you get sick you quickly learn right
there science and research isn't what
everybody was saying it is when it comes
down to wait I got Lyme disease what do
you mean is it getting better it's not
I'm trying this I'm trying to
antibiotics wait now I have multiple
sclerosis or what is this symptom
anxiety it's crippling depression and
you realize science the research doesn't
know anything about these things so then
where are we then someone said to me Jay
they said there's no science and
research to your information there's no
science of research - celery juice and
I'm like oh I didn't know science of
research fixed every chronic healed
person I didn't know we have nobody
suffering I didn't know no one was sick
and going to 50 doctors and that's the
world today celery juice is this barrier
breaker
it's
okay get ready because this is one of
the most powerful tools that's gonna
move you forward my wife used to suffer
from asthma when she was younger and she
realized the harmful chemicals in
cleaning products would always make it
worse now she only uses healthy
eco-friendly products in our home and
it's so easy to make sure we're doing
that with growth growth collaborative is
an online marketplace that delivers all
natural home beauty and personal care
products directly to your door grove
makes healthier home products accessible
and affordable we shop grove for
non-toxic this soap plant-based skin
care and tree free bath tissue
everything available at grove is
healthier for you and the planet and
really works grove delivers natural
brands you light like mrs. Maya's seven
generation Burt's Bees and groves
straight to your doorstep we recently
got the mrs. Meyers multi-surface
cleaner in the lavender scent which is
my favorite spring scent and let me tell
you it keeps our house smelling so fresh
new customers will get a free cleaning
set in these limited-edition sense when
you place your first order of $20 or
more try grove now before this exclusive
spring offer runs out for a limited time
my listeners get a three-piece cleaning
set from mrs. Meyers spring scents a
free 60 day VIP membership and a
surprise bonus gift just for you when
you sign up and place an order of $20 or
more check out Grove and our special
offer at Grove Co /je that's grove CO
not con /j I have six different revenue
streams that I run apart from making
videos and throughout the years I've
learned if you don't know your numbers
you don't truly know your business we're
currently growing my business icon media
but the problem growing businesses have
that keep them from knowing their
numbers is their mix of business systems
they have one system for accounting and
other for sales and other for inventory
and so on it's just this big inefficient
mess that takes up too much time and
resources we just started using NetSuite
by Oracle it's a business management
software that handles every aspect of
your business
in an easy-to-use cloud platform giving
you the visibility and control you need
in order to grow with NetSuite you save
time and money by managing sales finance
and accounting orders and HR instantly
right from your desktop or your phone
that's why NetSuite is the world's
number one cloud business system and
right now NetSuite is offering you
valuable insights with a free guide the
seven key strategies to grow your
profits at NetSuite comm /j that's
NetSuite comm /j to download your free
guide for seven key strategies to grow
your profits yeah I loved Anna and I
agree with you like I think everything
you just stated there I I agree with the
fact that science and research is
measuring that which has happened yeah
right it's rarely we call it
breakthrough science but it's not
breakthrough because it has to watch
something for a significant amount of
time or years you know what I mean like
there is these ideas or these unique
things that come out they get tested
over time yeah it's never that you can't
test something in two seconds and talk
about it yeah and science the research
is amazing we need it I'm Holly I'm all
for it in fact some incredible things do
happen from it but they're usually
theories that have to be proven somehow
correct right and then you have the
investors behind it to prove it and then
in the end you don't know we have
because it changes 10 years later we're
often wait we were wrong now we have a
whole bunch of things we're saying now
this it's this way and that's happened
so many times really difficult for
people you know it's incredible I mean
at the same level I've seen people say
why drink celery juice you're better off
just putting a little bit of sea salt or
a little bit of Himalayan rock salt
right in your water and it'll do better
because something because research in
science doesn't know anything about
celery juice research and science
doesn't know anything about putting
Himalayan sea salt in your water and
then that's in the same breath they'll
say something research and science
hasn't even studied yet either and
they'll say well make sure you do this
put salt in your water it's gonna help
you so much better than celery juice
because there's no signs behind celery
juice it's almost like do you know what
you just said is incredible so oh I
didn't know there like so much for
celery juice well you know you know what
it is is that you could put a lot of
time on that
hating on celery juice it doesn't sound
like the Westing thing when you have
something this powerful and moving
forward to this degree and this fast you
got all the stores selling out what's
there celery it's all it's all going you
got farm scrambling to actually grow it
as fast as they can and then and get
land up and grow it and grow it you know
farms don't make any money I mean
they're all subsidized most of them you
know how they struggle as it is when you
see all that people start getting this
they're getting nervous
and then when celery juice is helping
millions of people really fast it I
think it's a threat in many ways to so
many industries so ya know there's love
for celery juice tons of love out there
but also you got the people saying hey
wait a minute
leave your fiber and pulp in there no
leave your fiber and pulp and all the
other vegetables and stuff use it but
this extract it like a medicine right
tell me about some of the stories that
you've seen in your life of people
transformations whether it was frantic
illness just tell me a couple one or two
stories or examples where you've really
seen people who feel transformed through
sellers use debilitating eczema
debilitating psoriasis where people
suffer they can't get it they can't wear
clothes they can't leave the house
because they can't preclude thing on
their skin and they're just doing the
steroids they've tried the steroids you
try different things they've seen so
many doctors they suffer their skin is
cracking and bleeding everywhere
and celery juice brought into their
their lives and used correctly like I
talked about in the celery juice book
and it gets them to clear it up they
start to see benefits
I mean miraculous case is reversed it's
it's incredible I'm not just talking
about it got a little bit better I know
many cases many of them over the years
and now today where they get rid of that
debilitating Aksum a-- where they were
crying they cried they had to be on
painkillers they couldn't even move
their arms and legs and they got through
it on the other side of it also
debilitating chronic fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia multiple sclerosis getting
people forward with that people with
Lyme disease celery juices all of a
sudden the very thing
that's now changing everything with
their diagnosis that they've got or no
diagnosis where doctors are confused and
they're just sick and their home and
they got high anxiety and depression
I've seen the celery juice do something
for these people but for decades I've
seen it before it exploded before the
publication of the medical medium series
books in 2015 you know it was already
building it was a quiet storm I think it
snuck up on everybody it snuck up on the
world I think this health trend or
whatever we want to call it now has
snuck up in a way and became a tidal
wave just last year it finally became
this big tidal wave and I always say to
people you know what if you learn about
it now and you know it's it's important
so yeah and I also think that it's a
tidal wave for those who are really
looking and then there is a lot of us
who are interested but we don't find out
until someone brings it to the front of
our minds the front of eyes you know
what I mean they're gonna do it's like
until someone really breaks it down for
you like you have in this book like
until someone really explains you the
process of why it works how to take yeah
like you've done in this book like I
feel like even then if that doesn't
happen a lot of these trends just go
over our heads absolutely right and for
most people because these trends feel
like such it's still too hard yeah oh
it's like a short-term thing like oh I'm
gonna watch some I watch the video I'm
gonna try it for a week yeah but I don't
have a process yeah tell us about the
process that you outlined in this book
and how you've made it so simple you
know there's there's there's a there's
over a hundred questions always asked
how do I drink silver juice what do I do
- I do I put my blender with my other
food it's all that it has to be by
itself it has to be by itself in a
certain amount sixteen ounces is where
you want to be to start with it's
sixteen ounces of it jeast fresh very
fresh very important so you could you
sit at home fresh okay you can go to a
juice place I do recommend don't do the
HPP thing which is high pressure
pasteurization I mean there's nothing
wrong with HPP I mean you can do other
juices that are HPP you go into health
food stores grocery stores you see all
those drinks they look like they're
really fresh they look like they were
just done yesterday but they got a date
on them for a couple of weeks because
it's it's high pressure
pasteurization now I noticed that that's
happening with celery juice don't get
confused by that don't pick that one
because if you pick that one it's gonna
be hindered it's gonna lose its its its
healing benefits his potency exactly you
want it juice fresh go to your juice
bars go to health food stores that will
juice it right in front of you make sure
it's done right there do it at home and
that's where the magic happens so there
is gonna be there there is a confusion
developing where you may get you get the
bottled celery juice now sitting on
there people like well that must be as
good as everything else and if they're
not experiencing the benefits they they
need from drinking it then they get they
get forwarded by it they get pushed off
by it yeah so yeah that's just one
example I answer lots of questions can
you do while you're pregnant yeah you
can do celery juice can you do it while
you're breastfeeding yes so there's just
so many questions these are just a few
yeah and asked me consume straight often
it can't be that yeah you want you can
wait a little bit you can wait hours
later you can even wait a day later have
it in the fridge have in the fridge but
and that will still be better than say
something like in the store at high
pressure pass ratio you know when there
were two shut with a long show and
ideally straightaway yeah ideally that's
gonna have the most fancy yeah and talk
about what's in it that hasn't been
discovered yet and if someone says well
how would he know this voice he hears
how would I know epstein-barr was the
cause of thyroid problems and I was the
guy long before talking about it
everywhere talking about it the doctors
talking about it then publishing and
everything else and and and now they're
saying hey science research just found
there's a link to Epstein bar to thyroid
disease thyroid disorders same thing
with the celery juice yes I hear the
information I know what's in it there's
something called sodium cluster salts
that's the antiviral that's the that's
the pote that's the phytochemical
compound it's this sodium cluster salt
somebody might say well what is that
it's a subgroup of sodium undiscovered
by research in science you think that we
only have one type of sodium that's it
on the planet and that's it no there's
more than that it's a subgroup it's a
different thing going on in celery it's
not in anything else they're gonna find
it down the road they probably won't
call it sodium cluster salts are not
going to give me that credit
not gonna Pat me on the back and be like
yeah you're they're gonna name it
something else obviously but that's what
it is
it kills bugs here's the deal I'll just
simplify it people are sick
because they got bugs that's it
your your Hashimoto's thyroiditis your
rheumatoid arthritis bugs cause this
it's not your body attacking itself it's
bugs it's pathogens
that's viruses it's bacteria so when
people have their fibro there's a bug
involved that's what this is chronic
fatigue syndrome there's a bug so what's
going on is we're filled with bugs I
know that's kind of annoying we got
viruses like epstein-barr we got the
simplex is in us wreaking havoc we got
the hhv-6 is we have shingles viruses we
have bacteria and people have these bugs
in them we live with them they create
inflammation meanwhile the food Wars
that are going on the vegans against the
Palio's and and the keto and everything
else and everything fighting each other
but nobody realizes you guys are all
dealing with Epstein bars dealing with
strep a caucus you're dealing with strep
and button different viruses and the
reason why celery juice is working is
because the sodium cluster salts and
celery juice is annihilating a lot of
bugs and people it's breaking it down
it's killing them it's cleaning up their
livers it's getting the bugs out of the
livers and that's why they're
inflammation is actually getting better
and better Wow amazing and I was looking
at something you were saying about how
it's blood it's also stopping the
vicious cycle of addiction yeah yeah
which is incredible how does that work
well yeah that seems like a totally
different challenge in in my head at
least like from an uninformed point of
view so how is celery juice even helping
people with addiction well you know what
it revives your liver it starts restore
it your liver can actually hold more
what's called glycogen glucose because
that's what it needs to do it needs to
store glucose and glycogen the very
thing that we it's the very thing that
runs our blood sugar throughout our body
when our blood sugar is in unstable and
it's imbalance we tend to fall prey to
addiction really easy plus electrolytes
we all lack electrolytes so when you eat
a food of any kind of you drink water
you get some electrolytes naturally
occurring any kind of food you eat
there's a natural occurring electrolyte
going on there
well those are pieces you're collecting
all day long what did you have for
breakfast there's some electrolytes in
it what did you have for lunch there's a
few more electrolytes in it and then
dinner a few more or during the day
there's electrolytes in things we're
consuming but we're never getting enough
at once we're never getting the whole
electrolyte the whole lecture like
family at once right on the neurons
right with the neurotransmitter
chemicals using them right all of this
happening celery juice is like a
complete electrolyte still undiscovered
by research and science of course
research knows that there's antioxidants
in celery juice of course they know
there's vitamin A and K in there it's
funny and I've heard somebody say maybe
people are getting better because the
vitamin A and K and I'm like what about
the vitamin A and K that's in every
other fruit and vegetable what about all
of that plus all the supplements people
are you're still not moving forward why
is this doing it does it have a
different vitamin A and K what it does
have those has a full complete
electrolyte it goes to the brain fast
and easy clings on to the neurons
revives tired dehydrated
neurotransmitter chemicals start to
actually bring those back so your
electrical impulses fire fast so you
could be quick talking so you can
actually hear when you can actually
think what you're saying it all comes
the brain fog goes away everything
starts clearing up and those when those
electrolytes hit those neurons and spark
that fire and those electrical impulses
are cruising through those neurons and
that is precious that is like gold right
there and that's another reason why
addiction could stop so you want to
bring it back to addiction when those
electrolytes are hitting all those
neurons your electrical impulses are
firing and running through those neurons
and all that's happening and you're
starting to think clearer and your brain
fogs back and down you you don't fall
prey to addiction right there that alone
there's the blood sugar starts to
balance out because your liver is
healing getting better your glucose
reserves in your in your and your liver
are storing back up so it can control
part of the blood sugar problem that we
deal with because it's not just the
pancreas and when all that's happening
you get stronger your mind gets stronger
your control gets stronger you get you
know what you take control over your
life and that's what celery juice if you
want one
simple thing for me right there you know
what use celery juice to help take
control over your life absolutely
because it can it can be one of those
tools I'm not saying it fixes everything
in anything in one shot I'm not saying
this is literally the miracle that will
fix it all
no because everybody else is doing good
things this is that thing that pushes it
over the edge absolutely where you need
to go and that's why I mean your energy
and your your love for celery juice is
infectious and contagious I don't know
anyone in this room right now who is not
dedicated at least testing it but but
tell me about some of the lifestyle and
diet habits that can cause a conflict or
negate the amazing benefits of celery
juice what is it that we're doing in our
lifestyle or a diet that could slow down
or go against the benefits of celery all
right I'll tell you right now
look I know this is gonna get everybody
upset okay in the audience but probably
not everybody but most everybody if you
if there's something to take out of your
diet or wherever you stand whatever I'll
ER on whatever diet belief system you
are that you're that you're involved
with subscribe to whatever it is you
take you need to take eggs out so
chicken eggs have to come out of your
diet now I hate to be the breaker of
this news or the person that has to
break this news to everybody but what I
want to tell you is the most important
part the most important part of this
podcast probably for anybody to take in
is we live with these bugs inside of us
that create all of our illnesses whether
it's not happening now say we're younger
but it'll happen later when we're
turning 40 it'll happen later when we're
45 it'll have whatever it is we have
these bugs and it's like the viruses and
the bacteria the pathogens that are in
us eggs feed the pathogens bottom line
no matter what you believe in out there
whatever diet system whatever you
believe in protein and macros whatever
you're talking about in your life that
you believe in whether your trainers
whether your nutritionist whether your
doctors whatever it is just know that
when you eat the eggs it feeds the
pathogens and I hate to break it to
everybody but pathogens come from
sources they come from places they come
from petri dishes they come from labs a
long time ago and you know how they were
they were raised by being fed food one
of the foods that fed them was chicken
eggs we eat the eggs we feed our viruses
and we get sicker slowly over time
celery juice is getting you better
it's killing pathogens but if you keep
on feeding your pathogens then it's kind
of working against you right so that's
powerful tool right that's it yeah I
mean I've been in exit 16 years but I
had no idea that I've never heard anyone
raise doubt about eggs before yeah well
you're it's information you're not gonna
hear anywhere else and that's that's why
people heal with medical medium
information is because it's finally new
information information that is
different that no one even knew or
thought about or understood that's and
that's one of them right there same
thing with the gluten the gluten or the
gluten everybody thought gluten was just
inflammatory nobody knew gluten actually
is inflammatory because it feeds the
bugs too I brought that to town was what
anybody likes that or not I brought that
and they may say hey well he hears a
voice oh I don't want that information
but no guess what they'll find that out
pretty soon I think even more people are
talking about it I think doctors are
talking about it now because I've been
putting it out there for so many years
the reason why people get sick on gluten
and then someone else doesn't get sick
on gluten because you realize you can be
90 years old eating gluten they're all
your whole life you could be like 50
years old you've you've eaten it your
whole life you never had a problem with
gluten and then someone can't even eat
it at 16 18 25 and they have to take it
out because they have certain pathogens
inside their body they're feeding off of
gluten itself and then creating
inflammation it's not the gluten
creating it so that's why that should be
out too
you know you should get that out too but
there's a reason you should get gluten
now it's not like oh well he's just
saying no gluten cuz everybody says that
no there's a reason I know that reason
learn about it it'll help you absolutely
amazing and are there any other
lifestyle habits that could work against
this it could work against where people
are not absolutely what I mean
absolutely I'm not seeing the benefits
absolutely it could be you could be toad
eating something incredible incredible
no an amazing question thank you for
asking so here's what you got to be
concerned about when you're using celery
juice to not bombard your celery juice
with food
too close to it if you're drinking your
celery juice and it's not an empty
stomach you're not getting the benefits
it has to be on an empty stomach 16
ounces on an empty stomach is critical
that's what morning is best if you got
to do the afternoon fine and try to keep
food away from it so if you any
lifestyle of eating whatever you have
dotted with any kind of food lifestyle
whatsoever you just need that celery
juice on an empty stomach away from
those other foods that that right there
is critical the morning or evening makes
a difference
any mornings always best more than that
empty stomach in the morning that
hydrochloric acid gets built up
everything you know and that's another
part I want to talk about that digestion
and how the HCL builds up when you're
drinking celery juice why it builds up
how the stomach glands receive the the
celery juice and how they actually
recharge and give you hot you strong HCl
hydrochloric acid and then you break
down your food and your food doesn't rot
inside of you and you actually get
strong what your digestion and your
bloating goes down that's another thing
too that's really powerful wow that's
that's super powerful I didn't had no
idea yeah so with with the with having
in the morning how long often do you eat
breakfast okay you know try to give 20
minutes 20 minutes 20 minutes after the
celery juice is great okay half an hour
probably even better you know somewhere
around 20 minutes to a half an hour I
like a half an hour really being solid
like that but if someone needs fuel and
they're doing something or they're
running out of the house or whatever I
totally understand it but try to do
empty stomach try not to do coffee with
it try not to put anything in that
celery juice if you throw apple cider
vinegar in it you just killed it just
killed it you know how could you throw
something else in it I saw somebody out
there saying I'm gonna put my collagen
powder in here I'm like you just
destroyed your celery juice you're not
gonna see the benefits so you can't yet
you have to keep it clean
I'm not multiple times per day just once
a day no you do the celery juice once a
day but I like a lot of people that have
chronic illness do it twice a day
okay 32 ounces do you know at the
beginning 16 ounces do 16 ounces the end
of the day
absolutely and try not to have it with
food that's the goal but the truth is
you get the celery juice in you any way
you possibly can you're gonna get some
benefits but these are maximizing it
this is why the books critical the book
gives you all the information to how to
really do
this right if you think there isn't a
lot of information to it wait till you
read the book and then your mind is
blown and you're just like oh my god I
can't believe what can be done with
celery juice including like oral
therapies and stuff for problems that
people have like they have you know
ulcers and all this stuff in their mouth
and this book is actually explained so
much and here's the most important part
I loved about this book is that there's
almost 200 symptoms and conditions I
talked about inside this book and what
southern urges can do for it and why
it's working so if you have something
you're suffering with I talked about how
the celery juice is helping you hmm
and I loved one of the things I do love
about the book seeing is I don't think
there's ever been an audio file that has
the word celery mentioned more than this
right now which is awesome which I love
but what I love about the book is you
also have a whole chapter dedicated to
if people can't access celery and
alternatives that they can take yeah
which I thought was really refreshing
yes this is you know it's a book about
center would you be like hey if you
can't get it I mean yeah and I don't
know why people can't get it but maybe
you can tell me that but if there are
places people can't access it you
suggest some alternatives yes share
those with it yeah absolutely there's no
way to get celery juice you cannot you
can't get it it's not even possible or
just it's just not around and there's
nothing you can do you know there's
other things you can do I like the
cucumber juice it won't do what celery
juice does I don't want anybody confused
but it does some different things it
hydrates the body in a different way
than anything else could out there you
know it does hydrate the body it does it
does things that are really good for us
it's very cleansing very purifying it
won't it won't do what celery juice does
but it could be something you do for a
week before you can find the celery
juice again so you know juicing
cucumbers is actually helpful and so
when someone said to me recently I said
okay so what so let's just start juicing
different things and that's good no no
no those cucumber juice doesn't kind of
do it it just isn't but it's it's one of
those backups to get you by for a little
bit like a week or a few days and and
and but that's about it I mean honestly
it's it's gonna have to be the celery
juice or it's really in the end no-go
for what you're really yeah what you're
really and I know you cover in here but
I wanted to raise this because I know so
much not just of my audience but just so
many people in the world today we're
reading studies about it all the time
mental health
depression anxiety stress what celery
juice doing on a deeper level for stress
anxiety and depression well it's the
ultimate adrenal you know stabilizer
that's the that's the other thing with
this celery juice
I mean it's so helpful yeah you got the
letter lights got the sodium cluster
salts you got the heavy electrolytes in
there and in adrenals need that that's
so important the other thing is brain
that that's the other thing when you're
dealing with electrolytes and and
neurotransmitter chemicals electrical
impulses and that's in neurons you're
talking about distressing because here's
the deal
we our brains get dirty toxins in them
heavy metals mercury aluminum cadmium
lead nickel copper they get into her
brain you know someone said to me they
were like hey I don't have any metal in
my head what are you talking about he
said you ever have a fluoride treatment
did you ever have allergy I had tons of
those all through my life I go that's a
byproduct of aluminum right they're
byproduct of aluminum means it's still
aluminum it is part aluminum in a
different form it goes to the brain
directly so when you have that fluoride
treatment you're getting aluminum in
there it's in there has it left no
there's nothing you're doing in your
life to remove it we also get mercury in
the brain really easy we come into this
world with mercury in us from our
forefathers and foremothers well that's
the whole thing our ancestors give us
mercury it's passed down it doesn't just
it doesn't leave it gets constantly
passed down generation to generation to
generation and it's it's in US and it's
it's in our brain sits in other places
and it even could trigger off higher
anxiety and people it can trigger off
depression having that mercury having
those other metals inside of us and we
collect them here their inner water
there in other sources we just get it in
us celery juice helps loosen up those
metals stop stops them from oxidizing so
they don't rust in our brain so they
don't break down our brain tissue or
glial cells and other parts of our brain
it's critical it's it's just such a
critical part of anxiety and depression
celery just does help with it and I love
that because we're talking about this
simple antidote in one sense yeah which
is actually impact mental and physical
health you
which is actually quite rare usually we
look at them as separate usually it's
true okay I do this for my body and I'll
do this for my mind yeah but here you've
got one thing that's actually helping
both yeah I've run across so many people
and seen it throughout the years and you
see it on the internet now my depression
is alleviating you know my anxiety is
getting better things are getting better
just from doing the celery juice
crippling anxiety is so debilitating
people can't leave their houses I've
seen people suffer so greatly over the
years you know and when you don't have
anxiety you may not realize what they're
going through you may not know what
they're going through when you don't
have anxiety because it's hard to like
get into that person's shoes when you
don't have it yourself it doesn't really
make sense what do you mean you have
anxiety what do you mean you can't
function like what do you mean you can't
get out of the house and get in the car
and you got to take anxiety medications
because here's a deal when you're when
you haven't been to a lot of doctors and
you haven't struggled with your health
it's hard to get in touch with the ones
that are struggling it's an entirely
different crew you know when I get
interviewed a lot when media interviews
me and I tell them chronic illness
people are suffering they're struggling
they never put that in there ever that's
why I have tremendous respect for your
podcast for what we're doing right here
because I'm able to talk about the ones
that I fight for every single day so
that's what I do that's what I do I
fight for the people who are chronically
ill and they don't get heard that's the
thing I've been a messenger for them
I've been a voice for them all these
years to the people that are smart
enough to know science and research
hasn't had the answers for them and
doctors know that they haven't had the
answers that they needed to move forward
and they suffered it struggled anxiety
is one of those pieces of it it's
crippling it can really stop someone
from enjoying their life not enjoying
working you know functioning taking care
of things going to school and you know
I've seen people hey my anxieties
starting to alleviate a little bit more
and it's worth everything it is worth
even if you knock down that anxiety down
50% 25% the difference is someone being
able to stay out all day or so
good day in their career or start
writing or do something with their life
think about how empowering that is and
celery juice when that does that for
somebody with anxiety and you see that
happen you're like oh my god I'm gonna
fight for this I'm gonna fight for the
celery juice I don't care what it takes
I'm gonna put myself on the firing line
let's get this stuff out there more and
more for people absolutely and I love
what you said that it's really been this
organic emerging thing like it's
happening organically it hasn't been
funded it hasn't had any money put into
it an investment it's been organic it's
very first of people which is amazing
but you've also had organically a lot of
celebrities and influences reach out to
you yeah yeah who've become fans of your
work and supporters of you yeah and you
know I was I was asked recently too
about this and he said well what are
they be what are they being paid to do
it said there's not one celebrity I know
I know but it's a really good point
because people think it they're like
what are they getting out of this what
do you mean what are they getting us let
me tell you something about celebrities
that I know anyway okay I'm gonna be
straight out okay they actually care
about people suffering they actually
have tremendous compassion they actually
care about their fans their followers
they care about people on the planet and
they really really do it matters them
they're drinking celery juice it makes
them feel better and it gets them
healthier right so they could be a more
powerful voice in what they're doing
changing the world but it's it's even
more than that the celebrities i know
james van der beek and you know and and
Jenna Dewan and so many others you know
and Sly Stallone and so many others they
care about people they want people to
feel better it matters to them and if
they've been through pain - absolutely
they've been through a lot in their own
lives all and so when they see people
you know that are struggling that are
getting better because they know they're
spreading that that that information
about celery juice it matters it matters
to their souls you know it matters to
everybody to know that people are
getting better celebrities have
tremendous compassion the ones I know
unbelievable people and and it's just
great that they're doing you Pharrell
you know he's he's he's out that he
cares about people
hears about humankind and this this
right here it's not measurable this is
it's unmeasurable it's just it's that
powerful it's that incredible I love him
and this podcast has been such an
education for me
I hope that everyone listening and
watching I've been able to ask some of
those questions that you will be
thinking about too because I'm coming at
a point of just learning being a student
and someone who wants to experiment with
this so all of my questions have been
from my own desire to be an experimental
with this I'm excited to see its impact
on my life and I'm hoping everyone
listening and watching today has got
some of the information to get you going
but I really really hope that you're
gonna go and get the book because the
books gonna break it down for you
yeah the books gonna stop you from doing
a one-week test which is a fad to
actually making it sustainable and one
of the biggest reasons I see the
difference between us having a habit
that we do for one week versus
sustainable is one we're deeply
convinced of the reasons when you've sat
here and you've read this book and after
you've read this book if you haven't got
every reason you need to go and drink
celery juice the rest of your life then
that will be harder to give up yeah
whereas if you just think oh yeah I'm
gonna try this this is cool juice
podcast I loved it and you can try
you're gonna try it for a week and
you're gonna start yeah so take my
recommendation go get the book get the
deeper reasons and insights on how to
take it why to take it and and what to
do with your life around it to support
it and that will start making the
biggest difference is I feel I feel so
we're gonna end this episode with the
final five these are final five
questions usually answers are either one
word or one sentence maximum so this is
gonna be a big challenge for Anthony
because he's sorry what I love about you
just have so much to say but it's all
like it's it's all in depth like it's
real your insights are awesome so I'm
gonna try and get you to one word or one
so question number one is what's the
biggest health myth you've ever heard
there's so many of them tell us your
favorite one alright metabolism okay god
yeah I'm gonna let you tell me
metabolism just means that were alive
the discovery of metabolism just means
that we're alive we're living we have
blood throwing flowing through us okay
and that no one really knew that really
metabolism was just the discovery of hey
you're you're eating you're burning fuel
you're a living organism you're a living
being right but it's not why people gain
weight slow metabolism
and that's one of the greatest myths out
there they're gaining weight from livers
that are stagnant and sluggish
everybody's livers are bombarded they're
toxic that's why I came out with liver
rescue the book because their livers are
challenged and they're filled with
toxins and that's what puts the weight
on that's what makes things get the
lymphatic system gets swollen with water
the weight comes on the belly fat it's
from a liver of weak liver sick liver
stagnant sluggish liver it's not from
metabolism still to this day I'm sure
everybody in the audience right now my
god who's been totally just fed met
metabolism metabolism for the last 30 40
50 whatever it is they're just gonna be
all upset but I just trying to drop the
truth on you on that one it's a liver
you take care of your liver and that's
that you take care of that and then
everything starts getting better with
whey and what we think is metabolism
problems amazing yeah you're going to
the root I like you okay question number
two if you could give everyone in the
world
I have it to do for 30 days apart from
drinking celery juice every day what
would it be that the heavy-metal detox
movie I offer okay get the nettles out
get them out of the body that's the key
I mean okay there's so many different
habits you can do I get it there's so
many for your consciousness so much for
your just mental so much different
physical ones you can do but getting
metals out that's the habit right there
get some cilantro in you you know get
some get some spirulina in you know the
right ones the ones I care about because
those are the ones that actually work
you know get some things in you pull
them metals out I talked about it the
heavy metal detox smoothie that's the
one right there
you pull metals out things change too
it's like it's like the celery juice the
heavy-metal detox smoothie get into that
habit get into the hey look get into the
celery juice happen there you go awesome
question number three what are the top
three things on your grocery list
celery's okay that's a given right yeah
that's a given okay another one wild
blueberries okay that's the second one
right there because wild blueberries the
antioxidants that's a whole nother food
wild versus cultivated blueberry that
the one in the clam shell the pint-sized
clam shell that is the cultivated
blueberries the big blueberry
it doesn't do a fraction of what the
frozen while the blueberry you go into
the freezer section and you go in there
you'll see different brands I mean I use
the Wyman's one there's another brand
that's there use that there's different
brands but you get the frozen wild
blueberries that's the my god.that food
so celery that and I love apples okay
got to be a must yeah yeah yeah give me
another one let's have one more thing is
it alright papaya
okay that's another one and then wash
okay people call it ma che but Maj it's
a green it's an amazing green there's
not enough of it out there but you can
find it go to the health food store that
green is great leafy greens are good
awesome okay question four tell us about
the top three herbs that you couldn't
live with that lemon balm can't live
without it helps the neurological system
I've used it to actually help people
with anxiety depression of course but
also with neurological problems tics
spasms tingles numbness its antiviral
too like celery juice when you bring
that lemon balm in there it's a big deal
that one nettle leaf another incredible
herb without a doubt I've been
recommending it since I was a kid
because of spirits it's literally is
right off the start recommending it so
nettle leaf that's anti-inflammatory of
course why it also is antiviral in its
own right great medicine and of course
cook immuno to tumeric you know which is
spice wouldn't arise them but tumeric
it's in it's amazing so I like that
won't even know it's you know but you
got the yeah lemon balm nettle leaf and
then licorice roots another one amazing
and the final five question five what's
the best way we can all start listening
to our body more because I think for so
many of us we are constant radical but
changes right we're constantly just like
you could be going through pain and deal
and just having it there and sit there
for so long without listening how do how
do people people we may not all be able
to listen to spirits or channel or learn
but how can we listen to our bodies
better there's one thing that people
have to realize it's one of the most
incredible ones that when we get sick
it's not our body letting us down it's
not our bodies being faulty it's not our
body being a bad
physical you know aspect of us it's not
it's it's not our body giving up on us
and most importantly it's not our body
destroying us or going after immune
system or going after our organs or
going after anything what I'm trying to
say is your body doesn't hurt you it
doesn't destroy you it doesn't go after
anything and we need to know that our
body never attacks itself and it's the
first thing everybody thinks they think
their body's failing so no matter what
okay
there's one of the greatest tools is if
you start experiencing anything mental
emotional physical your body is not
going after you are hurting you or
attacking you that's the most important
that can protect you because we can't
there's there's people out there you can
tell them what what to do on how to
listen to their body or anything but
they might they might not be able to do
it or they might be too busy or forget
it but what they will do is their body's
letting them down the minute as an
athlete you think your body's failing
you anything it's just in life when
we're sick we think our body has now
said hey we're not helping you I'm not
helping you and that's it if you could
if you know your body loves you
unconditionally it's there for you it's
fighting for you in ways you cannot even
imagine that can bring you peace and get
you to where you need to be faster and
better well I was not expecting that
once but I love Don so that that
judgment that we place on our body
immediately is actually one of the most
negative things it is like that Lang the
most that language around am i he's
attacking me my body's letting me down
my body's failing yes my body's not
strong enough
yes that language is actually
programming us to lead to not doing
anything about see it's an evil seed
that sits inside every human being so no
matter what you're doing whether you're
meditating on top of the mountain
wherever you are it doesn't matter the
minute something's going wrong you go
right to my body is now wait a minute
turning against me in the moment and
what do I need to do to fix it no it's
not turning against you that's how it
works that is such an awesome once man I
absolutely love that I hope that message
is resonating very very clear the way we
think about a body talk about our body
talk to our body itself is gonna have a
huge impact
Anthony William thank you so much
Anthony's new book celery juice the most
powerful medicine of our time healing
millions worldwide is out right now you
can order it from all the good places
where books are sold
the medical medium on instagram the
medium on facebook where else can they
find you hey there and keep medical
medium calm also mental me right clear
yeah yeah that's a great place really oh
make sure you go follow Anthony on
social media at the medical medium
across the platforms medical medium calm
and make sure that if this has given you
some insight on why celery juice could
be so powerful it could truly change
your life go and get the book today as
well thank you so much honored to be
here no it's not you man I'm excited to
do a reading with yet some advice I
genuinely am i I want to do that can't
wait here we're gonna do it yeah
absolutely I think I think what you said
is so true that until we've really go
through pain and that's how it was for
me too I think because I'd I felt like
I'd mastered my mind and neglected my
body yeah and so when my body started to
give me signs that it needed more love
and care that's when I started to
realize because while you're young you
just feel like Superman yeah and you
feel like nothing's gonna happen and so
I totally get you and so if anyone is
listening and you're like well I haven't
got any problems yeah or my life's not
too bad that's the time to start really
taking that it is yeah Thank You Anthony
thank you so much I'm so grateful to
meet you happy to have you here hope
that was good for you
and we're not gonna edit anything else
everyone's gonna get the video of this
conversation if you're listening right
now you're gonna get it as it is we
haven't edited anything we haven't taken
anything out that was awesome that was
Anthony will you make sure you go follow
me on social media thank you so much for
listening or watching again we love you
being a part of this community make sure
you tag me and Anthony on Instagram or
Facebook or Twitter and share what
you've learned from this podcast we'd
also love to see your journeys if you
want to map your diary of taking celery
juice for a week two weeks a month
hopefully for life and for the rest of
the year then make sure you tell us
about it
tag at medical medium and tag me as well
on Instagram I'd love to see those posts
thank you again so much take care see
you soon