shades uh fructose intolerance right
we're gonna talk about that one food
sensitivity so i didn't really cut into
that
i gotta cut into that more talk about
that more diet belief systems
my paleo my animal protein my vegan and
my plant-based what am i what belief
system do i go into blood type this
that what do i do so there's that too
right carnivore
gonna talk about carnivore a little bit
that's gonna be interesting
keto plant-based like i said so so much
to talk about all of that
i'm anthony william the medical medium
number one new york times
best seller of hey number one new york
times best-selling author
of the book medical medium book series
right here that cleanses the heel right
here by the way
51 off amazon.com if you want a
comprehensive comprehensive guide to
walking through healing
um it's on sale 16.99 unbelievable in
the u.s
so anyway get it free at the library
just you know what i would go if you're
if you're like hey i don't know if i
want to start doing anything i want to
do and just go go to library get the
book out for free don't even pay for it
um so yeah so originator of the global
salary juice movement too okay
and i wanted to say that if you're new
here so you know what's going on
and um you know the bottom line is guys
there's a lot to talk about tonight
and i think it's critical because
everybody's getting brain screwed
for years about theories so theories are
totally brain screwing people
so bad it's unbelievable oxalates
right that theory lectins that theory
fructose intolerance
that theory and the list goes on and on
and on and it's squeezing people it's
squeezing them
you know in the whole bit so i really
want to talk about that
so let's head there you guys ready let's
just start and i'm going to answer
questions too so
um hey i'm glad everybody's coming on
incredible 85 days
dan yet 85 days on celery juice are you
kidding me that's the greatest thing
it's incredible i'm so proud of you
i got my comments coming up on the side
of the screen so i'm just looking over
here
this monitor here you guys you just
received your book rhonda you just
received it yesterday
so proud of you so happy about that hey
patricia hi from australia hey hi from
australia amazing
um um queen you said you're so
confused stick around we got so much to
talk about you guys
all of the stuff i'm glad everybody's
coming on here so there's so much
information we need to cover
you're just you're just finishing up day
9 of the 369 incredible
so many great comments coming through
here oh my god you guys are incredible
um so you have jill you have all the
books
proud of you amazing amazing amazing
it's four years uh karen four years on
celery juice
and you know you're staying with it
right because it's helping you because
that's the whole thing
because it's incredible you know it's
what happens and then when you go off it
you're like you can tell
it makes you feel so good makes you feel
good so let's let's go into some
information now
look you guys ready okay because i have
a question for you
so listen to this question here think
about this right now right
think about this question as we speak
okay so
if everyone is worried about what
they're eating
because they have a symptom or condition
so when you get a symptom
when you get diagnosed with a condition
you're worried about what you're eating
right
you know and the whole bit and you're
told that
it must be your foods causing the
problem right
it's your food causing the problem of
your symptom it's the food causing the
problem of your
of your condition you know and because
that happens to so many people where
they're you know they're worried about
that and then they get told hey
you know it's these foods then how come
so many people
are allowed to eat whatever they want
how come so many people are allowed to
eat
whatever they want to eat you know and
they can eat it for years and years and
years and years you know i hear about it
all the time
you know my parents can eat anything
they want at age 80.
my grandparents can eat whatever they
want in their 90s and they still are
eating whatever they want they could
have gluten they can have
anything dairy products all this stuff
they can eat junk they can have packaged
donuts
packaged donuts not even not even a
donut from a donut shop
and they can just eat what they want to
do and how come they can do it and
they're not worried
what about that whole thing they're not
worried about what they're eating what
they're not eating they're not
they're not even thinking about it okay
and then
what about people who like now like
everybody's worried they got a symptom
they got a condition
and now they're worried it's incredible
because there's a reason
and maybe look maybe you're one of the
people that you're thinking like well
you know the foods got me sick and
that's why i finally got a symptom
that's why i finally got a condition
well so for you
it took to your 20 to get a symptom and
the foods got you sick
why but why didn't they get like someone
who's 85
sick why can they eat all the gluten
they want to eat why can't they eat
everything they want to eat
look so um die you said my parents 96 94
so annoying they're uh they won't they
won't listen
oh my god you know and they're probably
eating what they want right 94 and 96
years old
and but yet you can be 40 years old and
we're worried about what we're eating
because we're dealing with symptoms
because that's the whole thing
everybody's getting symptoms now young
and younger and younger and getting
sicker with these symptoms and
conditions
and but the thing here there's a lot of
issues about this so
let's talk about that right now too okay
and
you know it's there's
how come how come someone doesn't get a
symptom
and how come somebody does get a symptom
all right science and research
both conventional and alternative don't
know why
someone gets tingles numbness mysterious
you know mysterious tingles numbness
aches and pains it's mysterious
dizziness vertigo okay
uh floaters in the eyes that are
mysterious
burning skin jaw pain that's mysterious
it won't go away
neck pain that's mysterious and won't go
away migraines
fibromyalgia all the different other
conditions oh my god you can list all
the autoimmune conditions science
research doesn't know it causes eczema
psoriasis all these different things so
it goes on and on and on
okay and but here's the deal
science and research both conventional
and alternative believe
that your body's attacking itself and in
the i'm telling you right now mark my
words on this
just mark them right here and right now
all right
that pretty soon coming up every single
symptom
every single condition somebody has
every single symptom every single
condition somebody has
it's gonna be called autoimmune no
matter what it's going to be rare few
symptoms or conditions they're not going
to call autoimmune they're going to
package up
everybody's mysterious symptom
everybody's mysterious condition
and they're going to lump it into
autoimmune because alternative
conventional
research in science medicine only
believe
that your body's destroying itself that
your body's creating this auto antibody
and it's going out to destroy your
glands like your thyroid condition is
because your body's attacking it
your eczema your psoriasis because your
body's attacking your skin it's
attacking your body
so that's how it's done right let's see
alternative medicine though and i'm
going to get into all the food stuff
it's so important we're on all things
food tonight
alternative medicine believes
that foods are triggering our autoimmune
foods are a trigger because alternative
medicine
science research doesn't know why we're
sick either
they don't know why we're sick either so
they're like well gluten is triggering
off your autoimmune gluten is triggering
off your body's problem well
interesting well how come all these
people that are older in the generation
they're 90 years old they're 85 years
old they're 80 years old you guys
and they're not getting triggered
by gluten they're not getting triggered
by dairy products they're not getting
triggered by something okay
it's because the younger generation now
has a lot of bugs and a lot more
toxins a lot more bugs and a lot more
toxins that's why
and so when you have a lot more bugs and
a lot more toxins
you end up getting symptoms and you end
up getting them early on
you know getting them at 19 years old 20
years old 22 years old 25 years old
you know getting at 35 40 however it is
you end up getting all these symptoms
all these conditions
you get diagnosed with the lyme you get
diagnosed with the fibro the multiple
sclerosis
uh you get diagnosed with fibromyalgia
all like i said that all these
rheumatoid arthritis you get all these
different diagnoses and
and that's what happens in the end okay
and so now
we're in this point where we have to
choose a belief system a diet belief
system
because we're being pushed into it we're
being pushed into having to choose
a diet belief system should i go vegan
should i go plant-based
should i start a keto diet should i
start a keto vegan diet should i start a
keto
animal protein diet should i do
carnivore what should i do and you know
and everybody's got their own tips
they're like try carnivore try keto
try this try that and there's all these
different belief systems we're getting
pushed into because we have no choice
because we want a quick fix we want an
answer because we're not getting an
answer from science or research to why
we're
really sick with all these different
symptoms and conditions so we get pushed
into this so now we're getting to where
now we gotta pick a diet belief system
we get pushed into
we end up getting totally brain screwed
in the end that's what happens and it's
really sad
because you know in the end it's not all
about food
it's not all about food in the end
it's about something else it's about the
bugs we have
inside of us is what it is
it's about the epstein bars it's about
this the shingles viruses it's about
cytomegalovirus it's about if you got
the herpes simplex one
the cold sore a fever blister a fever
blister is simplex okay so that's herpes
right
so you got the fever blister okay well
when that fever blister heals up and
it's gone
the virus still creates symptoms it
still can give you headaches it still
can give you jaw pain it still can give
you neck pain it still can make you feel
weird
it can still give you some braid fog it
can give you all kinds of stuff
but the bottom line is we have all these
different pathogens in
all of us we have the epstein bars we
have
sediment virus we got the simplexes we
got the streptococcus
and because of that and because so many
people are dealing with so
many pathogens and pathogenic issues
where we're we end up like
looking in all kind of alternative
sources because eventual medicine
doesn't believe food has anything to do
with anything
alternative medicine believes that
food's important
food is medicine alternate medicine
believes food is medicine
alternative medicine though still though
doesn't know
why everybody's sick with autoimmune
conditions so they call it autoimmune
the body attacking stuff they still
don't know why they'll say maybe it's
leaky gut
maybe it's something else maybe it's
candida maybe it's this theory maybe
it's that
and they're still confused so what
happens it leads to people to start like
okay
what do we do we gotta we gotta think
about foods get off of processed foods
get off of
uh fried foods get off of greasy foods
get off of fast foods start with that
you start feeling better you know get
off of that thing but it squeezes us
and we end up squeezing down to now
we're afraid of all kinds of things to
eating and then we gotta pick a diet
belief system
think about it would anybody go vegan or
plant-based would how many people would
really go vegan or plant-based if they
weren't
pushed that direction because they were
having a symptom or a condition right
of course you get the crowd that the you
know the animal rights crowd of course
and the animal rights crowd
they'll go vegan or plant-based some of
them will go vegan or plant-based
because
you know the whole thing of killing
animals and all that okay for sure
they'll
be that crowd but the majority of the
plant-based movement which is still
small
the majority of the vegan movement which
is still small
they're they're all about their symptoms
end up pushing them
into more plant-based or into
plant-based
because why would they ever do that same
thing with like with the paleo crowd or
the keto crowd or the animal protein
crowd you think
they would actually eat really clean
like they do and and
and keep out the processed foods and
keep out all the bad stuff and keep the
gluten out for good
and you think they'd actually do that if
they didn't have to because they weren't
developing some kind of symptom of some
kind they weren't developing some kind
of issue of some kind
you think they wouldn't i mean people
would want to eat pizza every night they
would want to eat pizza a few times a
week they would want pizza on their
weekends
they would want they would want all
their different
foods their mac and cheese all these
other things that's what they want to do
but people are getting pushed into
eating healthier and healthier
because their symptoms are actually
driving them there
and then alternative medicine will tell
them well
gluten is causing your condition well
that's interesting because it didn't
cause your condition for the first 15
years
in your life and then you develop
symptoms years later it wasn't the
gluten that created
that symptom 20 years later it wasn't
it wasn't you know something else that
created that symptom 20 30 years of
years later
so what did it and it's these pathogens
i'm talking about in the whole bit
so you know if we got a lot to cover
we're going to talk about oxalates
oxalic acid we're going to talk about
like spinach
people are worried about spinach
cruciferous we're going to talk about
that the gorgogenic foods
going to talk about lectins we're going
to talk about histamines
you're going to want to hang on for this
ride because this is a big night
fructose intolerance we're going to
cover that too so if you're somebody
that
you want to know about the stuff and i'm
going to be answering questions as we go
along some watching the monitor too
right here with all the questions so
um okay uh minerva
is it true that eggs feed viruses yes
that's medical medium information that's
where that originates from and yes it's
true
because pathogens were were created
they were raised in eggs and eggs
feeding them in the labs over the last
90 years pathogens were used i mean
pathogens
were basically raised using eggs as a
food
so what happens is when we eat our eggs
you may not feel anything now but as
years go on your eggs are
feeding viruses so once again it's not
the egg's fault
eggs were an amazing survival food and a
tasty one at that
but what happened is they ruined our
eggs the industries ruined our eggs and
i talk about that a lot all the time and
i talk about that and cleanse the heal
if you guys
get a copy of this you'll learn so much
it's unbelievable really
uh pamela says that's me plant-based
because of symptoms
pamela exactly and because you really
wouldn't be plant-based right
you wouldn't be if it wasn't for the
symptoms pushing you into it
same thing with a lot of people eating
like clean paleo and no carbs or
no doughnuts no cakes no cookies you
know like what no bagels with cream
cheese or whatever it's like
okay well we would stop those bagels and
cream cheese we would stop bagels and
butter
we would really stop that i mean no
people wouldn't want to stop their
bagels and butter and all that kind of
stuff and all that you know we do we
we're being squeezed and pushed into it
so i'm glad you i'm totally glad you
understand and
um so i'm going to cover look there's so
much to cover i'm going to talk about
oxalates i saw an oxalate question zip
through and zip up right there
and i'm going to talk about that too so
so much information i'm so glad you guys
are here hang on for this ride because
there's so much to cover
and a lot of info you know
when it comes to information about food
there's so much misinformation out there
and that's where we get stuck that's
where the chase happens that's where the
guessing games happen
that's where it's like we're totally
guessing and we're looking around at
every corner for a new thing or a quick
fix and we're like
what's what's the histamine foods what
are the histamine foods
what are the oxalate foods what are the
nightshades what are the
lectins what are the oxalates
so much information okay um so when it
comes when it comes to information about
food there's so much misinformation out
there we can call it smog
we can call it you know uh just
basically
noise we can call it noise too but
there's there's um okay so cheryl hey
cheryl
exactly you did this i was vegan for
four years
before medical medium and doing it all
wrong because really what is medical
medium information sharing
medical medium information is not about
a diet belief system
and that's the confusion out there i
noticed that some of the naysayers they
just want to package it up like oh he's
just a
there's plant-based information better
than his because he's a bad plant-based
what are you talking about like medical
medium information
welcomes all diets all diet systems
in whatever diet belief systems because
it's not about
it's about if you're going to be
plant-based be plant-based
exactly sure be plant-based so but let's
do it right
if you're going to be animal products
let's do it right if you're going to be
doing animal products
exactly because it's about other things
it's about other things
and so you got these food wars i always
talk about the the the
controversial food wars it's like the
animal protein people
you're all pissed off at the plant the
plant protein people
the you know the animal based diets all
you know they're all upset about the
plant-based diet so you got that whole
thing confusion going on meanwhile
they're all sick
you know it's incredible i'm reading out
a ton to heal right now meanwhile all
sides in the food wars which is
like all sides got all the different
food diet belief systems okay
meanwhile everybody still gets sick
everybody still gets their symptoms they
still get their conditions they don't
know what's causing them
you know and you'll learn about what's
causing your symptoms and conditions and
cleanse the heal so i mean if you get a
hold of this good library get it for
free if you don't want it
it's 51 off at amazon.com right now you
can check that out
um us and i mean it's a medical textbook
it's got 75 recipes in there over 200
symptoms of conditions in there
amanda says lovey anthony you saved my
life
you know um means a lot to me means a
lot to me
told my liver was so full of cancer on
march 18th
i'd be dead or dying by now liver rescue
gave me the answers
i've looked for on a 10-year cancer
nightmare trip
i'm writing about it bless you bless
your heart amanda god bless you
i'm so proud of you so proud of you
really am
um so let's go into a little bit more of
this too
so you know it's funny that the most
vocal people
that are on social media okay
are the people that feel the least sick
where it's as far as
vocal in the point where they're vocal
and they just want to cause like
shouting matches right like you know you
know the animal
protein people they're killing animals
the animal protein people are saying to
the vegans you're starving your kids
you're just feeding them lettuce and you
know it's terrible what's happening out
there you know meanwhile they don't know
what's going on with
why you have your tingles and numbness
your aches and pains your
your itchy skin your hives your chronic
acne
they just don't know what's causing all
this everybody plays these guessing
games with foods and it's locking us
down
to a total brainwashing situation
where now we're like where do i run from
now and and how it works so
um so the whole the whole point is here
is that
when you're dealing with multiple
sclerosis or eczema psoriasis acne lyme
disease endometriosis pcos
you know fibroids depression crippling
anxiety
crippling anxiety it's critical to know
why you're sick
and why you have a symptom and why we
have a condition
so okay you guys when we get our first
symptom
we don't like how it feels right you
don't like how it feels when you get
your first symptom
so naturally we want an answer to why we
have a symptom
like you want an answer like i want to
answer now why i'm
got this or i want to answer to why i
have that you want an answer
to why you have a symptom right both
conventional and altered medicine they
don't have the answers to why we're sick
but yet they still have help they still
can help they still can do all kinds of
great testing they still have
they still have band-aids they still
have all kinds of stuff and of course we
have
you know we have you know really really
powerful like neurosurgery surgery we
have all kinds of different things we
have great surgeons we have great
medical
you know science research in other areas
but when it comes down to autoimmune and
chronic illness and all these different
symptoms and conditions
we got the bloating and we got the
gastroparesis and the digestive problems
and we got constipation you know without
knowing why and we have crohn's we have
colitis we have ibs
we have all these conditions that
science research doesn't know about we
have eczema psoriasis vitiligo
scleroderma rosacea and science
researchers know about any of these
and so when we're uncomfortable and with
these migraines and
ocular migraines and floaters in the
eyes and we don't have answers
we we get to a point when we're looking
for answers
auto you know alternative science
alternative uh alternative medicine will
try to say well your foods are
triggering it they're triggering your
body
harming itself that's not correct that
is
incorrect information
incorrect information that's why someone
could be 60 years old eating what they
want all the gluten they want
and they are not getting all these
symptoms a 25 year old is getting when
she's getting
crippling anxiety horrible depression
itchy skin
hives everywhere you know all these
different things and
and then the 60 year old isn't getting
any of that
so basically what it is is people
they don't like being sick so it makes a
person miserable
so when you're in your 20s or in your
you know 30s whatever it is
you get trained that maybe it's oxalates
maybe it's lectins what foods are you
choosing
you start you you know you get trained
to run away
from the symptom you're experiencing to
try to find a quick
fix in some kind of category maybe it's
night shades
maybe it's the potato maybe it's
something else
and it can put us in a corner like trap
us like a rat
and stick us in the corner you guys
right and it and then it's no fruits
and you can't have a certain vegetable
then you can't have cruciferous you
can't have cauliflower you can't have
broccoli
you can't have cabbage you can't have
brussels sprouts you can't have a
nightshade you can't have
you know anything with a lectin in it
you can't have a bean you can't have an
oxalate you can't have spinach you can't
have a leafy green you can't have mush
you can't have kale
you can't have um lettuce for some
reason and so we're told you were even
told that herbs are problems
like herbs like chamomile it's part of
the ragweed family
so if you're you know a drag weed then
it's cameo is bad too and you get
squeezed
everywhere you go and that's a big
problem and when you get squeezed
and you get brain screwed and you get
squeezed and brain screwed
you're in less fruits no potatoes no
herbs no vegetables
no leafy greens no grains of any kind
no beans and then you can even get
squeezed as far and i've seen this
happen to
some people not a lot of people but you
get squeezed this far
down the rabbit hole into the carnivore
diet so now we're in just the carnivore
diet
okay where it's just meat and only meat
and only meat and only meat
and that carnivore diet can go with meat
turkey and chicken
and bacon or pork
but then it could minimize or it can go
to lamb and meat
and chicken and then all of a sudden you
lose your chicken and then because
you're just squeezing down you're like
confused as to your why you have
symptoms
and it's such it's such a brain problem
it's like it's not a brain problem it's
such
it's such a confusion and then you're
getting squeezed down
because the more you squeeze down and
you're not touching a fruit a vegetable
a leafy green
and because of somebody's theories or
because of how you're feeling
because you're feeling symptoms and you
don't know why you don't know what's
triggering it is something triggering it
is something activating it
and you get squeezed down right down to
the carnivore
and then things are coming down because
you're
minimizing it you're going so mono foods
and the reason why some people can do
this and they can go carnivore where
they're only on
meat only red meat is because
red meat won't feed the bugs and i
talked about this that's why people say
oh he's a plant-based guy only no i'm
not always
he's he's a whatever animal protein guy
no i'm not i'm neither of anything i'm
just about the answers
so you can get better so here's what it
is like the carnivore people get
squeezed right down to just meat
itself and by default and by accident
they're start they're feeling better for
the moment and they're feeling better
for the moment you guys
because they're not feeding the bugs
that are creating
all their symptoms that are creating
their fatigue their migraines their
aches and pains
their floaters in the eyes their tingles
are numbness their dizziness they're not
feeding the bugs and they're holding
back
leafy greens and fruits or certain
fruits and certain leafy greens and
vegetables and herbs
that would kill the bugs and guess what
when you kill the
bugs you feel them sometimes you feel
similar symptoms to what your symptoms
are you feel
the same symptoms to what your symptoms
are when you're killing the bugs
you know and this is when you're off
processed foods too and all this stuff
and what happens is people don't realize
that the reactions they're having
at any given time while they're eating
healthy foods or healthier foods
is because they're cleaning out years of
bug
toxins that are stored in their liver
they're cleaning out years of bug toxins
that are stored
inside inside their liver
you know inside inside their body inside
their spleen
inside their organs and that's what's
happening unless they're feeding
the bugs with foods that actually feed
the bugs and that's what i talk about
like in
cleanse the heel i talk about that's
what the information is know what foods
do feed things
tammy ross i thought the extra fruit
would make me gain weight
i'm losing weight just fine on your
program thank you so much
incredible tammy everybody gets thrown
into fruit fear
it's one of the things that they get
thrown into it's fruit fear
but it's it's theories about fruit
that create fruit fruit fear it's
theories
about all these things but what happens
tammy is fruit
helps to kill off your pathogens it
helps to get
rid of the pathogens it helps to clean
and cleanse
the liver it cleans up these things the
pathogen the bug toxins and you
end up in a better place when you're
doing the right stuff but what can
happen is so many people
they're so filled with all kinds of bugs
and toxins that the minute you start
cleaning that up a little bit
the minute you start bringing in those
frozen wild blueberries
and you start bringing in those bananas
you start bringing in that and that
leafy greens and more lettuce and you
start bringing in that cilantro and that
mosh and that kale or whatever it is
that spinach
and you start bringing all that in
you're going to be sweeping stuff
out of the intestinal tract lining
people have
rancid fats and rancid proteins for
years
sitting on the inside of the linings of
their intestinal tract
and in that in that mess that's inside
the lining of the intestinal tract it's
been there for years okay
there's a lot of different kinds of bugs
and it's sitting in there
and the minute you start you and it
gives you symptoms all these things give
you symptoms but then you start to clean
up and you start to heal and push that
stuff out
you start to wash all that stuff out of
you with the celery juice
you start to push all that stuff out of
you to get it out of your system and and
when you do that you might feel similar
symptoms the same symptom a little bit
you're like wait a minute
that was the dizziness i had the other
day i have it today is it because i just
had
a leafy green and you know we end up
running from
foods to avoid ex
experiencing something that might be
slightly uncomfortable
instead of solving the problem you see
how important this is
you know so it's a temporary band-aid
to keep on minimizing foods minimizing
foods minimizing foods because medical
medium information brought all these
foods back
this was going on for years stay away
from fruit stay away from oxalates
stay away from this stay away from that
stay away from night shades medical
medium information you guys
brought back nightshades brought back
the fruits
brought back the leafy greens brought
back all this stuff nobody even ate
leafy greens brought all this
in so you can have all these choices to
plug into your animal protein diet or
your plant-based diet
that's the difference and no one else is
doing that and that's the problem so you
got these food wars
everybody just takes a side of the aisle
nobody knows why anybody's sick
nobody knows why people are struggling
with a symptom condition and they're all
throwing pot shots
and theories and and and on those
theories it's back to fructose
intolerance
oxalates oxalic acid
salicylic acid i mean you can go on
there's so many of them i'm probably not
even mentioning right now
so that's how it works so ironically all
diet belief systems end up like
band-aids too
unless you know what to really avoid
because you know what's wrong
i've said this over and over again you
have to know what's causing your symptom
or you're just doing a band-aid all the
time you go plant-based that's not an
answer
unless you know what's causing your
symptom if you know what's causing your
symptom
then you can actually live on your
plant-based diet get
symptom-free and heal and if you if you
know your symptom
on an animal-based diet of any kind you
once you learn your scent with your
symptoms
causing your symptom you can work on
healing and then you can work with that
it's
using the right tools but here's what's
happening
everybody's picking the diet belief
system nobody knows why anybody's sick
out there
i mean come on and then the theories
start throwing around everywhere
but as the carnivore diet goes you get
so squeezed down
and you eliminate every single thing
possible because you're feeling an
uncomfortable experience
from eating a piece of fruit possibly or
eating a leafy green
because it's actually cleaning up the
very crap in your system that's giving
you the symptoms to begin with
but what you're doing is you're doing a
temporary band-aid by pushing all that
stuff away
so that you don't feel it and you get
pushed and squeezed into a corner
and now you're just eating meat alone
but in the end that's just a temporary
band-aid you have to remember that
and and you know and and remember you
had these symptoms
to begin with so these symptoms begin
with oh
end up coming back one way or another
and
one way or another they'll find their
way there temporarily the meat that
you're just stuck on only mono eating
won't feed the bugs in the moment
but what happens over time you'll lead
to deficiencies your immune system drops
down because
there's not enough stuff in meat by
itself
to keep you going there's just not
enough and
and i'm a pro meat guy i'm a pro
plant-based guy there's not enough
antioxidants to stop you from
aging and just meet by itself so you can
do it temporarily the carnivore thing
temporarily
but you'll end up getting deficient
you'll end up you know weighing too much
down on the liver the kidneys the heart
because too much protein and fat
constantly
and it's not a balanced diet like
everybody's always saying or you want a
balanced diet or you want a balanced
diet oh yeah this isn't a balanced diet
but i get it i get it
we get scared and we get pushed
into elimination you might be like
anthony i'm not on a carnivore diet what
are you talking about
well wait a minute are you on a
plant-based diet of all kinds of
different
things well you must be avoiding
something you already squeezed yourself
back
you had to get rid of gluten you're on
plant-based diet you had to get rid of
some of the grains probably
maybe you're on a keto animal protein
diet you got rid of something that
you're not eating anymore right
you clean up something no processed
foods you're getting squeezed a little
bit
and a little bit but you got to learn
what's causing you the problems which
got you there in the first place to even
want to eat right
to even want to eat good to even want to
care you have to know what's causing
that
so you can even get to that point so so
let's go let's keep on talking because
we've got a lot to cover
you want to be free of symptoms and
conditions that are making you
suffer and you know it's so
important to know and and so anyway
let's let's keep on moving on
for sure look everybody would love to
have their buffalo chicken wings
everybody would love to have their ice
cream everybody would love to have their
bread and butter
their donuts everybody would love to
have their cookies everybody would love
to have their cakes
everybody would love to have their pizza
every night or every other night come on
you know everybody would love that but
reason why we get squeezed out of that
because we got symptoms and we don't
know what's causing them if you want to
know what's causing some symptoms
take a look at this book get it free at
the library if you need to get it
on sale at amazon which is incredible
the sale they got going for this book
right now
let's talk about lectins let's go into
lectins a little bit really important
area
so lengthens is really funny okay over
the years
i've witnessed tens of thousands of
people get their lives back
i witnessed people healing before
my eyes i witness people
now healing before my eyes
more people have healed their symptoms
and conditions
by learning the truth with the medical
medium book series around this world
than in any other book or place or venue
or anything
okay and i've witnessed this throughout
the years
and witnessing it now and it has nothing
to do with lectins
okay interesting countless people
healing
millions of books around the world
because of grassroots healing
not because of pr and marketing nothing
like that no money behind it
and people healing and telling somebody
else about
these books okay and healing and it has
nothing to do with concerns about
lectins
interesting you know it's helped
countless
lives before even the publications of
these books because i worked with
thousands of people before these books
and i witnessed them heal before anybody
knew of the word lectin okay very
important
but for some reason some reason the
lectin
leaders didn't know they missed that
memo
they missed the memo that countless
people have healed from medical medium
books
tens of thousands of stories you can see
out there
thousands of people have seen over the
years and
the reports coming back of how many
people are healing
hmm without anything to do with lectins
interesting right
but electing leaders of lectin
theory-based
leaders seem to just miss that memo
there because they think everything's a
lectin problem
oh that's interesting it's not you know
lectins is one of those things that's so
silly because lectins aren't responsible
for digestive issues they're not
responsible for
digestion problems they're not
responsible because it's not lectins
that cause a problem it's not lectins
and fruits it's not lectins and
vegetables it's not lectins
and all this stuff it's one of the
stupider theories it's actually one of
the
it's actually one of the stupidest
theories of all the theories
that's the irony to it and i don't care
who i get upset or not or what not it's
tell you guys the truth
or don't tell you the truth what is it
gonna be you know what i mean that's why
i've always
always always been like i'll say it like
it is and you know and it's it's funny
on another note anything i've done in
media or anything else they they edit
every single thing
i say practically because i say it like
it is like this all the time
but the bottom line is it's about the
pathogens it's about certain toxins
that's why we're sick
it's not about the lectins critical
to know and that's these theories are
ridiculous and it'll
that will squeeze you you'll get lectin
screwed
okay and then that will it will squeeze
you
and squeeze you off and then you're now
now you're in that mindset
it's unbelievable what can happen all
right so let's go into oxalates a little
bit
okay so
patricia says we love you they know i
love you too you guys are amazing
julie you just did one day at advanced
369 you already did you did your first
day of advanced 369.
incredible advance 369 is really getting
people like to a place like an
unbelievable place
if you guys don't know about the
advanced 369 get the book that's my
recommendation
carol says since doing your suggestions
i can walk again for miles a day
oh my god i love knowing you can walk
again for miles
oh my god but i can't eat very many
forgot the rest of the question it went
up already
but you can walk a day for miles
incredible
and that's so good to know let's talk
about oxalates a little bit um
had amazing results i missed that
question too just the quest
the questions are cranking up had
amazing results on two weeks potato mono
eating cleanse
so joanna the mono eating cleanses
incredible guess what if you got scared
off about nightshades which is
ridiculous that's actually a theory
that's not
accurate on any level with no evidence
behind it if you ever get scared off
about nightshades like potato being
afraid of a potato
you lose your chance to heal and that's
what happens
that's what i'm talking about the belief
systems not just the diet belief systems
but the bad
theories they stop people from healing
and that's the difference between the mm
information and so i'm so proud of you
i'm so proud of you
um you you know with celery juice
and and different in a different mono
cleanse anybody can choose too they can
choose a different model cleanses and
the celery juice with it the amount
you can just move forward so i'm proud
of you proud of you
so there's oxalates in everything let's
talk about oxalates
everybody's like spinach high in
oxalates something else
high in oxalates oxalates oxalates and
you'll hear this okay another another
like mental trick another mental trick
from
from the industries and alternative
industry
not knowing what's causing your symptom
or condition it's so
sad okay so let's go into this a little
bit first of all
oxalates are in everything every single
thing
they're in meat how come nobody's
complaining about that
how come nobody's talking about oxalates
and meat right
they're always picking on spinach
they're always picking on a fruit a
berry they're always picking on an
apple they're always picking on a plum
um they're always picking on a pear
let's see what else they pick on oh
vegetables pick on all of all the
vegetables oxalates and all the
vegetables
but there's oxalate in meat cheese eggs
dairy products there's oxalates in
butter there's oxalates in every human
being
we're loaded with oxalates animals we
eat
are loaded with oxalates okay
oxalates are in everything everywhere
talk about a total total trick
played on everybody it's unbelievable
well wait a minute wait a minute i react
to an oxalate how do you really know
you're
ever reacting to an oxalate the only way
you could ever know or ever find out
is if they separate the oxalate and make
a pill out of it
filled with oxalates and they give you
that pill
that's loaded with oxalates okay
and they and you just or you drink a a
glass of oxalates it's the only way
you'll ever know
so somebody be like well i react to
oxalates you know i had
this apple where i had this wait a
minute how do you know you're not
reacting from the food you ate the night
before
that wasn't that wasn't an apple how do
you know you're not reacting to
the body cleaning out some toxins bug
toxins and toxins of different kinds
how do you know you're not reacting to
that how do you know you're not reacting
to something else like
what about plug-in air fresheners what
about
all kinds of other things that are
happening what about scented candles
what about somebody's cologne i've seen
somebody's cologne
make somebody sensitive sick in an hour
where they're literally just on a couch
with a splitting migraine because they
were breathing in somebody's cologne
you know maybe you're just reacting to
the bug poisons that were flushing out
of your liver
when you eat a cleansing food for the
first time in a long time
you know you don't know and so what
happens is the ultimate trick the ox
lake game
is one of the ultimate tricks of all
time and it really
just sucks it does you know you and and
if you have symptoms already
they're going to come and go no matter
what until you actually go to the root
cause
so until you actually go to the root
cause of your symptoms and conditions
and you know what's causing them can you
actually
like even understand and that's the
whole thing that's really hard for
people look
it's a guessing game saga over and over
and oxalates are involved in that and
let me tell you something interesting
there's antioxidants in all fruits and
vegetables
that cancel out oxalates that's another
thing too
so what about that whole thing um lisa
said maybe you're allergic to celery
question mark
all our bodies are different uh thus
some
allergic to one food herb item and
others not just a thought
well lisa is that how it works it's a
good question though
i mean no i'm really glad you brought
that up it
everybody is different 100 so different
it's unbelievable
someone else has more mercury in their
brain causing their anxiety than
somebody else does
somebody else has more aluminum in their
body causing their vitiligo than
somebody else does
somebody else has way more copper inside
their liver that's causing their
excellent psoriasis
than than somebody else does somebody
has more streptococcus
causing their acne to keep on blowing up
left and right
so when they have a little bit of gluten
their streptococcus feeds off the gluten
and their acne is just exploding
somebody else might have two different
types of streptococcus somebody might
have two varieties of epstein-barr
causing chronic fatigue syndrome
and something else and lupus somebody
might have
more metals on one side of the brain
more metals on the other side of the
brain less metals on the other side of
the brain
somebody might have shingles causing
trigeminal neuralgia somebody might have
epstein-barr causing their glaucoma
and this is why we're all different
every last bit of us
and we're different with different
varieties of bugs different mutations
different strains how many different
kinds
different relationships different places
we get them from public bathrooms
different places we get from different
restaurants everybody's different
people have more battles in them people
have more bugs in them people have
different toxins
i know somebody who's drenched in
gasoline
and they're going to be different from
here on out because they were drenched
in gasoline than everybody else
because they have gasoline inside their
liver and inside their bodies and organ
organs in their body and organs and they
have gasoline all through them
and everybody's different for all these
reasons and then
we're different from how our nervous
system is with it all with how many
neurotoxins everything else
so dale said how do you put how do you
how do you figure out your root
cause well okay go to the library
okay get the book out for free
get the book out for free and start
learning what the root causes are
so dale start learning what they are you
can figure it out get get the book out
for free
don't even buy the book it's 16.99 right
now on amazon but you don't have to buy
it you can get it for free at the
labyrinth
and and and definitely um so oxidate
okay kidney stones okay julie a theory
a theory oxalates are in every single
cell in your body
they're in every single organ okay
so so oxalates are everywhere we
are an oxalate
it's it's it's we are we are an oxalate
okay kidney stones that's from the liver
the liver getting stagnant and sluggish
and that's from the intestinal tract
getting getting caked on putrified
proteins
lining up the lines of the intestinal
tract rancid fats lining up the linings
of the intestinal tract all
all running through okay it's from a
burden of protein
too over protein we are the society
or the or the human race just kills
itself with protein
if you're thinking hey sounds like he's
plant-based
no plant-based people will kill
themselves the protein
they'll tank the nuts tank the seeds
they'll tank the protein powders and the
protein shakes
they'll kill themselves of protein too
and they'll create kidney stones
um hi franco
i'm not sure if i should commit sorry
i'm not sure if i should comment because
i don't know
if you see them from whichever feed
you're looking at on your screen
oh hi franco hey you know but just look
you commented there for sure i'm on the
feed right now
watching the feed um it's great having
you guys here
so we don't know why we're sick you guys
that's the problem
so we get you know we get to a point now
where we end up with okay let's talk
about fructose intolerance
that's a whole other thing too let's go
there first of all
who ate that much fruit i know going
through the years every single person i
talked to that came to me who was sick
every person i've ever talked to every
person a doctor called me up and wanted
to ask about wasn't eating fruit
ever thousands of doctors have contacted
me over the years and still do
and they want advice about their
patients so i spend a lot of time you
guys
talking to doctors every day that's what
i do now
in between writing the books in between
trying to do all these this free
information i'm dumping out on you just
to free information all the time
and i talk to doctors all the time every
single day
and they'll ask me about patience and
you know and they'll say they'll say
you know and what happens is they're not
eating fruit
and but they're sick and they come in
sick who eats that much fruit
so the fructose intolerance
the the fructose intolerance thing is
just really
a whole it's a mistake all on its own
in a lot of ways and i'll talk into a
little bit let's talk about it first of
all one of the reasons why people get
the fructose intolerance tag is because
they have
insulin resistance but they have insulin
resistance on all sugar
they get insulin resistance on cane
sugar insulin resistance on
maple syrup insulin resistance on um
starchy vegetables insulin resistance on
raw honey or honey sugar cubes anything
they have insulin resistance you know
meanwhile
they're not going to say that they're
cane sugar
intolerant they're not going to say
they're
you don't hear that too often cane sugar
intolerant they're not maple syrup
intolerant
you don't hear that right they're not
honey intolerant right
so you don't hear that that they're not
honey intolerant okay
but they'll be picked on the fruit will
be picked on because the makers
of the fructose intolerance movement was
anti-fruit haters
upon fruit see where the bias comes in
hmm that's where the bias comes in
interesting meanwhile
are you talking about the bloop the two
blueberries you got in a blueberry
muffin years ago
are you talking about the strawberries
in a strawberry shortcake you had
were you talking about the fruit pie you
ate
out of a package when you were 10 years
old are you talking about the apple in
your lunch box
you talking about the banana you had
every other day
like you know what's going on here see
and and you know it's the whole thing so
elizabeth um i get breathing problems
thick air when i eat too much sweet
fruit or when i eat too much
okay so when you eat too much this is
not just a sweet fruit
or when you eat too much with other
foods too so elizabeth if you eat too
much
you end up having the breathing problems
okay i've seen that so many times
no intestinal problems always breathing
what is that it's better now after
cleansing and changing the diet
in celery juice nine months now see it's
better right and i'll talk about that a
little bit okay
and but still have to be careful with
some fruit
um or do i just go for it it's not the
fruit
that's the problem with that okay it's
it's what happens
fruit is very very water rich
it's very water rich okay and a lot of
people
their stomach shrink and they eat small
amounts of chicken they'll eat
small amounts of a vegetable a chicken
or something to eat small amounts of
food
and then when you eat fruit it's really
water rich too that's the one thing too
so when you have sensitive nerves
sensitive nerves because originally
you're dealing with pathogens and you're
dealing with pathogen toxins and
inflamed nerves so what i've
seen with people and i talked to doctors
and you can talk to your doctor about
this too this information what i've
talked to doctors about helping doctors
with
is that nerves the vagus nerve gets
sensitive it gets inflamed because of
neurotoxins because
we end up having symptoms these symptoms
are caused by pathogens pathogens such
as viruses such as ebv
and such and those kinds of viruses they
release neurotoxins in the shingles
virus and such
and these neurotoxins inflame the vagus
and phrenic nerve guess where those
nerves go
down your neck dump through the phrenic
nerve vagus nerve right down to your
stomach through your chest
and so what happens is if you fill up
with too much
food you can get that can't breathe too
easy get that tightness of the chest you
can get that all that because the nerves
feeling pressure on the nerves so yeah
you got if you down a whole melon
you're going to feel that pressure on
those sensitive nerves but the reason
why the sensitive nerves are getting
better and you feel less pressure and
less pressure and now you're doing so
much better
is because you've been cleaning up those
neurotoxins you can talk to your doctor
you know say hey
tell your doctor about this information
um but it's really
um yeah so so incredible um
so i'm really happy about this you know
so you guys i'm happy about you guys
being here so much information to talk
about i'm happy about all the comments
i'm seeing
this is so great so let's talk about the
fructose intolerance a little bit
so hereditary fructose intolerance hfi
okay hereditary fructose intolerance
another theory
another theory because they don't know
what's causing symptoms or conditions
so what happens is when alternative
science and research doesn't know what
causes your symptoms and conditions you
get all these
bias approaches that develop and these
bias approaches that don't know why
we're sick
and so they'll say well maybe it's the
aldolase b
iso enzyme so maybe it's all the lace b
is enzyme maybe that's it
maybe people are missing that and that
needs to be there for fructose funny
what that doesn't need to be there for
um
maple syrup that doesn't need to be
there for honey that doesn't need to
first of all no one loses that even if
someone's low on it they can eat all the
fruit they want
how about testing people with who are
eating all the fruit they want or low at
i've seen that accidentally happen did
you know i
saw i saw that alternative doctors even
told me but they said hey
alternative functional medicine doctors
reach out to me and they said you know
what i'm into this fructose intolerance
thing anthony i know you're not
but let me just tell you something
interesting that happened and
they said they said i i tested a patient
for fructose intolerance okay so i was
looking at their all the lace b
to see if it was low and and the patient
wasn't having any problems with fruit at
all in fact
they felt better eating fruit they did
better when they eat fruit
in fact they healed while eating fruit
through the recommendations i gave the
functional medicine doctor
for their patients and then the
functional medicine doctor said
i decided to run in all the lace b
test i saw enzyme tests to see if it was
low
and it was low but how come they were
able to eat fruit perfectly fine and it
got them better
so because all the latest be iceland's
on has nothing to do with anything
there's nothing to do with someone
eating fruit or not but this is the
accidents that happen
these accidents end up cheating people
so now you're afraid of a piece of fruit
now you're afraid of a berry
now you're now you're not getting the
healing you need now you're not can i
just tell you something
you need you need
to actually be you need to have glucose
in your body to live
you need to have sugar in your system we
can't
function without it we live
and breathe because of sugar if you take
out glucose
we die okay remove glucose from
us we lay there and we die did you know
that
glucose is critical to every cell in our
body it's how we build muscles it's how
we use our muscles that's how we wake up
in the morning it's how we function it's
how we think
it's how we can do things all of it
and so glucose is critical but what
here but what the makers of the fructose
intolerance theory don't know
is that when your body's filled with all
this
fat fat in her liver fattener organs fat
in our bloodstream fat in our intestinal
tract lining
we get a little insulin and insulin
resistance so then they'll blame
fructose intolerance on that
but they'll say fruits doing the insulin
resistance they won't say maple syrup is
they won't say honey oh fruit fruits an
attack on fruit
but you yes you get a little bit of
insulin resistance if you fill the fats
that's the whole point
when you learn how to get the fats out
of the liver when you learn how to clean
the fats out of the body the rancid ones
when you learn how to lower your fat so
you can get the glucose you need to
thrive
then you just there is no anything like
the worry about that it's crazy
and when we're loaded up with pathogens
when we're loaded with bacteria when
we're loaded up with
bugs and bacterial toxins and when our
liver stagnant and our liver is clogged
you guys
and we're loaded up with all that and
then
fruit ends up cleaning that out and you
might get a little bit of reaction you
might get a little bit of insulin
resistance
you might get a little bit of reaction
because guess what the fruits cleaning
that
crap out the crap that's been building
and you giving you symptoms to begin
with that ended up at the doctor's
office anyway
it's about knowing what the problems are
instead of getting
trapped in the theories from hell you
know i call them
theories from hell for a reason over the
years i said great another theory from
hell
to take people and make their lives
miserable let's talk about histamines
this is good tea by the way some
peppermint tea
so oh there's a lot of people they'll
get told they're sensitive to peppermint
are they allergic to peppermint they
shouldn't
have peppermint it's like are you
kidding i'm not talking about peppermint
candies here i'm talking about
peppermint tea incredible for you so the
but let's talk about histamines a little
bit so histamines
people think food creates
they're the cause of histamines they're
the cause of histamine reactions
okay it's not foods causing histamine
reactions what about the 90 year old
what about the 70 year old what about
the 80 year old who doesn't have any
histamine reactions and they can eat
everything under the sun
danielle i eat loads of fruit and i have
diabetes type one yet i'm on such a low
dose of insulin
danielle exactly and then if you
if you bring in all these fats you'll
you'll
you'll need more insulin you'll get the
insulin resistance
incredible brilliant you're eating a lot
of fruits
exactly fruits get rid of
diabetes over time they knock down those
numbers for type 1 they get rid of type
2 insulin resistance hypoglycemia
donna stern hi please tell me how to
find out why lectins cause my severe
migraines
no one seems to know what are you taking
just
is it lectins either you would never
know
really if lectins are causing a migraine
unless you took a pill that was filled
with all these leptins in it like elect
you know which you never want to do but
you mean the case because that would be
just ridiculous in general
anyway i would learn about what's going
on with foods i would learn about the
medical medium book so you really learn
about the lectin thing i was just
talking about that earlier
migraines you got you have to know the
cause of migraines so if you go in this
book
there's over 200 symptoms and conditions
you guys the book is on sale right now
at
amazon for nothing like 16.99
if and if that's too much money 1699
for this medical textbook go get it free
at the library you look for the cause
of migraines is what you do so i go in
here in headaches and migraines so i'm
in here now
in cleanse to heal okay so let's go in
here
headaches and migraines all right
lectins don't cause
migraines lectins don't cause headaches
and that's the whole thing there's no
science and research
that lines up a leptin to a headache you
can't
relax into a migraine because what about
all the people that can eat all the
lectins of any kind they want
all the leptins they want and they don't
have a migraine all the lectins they
want and they don't have a symptom
because and what about all the people
that healed from all their symptoms and
conditions that i was talking about
earlier
that never even knew about lectins
lectins are
just noise is what they are so we have
to be careful
true cause of headaches and migraines
i'm in here now and cleanse the heel
okay when physical injury is not a
factor and has been ruled out so
physical injury
has been ruled out for your migraine and
headache okay
commonly caused is over the 30 varieties
of shingles the shingles virus you can
talk to your doctor
bring them bring this textbook medical
textbook to your doctor
can talk to your doctor about it but
there's over 30 varieties of shingles
and some of those varieties many of
those varieties cause
migraines they affect the nerves it's a
nerve-based migraine
when you look in here okay when you look
in here but go to your doctor
and and and talk to your doctor about
this information so your doctor can
actually help you find out what's going
on
so epstein-barr can actually produce
neurotoxin giving people headaches
i've seen bar giving people migraines
and and what happens is the vagus nerve
and the phrenic nerves play a role they
get inflamed
toxic heavy metals actually create
migraines
toxic heavy metals as well so it's
really important to understand all these
different things
you know it's important to understand so
um all these different things can do
this and lectins are not why people have
headaches and migraines let's talk about
histamines right now
i'm looking through kinds of heal
there's over 200 symptoms of conditions
and in the chapter in the back of the
book you can see and you can find out
your causes and go to your doctor
and and and talked about that and you'll
see supplements and protocols
and how to use them and you can bring
that to your doctor as well
that's what i would do if i had a
migraine i'd take this book
i'd read it i take a look at it talk to
your doctor if you want of course
there's hundreds of customized
protocols in medical medium information
it's not one thing if you hear somebody
say
i tried medical medium you have did you
do 32 ounces of celery juice every
single morning
did you do the heavy metal detox
smoothie every day did you do the
morning cleanse or wait did you do the
369 advance cleanse
did you do the um did you do the
meditations in the medical medium books
did you do all these things that you can
customize
thousands of protocols in here so
somebody can get better because
everybody has something different inside
of them causing the problem
so let's go into this a little bit about
histamine people think food
creates histamines but no
yeah you can get elevated histamines
when eating foods but
why because certain foods
feed bugs and other certain
foods kill bugs
that's how it works certain foods
feed bugs driving up histamines
okay and certain foods
kill bugs and clean up their mess
out of the system which can drive up
histamines
it's a theory with nothing behind it of
knowing what's going on
the theory is histamines are created by
your body
your body's creating it it's kind of
like similar to autoimmune it's a
reaction occurring
you know you really don't know why they
have no idea but you know there's all
these different theories to why
but we end up lost and then we're stuck
in the noise now about histamine food
histamine creating foods
and we run from our
uncomfortable experiences with food we
don't know what's triggering what's not
triggering we don't know what's causing
it
we run we're running from our symptoms
we're playing hide-and-go-seek
we're now in a tree and then all of a
sudden lectins are scaring us now we're
somewhere else behind a bush and all of
a sudden histamines are scaring us now
we're hiding we're playing high go seek
it's unbelievable
rebecca i'm 76 days straight celery
juicing really incredible
have doubled the amount now last three
weeks and i feel the best i have in
nine years i love fruits thank you for
your information
i gave it a go listening to you a
hundred percent no
cheating and it works oh my god
incredible
so the biggest thank you i'm a fan and
share with anyone that will listen now
so you know when you hear well when you
get a chance if you hear somebody saying
he's just fruits and vegetables is
celery juice
therapeutically just fruits and
vegetables no uh plant-based people
weren't doing therapeutic celery juice
unless they got it from me
um animal-based protein animal-based you
know paleo diets weren't doing celery
juice
unless they got it for medical medium
information it's it's a tool
you can you know you can actually use
and or
the heavy metal detox um plant-based
people aren't doing heavy metal detox
um paleo people are doing heavy metal
detox medical medium information is not
uh just fruits and vegetables so you
know stick up for me when you get a
chance on that too
it's about information to how you can
therapeutically use tools
into whatever diet belief system you
have to seek and heal um
so i'm really proud of you really proud
of you so
um kaz um what clogs the liver
lipids made from what fructose
what what closet closet toxins
pesticides herbicides fungicides air
fresheners that are plugged in
sent to candles cologne perfume solvents
cleaning house supplies that are that
are conventional
um gasoline at your gas pump fats from
your foods lots of fats
whether they're bad fats whether they're
healthier fats they still clog up the
liver
pathogens pathogens too um pathogens and
their toxins the epstein bars the
shingles the
hhv sixes cytomegalovirus simplexes
whatever the strep all
that's all the stuff that clogs it up
not fructose
but it's a good question though
catherine eating fresh fruit and greens
gives me bloating
ammonia permeability with heavy heart
palpitations
migraines heavy breathing and making me
bed bound making it impossible for me to
push through
also getting fat free also getting fat
free until the afternoon gives me such
heavy symptoms
i only eat coconut milk
and nuts as fat but
still can't go off of it how do i make
the transfer to fresh fruit and greens
and less fat in a way that's not so hard
on my body
been off the no foods and on celery
juice for
one and a half years and tried enzymes
and aloe vera juice
and so on how do i how do i get on
um so you know ammonia
ammonia permeability something really
important to know okay so ammonia
permeability is when your hydrochloric
acid isn't strong enough to break down a
lot of foods this is
medical medium information only out
there okay so with about ammonia
permeability
and and that's mm info and so no one
knows about that so if you want if
you're new
this is medical medium information you
guys is all unique and original
i'm just saying that i'm not trying to
toot my own horn it is all unique and
original it's from above
and so it's important to know that i
don't say that enough so people think
you could just google something and it's
out there or something or you can just
stop on the internet search or something
no one knows about the ammonia
permeability they only think there's
such
a leaky gut or something and that's not
correct so
first of all that building up that hcl
which is the stomach gland so it's about
recovering those
over time it's not an easy thing and
when you have pathogens
in the system everything gets sensitive
the nerves get sensitive the bloating
can happen because of the
the hcl being so low i've talked to a
lot of doctors about this with their
patients
and um and so would would like
this is what i would do i'd go to my
practitioner and say i want to do
i want to do um one of the mono eating
cleanses
like just potato only so the celery
juice potato and some maybe some butter
leaf lettuce
and or some some romaine lettuce or red
leaf lettuce or something and i would do
i would go mono eating if i had this
because what happens is
with with any types of varieties of
gastroparesis whatsoever because that's
what
what happens with any with people that
with gastroparesis any types of
varieties of gastroparesis any type of
varieties of
of any kind of digestive problems and
bloating and all these things that
people have
it's the mono eating cleanses are
designed so read that whole section with
your doctor your practitioner
so you guys it so much information
so much going on i don't want you
blaming your body i don't want you
lost in the ball of confusion
with all the different theories they can
really
push you in to a corner
and then but yet the makers of the
theories don't know why you're sick to
begin with
so difficult so difficult
um it really is so i wouldn't drink any
water
i wouldn't drink any water that's got
the manipulated molecules man-made water
and man-made water machines or man-made
store-bought water or man-made mlm
pyramid scheme multi-level marketing
experiment scheme water businesses
that mess around with molecules okay
terrible idea terrible terrible term
personally my opinion
would never do it would never do the
alkaline ionized water either
so manipulated molecules manipulated
water with ionizing
i would not do it whatsoever in my
personal
opinion and what i've seen for years
causes more problems and more problems
and when you
and the only reason why people get they
think they get a benefit from one or the
other
is because they're already doing things
to counter it
they're countering it with doing good
things for themselves like getting rid
of processed foods getting rid of other
things but
in the end those waters will just those
mutated waters will just send you down
the wrong direction so be careful with
those i always say that i'm
a big a big um
not a big fan of them so
jamie you got cleansed the heel you love
it yay
incredible did you get it on the
discount the 16.99
51 off this is crazy i mean if you
didn't
no i'm just glad you have it but on
amazon.com right now in the u.s
um it says why do i get headaches from
the heavy metal detox the heavy metal
detox
smoothie can't give people headaches um
and did you have headaches before
um is this the first headache you've
ever had uh just questions to ask
questions to ask and these questions i i
talk to doctors about all the time
it's not the smoothie that gives you the
headache the smoothie the cleans out the
junk it cleans out the pathogens
the pathogens give you headaches it
gives people headaches and i tell
doctors that all the time pathogens and
toxins give people headaches
and when you're moving out pathogens and
doing something good and cleaning that
stuff out
it could it could possibly stimulate a
symptom you already have
but in if in and if you've never had
that symptom before
what else are you doing is it air
fresheners that are plugged in did you
get exposed to some bad cologne did you
get exposed to
insecticides pesticides herbicides in
your neighborhood did somebody
cover their lawn with um with lawn
treatment and fertilizer chemical
fertilizers next to you the other day
did somebody did your neighbors spray
their are you an apartment and the
downstairs
the downstairs neighbor in your
apartment just had an insecticide
treatment all through and a termite
treatment
there you can go list goes on and on and
on
about just how much could be going on
there so just
look at all that and see what's going on
um kayla oh i always drink the alkaline
water from trader joe's
um listen the trader joe's by the way
it's a great place
great place to get food and so forth and
everything but um but as far as out yeah
the alkaline
the alkaline ionized water um
it in my opinion overall alkaline
ionized water in my opinion
is not is not a great it's not a great
thing and i wouldn't do the bottled
man-made manipulated alkaline water i
wouldn't do that
either so i wouldn't do either or it's
not a good thing
i i talked about that in past i'm going
to do a big water talk again
so i'm going to do a whole nother water
talk and i'm going to go into it through
water purifiers water purification water
filtration
ions this that i'm just going to talk
about all of it eventually again
so brenda why do fresh fruits and
vegetables make my mouth itchy
an esophagus swell fresh fruits and
vegetables do
um which fresh fruit or which vegetable
too
does one do it more than another um
what's
you know what you know what symptoms are
you dealing with on a bait
is anything else make it happen at all
um that's not making it happen
because i just went through this whole
thing that what we do is when we
when we push away more fresh fruits and
more vegetables and all that
and we get cornered and now we're eating
very little things
to the point where eating basically just
meat or something it
because we're not getting a reaction we
what happens is the fresh fruits and
vegetables they sweep out the neurotoxin
so when you got neurotoxins we get in
trouble with the neurotoxins
and so neurotoxins are a big part of why
so many people are dealing with those
symptoms
um but you can you know those
neurotoxins can be trouble
and they can make all that happen but
what i would do is look
here's what i would do if that was
happening in me i i would get the book
look at the mono eating cleanse so you
can actually
you can you can go in that direction the
model eating cleanses that's what i've
always told doctors
to tell their patients and and and so
many doctors right now
that i have uh that i'm friends with
that i know that contact me every day
because the books are everywhere on the
planet so doctors just
they contact us non-stop um
and they want information for patients
and so forth and i've always told try
the mono eating
um and as you're healing you can end up
eating more so what i've noticed
that i've had doctors do this with their
patients is
when they do the mono eating long enough
they start bringing in more and they
don't get that swelling and they don't
get that reaction then they don't get
that swelling they don't get that
reaction and
therefore therefore
looking at all the different questions
spring water is amazing
patricia said same here
daisy when starting the heavy metal
detox i started getting dizzy and
lightheaded too
then it went away after pushing out all
the toxins exactly you pushed out all
the toxins
what happens is that disney
enlightenment lightheadedness
you know could have been one of your
symptoms daisy from like that you've
been dealing with on and off for years
did you ever get dizziness
at all before and then once you start
pushing that out then that's the whole
point you get that out and then you're
you're
you're you're free and you move forward
with your life and you know and if
you get more could be in there though
that needs to be pushed out
um so as far as different waters and
stuff
so andy andy you said which
kind of water then spring water is great
reverse osmosis is great
distilled water is fine but make sure
you squeeze lemon and put lemon in it
purified uh purified water spring water
um you know yeah a really good purifier
could be great i like berkey that's one
of the purifiers out there that i like
near g you can do that get a whole house
filtration that's
you know you can get a purifier but but
yeah i know the ionizers
don't like alkaline ionizers water
machines i don't like the also i don't
like the other thing too the molecular
like mutated water that's out there too
man-made molecular it's just
for the molecules it's straight it
actually changes the molecule structures
and all that just don't like that at all
so yeah spring water ro water uh
purified water sure whatever put lemon
in it
michelle said this is so helpful anthony
oh bless your heart i'm trying trying my
best to get you guys as much free
information as i can and so you guys
have every
opportunity you can too so it's
important i'm just
reading you know
masela says he said he drinks alkaline
water from trader joe's no i don't
no i don't drink alkaline water from
trader joe's
um so if i'm in trader joe's i
i buy the spring water that's what i do
so if i'm in trader joe's i buy the
spring water because trader joe's is
great spring water
but i don't drink alkaline water no
meaning man-manipulated created alkaline
water i don't personally drink
or recommend my opinion
um sandra i'm seeing a lot of uh
anaphylaxis
can you please explain you're seeing a
lot of that out there
you know um i'm gonna do that's gonna
i'm gonna do since we're running so late
tonight
that needs that needs um so many details
that i want to talk about
and i haven't i talked about it before
one time really thoroughly but i'm going
to talk about it again
so because it just needs more time it
can't be done in just a minute
so anyway you guys it's been incredible
i'm honored to be here um you know i
care about you guys and i believe in you
and i believe in your healing process
and i believe in the hard work you're
doing
and i'm proud of all of you have
compassion for yourself pat yourself on
the back
okay be easy on yourself keep a light
heart
know that i care and i know how hard you
guys are working
you know plans to heal i mean if you
have questions
you know learn about what's causing
symptoms and conditions so you can work
on healing and
getting the information and consequence
right here like
learn about that it's important and just
know i stand with you with everything
and just just one
one day at a time with your healing
process one hour at a time one day at a
time
for many people it's three steps up two
steps back i'm proud of you guys greatly
and you're doing an amazing job may the
angels be with you tonight while you
sleep
and they're looking over you and god
bless you
take care