e
e e
hello and welcome to the medical medium
live stream it is night two of the pizza
party here at Cafe Gratitude in Venice
California I am your host Danielle
delate and I'm so excited to be joining
you tonight we're going to kick things
off with our first guest who would like
to come over and talk to us hello my
name is Danielle hello Danielle I've
been watching you on live stream and
this is my first time here and I am so
excited oh I'm so excited to be here
with you what's your name so you can
share the audience it's a long one it's
Gail Rapa port wiland and so because I
had to give my husband a little bit of
you know show in that name well it's so
nice to meet you what was it that made
you want to attend this evening well
I've been actually trying three is a
charm the first one I had terrible
vertigo second one I hope you're all
okay the LA fires and but now I'm here
and I just am so excited my massage
therapist 5 years ago
has um turned me on to Medical medium
and it was the best thing that has ever
happened to me I am a intense follower
I'm a type A personality so I do it just
as he tells us to wow so you've been
using it for quite some time have you
noticed any health benefits absolutely I
uh had indigestion horribly I was doing
oh my God I hate to mention pyac you
don't want to do that that's a horrible
pill MH and so but doing medical median
I can eat spicy food I have no
indigestion and working on when I had
the vertigo his protocol of course and
that took away my vertigo and I have
osteoporosis I'm working on all the
vimergy which I love all those products
and I'm April 4th I'm an ageless goddess
I'm going to be
70 and so you know but medical median
there you go and I have a gift for you
oh wow thank you what is this this is an
angel I'm an artist a full-time
professional artist and I often listen
to Anthony and his podcasts and his live
streams while I'm painting Angels
because I feel his Spirit of compassion
goes into my angels and I want you to
have this one oh wow this is this is
absolutely gorgeous and you made this
this is your your
artwork oh wow thank you you so much
pleasure absolutely look at all that
you're doing and and the love and the
joy that you give all these people and
Anthony gives it so openly and without
wanting anything back he just he's just
an amazing person and I love him yeah he
is such an incredible human and the fact
that so many people travel from all over
the world this community isn't it just
so beautiful this community to be here
this evening they travel from everywhere
excited as waiting online we were
talking about our stories and you know
not to have the question well why don't
you eat eggs you know it's well you know
ask
Anthony where did you travel from to be
here this evening the Central Coast of
California so I'm only about three and a
half hours away we live in paradise and
uh I am grateful to live there I'm
grateful to be able to be here and I'm
grateful for Cafe Gratitude I've been
eating here for years and it's just it's
a marvelous place with marvelous people
and it's just so nice saying what you're
grateful for when you're here yeah and
what an amazing collaboration between
Cafe Gratitude and medical medium what
are you most excited about with this
collaboration well we actually came here
for breakfast this morning also and so I
had his smoothie and what I'm excited
about because the menu you can choose
things that I don't have to think about
I don't have to go well is there egg in
this is there Che in this it's I can
just go eeny meeny miny mo and pick six
things on the menu and I'm good do you
love that you can come to a place and
also be surrounded by people that
support your healing Journey absolutely
because again in in our world that we
live and everybody has a right to their
own choices of what their journey is but
we are very special community and our
journey is different than others and
we're choosing a different path and so
sometimes when you choose a different
path than everybody else it's a little
bit harder you get a little push back
yes yes that's true what is one piece of
information from medical medium that
stands out to you that really helped you
with your healing Journey well you know
I honestly do the lemon water and then I
do the celery juice and this is
difficult is not having fat before noon
pretty much so you're like okay what do
I eat but I think it makes a huge
difference to be able to cleanse your
liver and give it time to cleanse
because your body is meant to heal food
is medicine though some don't believe
that and I love the medicine that he
imparts to all of us yes do you have any
encouraging message you would like to
share with those who are going through
their healing Journey you know it's one
step at a time one day at a time and I
believe in manifestation if you believe
I believe as my father May he rest in
peace you can do anything you put your
mind to yes yeah those are beautiful
words and you're also quite artistic
with the painting did you find uh that
your artistic side and spiritual side
kind of you had learned some lessons in
those areas as well as when you're doing
your healing Journey well I can give you
this angels have always shown up in my
paintings and it's I just left them
there like okay fine whatever but when I
connected with medical medium and
company I started feeling like I was
painting angels to make a difference in
people's lives and I do pay it forward
like here a lot with my angels yeah wow
so beautiful thank you so much may I
give you a hug oh
yes so lovely to meet you enjoy the rest
of your evening perhaps I'll see you
later in the night thank you so much I'm
going to put this over
here and
then we're going to grab our next guest
just one
moment our next guest if you'd like to
join us over
here hi I'm Danielle very nice to meet
you Daniel so happy to see you yes
what's your name I'm Billy from Taiwan
hello oh hello did you travel all the
way from taian to be here yes I just
arrived yesterday and I will leave
tomorrow just for him wow yeah just for
tonight yeah just for tonight why did
you want to travel all that way for a
very quick journey to meet aw and to be
here at Cafe Gratitude for this medical
medium pizza party because I really want
to expressing my gratitude for him he
really saved my life and the people
around me um I can have a chance to help
then change to be a better person and
more Healy way yeah
so it's more than the world can describe
how I feel right now because since uh
2017 I found his book uh um it really
turned my life to be a better person yes
wow so what are some of the health
benefits you've discovered using medical
medium
information um I first starting uh I
starting quit the uh trouble foods and
uh I used to eat lots of egg and milk
every day and uh I wasn't know the
gluten cuz my body Simon so seriously
and
um probably around the two years ago the
Sim starting getting worse
so I I I say to myself okay maybe let's
the time I have to make a real change
and then I starting to re reack to
reread his old books and trying to using
all his protocols as much as I can and
the F feral um disappear in a very short
time so that's the first sign wow yeah
saying that's the first sign were there
other symptoms and conditions that also
improved yes and like a brain Fox I used
to suffer lot of FR brain F and working
in a beauty industry they makes me easy
to uh lost souls and cannot F very
easily and they also improve a lot still
has s in need to change but I think it
will better yeah Day by
you're on your healing Journey you're
getting there thank you so much what is
it about this collaboration between
medical medium and Cafe Gratitude that
most excites you for dinner tonight I
never tried before so this is will be my
first time so I very exciting to try
every dishes yes well you're in for a
treat I just had the pizza and it is so
good the crust is amazing thank you so
much okay I will definitely try it yeah
you're going to have so much fun do you
have a message you'd like to share with
those people watching online who are
currently in their healing Journey um I
want to say is you can do it no M and uh
try your best and don't give yourself
too much pressures yes because life is
not easy just like what aw say and U we
have to keep Faith yes yes well thank
you so much for your time really
appreciate it up next is your meet and
greet so I'll let you go get ready for
that and we'll talk to some someone else
who's arrived here for tonight's pizza
party hello I'm Danielle Danielle it's
really nice to meet you oh it's so
lovely to meet you really nice to meet
you nice to meet you too and what's your
name for people watching at home my name
is Susie and I'm Danielle uh it's so
great to be interviewing you where did
you travel from to be here this evening
not far from Santa Barbara yeah so I'm
close yes you're lucky to have this not
too far from your home we're very lucky
very lucky did you come here this
evening with anyone or travel solo I did
I came with my very good friend uh Kim
um she came with me as support oh yeah
beautiful beautiful so how did you
discover the medical medium information
well it's a long story but essentially
I'm a nurse 40 years I had been a nurse
and I had gotten very sick and of course
went the whole medical route trying to
get well um I got covid I ended up in
bed and I just knew I could fix this and
they kept saying I couldn't and I kept
putting me on more pills and I was not
buying it I just knew food was medicine
and somehow I found this Epstein bar
which I knew my tighters were high and
there he was I Googled it and found
medical medium uh bought bought every
book I have all of them except for the
brain Sabers but um took a couple years
uh so how did you how did you first
start that healing Journey what did you
start with was it the celery juice the
detox smoothie I started right in all
the way celery juice detox smoothie I
eliminated all the fats um it took a
while for some some fats like nuts and
stuff to leave leave my diet but it it
was a process and it all was it's but it
took a good year before I started me
things started to get better but I also
got really sick too while I was detoxing
because I was pretty sick that's
interesting because some people say it
happens you know they'll feel it within
a week and that's great for you to share
that it took time for you for people who
are on their healing journey and trying
this stick with it right yes no I got
sicker before I got better for sure I
was swollen I couldn't walk uh yeah it
was hard and it was really hard to get
up and do it and do that celery juice
and do those do those protocols but I
believed in that food was medicine yeah
food was medicine and proof is I'm here
I went to the book signing and I was
still pretty sick then and uh it's taken
this I'm really starting to feel good
now oh amazing so what are some of the
health benefits that you felt now that
you're that you're feeling this
way uh energy Joy uh I can don't have
the pain that I used to have I had such
bad fibromyalgia pain I couldn't even
hold my head up from the pillow I ended
up at a pain clinic you know on
medications and uh slowly but surely
it's just all gotten better I've
actually gotten back to yoga for the
first time in two and a half years um
I'm back to I'm I'm a surfer I go to the
beach I may I hope this year to get back
into that um I'm a gardening Enthusiast
I'm back to being able to start a garden
this year for the first time in over
three years so there's a lot of benefits
um Clarity in my brain I you know no
more trigeminal neuralgia that was was
horrible uh teeth pain uh bloating I
mean it just it goes on and on and on
I'm one of those people that the list
was this long uh of symptoms and that's
just incredible all these things that
you're back to doing you know the yoga
and you're here and you feel well enough
to be here tonight that's so much that's
great excited to be here tonight I
really am this is a I got I was on the
list but then we you know canceled and
so I was happy to to be able to come
back and do this yeah so is this like a
celebration of your health too to be
able to come here and to just have the
energy and feel good enough to do these
things and to be with all these people
that have done this this is I mean
there's nothing like it there's nothing
like it and being a nurse a critical
care nurse for 40 years you know I
always took care of myself because I
never wanted to be one of those people
and I was one of those people I was so
sick and I I didn't understand what had
happened and then to have doctors just
say good luck with that good luck here
you know you're depressed you know you
need this or you need that and just it
blew my mind that even these were my
friends doctors I had worked with for 40
years yeah nope so so in having healed
this way with food and having tried
doctors and then coming to the medical
media protocol how does that affect you
with your nursing and I had well first
of all I had to quit nursing so first of
all I quit uh second of all I've decided
that I am going to do me I've taken care
of people all my life and I've took care
of family members and a lot of people
and now it's me so that's really me yeah
I'm nursing me if they want my inner
help they have to understand who where
I'm coming from now because I'm not
going to say go see a doctor I'm not
there anymore I I hope someday to say I
I don't have to go see a doctor ever
again I'm still working on some things
but yeah no it's I just don't it's it
blows my mind that that's what I did and
I self-educated and I always believed in
what I did
and it's not it's not there I don't I
don't feel that way anymore you're on on
a different path now but do you have any
encouraging words you would like to
share with the community watching I just
faith and believing and sticking to it
um for some people it gets worse before
it gets better um believe in yourself
and man I'll tell you if it wasn't for
all the social media and stuff laying in
that uh mattress Island I don't know
where I would be today because they
really p hold me up too all these
wonderful people that I've met in line
all the people I've seen on Instagram
while I laid in that bed barely able to
hold my head they gave me what I needed
to keep going and I really all of his
all of his stuff too but all these
social media people don't realize the
power that they have to help us and they
really did and I've reached out to every
one of them in line today um people in
in
Australia uh to heal from within she's
amazing Anna she helped me through so
much
uh pain and and and disbelief so anyways
that's kind of where I'm at right now
just stick to the program and follow
these people these people these people
are power yeah the community is hailing
together absolutely that's what's so
much fun to come here and have all these
people here it's so uplifting well thank
you so much for talking to us that was
so much fun lovely to meet you too yeah
thank I'm going to talk to the next
person waiting here as well hello hi I'm
Danielle hi I'm car nice to meet you so
nice to meet you where did you travel
from to be here this evening I traveled
from the East Coast I'm from New Jersey
actually yeah so what was it that made
you want to attend this evening well
I've always wanted to meet Anthony
William and I've always wanted to go to
one of these big meetups for for his
information and yeah I'm just really
happy to be here and what are you most
excited about with this collaboration
between Cafe Gratitude and medical
medium the pizza yeah it's really
exciting um yeah you don't get to eat a
lot of P Pizza when you're eating clean
cuz yeah but it's I'm really excited to
try it tonight yeah oh you're in for a
delicious trait by the way I'm excited
so when did you discover medical medium
information how did you come across it
and how long have you been using it for
um I discovered it 6 years ago um I was
really sick um I knew I needed answers I
was trying a lot of different natural
remedies but nothing was really working
but I had a lot of faith that there was
something out there that would help me
heal and um I really feel like I was
guided spiritually to this information
and um when I read the first book I it
just clicked I knew that it was what I
had been praying for and hoping for so
yeah wow did you have uh experienc
health benefits from using the
information oh yeah definitely I was um
I was in college um and like falling
asleep and like I couldn't stay awake I
was having brain fog a lot of chronic
fatigue and um gut health issues and
I've been able to heal all of that um in
the six years that I've been following I
still have some symptoms but you know I
know I can heal because I've healed
everything else so yeah it's been
amazing and that's incredible what's one
of your favorite things about the
medical medium information um that it
comes from above uh that it's grounded
spirituality um that it's you know the
physical and the spiritual um and I love
the nature meditations but yeah just
that it's both spiritual and physical a
lot of people talk about their healing
journey and that it also is quite
spiritual did you learn any spiritual
lessons along the way oh definitely um
to keep a light heart is a huge one I
love that one um also just you know
working for God that's huge waking up in
the morning and saying that you work for
God that's really such a a great way to
like you know set an intention for the
day um yeah there's so there I feel like
I can name so many things but yeah those
are the ones that I love what are some
of the protocols that you most enjoy um
I love the celery juice the heavy metal
detox is my favorite the Smoothie um I
love that you can eat all the fruit that
you want um yeah I love the 369 cleanse
pretty much everything about the books I
love yeah did you travel you tonight
with anyone or did you come solo yeah I
came with my boyfriend Tyler he's just
over there yeah yeah now is he into the
medical medium information he is yes
yeah beautiful did you introduce him to
it I did yes yeah so you make him a
celery juice in the morning or yeah and
sometimes he makes it for me you know
it's really nice if he gets up before me
I get that little treat which is nice
yeah that's so nice sounds like he
really supports you in your healing
Journey oh yeah definitely we we support
each other and it's it's really helpful
to have somebody who understands like
how you eat and can help take care of
you when you're you know feeling run
down and vice versa so yeah it's it's
it's a game changer it's really amazing
yeah I think it's also fun being in the
kitchen together right making the juices
and the different recipes oh yeah it
definitely is we have so much fun like
making the medical medium recipes trying
the new things yeah we and we both love
eating this way so it's just it's so
much fun oh that's great do you have a
favorite recipe we okay we love all the
cookie recipes um I can't remember the
name of one but we love the cookies yeah
and just I don't know all of them I I
guess all of them so much so many
amazing recipes and tonight you're going
to have cookies as well after that pizza
so you're just going to be having the
time of your life it's going to be so
much fun I'm going to let you go and get
ready for the meet and greet uh we'll
talk to you later tonight yeah thank you
so much bye we're going to talk to our
next guest over here
hello how how are you I'm Danielle
Marcel so nice to meet you where did you
travel from to be here today North
Carolina oh beautiful and did you come
with anyone or uh this time I came by
myself did you meet anyone in line that
you're friends with in the community
a lot of people that been in Culver City
or Calabasas that's those two events
I've been before and have you connected
and stayed in touch with those people
during this time I didn't stay in touch
with them but it was always you know
nice even yesterday and today to see
them
again so nice how did you come across
medical medium
information my story started in
2014 I've listened to his uh interview
on uh pled pure nation and also on
mastering diabetes and at that time I
was vegan and I thought you know hm
medium I didn't really I wasn't sure uh
but I uh tuned into hey house radio and
I started listening to his podcast his
radio shows and so I started learning
and I enjoyed it I started kind of
picking few things off of his
information hoping I could get that
phone call with him I called every
Monday but I wasn't uh lucky enough but
I also signed up at his page for the um
um
practitioners on his website back then
in 2015 16 on his website there was a
link for practitioners uh but I know the
line is long so I'm still hoping to get
that if he's still doing it uh to be
able to learn how I can um improve my
skills to help my clients so and what
are some of the symptoms and conditions
you've healed using medical medium
information a lot of neurological
conditions and uh right now I'm still
working on fragrance sensitivity and
chemical sensitivity because once the
bug came to town I was so compromised I
lost sense of smell and I was getting so
sick but I didn't know what was causing
it until about 8 months later when my
smell came back and I realized every
time I smell perfume cologne every time
I got exposed to any kind of a bleach
smell ammonia smell I was being so
compromised I would cancel the work next
day because I was just sleeping I was
nauseated I was tired would get bloated
and so I started uh doing a lot of
advanced heavy metal detox movie and a
lot of advanced extractors movie which
helps greatly I'm still not 100% healed
from it but I can walk into a shoe store
without wearing a VCC respirator so
that's a big step and just last night um
when I went back to my hotel room I was
going to sleep and I realized the Linens
were heavily um smelling as a bleach so
I thought this is not good but I didn't
know how bad it was until the morning
when I woke up with my face swollen
buffed eyes um runny nose I was tearing
just one side of one one of my eyes were
just constantly tearing and um I came
here to Cafe Gratitude and first thing I
asked them please tell me if you have a
hibiscus tea because that's what Anthony
recommends a hibiscus rose hips
raspberries and uh also uh blackberry
leaves for
bleach exposure um and so they served me
a hibiscus tea I drink that and I now
got the reset and I had a reset
throughout the day and I made more
hibiscus tea just before I showed up
here have my immune uh support
supplement and I'm feeling much better
so I know his information works and it
works quickly because in the morning I
was wondering if I was going to make it
here tonight but I'm here and you're
here because of his information you were
able to put that into practice today you
made it here and you're about to meet aw
it's about to start the meet and greet
so would you like to stand with me here
while we head over to the meet and greet
the live stream's going to watch that
now with aw and you're going to head
over there and meet the man himself yeah
how exciting thank you thank you so
much hey how are you good to see you
good to see you and I want just to have
this love and this feeling home again
with you so I'm just honored oh I'm
honored too thank you do you want me to
sign this yes and this is for you would
love to oh look at this one yes aha I
love this one oh yeah me
too is s having a message for me this
pen is
nice
wow thank you is this for me oh that's
wonderful look at this this is from
Germany these okay it's a few different
cards in here though yes yes from some
different people um no
no that's okay that's great that's
wonderful you want to get a picture yes
please oh of course just a
sec amazing I hope you enjoy the food
tonight thank you for coming truly okay
I will see you I can't wait I can't wait
look at you how are you I'm good I love
your
hat my name I came from Germany really
that's a long trip how long did it take
11 hours 11 hours waa that's a long
that's a long flight I I don't think I
could do an 11-hour flight I'd get stir
I would get Stir Crazy on there you know
how did you keep busy on there um I
there was a TV a little TV there was
there's a TV on the plan
did you see a movie yes oh okay that's
that well that okay that works I could
do that I could do an 11h hour flight if
I see a movie I have a question sure
sure um my bunny is ill and his name is
Amigo can you tell me what I could do
what what he have what he has what's he
um what does the what does the uh vet
say about the bunny did you take the
bunny to somebody um no and they is
there anybody to take a look at the
bunny yes my sisters can they can they
see the bunny yes I I I would show them
so they know and so they haven't seen
your bunny
yet I would definitely show your sisters
the bunny okay and can you give the
bunny a little bit of B12 do you can is
there B12 anywhere out there and um
couple of tiny drops of B12 for the
bunny yes just a little bit you know you
know a tiny drop you know like one tiny
drop a droplet and then cuz the bunny's
small and I would do that okay okay and
uh and then have have the bunny looked
at if you
can do you want to take a
picture here step forward here amazing I
can't believe you're
here amazing you're brave to make this
trip thank you for coming are you going
to enjoy the food amazing want to get a
picture again oh wait is this Mom I
thought he came
alone I thought he made the flight alone
he wanted to take all the time him I was
like the brave he's he's still
Brave you coming over here just for the
picture here step forward a little bit
we got to give the bunny a little B12
yes I heard this okay okay good good
thank you I I have you got some presents
my soy I'm so excited this is a lot here
I have a lot I have big job for you okay
we have a community in Germany yep a
community there her name is better
together okay and there are lot of
people uh with their prayers and letters
and presents for you they all in this B
for you amazing yes amazing I'm
listening to Spirit now about it there
is a large community there this is
incredible and this is look at these huh
yeah very
special uh presents for wow this is just
beautiful it really is and this is from
my friend Kya okay from Kya yeah the
leader of this community a present for
you oh my God if it's possible this is
beautiful the wrapper it's beautiful you
can want me to sign this let me do that
do you have a p i have a pen here I'll
hand this to
you maybe here you can continue I'm
sorry there you go amazing amazing you
can
yes this is for you okay that's for I
put it back in the bag this is fun I'm
having a
day this is um from me to you
okay
amazing so I have um picture for you oh
my god what is this Arabic calligraphy
who did this me you did this yes I hope
you see the C the that's a hummingbird
yes and the meaning it's some special
numbers here h no it's no that's just
the
design the name is um God is God always
wins this is the Me O that's wonderful
and this means thank you wo that's
tremendous tremendous spiritual wo
that's beautiful yes it is you have the
you signed it I signed okay that's a
nice signature my name is
f can I frame this of course okay okay
so this is my questions because I have a
lot of okay but we're we're running a
little behind you let's get a picture
here and this is um I have baked you Bak
these yes I because in Germany I have a
baking that's amazing okay I also have
some we get a picture of
together thank you so much seriously
thank you thank you do you have a bag
for me or yes you can put everything
inside this good good I just don't want
to lose it okay I'm sorry I don't want
to okay just one thing
okay this is for
you last thing
is yes I'm sorry oh no your pen sorry
sorry about
that this is my book my book there we go
all right get some food and relax thank
you for coming
from
Germany thank you very much okay bless
your heart than you thank
you all right thank Hi how are you good
to see you look at you I am absolutely
thrilled to be here and I'm going to
just mention my friend Dina who 5 years
ago massage therapist open my heart to
you Dina Dina wow W she's your massage
therapist and she said you have to
listen to this guy he's a he's a good
guy I don't want to I don't want to look
at Med medium stuff no he's a good guy
he's a good guy you have to trust me
well I painted this while I listen to
you I I'm a full-time professional
artist and when I listen to your podcast
and I listen to your voice and I listen
to you talking to Spirit of compassion I
paint something called Angel within cuz
I believe we all have an angel with it
this is beautiful thank you there's
three Angels on the front of this can we
get a picture together oh my God here
step forward a little bit
here and I have an easel with it for
you the original
easel original the original easel and
I'm going to do this quick okay I want
you do I put this back in here yeah I
didn't want to bring the book because
want me to sign this just sign this and
I'll put it in your wonderful book cuz
my book is so tattered and such a mess
and I just wanted to ask you one thing
okay is because I'm going to be 70 April
4th I am only only on vimergy nothing
else oh my God I cured my indigestion I
have cured I can eat spicy food now wow
but we're working on osteoporosis and
Bones any you know I do the MSA it it's
deeper so you got to go a little deeper
just keep on forging it head and you're
an artist right you open up the books
and you know there's there's places in
there you'll
find I I feel you thank you so
much you hello hello how are you fine
can you make a trip here yeah look at
you did you make a long trip here oh yes
come from Germany uh do you want
signature for me of course of course in
my book this is my first book this uh
it's coming with my my sah amazing
saying Sarah can you tell me what's
about us and him dad and we miss him so
much you miss him can you
piure I can only send I can send prayers
and spirit of compassion can send
prayers okay yes yeah yeah that's all
make a sign you want me to sign yes
anything else this here here in the
picture thank you yes oh right I'm so
thankful and can you tell me what I can
do for her is she because she is um sick
also and what can I do what's the right
for
her um well you're doing already some
things right you're doing already some
stuff from from the books and everything
from the information you keep keep up
all the good stuff your mom you you know
you can look and see it it's coming okay
okay can I let's get a picture yeah
let's get a picture before we run out of
time here come forward
here
ready amazing get some food and thank
you for coming thank
you sorry thank you thank you thank you
thank you for coming hi
my flight got cancelled and I got a
ticket what for tonight so it was nice
to be good good I just want to say thank
you for being a gift to humanity is this
a gift for me yes I have friend we have
a mutual friend Dr lne oh my God that's
my daughter's pediatrician we talk about
you all the time that's connection yeah
Diana
Diana her do you have anything to say in
terms of what more we could do for my
family's Heth myself my daughters and my
husband that could revamp
anything I mean it's good to change it's
good to change things up a little bit
too so take a look and you can you can
change things up a little because that
that's always a good thing because
there's so many different tools there so
but but look into some of those theistic
tools and the meditations in the first
book look into those and and and you
know and focus on that a little bit as
well thank you so much yes thank you for
the coconut water of course I know you
need it I do I do yes
amazing thank
you
oh okay
you wait I don't even
know hey hey how are how are you good to
see you I'm back here for round two cuz
the food was so good oh did you like the
pizza it was delicious my God can't
remember the last time I had pizza I
know right that was so good I mean what
the heck you want to get a picture again
let's get another
one I mean come on pizza every
night man how incredible is that to have
pizza right after everything thank you
and I just want to say thank you to your
family and your wife for everything that
they support you that they do well I'm
sure they're watching this right now
okay and so that they're seeing that so
that's very kind truly kind can I thank
you for coming can I is there a message
fromc
um just don't stop just keep on doing
all the work that you're doing you know
and it's okay if you take a break once
in a while because that's okay but but
continue you know continue on and do
your healing like you are okay I'm proud
of you thank you thank you
hello good to see you you want to get a
picture yes I would love a picture okay
step forward
here yay did you like the pizza oh
everything was wonderful
amazing well I hope hope you like it
again and you know get another bite of
it cuz I know I'm going to today I mean
so I'm excited wonderful may I ask you a
question um I'm having a hard time
sticking to the protocol and um I was
wondering if it's like free will or if
it's negative entities or if you had a
suggestion about are you doing are you
doing um are you doing any of the
shifters at all any of the brain shot
the shifters not so much but
intermittently but not regularly I would
focus on those they will help okay they
will help and it'll help keep you on
track any one of those you can choose oh
that's wonderful yeah yeah thank you so
much glad you're here
amazing hello Mr Williams good to see
you I'm look at you this is and Isaac
our main supporter our leader oh really
the the leader of the family for sure
good to see you oh my God it's a great
honor yeah so Isaac was diagnosed with a
slight speech delay we're concerned
because we were eating a lot of fish
during her pregnancy okay and with the
heavy metals um is detoxing enough what
kind of fish were you having when when
you were pregnant macel lots of Mac
small small fish that's good what
else H Salon okay okay some Farm the
salon later we we know we need to eat
the Alaska wild well no it it's not the
worst I mean I mean even though you you
did you did some fish while pregnant
that's just you keep a light heart you
know and macal they're really they're
not really that high in in metal so
that's good all those things you know
that's not
well pregnant women do a lot worse out
there okay they're doing a lot worse
things and so you're you you did
wonderful okay are you working on the
hmd yes definitely doing the hmd every
morning C every morning in the heavy
metal detox okay okay how old how old is
this little one how old is Isaac 19
months oh yeah it's it's it's good it's
early very early while you're doing all
these things and that's important
I'm proud of you do you want to get a
picture yes please okay
okay
[Laughter]
Isaac I just say I'm proud of you
guys I'm proud of you guys where did you
guys come from how far an hour oh
perfect I love that yeah it's good to be
close
by did you did you try any of the food
here yet yeah okay I'm excited for you
guys I'm excited for you
guys all th sure here you go hi Hi how
are you good to see
you again I no I know do you want to get
another picture
yeah in the picture she want you in the
picture you play some the music it was
so wonderful that's amazing GL I'm glad
I'm glad he's in the picture let go for
it a little bit I keep listening to he's
a handsome
fell this is amazing thank you enjoy the
night hey what's going you got a book I
was so excited yesterday and I forgot it
I I I I'm happy I'm happy did you just
get this did you were English I mean in
in in German I have it a long time but I
now I got it in English because we I
found a lot of um mistakes the
translation and so I decided to buy all
in English but I also you get them in
English too amazing amazing I have both
in every single book in English and and
in German in German yeah amazing and
what I also forgot yesterday is to give
you this letter and there is attached
the list of that's a big letter yeah
that's a very big
letter I collected questions from the
medical medium practition Community are
they in here is that what this is yeah
German speaking it's attached to my
letter I'm very there are I'm very proud
of the German community medical medium
German community and communities
actually and very proud of them all I
mean I I I um you know there's a lot of
things I'm grateful for and a lot of
things I'm thankful for and I am
thankful for the you the German uh
community so I think about that a lot
and so thank you this is very special so
the questions are in here yes there are
questions and we hope that you can pick
them out from and and maybe answer maybe
answer them sometime I'll hold on to
this okay good I'll look at that I'm
sure a lot of are already answered in
the new book so okay yeah okay because
this this list uh we did when we didn't
know
thank you for coming thank you bless
your heart we didn't know about
the the list is okay okay okay no that
makes sense hi Anthony hey how are you
good to see you good to see you again
thank you for coming you got a book for
me yeah okay I got a pen oh thank you oh
here we are oh thank you so
much thank you whoa
[Laughter]
slippery thank you thank you thank you
so much
amazing
wow thank you oh this my well want to
get a picture yeah let's get a picture
for yesterday I forgot my question for
you yeah it's a beautiful book
thank you so much try to get some food
and enjoy yourself okay
truly thank you hi again hey good to see
you you want to get a picture I got this
shirt from a really compassionate loving
Prophet wow um I have a two-part
question um well one part might be all
we have time for okay I lose my my I had
the thyroid that I'm healing and I lose
my uh voice around crowds like this so I
lost it from last night but I'm my
question for Spirit of compassion is is
there any particular brain shot to focus
on her supplement that would help like
whatever that situation what's your
favorite book the thyroid healing book
the thyroid healing book that's your
favorite and you've done the
90day no I've done the 28 day the 369
look into look into the 90day in the
thyroid book definitely that might be a
good thing let's get a
picture yes
awesome thank you for coming thank
you hi hey again I know I know good to
see you want to get a picture
okay you're here we should get a picture
I
know just great is it safe to give dogs
spirina I give my dog spirina like my
dog just a little bit Yeah like he waits
for the heavy metal detox every time I
make it I I give my dogs the heavy metal
detox every day okay thank you thank
you hi nice hat good to see you from
Austin from Austria Austria oh my God
big difference be here again I to all
your events no I'm glad I'm glad thank
you so much I'm honored you want to get
a picture sure okay wonderful and can I
ask you something then sure what's going
on
can I ask you in so which my biggest
struggle still is and if um and which
are the three best um medical medium
tools I would use for that to get rid of
that what's your favorite medical meme
tools that you're doing propolis the
propolis yeah Advanced um 369 you're
doing the advance 369 amazing how long
you been doing that how I started
actually that's how it started yeah I
didn't know you at all but I start the
369 that's that's beautiful that's
beautiful cuz I had really such a bad um
condition that I was almost did you do
the spinach soup the spinach soup um
bring that in okay bring in thank you so
much biggest struggler is the the liver
or what would it be uh spirit just says
spinach soup bring it in okay thank you
very
much hey how are you hello hello hello
such an honor honor to see you thank you
for coming want to get a picture
sure thanks for coming thank you for
having me have you been here before no
my first one this is your first one have
you been in here before and and have you
eaten here I've eaten at the other
location last night oh amazing did you
try any the medical medium thises um I
tried yes it was the uh papaya salad
okay Co I love that that's a great one
yeah yeah you're Italian too I'm Italian
absolutely the pizza's good pizza's good
okay it's good it doesn't have all that
dripping oil and dripping grease yeah it
trickers the crust you know and it
doesn't have all that gluten and it
doesn't have you know all other hidden
weird things it is clean yes and so you
can eat the pizza without worrying and
that's very special very special it is
special is there anything that wants me
to know that you okay yeah I mean with
you it's just you
know you actually are really hard on
yourself at times you got to not not do
that okay you got to have more
compassion for yourself do you you have
compassion for others spirit says but
you got to have a little for yourself
too you got to save a little for
yourself okay right okay right thank you
anthy love you love
you
hey good to see I know I know jacket
it's an honor you have a jacket you have
a leather jacket
too good to see you very nice to see you
again this time I was very nervous and
yes I was bless your heart yes thank you
so much thank you so much for being here
where did you come from I come from
Taiwan amazing you came all the way from
there to here yeah I just arrived yest
today and I will leave tomorrow oh my
God you're that fast and that's a long
that's a long trip it's an honor to have
you here seriously thank you for for
making the trip you want to take a
picture together yes going step forward
a little bit
okay my God this amazing thank you so
much thank you so much been sharing what
you have and it's been not easy means
the world to me it does truly
does have a reest
i
wow look at
this well that's a tough one okay that's
a that's a tough one but you know you
know what though are you on are you on
social yes
okay okay so I could I do you watch the
lives and okay I'll look out for your
I'll look out for you on social okay
what's your handle life performer life
performer okay perfect all right thank
you thank you I appreciate I
do oh how's it going hey good to see you
want to get a pick again yeah let's go
step forward oh yeah
enjoy the night get some food uh my wife
she was really grateful yes yesterday
and I I have the question for you I'm
very sorry my no can I ask is it okay my
nocturnal emissions what's the root
cause of it and what's the healing tool
that I can use to get rid of them or
reduce the frequency of
them you know when you do when you do
your Wi-Fi and everything when you do
your your Tech and all your right
equipment and everything just um you
know turn it off more so turn it off
more than normal yeah cuz you turn it
off but turn it off more so when you can
that that's what I'm getting Spirit day
not because not because of problems from
it but from something where it gives you
a relaxation among your body to be away
from it a little bit more it relaxes
everything your brain your nervous
system and Spirit say important just
crap something up okay thank you thank
you thank you hi Anthony good to see you
again good to see you yesterday I was so
nervous you're not nervous today yes I
am but it's better and I didn't get the
chance to thank you for everything you
do really it means the word to me thank
you I'm honored I'm honored I'm too do
you want to get a picture another one
okay let's go
amazing did she enjoy the food last
night yeah it was awesome okay more food
tonight does Spirit have a message for
me please what was spirit's message
yesterday
okay
thank hi Anthony good to see you well
you're a tall guy you might hit the boom
yeah so I want to say you again I'm so
grateful for your information you're
doing such a good job I mean it's it's
unbelievable how far did you come to get
here uh here from Germany Germany
Germany yeah you made the trip yeah you
know I'm honored that you made the trip
okay I am that's a long that's a long
trip thank you and it means the world
okay thank you y you told me that um I
have continuous exposure at home can
please say what it is because you said
it's like keeping me from from healing
like it's holding me back it's not
holding you back you're going to heal
right you're going to heal you're going
to move your healing forward no matter
what okay it might not even be there
much longer it's environment it's on the
outside
a keep
going get
[Laughter]
going that's a hint so I can do anything
that's a hint I gave you a good
hint you're on you're
on hey what you oh my god what what the
heck you're here is unbelievable what
God look at you you're
amazing I know you guys thank you so
much for like you and so sharing
information it has changed my family and
me my our lives and then there are many
people in Taiwan they are working really
hard on killing you're always you're
always speaking on behalf of everybody
there and it means the world to me you
know cuz I know yeah I know your support
is important very important uh for me
you know just so you know okay I I think
about it all the time thank you and
here's the message they want you to have
okay I don't I don't have to read it now
though right no this it's in here no all
of
these is this a new one or one is this
is it is this your friend did this one
okay that's 2021 oh oh oh my god oh
that's right okay
for you they they couldn't be here in
person tonight okay this is from people
in the Taiwan community and dry mangoes
from Taiwan are you serious yes from
dried mangoes from Taiwan oh that's
insane really can I look at that
yeah these are from oh my God I don't
see them usually this is amazing the way
they look H and I don't see I don't when
they're dried like that here I don't see
him look like this try it if you want
very very very nice okay thank you bless
your heart unbelievable have you ever
tried these do you ever eat these they
taste good okay okay now I I feel even
better because if she says they taste
good then we're really good
[Music]
okay thank you for coming thank you for
making the trip seriously okay she has a
small question you
do what's going on do you think unn are
real
unicorns I definitely believe they're
real definitely I haven't seen one but I
believe they're real yes do you believe
they're real I believe they're real I
hope to see one someday thank
you love you guys
seriously hi Anthony hey good to see
look at you I got my leather Anthony
jacket I like it I like it I know I'm
into I'm into the leather jacket look
right no I got it for you Amor do you
want to get a picture yeah go and I was
wondering if you had um so had a hot tip
for
me thank
you um what does Spirit say walks you
doing walks I could do more
it's going to be good yes you do do it
clears the mind it clears the
Consciousness and that helps you thank
you bless you hi hey look at you Anthony
Williams the real me good to see you it
is the real me yes yeah my dad's a huge
fan of you wow that's that's
mind-blowing we're both from Mexico yeah
wow and uh yeah just your dad your dad
and you were both from Mexico well I was
born you were born here but yeah my dad
dad was born in yeah my dad's in San
Diego we're both from San Diego andana
we just we're both huge fans oh thank
you thank you for your support I'm so
happy you came yeah thank you for is
this the first time here yeah in Cafe
Gratitude yes and okay that's exciting
not in in Los Angeles no no but uh I was
wondering if there was a message from
SLC or for Dad not for
me I mean for both I me for both of you
guys um do you know that medical M
information like Liver Rescue M right
mhm um make sure you look in the book uh
protect livers okay your family line
okay so all right let's get a picture
okay thank you yes of course move up
forward a little bit here okay
perfect thank thank you for coming get
some good food of course you can oh you
this
side Anthony how are you hey hey no way
no way no you're support is very
important to me you know that right yeah
thank you yeah it's been such an honor
to like have you in my life and
everything you've done and I feel bad
the first two events I didn't like say
anything but um hey you're here now yeah
thank you you're here now it's okay if
you didn't say anything you probably in
shock because I was in shock okay when
do I do anything in person right so the
first event right in June you know it
might have been it might have been just
a shock I was in shock yeah I was I had
a question um what determines a person's
sexuality what determines it
mhm the soul has a lot to do with things
I mean I can say that okay so it's not
just physicality the soul has a lot to
do things yeah yeah and I should
probably talk more about that you know
as I go along um there so many things to
talk about I mean I but at least at
least I know that something that's been
on my mind to want to get information
out there I can't believe you're here
yeah want to get a picture yeah let's do
it amazing good to see you good to see
you you going to have the pizza tonight
yeah okay that cheers me
up hello look at you hi good to see you
you oh good good good glad you're here
thank you it's an honor to meet you
really really grateful for all that you
have done for me and my family H you
gave gave my husband back to me and uh
now we can have a life oh my God yes he
was really sick he was yes yes my God
where is he now yeah he's here yeah come
over here look at youy it's an honor
it's glad to meet you again wow how did
you guys meet in the Netherlands um I
went to do a study there and then uh
yeah we meet there yeah it's very
special yes how long you guys been
together um 2016 already n yeah yes 9
years N9 years and you're still keeping
them around still keeping around having
our second child right now yep yep
amazing amazing I'm so proud of you guys
you want to get a picture together okay
incredible here come forward here a
question later on yeah
telling me you've been very sick over
all these years right yeah yeah here we
got to come forward and that'll that'll
make things easier there we
go amazing tell me it's like um when I
was younger I was like 16 17 years old I
think I fell down with the bike and I
damaged my front thee so I have crowns
here okay but back then they put uh yeah
metals on the back they put yeah they
put different things I'm scratching
while I buite every time and I'm
wondering if I I heal a lot like 90% I
think it's like that that last 10% are
you finding a good a good um Dental
person all that that's right but some
people say like yeah leave it leave it
because the glue from back then is
really tough to get loose to loosen up
um I saw your podcast with the dentist
reach out to
them um they said they take a look um
since I'm from Europe they said like
it's too far away so we should find
someone more close by I understand I
understand well look um you know keep on
keep on working on it always just keep
on you'll find somebody that might that
may understand close by which you remove
possible or I I don't think does it make
me sick or I'm not I'm not worried okay
I'm not worried so take your time and
whatever happens naturally bless your
heart you guys thank you very much maybe
maybe I have another question well I got
to I got to get you guys I got to get
you guys in thank you so much enjoy the
food enjoy the
food what what is going on you guys
we're celebrating
healing
yay guys are going to get me dancing oh
you you are a dancer no
[Applause]
yeah robot we love
it I got to do a better version than
that though you guys
good to see you guys what's going on
yeah we came from Munich and M happy to
be here that's that's crazy what the
heck that's a long trip you know that's
a long trip right we have to we got some
music
going sorry sorry sorry it won't shut
off I I think now I got it okayy just
one question regarding my health do I
better explain do a explain surgery or
keep your your protocol because I'm
doing B big question for just being here
I it's a there's a lot there's a lot so
I won't be able to answer that one
because there's so much there's so many
things involved you know um do you have
a good person you talk to do you doing
different seeing different people to
give you different opinions just
considering it I'm considering I'm doing
all the information implementing
everything but I wonder you find a
practitioner that understands the
information you find a doctor that
understands I would just keep on looking
find the right person and and and then
you know have that that communication
with them for a decision like that all
right but keep on doing all the good
stuff I will very important I'm not
saying don't do that we have something
for your JS what what is this it's for
you really and this is for you JS you
guys did we get a picture we got one we
didn't get one okay let's get a picture
amazing the dosent it
you guys we have to come forward we will
okay okay okay good good okay that's
good May back a little bit back a
little all
[Music]
right amazing thank you thank you get
some good food bless your heart you want
me to grab take these is this what you
want me to have please take it
okay okay thank you this is this is for
me too oh my God look at this do you
want to take a picture and this you want
to take a quick picture of this right
here look at
that amazing you guys enjoy the food
okay thank
[Music]
you hey hi the spirit have a message for
her the spirit have M are you taking
care of yourself are you working hard
taking care of
yourself right that's all that matters
okay you're doing good you're doing good
work that's what spirit says you're
doing good work you're going to cry or
you're crying on me
now fine J is going to be done next week
so I think that makes a big difference
hopefully
too you're doing good work
okay God loves you for it let's get a
picture let's get a picture together
helps thank you
Anthony amazing one here one here thank
you incredible get some good food
Anthony I have these letters for you
okay has all Mom they're trying to hear
the children with medical media
information sorry I'm crying but so it
breaks my heart and is so much suffering
and I also I know you're going to get me
crying and if you get me crying and then
uh yeah that's going to be
tough have so much you give so much
support and then you have so much
support for moms especially because you
know how hard it is thank you
andar kids too so thank you right be
happy they all watching now get me
getting me choked up for sure they love
you and you you do so much for us thank
you Anthony yeah give me Aug thank you
what's your heart
okay all right all right come on inside
come on
inside okay hi Anthony St you again how
you doing good to see you want to get a
picture right away we'll get a picture
thank you so much how's the Pizza um it
was fantastic fantastic you're here
you're here again for it it's good yes I
can't wait yes the pizza is better than
seeing me okay oh
no believe me no way it
is okay if I was coming here I'd be
running for the pizza yeah yeah does
Spirit have any messages for me to does
Spirit have any messages what's your
favorite medical medium tool um celery
juice how much are you doing every day
30 2 O it's exactly what you could be
doing that's perfect it's what you
should be doing okay and if I may ask
talk about Minas one day Minas Min well
that would be nice if you cover that at
some point okay I will I'm making a note
of that okay yes thank you love you lots
of
love hey oh I know look at what is this
disappeared you want me to sign this
sign it again wait a minute it
disappeared my signature disappeared
this you see thise you see it was on
there I sucked all the energy it
disappeared it really did it did and I I
sat by my bed you have a ballp point
ball point you got a ball
point you
go thank you so much I so appreciate you
and I just want to say thank you for
everything and for like everybody else
here you've saved my life means the
world okay I'm nurse 40 years I had to
put my job and 40 years as a nurse years
a nurse critical care nurse and they
couldn't help me and I found your
information while laying on mattress
Island and the rest is I'm here 2 and
1/2 years later I'm standing and I'm
getting to meet you and it means a lot
to me that means a lot to me okay and
and listen I'm honored okay I'm standing
in front of a nurse somebody who did
that much service for that many decades
okay you got me beat that's a big deal
all right so I I I love you for the good
work you've done okay helping others it
means the world to me I really
appreciate it want to get a picture I
want to give you something that I I
painted while being on we got some
ladybugs ladybugs mattress Island
okay amazing thank you put him in your
garden oh my God I will put him in your
garden thank you so much take care get
some good
food hey she how are you she's my friend
she is you guys are friends 50 years
good good 50 years a friendship for 50
years okay that's a big deal I know it's
a really big deal and thank you I knew
it this so okay well that's good want to
get a picture let's do it
ready amazing thank you get some good
food I
will uh-oh what's going on here are you
okay you're going to get me crying I'm
actually close to crying already today
and I'm trying to keep it
together listen you know I'm miked okay
so anything you say I'm hot miked right
now okay everywhere so anything you say
you know it's going to be hot
everybody's going to hear so you said
you don't feel
well thoughts and Visions okay okay all
right well that might have gone out
there
that might have gone out there all right
um what are you doing in the medical
medium stuff what are you doing celery
juice Advanced hmds regular extractor
you're doing the advanced hmd yeah
you're doing all the good stuff how long
youve been doing medical medium since
2018 amazing but that hit me L year is
it it did yeah so you got lots of
exposures happening in your life keep up
all the good work okay you know what
helps you heal is it met brain or is it
spiritual you're on the right track keep
up all the good stuff is this you want
to get a picture
yeah okay ready yeah we're okay okay you
got
it there we go thank you for this
okay uh who's this
who is this I know
you you want to get a
picture how you
doing what's going
on let's get a p let get a picture come
on you ready let's go forward
here on and God
ins you ready
get some good food tonight get some good
food what is
this this is about the most trusting
gift I can give you is it okay okay I'm
going to remember this
okay okay I will all right well then I'm
going to make sure that we have to keep
this one very safe which we keep all of
them very safe but we have to keep that
one very safe and uh I think it's August
birthday
is is this for
me okay okay thank you thank you okay
get inside get some good food thank you
for
coming who's this fell right here thank
you for making the conscious choice to
be the messenger I'm honored man you got
a strong handshake how you doing I'm
here you told me to do my best to come
so and you came I'm here that means
World okay yeah that's incredible that
you guys how far did you guys come from
it how far did you travel Oklahoma
Oklahoma you guys are ois yeah
unbelievable and for now and for now
unbelievable you guys want to get a
picture together yeah let's go up here
thank you for coming you guys seriously
[Music]
amazing can I ask you one quick question
Who do you got cooking um can you tell
if Benny is now in the soul of t or is
the soul of
Tam it's a big question yeah I do you
ask that question at all do you ask up
do you ask God that question do you ask
the The Ether are you asking at night
before bed I will do that do that do
that that's important that's the time to
ask thank you okay let your heart get
some good food yeah hello hello good to
see you good to see you you got a a note
um it's from I'm delivering it from
somebody from December it's been through
a lot of pants so you're like the post
office you're get the postmaster you're
giving me a good delivery thank you
thank you you want to get a picture yes
I do here step forward here and I want
to thank you
also
amazing have you tried the Pizza not yet
I'm dying to thank you for coming thank
you for this community it's means a
world to me it means a world to me I
don't say it enough but it means the
world to me hopefully I express it
tonight when I when I talk tonight yes
you will and my the friends who I have
are like my family that means the
world what what are you
doing hey you want to come here too are
you guys together you guys together
right
you're leaving him behind uhuh is that
what you're
doing she got dibs cuz she knows you
longer yeah yeah I was I feel like we're
old friends even though we've never met
and I that's how the medical me
Community works okay that's how it all
works I just want to say thank you so
much thank you you and spirit so much
you know this
information I'm honored I'm honored it's
good to see you guys you know that right
to see you get a picture I love your
beard you got a great beard I love that
and I have a little a little guy I don't
know I'm not going to lose this place
this one small this one I don't want to
lose okay don't lose that especially
after tonight after the light blast I
might drop this somewhere so small let's
get a picture you guys come
on you want to come forward a little bit
amazing thanks guys get some good food
okay I want to say thank you so much you
help me heal from schizophrenia and
addiction amazing you know I'm proud of
you right yes and I wanted to say is
there any words that Spirit might have
for me or my
girlfriend you know you have you have
faith okay keep it strong all right all
right you know you know he's got faith
now right he was lacking it before but
then he he built it up he's strong now
strong okay so just keep keep that there
all right yeah thank you so go right
thank you so much brother love you too
thank you I love you appreciate it thank
you're a good man and I'm proud of you
seriously so much don't lose
this everyday lives do we experience so
many heartaches
they don't understand why horrible
things are occurring in their lives they
feel something must be behind this it's
important to understand the realm that's
very rarely seen by the
eyes in all these decades I've been
asked about angels asked about the
afterlife I've been asked about
demons to understand demonic forces is
to understand Injustice and to ition and
trickery by the end of this original
audio you're going to understand the
forces at work in our lives you are
going to be awakened and you're going to
understand how to regain your power to
help protect yourself and your loved
ones so we can play our part in stopping
demonic forces in their tracks like
never before
[Music]
hi Mi was here last night I know I know
I figured we were just just saying that
want get another picture I would love
can you say hello to my mom and dad
though Barbie Day Mom Dad
watching I'm honored they're watching oh
well yeah
absolutely amazing they watching on
rumble or YouTube uh YouTube okay good
good can I give you a little some good
get some good food thank you so much for
doing this do over put a lot of work
into this and I really appreciate it
thank you thank
you hey how you doing I'm good I'm good
oh my God how are you you're good you're
good trying to have fun I mean I'm
having fun I hope you're having no no
I'm having a blast I'm having a blast
trust me good good good do you like the
food here I do I like the food here I'm
so grateful for Cafe Gratitude I am too
I wish they were
inula could be in want to be there want
to get a picture yes please step forward
step forward
okay thank you for coming bless your
heart seriously oh my god did you oh
nice to see you good to see you Anthony
for well thank you for doing this and I
just wanted to tell
you um
I've never been able to like fully
Express like how grateful I am for like
how much you for your support and for
your love and and your understanding um
it just really means a lot to me and I
just I pray for you all the time I'd
love I'd love to say a little prayer for
you if that's okay is that okay God
thank you for Anthony thank you for
protecting him thank you God he is a
prophet that you've given him such a
powerful voice and for giving him to us
as a
messenger thank you Jesus that no weapon
formed against him will prosper thank
you for surrounding him with armies and
Angels thank you for surrounding him and
filling him up God that he won't be
depleted or exhausted that you would
just give him energy and strength and
peace thank you God for all the just for
blessing us with Anthony and for just
protecting him God that the enemy
couldn't even get anywhere near him that
any plan of the enemy would be
completely destroyed in advance and we
just thank you God for just his light
and for who he is and I just pray that
you would bless him 10 fold for all that
he's done for us in Jesus name amen oh
bless your heart bless your heart okay
thank you I'll take any prayers I can
get all right you mean everything it
means world to me you want to get a
picture oh yeah okay okay you ready
right
here I'm doing everything not to cry
tonight but that one almost that almost
did it okay so just love
you good to see you same here I thought
I'd never get to meet you and here I am
you thought you'd never get to meet me
huh no I've read all your books but I
never thought did you get the brain
saver yet
no oh did I yes I did you did right yes
there's a lot in there there's a lot in
there do you want to get a picture yes
there's the
oh looking forward to your new book I
mean your new audio oh thank you thank
you cuz I'm hoping I'm hoping you like
it yeah I'm sure I
will I'm nervous about that one too
there a lot of information in that and
um I'm hoping I'm hoping the world is
ready yeah it'll be ready I think so I
think
so hi this see you H that's my mom
that's your mom I got her her first book
really she's been addicted ever since
well she even said she's looking at
brains saver too so I know I think it's
great yeah you you I you're amazing like
I follow you and I listen to whatever
like I buy my supplement from vem I got
my Omega everything you say I don't even
have to research I just trust your
opinion so thank you for everything you
do like I lifechanging for my mom like
she you've changed her she's happy
you've changed her life you've changed
her life yeah yeah so thank you so I
want to well she's laughing and she's
she's happy and it's just a beautiful
thing to see you want to step forward
and we'll get a picture
yeah amazing thank you
so we met yesterday how are you how are
you yes I just I just uh I want I want
to ask you to put some light into this
neckl into these yeah my my dad can you
put it in my hand yes right
here and then can you put that one in my
hand absolutely Here It
Go amazing let's get a picture and also
text the 369 champ he asked me to ask
you where's the the Right comes
from is is no I I'll talk about that I
think I'll talk about that okay it comes
from behind the stars but spirit says
comes from no specific place
place oh oh wait wait wait look oh
yeah oh yeah can we do the
picture there you
go your hard
okay thank you so much oh thank
you oh you're
hey what's going on good to see you good
to see you hi can I give you a hug yes
of course my God oh my God that's a big
ug thanks for where did you come from I
came from Las Vegas nice really yeah did
you drive it no I flew I fle this
morning I'm leaving tonight okay um and
I came because my baby um wanted to meet
you oh my God this is the best moment
ever this is this is amazing I mean I
want to meet you but he really to meet
you oh my God and honored truly okay
yeah and I'm um my journey is pretty new
just like 4 months and is because baby
wanted four months is a still a good
amount of time okay some people just do
4 hours of of the medical meeme
information and so that's beautiful yeah
and it's all because of him he wanted me
on time to be on medical medium yeah
that's amazing did you get the message
did he give you the message well I lost
my taste for meat you know which I love
I love Meats I love fat I still do but
baby wanted something different and so
can I ask the baby wanted something
different I was like
Mommy yeah I want something different
can I ask you two questions go ahead
yeah let's try to get through one okay
one um which is worse butter or um
canola oil if you had to that's a really
good question oh my
God canola oil is really
bad Butter's pretty darn
bad I'm probably going to get a lot of
not not friendly
friendly people aren't going to like
that one um they'll they're okay with
Canola being bad they're not okay with
butter being
bad if it was me personally and canola
is bad if there was a little bit of
canola in something
and a little bit of butter and something
I would eat the little bit of canola and
something I'm just saying and and and
that's not to say I'm eating canola cuz
I'm not but yeah but yeah I don't like
either or and then can I have my second
question yeah yeah okay I'm in a mommy
medical medium group and then we were
all
wondering wait what's the other question
okay if you can tell us while we're
taking a picture that could help Okay um
it's sorry it um so no fats is really
good for you right well you know what it
is is just people are doing so much fat
okay they're just they're killing their
livers and then in the end they're just
getting sick so yeah no so if you have
less fat or no fat um that's really good
for you okay and but um avocados are so
healthy so they are no that's a that's a
great food so as a pregnant person is it
okay if one does no fat well here's the
thing there's fat in everything no
matter what so there's no such thing as
no fat but but avocado is amazing for
pregnancy amazing for babies so
definitely it's one of the best foods
ever for babies okay so you want avocado
you avocado is amazing okay and then can
I have a photo on you got somebody else
oh just a photo on my phone oh on your
phone okay ready oh I uh I I turned it
off
all
right
okay okay thank
you all right enjoy the food tonight I'm
so proud of
you hey what's going on my hands are
freezing oh my still working on my
temperature oh my God how you been good
I we had the light FL and Boulder I know
I know you were there I saw you were you
were on the right side you weren't you
weren't on the left side of me you were
on this side of me yes yes I saw you you
were uh 1 2 3 4 5 you were five rows in
somewhere around there yes I always sit
up front I have a a a photographic
psychic memory unfortunately in many
ways it's fortunate in many ways but
it's not fortunate in others yeah but no
I came up on stage yeah no I know but I
remember where sitting I know I know you
were on stage but I remember exactly the
seat you were in okay want to get a
picture yes thank
you amazing thank you for coming are you
going to enjoy the food yes yes I'm
really looking forward to it it's our 5
year anniversary by the way 5 years 5
years next month okay that's incredible
April hello hey what's going on it's
good to see you this guy how did you get
him here that's easy she's draged
multile times 10 years yeah you'll drag
him you'll drag them anywhere do you
take them into the store he goes himself
no you know what you've gotten better at
things that the start it took a while to
get him into took a little while to
start a few years but there's no choice
good to see you guys want to get a
picture do come forward here a little
bit all right okay
amazing I did want to ask you something
um so you've done so much for us there's
a lot of us who are healed or feeling
healed what can we do for
you your support you guys you guys send
out all the support even through your
Consciousness every day you guys think
about the information you you you know
you listen to the the podcast you guys
you guys give me beautiful support okay
and and you know and you fight for the
community you fight for me it's like I'm
fighting for you guys I I can't ask for
anything else okay are all right you're
the best but we're Beyond prayers we're
here to help so let us know okay that
does mean that does mean a lot okay
thank you for enjoy the pizzas tonight I
know I'm going to okay hi good to see
you you thank you thank you for coming
yeah thanks for having me so I heard a
rumor that we could ask if sfc has a
message for us let's see if there's even
a message sometimes yeah there might not
be a
message okay I'm I'm way over to the
left let me ask you where do you want me
to
go how how much medical medum stuff are
you doing every day are you are you have
you been increasing any or it's just cuz
keep trying yeah that that's the message
where we got to get you back into into
it strong at some point but you're going
to be able to do it that's the message
it's going to come and you're going to
say you know what it's time okay let's
get a picture
together what
hi amazing enjoy the night I hope you
love the food cuz I
do oh oh you're with your
friend okay okay y y
the
de what's up what are
you you got the jacket yes got the
jacket do you like this one to picture I
love it I love it are you
kidding okay I have I have a question
for
you thank you for coming tonight okay
you're the coolest of the cool so are
you okay so you know how you say that we
don't manifest our illnesses or like
issues and stuff correct I think I think
the way you're saying it yes that's
that's correct so how much of it is like
a matrix attack how much his past lives
or Karma we're releasing and like is a
lot of a lot of it Matrix attacks
because we're like really trying to
cleanse and like you know we're our
bodies are getting pure we're not you're
going you're going to love the Angels
demons and spiritual tools audio you're
you're you're you're going to love it I
mean the answers that come through there
I mean I yeah you really
okay so you're not going to tell me well
no maybe I should talk about it more
though cuz it's such a big answer I mean
if I answer a piece of it it's going to
be missing 10 pieces right now that's
the only problem you know what I mean
yeah it's a huge question it's like the
meaning of life question it's like
what's the meaning of life that's how
big that question is so I I wouldn't
even be able to answer it all I'd leave
it I would leave it like I would leave
Parts out and then and then people would
be like wait a minute this is doesn't
make sense what about this what about
that okay but um but yeah it it's
there's so much there's so much okay we
don't create our illness right okay we
don't we don't manifest our illness we
don't create it okay doesn't work that
way um but um but yeah there there's a
lot of information the best but there's
Matrix attacks right huh there's Matrix
attacks right if you call it Matrix yeah
I mean there's a grid there's a grid
there's a grid I talk about it's coming
up okay all right thank you I appreciate
you you're the best all right Christian
hey Anthony what's going on how's it
going I can't believe you're here can
you see me amazing yeah I can't believe
I'm here too good to see you amazing I
miss you I miss you too yeah miss you
I'm proud of you are you doing all good
stuff you're doing everything I'm I'm
easier on myself that's what I love to
hear that's what I love to hear I've
been I've been asking Spirit to to you
know bring me the compassion for myself
yep so I could feel it and that way I
can handle whatever I'm up against yeah
I've I've been working on it I'm proud
of you and it's it's been it's been 7
years uh seven like 7 years since I uh
found the information that's that's
amazing you know that's amazing I mean
and to have that endurance to have that
commitment for that long you know I'm
proud of you right don't forget it I'm
not going to forget all right let's get
a picture yeah you can't forget this
time here come forward amazing
you know I'm proud of you love you I
love you too you know that brother I
know all right good good as long as you
know it all right I know it love you
Spirit hi Anthony good to see you again
how are you good to see you good I'm
glad you're here yeah me too um so I
just wanted to like tell you kind of
like how much I've come how far I've
come just like with the information and
like what I've been through sort of and
I just like want to say thank you for
like just I just remember watching a
video for the first time and just being
like who is this guy like what is he
doing and like this is so interesting
and I need to know everything about it
how long ago was that that was 3 and a
half years ago oh my God and you're
watching and you're like who is this who
is this guy talking about banana mono
and my I was like what is he talking
about like only eating bananas this
guy's crazy and then I did it and then I
like found your book and like the next
day I started a 369 cleanse which
probably isn't like not going to
recommend that cuz I kind of fell off
trained but then got back on and and I
just feel like yeah I'm just so like
grateful and just like for everything
and all your hard work and all your
effort and just like always being one
step ahead and always just just putting
in like the the True Grit and it just
like it's it's so like I'm so grateful
and I'm just so appreciative I just
wanted you to know that thank you you're
the greatest okay and I appreciate all
that I do I do I heard every word and
spirit heard every word Spirit of course
I love spirit and like he's so amazing
and so kind and generous to all of us so
thank you so thank you for coming again
okay you want to get another picture
let's go let's get
one amazing of course of course I'm
proud of you okay thank
you look what are you doing good to see
you again how you doing good to see you
good to see you um thank you for coming
again yeah um it's just been really
intense uh lately me I'm just I'm just
wondering I just really need some hope
as far as like what I should do with my
healing and like where I should go with
it I tried the mono cleans uh again was
that hard to do it was hard to do I had
I lost some weight and uh it really
scared me are you getting enough you get
enough calories I try to get as many
calories as possible I don't want to
anyone else well that's the thing about
good thing but that's the thing about
hard for me yeah listen it's important
to know
like you can eat as much as you need to
eat there's no there's no portion thing
there's no nothing like you make sure
you're eating enough yeah because this
the medical meme information is the only
information that doesn't minimize
portions no no every single cleanse out
there in the world every single diet
belief system they they restrict and
they restrict and they restrict but
there's no restrictions so don't hold
back no I didn't build yourself up yeah
I ate as much as possible but I was
still it was still really hard what I
mean what does Spirit say I I should
well I mean it's like this okay you know
you're on the right track you know
you're taking care of yourself really
good okay and then that's what you do
you keep you keep you're here right now
you're doing better in so many ways so
much pain and Agony so it's so it's so
hard know I know I know and the doctors
don't have I don't sleep well I I like
for days sometimes I don't sleep cuz of
my my pain what do the doctors say here
come on step forward what are they
saying the do the
doctors I do see doctors I do see
doctors but they don't oh they're not
helping they're not
helping it's not easy it's not e I tried
medications and they don't work keep
keep up all the good work keep on
working on it I'm proud of you okay okay
a little bit at a time all right welcome
be easy on
yourself goodbye heyy hello hello hey
how how are you good to see you good to
see you again always a friendly face oh
good to see you I I I get something in
my mind in the morning I wake up 5:00
a.m. in the morning and I was thinking
wait a minute this year what what is
really happening right now this live
stream and all the stuff it's like a
Hollywood production and know what
thinking this must be a high price
ticket to come in but it's for it's for
free for the people right they can watch
it and I was thinking it's free how how
many people are working here and do do
everything for for us and I know I know
that's what I try to do I try to keep
everything for free and that's what I
that's what I do because you got people
who are ically sick and they've been
through a lot and the industry
is very dirty out there and all they do
is just you know everything's a price
everything's a price they don't care how
sick you are what you've been through
yes you know and the spirit of
compassion we fight to make sure that
doesn't happen here the best we can um
and so just thank you for coming okay
you want to get a picture yeah for sure
thank thank you so much
so
yeah
okay thank you my brother just one
little thing um maybe in the future I
will uh will do a little um like a
podcast or something like this maybe I
can ask you in the future to I'm sure
I'm sure I'm
sure we'll do it we'll do it it'll come
thank you so
much hi thank you for saving my life
well I can't believe your real and like
I can see you I'm real I exist I've read
all your books I've read them multiple
times watched all your shows all of your
podcasts it's amazing to see you thank
you thank you I'm tot thank you for your
support and everything let's get a
picture thank you for all your
support thank you for reading all the
books yeah does you have any
advice I mean you're on track you're
doing it yeah well the thing is with you
is you like a lot of information you
like seeing different things and stuff
and that's that's very special about you
you just don't get fixated on one thing
only and so you're looking at the big
picture okay that's what you do you tend
to look at the big picture just keep on
doing that thankk
you uh what's going on here who's this
guy nice to meet you nice to meet you
this is your son
yes nice to meet you nice to meet you
too good to see you good to see you how
are you guys tonight uh great I'm get to
meet you and I'm very grateful and
thankful for what the effort that you've
put into the work that you do uh it's
changed my life and in many ways not
just Health but like yeah in in every
aspect that's that's that means the
world yeah you got a good kid here thank
you you got a really good kid thank
God you guys want to get a photo I love
a photo yeah come on let's get a photo
together you want to be on the left side
of me right side of me how do we do this
here I think we we have you want to step
forward a little bit okay amazing of
course of course of
course I'm proud of your son I'm proud
of you seriously are you going to have
some good food tonight yeah I think so
your heart thank you God bless you too
thank
you hey hey how are you fine how are you
good to see you good to see you always
well I'm honored okay do you want to get
a picture y here step forward
here thank you foring and get some good
food yeah will all right you go hith to
see I love your necklace thank you thank
you for everything that you do and I'm
so happy to be here I'm so excited I'm
just glad you're here I'm glad you're
here thank you do you like the food here
I love the food here delicious I'm
looking forward to it tonight good I
have a question um all the terrible
things that happen to the animals on
this planet it eats me up in sign me too
how do I deal with that that's a sore
spot for me truly you know cuz that's a
you then that's a really sad thing truly
a sad thing um it's
uh you know God takes care of
them when they leave and they've been
they've been you know wronged and
injustic upon the animals you know God
truly takes care of them when they leave
get some good food you're going to get
me crying animals is animals is a tough
one
yes Jess what are you doing here comes
all the
praise good to see you likewise I'm very
happy thanks for making it back here no
I'm so happy I was able to get the Tien
but I want to is that camera a this is a
great this is a great jacket right here
I was going to wear a hat too but I
didn't want to to confus us so I've worn
this one a 100 times maybe maybe more
nice yeah but anybody who's watching
Anthony's the real guy in man I mean
honestly blush I'm Going to blush it's
just pra pra sprays get the book I mean
help me out here like eye
problems um anxiety depression weight
problems everything um uh arthritis you
name it it's it's just all healed thanks
to you you so I just want to give praise
praise praise so thank you so much thank
you man it means the world and Lucille
says hi so okay okay I I understand yeah
so much appreciated well let's get a
picture J let's get a picture it's
amazing and you're like 6 foot six 6'
6 all good
stuff all right good see I forget I know
you're tall but I forget how tall you
are it's amazing man well mm Made Me 2
in
since last time so there you go I love
it you're the best okay you too mank
thanks for coming tonight for real for
real look at you look at you doing look
at you look what you're doing so
wonderful to meet you how you doing do
you want to get a picture yeah let's get
a picture here step step forward
here did you like the food last night
excuse me did you like the food here I
it's my I love the food you love the
last did you last event yes it was
amazing thank you that I can be here and
have this amazing time and that I can
meet you and for everything that you do
and can I ask you something tell me
about my new apartment should I should I
stay in there or you don't like
it no you don't like it I I like it I
like it but there are problems there are
problems with smells with smoke and
other fragrances and maybe it's not good
for but they're out of there though
they're you it's all gone into it's left
it's going into it but we tried to make
it good but I don't
know I I is it really bothering you or
you think you're okay yeah I it's not
it's you can you can sleep in it right
with the air filter that's good that's
important okay where should I direct a
lie to tonight no no only you only you
know that tonight okay when I asked I'm
going to ask everybody and then you
start thinking about it now though start
thinking about it now so then you you're
ready okay okay let's get a picture have
you had we already had
one okay thank you hi Anthony I'm Daria
so good to see you to see you I've been
following M INF for8 years now that's
all I know I'm just getting started and
you're just such a big part of my life
and my health journey and even my family
back in Russia are now trying to follow
along my mom my dad had celery juice for
the first time this week it took me many
years so I'm very excited and just want
to thank you from the bottom of my heart
I know you go through a lot of
challenges to put this information out
for everyone and just thank you so much
for for your work and tell your folks
prev yet okay okay well thank you for
coming and I also we have a community of
medic comedian Folks up in the Bay area
and we signed this card for you I know
they're all watching um and we oh my God
look at this yeah it's a little little
smile it's a ligh heart thank you this
is very special from the Bay Area
amazing there's a lot of amazing Folks
up there some couldn't make it today
some still bedridden but we're all
grateful for you one day at a time one
day at a time for many one hour right
yeah I was wondering if I could ask I
always feel so conflicted and confused
about if I'm going in the right
direction with my work and my studies
and I was wondering if s so has any you
can't go wrong you can't go wrong with
that you you go you you'll
you'll if
it it's supposed to happening because
you you're on it you're doing it right
and then it'll shift when it needs a
shift it'll just hit you and you're like
okay it's time all right let's get a
picture thank you yes here come forward
thank you so much God bless you God
bless you
okay okay what do we have here Frank
Frank you yes it's an honor this my wife
this my honor this is your wife who got
who into what now she got me into this
you got him into it how did you do that
it's very hard very hard you get here's
the thing though but once you get him
into it once he finally says okay okay
that's
it that's it right he's in it yeah he's
in it once he's in it he's in it he
doesn't have any choice he don't have
you don't have the choice I mean
honestly he has to take his lemon water
and celery juice I four lemon trees in
my back you got four lemon trees celer
dishes what kind of lemons do you want
do you know what lemon it is
is it a Myer lemon is it a Myer lemon is
it a is it a regular lemon the
kind yes I also have the lime those are
the best ones you got a lime too oh
fresh lime off the
tree cut it Pour squeeze it in there
I'll be thinking about you okay when I
have lemon water I'm so proud of you
she's doing she following your book you
know I'm proud of you okay I'm proud of
you too thank you so much for all your
doing thank you for making the trip
where did you guys come from from
brenwood brenwood nice I'm glad I'm glad
I'm glad I hope you come in and have the
pizza someday of course it's here clean
we come here thank you appreciate it
again get a picture sorry you guys want
to get
picture oh I did you want to step
forward a little bit oh in the book go
ahead okay thank you
[Music]
amazing I'm proud of you guys I'm proud
of you okay bless your heart get some
good food tonight I I'm looking forward
to
it Anthony good to see you again look at
you good to see you you got a book for
me yes ah nice nice I got my vitality
and motivation back and I feel like it's
easier to laugh and sing now and I want
you to know that yeah your Soul's
healing
your physical body is healing and your
Soul's coming back to you and you're get
you're getting your life back and that
that that means everything to me okay
that's what it's about right there means
everything I don't know why I always do
that but I do here you
go that's your heart I you want to get a
picture um set forward here thank you
amazing proud of you you going to get
some good food tonight yes Pizza cookies
pizza that's right Anthony to see you my
gosh going to give you a hug what's
going on what's going on huh oh I just
love you so
much I don't even know what to say I'm
so grateful to you for changing my life
it means the world okay it does it does
yeah you know if you've been through a
lot and I know you have it it matters it
matters to me okay yeah I know you work
hard yeah I already know that I actually
already know that I don't have to ask I
don't have to say oh you doing enough
enough or H I know I know you are yeah
yeah want to get a picture yeah
absolutely okay step forward a little
bit okay amazing yeah you ready how's
that
Mikey thank you for coming tonight
you're going to get some good food
tonight okay okay cheers me up you're
going to get me
crying you H how are you wow strong and
shap thank you good to see you thank you
I saw you in the line I'm like hey
what's going on I'm here I'm glad you're
here cuz my mother she's a big fan so oh
my God everyone that you know do you
want to say hi to her because you're
you're we on right here oh I'm oh hey Ma
sorry I'm late hit some traffic yeah
she's the reason why I'm here she saw
that you know I wasn't looking well and
I'm like I'm not feeling well she's like
started bringing me the the the morning
smoothie and really yeah that's she was
just like you got to do this yeah I went
to visit her and she's like it's
probably your liver she just got me on
it and I was been on this healing
Journey for 5 years now so wow you got
some Mom oh my
God I'm I'm proud of you I'm proud of
her okay thank you cuz you're the one
that that started the whole thing we're
living our best life and we were able to
share with our family and our friends
you know you look amazing okay thank you
for coming down here you're repping your
mom yeah absolutely amazing let's get a
picture might get another
picture oh that
camera amazing amazing thank you I'll
see you later enjoy the food I
will hey what's going on how are you
good it's uh it's good to be here but
also yeah just like
surreal I'm honored you're here okay
thank you I am I am want to get a
picture together all right good good
good move forward here a little
bit thanks for coming thanks man get
some good
food look at you you got a book yes I do
and a Sharpie want to take the you want
to take the cap off for me yes sir
thank you so much I I I I just wanted to
make sure I told you in person how
grateful I am for everything um I I got
you a gift uh really yeah this these are
my dogs um this is lucky and Lily from
their puppy Hood up into dogood well
this these are two two dogs this is so
they're just oh I I see you got the
different pictures I love that those are
him eating the blueberries and I was
able to reverse his Alzheimer's with
your smoothie okay so I'm giving him
extra months because of your smoothie
and I'm I gave L I'm going to wear that
T-shirt with great great honor okay I
want you to know that you might want to
get a cap back
on thank you so much I really appreciate
everything you do here come up here
thank you I'm so grateful for everything
you do let's get a picture thank you I'm
honored you're here thank you so much
than get some good food tonight do you
want me to take this please I'm excited
about this I love dogs I can't express
how grateful I am for everything thank
you so much thank
you thank you all right
here we here look at this guy here thank
you you picked a tall one right
y we just wanted to say thank you so
much sure thank you for sharing your
knowledge and your healing with us and
with the world we really appreciate I'm
honored thank you for coming you guys we
have your books sorry we didn't bring
them we'll bring them next time that's
okay that's okay you guys brought
yourselves okay we did did right bring
next time have you eaten here before no
I'm excited to try it okay this is cool
yeah this is cool got some pizzas
tonight you know excellent guilt-free
pizzas okay we haven't had pizza in so
long not all that dripping oil and
cheese and grease and salt and
everything it's clean and so good for
you fantastic let's get a picture you
guys how long you've been doing medical
meeting here step forward a little bit
oh yeah just come forward a little bit
here Mike is this good why am I in the
middle you're in the
middle thank you thank you how long you
been doing the medical medium stuff now
um about 3 years 3 years long time
that's that's incredible yeah yeah
that's incredible we keep up all the
good work thank you so 65 you're keeping
me young you you're yeah you're young
and you look young love you
guys hello nice to we have yes I do this
is for my friend Barb or not Barbara um
Monica Monica yeah you've signed my book
already this my third medical media
event and I still have a picture with
you
thank you super yes so I just want to
thank you and also does the spirit of
compassion have any messages for me does
the spirit of compassion have any
messages for
me I'm I'm
listening do you like what's your
favorite color you like colors like it's
a big thing for you you like things with
color I do don't don't don't lose that
just you know nurture that more okay and
then when um Springtime comes right you
know look at flowers and and always
think about the colors because for with
you and maybe not with everybody
else but with you it it it it kind of
rewires you okay I find it healing
sometimes exactly here step
forward amazing get some good food thank
you so much
take your time sorry no take your time
it's okay I'm not going to run don't all
right so nice to see you bless your
heart thank you for coming thank you two
years ago I was told by doctors that
both my shoulders both my hips would
need to be replaced and so one year on
MM my shoulders look at this I couldn't
oh my God you got rid of the Frozen
shoulders they were both it was so right
it was really
awful and people don't realize that when
you have a frozen shoulder what that
really means you can't lift up your arm
you just can't you can't do that yeah it
was miserable my right hip is still and
I've healed my sight my hearing my dent
a lot of dental he but my right hip is
still so bad and I was wondering does s
so think that I can heal my right hip
without having to put like a bunch of
metal or ceramic in my body well you
know you're look at all that you're
healing yes just keep keep on forging
ahead keep keep on working on things and
you see where you are yeah but you're
but you're stopping the aging process
you're you know you're reversing so much
just stay on track and and and and see
you know and one day at a time one day
at a time get a picture do you think you
would ever do a podcast on how to avoid
joint replacement uh it's very possible
is it possible yes it is it is very
possible I can do one thank you ready
right here you're welcome
amazing get some good food your
heart we got a book so happy to see you
good to see you good to see
you amazing thank you for coming tonight
yeah into your Culver City one your c
one calabas is2 dee day yeah I have a
present for you I wanted to tell you how
much you have profoundly changed my
heart and soul forever really you and so
so this is for you oh my God look at
that oh my God that's so nice should I
keep it back in here in there if you
want I just want oh my God thank you
let's going to H in my life to ask you a
quick question step forward um I've done
the 369 for 8 months straight at one
point but then I fall off the wagon and
stuff and I'm wondering when that's okay
that's okay don't don't be tough don't
be hard on yourself when if that happens
okay when you're ready you'll know you
wake up in the morning you go in the
kitchen you'll be like this is this is
my time right now I'm going to do it now
okay yeah and how long will it take if I
do it for a year will it fix my fatty
liver
disease one day at a time one day at a
time it it does miracles for a lot of
people for a lot of different things and
just you know when you're ready get back
get back on the horse I think this is
going to get me back but how long do I
to for a year 2 years it it's it
sometimes it takes time A lot of people
been on it for a long
time hey Anthony good to see you good to
see you thanks for doing all this than
you're welcome thanks for coming here
yeah of course you King I'm Liam me to
78 787 son no
way no way I've been doing your protocol
since I was 10 years old I've been doing
the morning cleanse he's been doing this
since 10 yeah come on I've been really
good to see you I've been reading your
comments for many years I've been
following your information for many
years too it's always good it's always
good too your comments are always solid
every time you every time I I catch one
I'm like ah yeah yeah solid guy solid
guy who's this my wife she's the one
that introduced me to comian did you how
did you how did you get him to do it I
don't know he was pretty uh down yeah so
I was like you just like come on yeah it
was a really low point it's so actually
six years ago this month that I had the
first glass of celer juice I was feeling
really really down and is that when your
son like how old are you now uh almost
15 almost 15 almost 15 so he started
later he started with an ouns yeah what
did you what was it like to have your
first ounce of celery juice it was
disgusting it was disgusting some days I
still think that you know some days some
days some days here we'll stand you over
here some days yeah I'm like this is a
just a terrible tasting batch of celery
juice I don't blame you one bit Yeah
shoot um if Spirit of compassion doesn't
mind uh where does he recommend me
direct the light from tonight's light
bus uh is it are you okay if I tell you
that you're an overthinker yeah is that
all right or yeah yeah that's great okay
okay okay well but but it's also the
times of day and night you think and
even night what time do you go to bed at
night like 9:30 10:00 yeah and then what
time do you start thinking in the
morning um like pretty much when I get
up when you get up yeah you think in
your sleep probably and I don't run too
I don't run into that too
often he thinks spirit says he thinks in
his
sleep did you ever watch him sleep yeah
does he move at
all he does yeah yeah he speaks and he
he talks and he he he he he talks in his
sleep once in a while yeah he's a sleep
talker probably more than you know cuz
you're probably sleeping a lot during
that time yeah he's a sleep talker he's
a sleep thinker he's an overthinker so
let's get the light there it's good to
be that though don't get me wrong it's
good to be that but we'll send some some
light in there to strengthen since you
do so much thinking all right is it okay
if I just ask you one more quick
question shot has Spirit of compassion
ever helped you pass a test in
school yes yes straight in fact I didn't
learn anything in school because of it
that's
awesome
Yep anything I did in school that was
good spirit gave me the answers and yeah
that's cool yeah good thanks anthy all
right until I didn't even want to hear
spirit anymore and then that's when I
did back
school thank you thank you thank you
nice meeting you love you guys get some
good food good to see you okay thank you
for your
support hi Anthony
hey my name is Eden hi it's uh a
pleasure to meet you good to see you
this for you this for me thank you I a
psychiat it says aw from Dr Eden H
poning thank you it's amazing I'm a
psychiatrist I amazing yeah I started
doing chats with people on Instagram who
have healed using information God I got
a lot of respect for psychiatrists okay
I do I do I know and and um especially
when they're like learning medical
medium information forget it you know
yeah well I really felt for um Dr Nesbit
at your last live you know Dr NES
um I heard from my friend well that was
Charlie no I know but then but then
nesbet oh nesbet was on the phone yes
yeah he fell ill he was eating chicken
so I thought let me call him nesid can't
stop the the drinking and what's with
the cannibalism so I said you know what
I I I just reached out to my colleague
he was a little cold I put him in here
and I picked him up from the airport
okay yeah yeah yeah he's here to try
plant plant-based food wait a minute
wait a minute this is not this is an
impostor is it oh no he told is this Dr
n he said he wanted to try the
plant-based food is that
[Laughter]
him Dr nesbet how the heck did you get
how the heck did you get here old
classmates no it's it's it's it's a Dr
it's an impostor oh no Dr nesbet know
how I know he pulled the hole over my
eyes Dr Nesbit said he's a psychiatrist
didn't say he's a board certified
psychiatrist which he always
says um this is a cousin of Dr Nesbit
which is also a doctor too okay just a
different kind of doctor not a
psychiatrist sport no all right sorry
you got I got to send you back thank you
no no no take care take care all right
thank all right want to get a picture
yes please here move forward here I'm
I'm way over yeah I'm way over
here amazing you're a blessing thank you
so much take care take care of take care
of this baby right this way man
maybe
hello I'm Ken good to see you hello Sean
Sean what nice to meet you nice to meet
you too what did you say Sean we're
going on a trip I did I he was like
where are we going I said you threw him
in you threw him in the car that's what
I did for myself for my
birthday he was like where are we going
yeah you're like we're going somewhere
don't worry Sean I knew you knew I knew
and I could not wait do you guys want to
get a picture yes we do step up here
thank you for thank you for being to the
conduit for ass so I would not be here
oh you're
welcome thank you Sean thank you for
coming seriously you guys are going to
get some good food yeah it's an honor
it's an honor having you here it's an
honor thank you my
brother what's going on good to see you
how are you good how are you doing is
that is that a crystal are those
crystals I think it's
organ tell us the pyramids were good
that's amazing yeah no I know that's an
organite uh necklace I think so that's
what it said it was very special can I
ask you Anthony if the spirit has any
messages for me you have a loving kind
heart okay Spirit knows this okay but
remind yourself of that okay let's get a
picture here step
forward thank you for everything you do
for us
thank you get some good food thank you
hello hi I'm
Alisia and thank you for everything that
you do for us thank you in particular
for connecting me to the angels the
angels have been really important to me
and I thank you for
that I'm about to turn 50 and I wonder
if you have any advice as on my healing
Journey for this next phase in my life
you're you're working on your healing
every day are you doing which which
which is your favorite medical M tour
are you doing some tools um celery um
369 drink the celery juice and lemon
water um don't stop the lemon water okay
make sure you keep all those tools in
there fantastic how much lemon do you
put in your lemon water one really
entire in the 32 l oh that's really good
I'm proud of you keep keep keep moving
forward you know
okay here step step here thank you thank
you right here where are we going a
little bit
okay amazing get some good food thank
you what's going on hi nice to meet you
how are you how are you good good um my
name is Yuko and I can't believe I get
this chance to meet you and I'm not sure
what to say but well I'm just glad
you're here thank you thank you where
where'd you come from um I'm from
Seattle Seattle um uh friend friend of
Noel and dick shepher oh really yes yes
oh my God I hope they're watching this
look who I have here Noel check this out
okay
amazing those two are very special
people they are oh oh
the Shepherds yeah she yes they're the
best thank you for coming and I really
appreciate it thank you thank you for
everything holding this amazing event
all the events for us and for caring and
yeah much appreciate well your friends
are your friends are healers and they
they have a a lot of years of healing
experience and I have a lot of respect
for them cuz they're my friends
too bless your heart
hi hey how you doing my name is Al nice
to meet you nice to meet you really
appreciate you I have to say my life was
very tough like at dark times I was in
disability doctors couldn't help
couldn't do anything you were you were
on disability that's well like at let's
say let's put it that way disability
leave from work yes and then you
couldn't work anymore no I I could even
go to grocery store which is like a
quarter mile without taking a break I
had to like sit down and wait until like
break my heart it breaks my heart to
know that you had to do that and I'll
tell you like um I was I understand that
I do I do it's unless you've been there
no one understands that unless they you
know they've been there you actually had
to take a break to get to the store yeah
just around the corner yeah and once I
start start following your information
which I actually was following for for a
couple years and I actually
unfortunately I couldn't trust I would
be in a totally different spot if I just
start following you from the very
beginning so you didn't trust it yet no
it took you a little time yeah what do
you what you're meeting me in person now
what do you think well even before after
even before you trust me and you were
there yeah my life improved within 2
weeks after trying your protocol I get
back to work hopefully you still stay
with it after meeting me I hope I I meet
your expectations of course you're a
blessing you're a blessing stand forward
a little bit
amazing thank you thank
you thank you so much I'm proud of you
by the way I'm proud of you okay
remember
that got to get
myself hi Anthony to meet you again you
so I have a question have you ever heard
that women are capable of stopping and
controlling their reproductive
system or stopping and controlling yeah
like to stop ovulating because we only
want to have like two kids per se and
then our immune system drops by like 80
to 90% so if we could stop ovulating
when we don't want to have kids that
could really save a woman's
life no I know and but but the but even
though um even though there's control or
control control can happen to that
degree then there's
God and then there's um you the Angelic
realm and there's things that happen for
reasons we just can't we we can't
measure and we can't understand and and
and sometimes it just you know overrides
a certain course and changes a direction
and so it
it you know nothing's guaranteed you
know and that's the one thing
about God and the Angelic realm and the
spiritual realm is things happen when we
don't even realize why they're happening
then or not and
so but I but I've heard I've heard of
something like in that that belief yeah
and um cuz when I read your book I
prayed for one thing menopause yep you
know and I was with a group of women
that we were all saying yeah when we
read his book we just prayed that we
would have that happen sooner than later
because our imun system is being
destroyed by our reproductive system
right so is God just angry at women and
we're not going to survive the viral a
[__] this way no you know it it's it but
there's things though you know that's
there's tools to over overcompensate
anything and and keep strong too so
there's a lot of tools as well you know
but no I understand I understand get a
photo yeah okay very interesting it's
it's a deep talk it's a deep talk I want
to interview you here step forward here
it's a deep talk I'm going to talk about
more but I'll do a podcast episode and
cover that wonderful okay thank you cuz
I have so many things to say and that's
why I'm yeah and then there's the things
you're not allowed to say which I'm
really interested in there probably are
things I'm not allowed to say there is
there's always something I'm not allowed
to say
hey hi how are you good to see you good
to see you hey nice to meet you nice to
meet you McGee McGee I know that I know
that amazing this is my twin is your
twin oh my God I was having like a
psychedelic psychedelic moment or huc I
was
hallucinated it was as if I was on COC
ibin or something which I do not take
which I do not take on any level good to
see you guys see you want to get a
picture yeah absolutely want to step
forward like oh closer back oh back
[Music]
sorry yeah
yeah by the way thanks for all your
support okay thank you thank so much and
thank you for saving her you know she's
I saw her when she was in bed and
couldn't get out of bed and we're only
18 and you know to see her now she's
getting married and what yeah she's
getting married in May Portugal you know
she says yes to life always and I I know
it's because of finding your books and
I'm really grateful I love you my God
you guys are amazing okay she's healing
vertigo too guys you're healing some
vertigo too I'm proud you well got the
tool so thank you take your time I do
want to ask if Spirit has anything to
say to me but my God Spirit loves you
right but but you know you you've
already gotten to a place you already
care about yourself on a compassion of
love you're taking care of yourself and
you've dropped so many different
negative like thoughts and all kinds of
things because of hardships you've moved
forward okay appreciate that so thank
you
an he how are you good to see want to
get a [__] in sure sure move forward up
here are you
amaz is there a message has for
me just always keep a light heart okay
and I tell a lot of people that but with
you like you know you keep a light heart
sometimes but then you know you're in
this this other kind of frequency you
got to always not worry about the little
stuff worry about the little stu okay
okay hey good to see you good to see you
again yes want to take a picture i' i'
love to here come on up I'd love to know
if um I'd love to know if s so has any
anything any information to share with
me and I wanted to thank you for sharing
your
gift with all of
us hard to talk while smiling so much
but you your information helped me get
off mattress Island I started healing
with wild blueberry smoothies in 200
2006 and then uh she introduced me to
Hay House and then I found you in 2014
so I think the way I found the blueberry
smoothies must have been from somebody
who saw you lecture back in the day um
but I've continued healing from there
and it's been a really beautiful and
special experience and I'm so make sure
you're doing the wild blueberries now
right yes yes and I was then too good
good good all right good that's
important where did you live then uh in
the middle of nowhere I still live in
the middle of nowhere okay so how did
you how did you get a wild blueberry in
the middle of nowhere that's amazing
this is like huh that's amazing okay
than you I drove to Trader joon's huh
that's amazing 06 yeah I never would
have found you if it weren't for my
friend T know I'm proud of you right do
you guys know each other do you want to
get a picture together to
on is that a doctor's Cod it is oh my
God doctor traditional Chinese medicine
really oh my God that's amazing she
became one after she sent me to you so
she's totally brand new to mm and I
wanted to meet my hero and she's My
Heroine too don't don't stop the
smoothies don't stop all the that you're
doing doing celery juice too yes yes
like daily for many years although I've
been I do slack periodically okay
sometimes I slack cuz I'm not a mattress
Island no no worries I'm just so happy
you're off mattress Island okay and I'm
proud of you and I'm so glad that you've
been doing this for so long okay bless
your hearts than you all right thank you
for
everything anthy it's so good to see you
again my poet my love love you so much
I'm so grateful for you and
um I'm just not going to let
you I'm not going to let you go this is
my girlfriend Christine it's her first
time meeting you really so I to meet you
okay it's going to be her first light
blast so I'm excited for her to share in
the experience I I wanted to tell you
I've been I've been going through some
really um emotional trauma with my
mother most
recently and um like super heavy I'm
sure you can feel it but all I wanted to
say
was the timing couldn't be better to be
here with you and being here with you I
I feel like you're my this is my soft
space you're my soft space to we're
going to we're going to do some healing
tonight the light blast is going to be
really powerful tonight yeah so than
thank you for being my soft place I want
you to know that yeah thank you m you
want to get a picture you want to move
forward bit you
guys amazing guys get some good food
okay good to meet you too love you
too what's going
on long time no I know I know excited
I'm glad you're here so excited I'm glad
you're here you're excited about food
tonight too so excited Anthony can I be
selfish and ask if I have a message from
Spirit of
compassion you're how much how much um
how long You' been doing medical meeting
now six seven years perfect perfect okay
good because spirit says that um there's
still some things to add okay okay but
you can subtract too you you can
subtract a couple of things and then you
can add a couple of things okay okay so
there's a
reason but it but what I'm saying is
kind of shift around a little bit like
look back into it okay and then try some
different things okay I don't I don't I
don't know exactly the reason but that's
what spirit's saying so okay it's good
it's good it's good stuff thank
you amazing get some good food time
okay go ahead okay you do
okay okay are you guys together or no we
are well we came together you you came
together yeah hi fantastic yeah nice to
meet you I feel like we should know each
other cuz i' you've made yourself so
available to everyone I mean coming you
know being I came to like the last two
events too so it's just like well at
cver city and Calabasas amazing and now
you're here at Cafe Gratitude I'm here
okay I gave her your book forever ago
and I haven't followed your work as well
as she has she's been so devoted I'm
just glad you gave her the book okay
thank you for doing
it's okay if you haven't followed
everything or follow enough but she's
been really devoted that's aming that's
amazing she was saying that you um we
we're sorry we were giving some readings
so we were curious if you were getting
any messages can you what's saying to
you right now I'm so curious just still
keep up on it okay you got more work to
do yes there's more work to do but you
know just hopefully tonight with the
light blast and everything you get more
inspired you are inspired but there's
still more to do
L heart we got we got yep we got some
work but that's okay that's okay that's
good okay let's get a photo ready thank
you so
[Music]
much amazing thank you so much okay I'll
see you guys thank you so much don't
forget oh you guys
are you guys ready yeah it's great to
meet you again how are you doing good
how about you great to meet you too how
are you great I'm I'm honored that
you're here he made some artwork for you
really you want to explain it to
him oh my God that's amazing these are
the
be is that a
bee these are
bees amazing
is whoa and what are these here flowers
flowers amazing and what's this here I
got drinking celery juice oh my God is
that the celery juice right there this
is incredible this is Inc this is from
my daughter she couldn't be here oh my
God so she wanted me to bring that to
you those are those are our two dogs
that we just rescued whoo this is
amazing with the
butterflies so that's for you oh this is
so special thing you want to get a
picture you guys yes you ready you want
me to be ready we can you want me to be
we can we're going to look this way so
I'll have you guys move forward a little
bit you want me to want to hold one for
me amazing thank you guys are you going
to get some good food yes I can't wait
I'm glad glad you guys are I can't wait
to eat myself
amazing hi hey I'm again yes yes good to
see you good to see you here uh come
over here you want to get a picture
let's
go amazing thanks for coming you got a
little little sign a little something
here yes and does Spirit of compassion
have any um business advice for me cuz
I'm I'm struggling to get the VY into
South Africa with all the legal stuff so
well you know what there's look in the
books and find other tools that you can
get there there's still things and foods
and things and the Brain shots and just
just keep on looking because there's
there's things you can do okay bless
your
heart hi hey how are you good to see you
um can I ask you a question you always
say that we're at the Forefront of time
what does that mean it means that
um billions and billions of people have
have come and gone
civilizations have come and gone
thousands tens of thousands hundreds of
thousands of years right
and why are we the small little group of
people out of all that why are we here
in the present moment right up against
time right so right now is a is it
because we all won the lottery with one
in you know one and uh 900 trillion no
it's yeah we're here we're we're on the
Forefront of time and it's something
very special about it I don't know if
that that if that is maybe I'll talk
about that all
right amazing thank you enjoy the
food hey how you doing cool hat where'd
you come from um I'm from uh Northern
California nice you made the trip down
here did you drive it no I flew you flew
yeah yeah that's for Northern California
that's what you have to do we have to
yeah it's a long drive I'm happy to be
able to make it to see you well I'm
honored thank you for coming I only F
you for four months uh really you only
found me how much four months yeah 4
months thank you for thank you for um
doing the medical medium stuff and fing
me I'm honored thank you um I would like
to ask if you have any advice um because
I I lost so much weight I I've been
doing it but I lost so much weight I
don't know if I'm doing it right I don't
know if you have any don't don't
um you know
don't just are you doing 369 or are you
doing 28 to what are you doing are you
doing different different uh cleanses I
think I lost weight initially to begin
with and then I try to do the simple
c um
are you trying to exercise a little what
can you do for
exercise uh I would probably start
walking can you're walking yeah you're
walking and you build up a little more
muscle to see and that brings up the
weight so and because you're eating so
good you should build up muscle
fast all you have to do is move a little
and muscle builds quick because you're
doing all the right things you're giving
your muscle what they need so once you
start using them they build really quick
and then you'll see your weight go up
and then and also there's no there's no
portion control so always know that cuz
cleanses did you do anything healthy
like try to do anything in the health
world before
this nothing at all you just went
straight to
this that's I Chang to vegan in
overnight well were you doing other
things in the health movement a health
world out there I just I was you're
you're very
rare you know how I always say you know
how I say people don't just go straight
to Medical medium first they have to go
through everything they have to try
everything oh yeah yeah I did I went I
went through the doctors and doctor okay
see I I almost was like Spirit what are
you telling me because she's telling me
something different and spirit's telling
me something different I did I and I'm
like okay then I got I got to find you
okay okay okay okay good good good okay
let's get a picture yeah thank
you I thought I was losing my
mind okay I'm so happy you're here keep
up all the good things okay thank
you
hello SI for 33 years everything better
I'm okay I was oh my God you're okay yes
I'm okay that is what matters thank you
thank you so much
and um thank you so much for all the
spiritual
information thank you 33 years I'm all
I'm okay okay that cheers me up okay
here let's get a picture here come
forward a little
bit they told me i' be in a
wheelchair my God you're standing here
yeah I know and I wore my black jacket
so
[Music]
to amazing I'm proud of you
hi anth are you I'm good thank you it is
so good to meet you and to be able to
say thank you for you know saving my
life and only that yeah yeah just that
no you you worked hard for it though
okay yeah you know but you work hard no
matter what you do in this world and I'm
just grateful to have something that
works that's a good that's wisdom right
there you work hard no matter what you
do in this world there's a lot of wisdom
in that well thank you so much you want
to get a picture yes absolutely
thank you thank you for being here you
bless you you got a book for me yes
what's going on Hi how are you good good
good good where'd you get this guy found
on the street you found him somewhere
huh yeah what a great guy he really is
I'm very
lucky he got a good smile on him and
everything he does he does it's all his
teeth too it's all his teeth it's all of
his teeth what come
on I say that all the time like like me
hate me like the way I look hate the way
I look I still got all my Teeth podcast
doctors don't have all their teeth
that's what I always say good to see you
guys good
do you want to get a picture together
yes thank you thank you and I have no
root canals all right oh wow so podcast
doctors have all renals all
right I'm just try I'm just trying to
I'm just talking silly here come
on thank
you thanks guys you guys going to get
some you're going to get some good food
of
than what's going on hello hi meet you
meet you too I've been to all your
events I'm so obsessed my God I'm
honored I'm honored to be here right
next to you I just doesn't even feel
real oh thanks for thanks for coming
thank you yeah thanks for saving my life
my God like many times over oh so I I'm
so sorry you even went through all that
you've gone through you know that's the
thing yeah it's okay you got me through
it oh thanks for being here to get a
picture I would love one okay we got one
here okay you
ready okay and we can get one here is
that okay here step forward a little
bit you thanks for being here you going
to get some food tonight I am so ready
you are
amazing thanks hello hey how are you
good how are you thanks for coming thank
you I'm just a little nervous but thank
you for where did you where' you come
from from Sonora really near Yus oh nice
area kind of out of Thea amazing but
you're here yes thanks for taking the
trip I wanted to ask you one question
yeah is there can is there such a thing
is too much celery juice in one day well
I mean it all depends
can I drink 3 32 o three 32 o
two how do you how do you like the well
2 32
o did you do 64 3 that's 64 then you not
going to
like okay yeah of course you can I know
it's a silly question of course you can
but you might be going the bathroom
that's what I'm trying to say oh I know
I I'm asking Spirit like uh are you
going to be are you going to be in the
grocery store and then and then having
you know a bathroom experience it
happens it happens it happens oh strain
it strain it I do if you you have to if
you strain it you should be good if you
don't strain it and you do that many
ounces you'll be going to the bathroom I
know I know here thank you thank you so
[Music]
much but but but ask your doctor what
does your doctor say about that much
I'm going to see a natural one next week
okay good good thank you so much all
right hey Anthony nice to see you again
Auto 144 oh my God oh my God no I'm not
special uh in a certain way I know sure
you're not special okay I'm so happy to
see you again good to see you I'm 5
years on it okay and was my sister in
Germany who sent me the first two books
yes yeah I didn't know about you I knew
that is what I'm supposed to do this is
how I heal I'm proud of you yes I thank
you so much keep up all the good work
you want to Adventure absolutely
absolutely amazing get some good food oh
yeah that is the
[Music]
best all right
good
Bes hi good is this this is for you this
is a wedding invitation really yeah oh
my God for who and where we're going
where did you find him come on where
where was he in a bar he's in a bar so
you know what nothing wrong with that at
all in fact that's amazing all right you
found a good one I did yeah this is also
for you it's a new polo okay yeah
okay we hope you like it yeah I do I do
thank you okay wonderful who's this this
is my mom what yeah yeah this is my mom
last time we came in October remember
you were saying that we could send we
could send light and I sent my light to
my mom and um she has hard time drinking
lemon water and celery guess what what
you're doing tell them what you're doing
you know what are you
doing I know you're a big supporter and
you know I appreciate you yeah okay
seriously I want you to know that yes
okay I know that she's a big supporter
in the community we know that and um
bless your heart okay seriously right
all right want to get a picture you
guys you got to step forward probably
this way my God I can't believe you're
getting married
oh bless your heart you guys enjoy the
food tonight okay all right it's been a
great honor okay seriously and uh bless
your heart great honor all right all
right I love you
guys hey how you doing so good to meet
you yeah I got Co last year and after Co
after weeks the skin and the GI I lost
so much weight from last year okay from
last year it triggered it was a trigger
it was a trigger it was a big trigger
for me and I got on your on your celery
juice two weeks ago okay and I feel
better it's going to take time it's
going to take one day one day at a time
so you've been doing medical meme for
like two weeks two weeks yeah yeah you
know what it's a good time to start good
okay you want to get a picture any
message from the oh my God the message
is you're just on the right track okay
you're on the right track okay okay
let's get a picture
here wa come forward here yep there you
go thank you thank you get some good
food
tonight
amazing for
back in 2015 when I wasn't feeling well
and had a lot of chronic illness and
just like everybody in this community we
come to the information desperate and uh
we're ready at that point I was ready I
cried when I heard Anthony the first
time because it was so overwhelming I
knew it was truth and it was a really
big deal but life threw us a lot of Cur
balls at you and it turned out that I
went through some really really rough
stuff in the in the course of the 9
years when I spoke to him the first time
he told me I needed some self-compassion
and I actually went home and Googled it
what is self-compassion anyway and so
that started my journey towards
self-compassion and and I'm here and I'm
here and that's that's a miracle it's a
miracle I was in a wheelchair when I
started um very legally blind still
still have a lot of vision problems but
not nearly like I did um it's healing
and brain fog depersonalization
depression just a lot of trauma in my
life and the information has just got me
out of the wheelchair got me to be able
to express myself and socialize again
and not feel alone and just healed so
much physical neurological pain in 20121
I got super sick and I dropped 40 lbs in
30 days the doctors didn't know what's
wrong with me and they just kept pushing
medication on me and I would try it and
flare and got so sick to where I wrote
like a will out for who my children
would go to when I died um I could not
cook I couldn't clean I couldn't drive I
was on mattress Island for 2 years and I
kept seeing Anthony Williams um videos
on Facebook oh my God and my cousin
actually healed colon cancer from his
protocols so I reached out to him and
he's like it's safe it's okay to try
that there's no way 3 years ago I'd be
able to fly to something like this if
you just listen listen to his words
listen to the protocols try it your body
will start to thrive and you'll see a
difference that gives you the hope to
keep
[Music]
going my health
was five
four good to see you thanks for coming I
have my skin issues since two months
because of the Sant me lot of heat and I
work with stress I drive a lot so all my
face becomes red and something I get how
what are you doing with how how long
youve been doing medical medium uh like
I've started like 2 months two months
celery you got a ways to go you take a
little bit at a time the tools are in
there yeah they're in there so you just
just a little bit you'll find them
you'll find them you're just starting
out and you start with the celery juice
and then you're moving you know you move
to the next thing right yeah yeah yeah
yeah before I didn't had now like since
Santana wins lot of heat I think in my
body like a lot of heat develops so
you always have to know that you know it
was on its way and you're doing things
now yeah to try to stop it
yeah okay want to get a picture what uh
spirit of compassion has messaged for me
just stay on track okay stand TR very
important that's what the message is
like the one I gave you was from Spirit
okay
okay right here
[Music]
thank you amazing thank you thank
you hey Anthony good to see you how you
doing yeah I'm good how are you how's
your hip oh how how how am I no how's
your hip didn't you say you had an achy
hip or was that a joke yesterday it was
a joke okay I was like oh he's got an
achy hip I you wondering huh yesterday
he said that I going to ask him about
his
hip you got me good to see you thank to
see to thank you for coming you want to
get a picture yeah also I wanted to ask
if so has any m me for me IFC has any
messages for
me you know you H you have all this
compassion for everything you have
compassion for animals that's a big
thing for you but you but you have to
have compassion for yourself too because
you beat yourself up but do you have all
this compassion and you know there
there's something to respect with that
yes but you have to still have be more
compassion for yourself okay thank you
yeah sorry is it here or here what's
what is your favorite animal probably
dogs thank you for coming get some good
food thank
you how are you good to see you thank
you for coming yeah thank you so much
I've been applying your information for
9 years and I've been uh free from
ovarian cancer for8 years now thanks to
you and I help other people do the same
oh my God I'm so proud of you you
changed my life um my family my friends
my clients of course the community um
you know we have your I'm trying my best
but you know what the best people in the
world are in this community and they're
Fighters and they work hard and they
care and I mean I I'm just so lucky so
lucky we feel the same you want to get a
pict together thank you yes of course
here step forward here oh here
thank you for coming get some good food
tonight I'm proud of you seriously it's
mindblowing can I ask does Spirit have
anything or you have to share with
me what what what's your favorite
hobby because you've like lost touch of
something from a long time ago I I think
I've been working so much and helping so
many clients that there's something from
years ago though think about SK okay
okay and that might be it but think
about what you did a long time ago
reconnect thank you thank
you hey hi good to see you how are you
thank you so much for everything I owe
it all to you and spirit of compassion
thanks for coming I'm a medical medium
type 1 diabetic wow and I yes and I hold
a diabetes support group so on behalf of
the medical medium diabetic my God
you're you're out there speaking good
words
there're speaking good words about
medical me in the diabetes world yes of
course I so I was wondering if there's
anything you can tell us um for type 1
diabetics based on whether it's
reversible or not well you know and I I
I think I've said this in the books and
stuff like the pancreas gets injured by
all these other things so you know think
about that because the information's
there it's not just about food it's
about what caused the pancreas
injury right like remember the pathogens
and things like that so what do you do
when it's pathogens and stuff like that
you do little things to go after
pathogens you know so there's there's
information there so I feel like stress
and adrenaline is one of the main things
that injured my pancreas and but it's
ongoing it's something I constantly am
struggling with and it's like one of
those things it's not it's not just like
straight forward it's a vicious cycle
but that's one right that's that's it's
not the the it's not the but it's one
okay there's lots of things that add to
it okay and that's one of them but
you're doing things to protect you with
your adrenaline too remember that yeah
let's get a picture okay thank you so
much thank you for coming tonight so
much Anthony thanks so
much you got a book for me would you
please sign thank you so
much you may I give you a hug sure of
course of course thank you so much
Anthony thank you for coming thank you
I've been hooked ever since 2016 when I
did my first 28 day cleanse and so um
the 28 day cleanse I did the 28 day
cleanse and so yes I've um just had a
lot of healing and also spiritual growth
and my creativity has changed so oh my
God that's amazing I'm so proud of you
that's a long time on medical medium I'm
proud I'm proud it's been like back and
forth but now I've going through a next
wave of uh just being stronger about it
what's your favorite medical meem book
um I would say brains saer is the one
mhm I love that book yeah it's amazing
it is isn't it it is it is I'm doing the
shots right now I did the truth
stabilizer today and so yeah yeah I
haven't had a chance to talk about that
book that much oh it's it's so sad it's
like I haven't even spoken about it and
it's the best best book it's just yeah
it's amazing thank you so much want to
step forward yes please thank you for
all your hard work thank you oh
yes thanks for coming have a great night
get some good food I will thank
you you guys together yes this is my
daughter can I have a hun of course yes
this is your daughter hi Summer nice to
meet summer nice to meet you thanks for
coming you guys where did you come from
oh we live 10 minutes away we at the C
city after you get stuffed you can just
stuffed on food and you're like okay you
just go right home y so I just want to
thank turn on a movie relax you know
you're amazing I called you a rockstar
once and you said rock stars have it
easy but I think you know what I mean
you're rockars have it easy I don't care
what anybody says they have it easy this
hoopla like a big the biggest rockar
this this deal is like
you're too kind okay do you guys want to
get a picture
yes you want to move forward a little
bit sure right
mik yeah
right thank you guys are you going to
get good food much much love thank you
for
coming and that's my sister she that's
your
sister oh no oh my God what's your
favorite medical medium book uh cleans
to heel cleans to heel yes it's a hard
one to beat so fortunate that this is
the fourth time I've got to see you oh W
your heart let's get a picture yeah look
Ready Step up
here oh have a good night tonight I know
I know I have a sluggish liver but is
there anything that you can tell me that
I should do other than like the you know
the usual like celery juice and uh are
you doing the meditations no I'll get on
did you do the Liver Rescue meditations
um I I've done rescue but I have to the
369 I've done the 28 cleanse but yes
I'll do the meditations the meditations
and Li rescue okay thank
you hey how are you good to meet you too
thank you for coming thank you for
everything you've done for us a bless
your heart do you want to get a picture
yes want to step forward here yes
are you g to get some good food tonight
bless your
heart feel like I'm coming to see Santa
sit on your
lap your skin looks great hey thanks I
appreciate it you got a good beard thank
you I uh got a good beard I work with
the police officers and Military mental
health and I try to I got a lot of
respect for police officer
yeah I have police in my family and oh
yeah y y it's just it's a big deal ah
yeah yeah well I try to uh you know they
have a lot of vinaa fatigue as you
imagine I try to put your off of your
stuff to them as much as possible and uh
it's a lot of success and I'm thrilled
to have found you years ago and I did I
didn't have a help problem but I was
helping other people and thank you can
can I say thank you for spreading the
message yeah thanks thank you and
helping out such good people out there
thanks proud you okay thank you thank
you that's great to hear let's get a
picture all
right you going to get some good food
tonight yeah I'm excited thank you so
much anth look at you huh Mary nice to
see you nice to see you thanks for
coming oh my god of course I want to
tell you how much you've helped not only
me but so many friends and family oh God
bless you bless you no bless you like
amazing just the little things you know
like celery juice every day or something
it's it's a blessing it just is well I'm
just glad look I'm glad I can help in
any way okay for your family and people
you know that means the world thank do
you want to get a picture I do but I
also want to ask you uh anything you can
tell me about my
throat any well spirit says it's uh
nerve related did the doctor say that no
I'm not talking to a doctor so just was
hoping you could give me a clue to guide
me where to go there's got to be
somebody out there that can understand
you know keep on looking are you still
looking no I'm fearful well it doesn't
mean you need to do anything you don't
want to do keep that in mind okay but
yeah no it's it's it's nerve nerve is
what spirit says but all right thank you
but you there's got to be somebody out
there okay
thank you and
then and then you got the the medical
medium information yes that's that's
what you're working on just take one of
the Books open it up go to Medical
medium book one okay the new edition
okay okay open that up start looking
through there there's stuff in there for
this okay 9 years uh before you had the
books that's when I started start
introducing can I tell you I'm honored
that you're here and I I warms my heart
to know you've been doing this this long
okay bless your heart thank you for
coming out here okay oh yeah absolutely
and I'm proud of you thank you thank
you Hi how are you sir can me give you a
hug oh give me a hug yeah how you guys
doing good good to see you look at this
guy good to see you again haven't seen
you since the book I know I know this is
amazing thanks for coming you guys so
happy to be here thanks
forette of course of course I think she
just has one one question how long have
you guys been together 5 years 5 years
yeah 5 years coming up on six yeah and
you haven't booted them out yet huh not
yet okay did your turn oh yeah
sorry you ask you a question um I wanted
to know if you were ever planning on
releasing the book series in
Arabic yeah oh I would love to do that
of course yeah I mean you know I'm I'm
hoping that happens I wouldn't doubt it
if it doesn't okay okay I wouldn't doubt
it come on up here you want to take a
picture yeah I do ready stand up a
little little
further awesome awesome thank you you
guys a question about one
um seeing it often I know you talked
about significance with like it being
God energy it is definitely it is it's a
great number it's a number to focus you
know how everybody focuses on 11 yeah 11
11 focus on 144 thank
you okay
uh you want to here hold on
okay let's head into back we work on
that sorry I don't want to drop my pants
over here
okay I uh had a condition of uh kind of
heavy brain fog for about a decade and I
saw doctors alternative doctors uh tried
weird things nothing was working and
then I found the medical medium
information and started celery juice and
within about 3 weeks I started feeling a
difference and within 3 months like 95%
gone after that I was sold and um I've
Incorporated everything into my
lifestyle since then I end up getting
sick basically something he calls the
lme disease trap which lime disease is a
trap it was supposed to be antibiotics
bacteria which it's not it's heavy
metals and vir is I traveled the world
China Germany seen tons of doctors the
same story of spending money and I read
his book on the Lim trap and it was the
complete opposite of the Matrix that we
all told and you know I guess
brainwashed with and I was like wow I
learned the exact opposite of what it is
up down left right black
white and it just blew my mind and I had
a lot of Dreams after reading that
chapter and then you know you cry then
you dive into the material and you start
healing and then put as much work in as
you can to get better the first thing
that healed was my gums regenerated I
had gum recession my gums grew back in
my teeth REM mineralized I was starting
to lose my hearing and I was starting to
have trouble with sight and so my
hearing came back I used to have to
watch TV with you know subtitles and I
would always ask people what did you say
what did you say so that's amazing to
have your your senses regenerate so
profound
amazing you got a
picture oh my God you must be so happy
yeah she's
two the best new ever you want to get a
picture of together so you don't tell
your wife I said hi yeah she's watching
now right yeah 10 years we're going on
10 years doing mm protocols that's
amazing that's a long time I'm proud of
both of you okay it's it it is it's uh
it's even more than that it's
um it just becomes part of the soul and
Consciousness it's so it's so incredible
doing yeah I'm proud of you guys you
know that right let's get a
picture looking forward to the uh
angel I am too I'm nervous though but
I'm be good hello hello we're back hi
back good to see love the food how you
doing food's good food's great I don't
know not yet we haven't had it you got
the kids yeah we what's going
on that is really cool that shirt what's
happening how you doing you're doing
good yes thank you you guys you guys uh
you guys uh you staying in town where
are you no we live in you live right
there 30 minutes yeah that's it you just
got to do you ever come here and try the
medical mem food oh yeah we do all right
we make the journey for it all right
thank you thank you it's it's it's it's
worth the journey thank you man thank
you you guys want to get a picture sure
sure how do we do this do you want to go
the middle now we're going to get Jay in
here what's your favorite band favorite
band yeah got Oh
Come tricky you know I like Van Morrison
I mean I oh my God it's really tricky I
like Zeppelin am I in are we all
here little more I like Black Sabbath I
like Leed zein I like Van Morrison what
else do I like I like golden oldies
golden oh there you
go all right can you I like a lot of
stuff they're joh oats I mean I could go
on and on and on I know right we know
you play music all right thank I love
music all right you guys amazing good to
see you thank you for coming you guys
good how you doing
hey hey good to see you good to see you
good to see you hey look at you huh hey
look at you know look look at lady right
here I know I to you guys are amazing
you guys want to get a picture together
yeah all right all right you ready
uh-huh amazing
proud of you guys I wanted to can I ask
a question shoot shoot so so my parents
passed away and I was wondering if I
could share the blast the light blast
with them like can you share let's try
it let's just try it okay Spirit yeah
yeah let's try it tonight why not why
not I I mean God works in mysterious
ways it's just thanks a lot thank
you hello hey how are you I'm Stephanie
nice to meet you thanks for having me
for coming thanks um I had a question
yes um first trimester of pregnancy I
have so many patients that are
incredibly nauseous the minute B for
second trimester they feel better you're
are you a a practitioner uh naturop pics
doctor really oh my God I'm proud of you
that's amazing how long you been oh
really wa it's hard work it's fun what
what school um National University in
outside of Chicago oh my God it's
amazing I'm really proud of you so you
with the nausey in the first trimester
is that what you're saying but why does
it always usually resolve in the second
trimester because the because the organs
have been pushed up enough interesting
the first trimester the organs are all
getting pushed and and in because it's
like it just starts to happen like that
it it it creates it nausea okay by
second trimester the organs are pretty
much they're moved enough where the
where the vagus nerves aren't being hit
got it anymore but at the beginning of
the first trimester the Vegas nerves are
being hit and it's starting to St
but but yeah if that makes any
sense let's get a
picture well thank you for all the work
you're doing okay for it's an honor to
meet
you what's going on okay there I yeah I
know you oh my God I feel like I can't I
don't even know what to ask you thank
you for coming okay you want to get a
picture let's get a picture come on
let's go yeah you like the food I love
the
food of course of course thank you for
everything amazing thank youth thank you
being oh you're the best
hello hi thank you can I give you a hug
yeah yes yes are you the last one in
line I'm that happens every event where
I would be so late from neuro fatigue
and then I get here right before it's
cut off so I'm blessed thank you so much
for these collaborations and I do the
hand things I did that last time and um
I use I do my hands too when I'm talking
it's really weird and fake but uh thank
you for the collaborations and thank you
for the Angels and Demons chapter it's
really
relevant oh I hope you like it I'm
excited I I have one question I want to
cut you off sorry goad I think some
people are going to be like wait a
minute that's not that can't be how it
works or wait a minute I'm just we'll
see you got a question sounds like me
yeah um but we'll see we'll see I'm
excited my question is um given this
violent spiritual experience I've had
with my life the sabotage the hijacking
of everything does s so have any
information for me there's a lot of
tools that are coming that you're going
to see and you're going to be able to
use and it's just going to line up line
up I love that yeah you you'll see
there's some serious tools okay right
thank want to get a picture yeah step
forward here
oh there we
go thank you for coming get some good
food hey you want to get a picture come
on let's get a picture here St
forward what you think about the food
last night um um yeah it is good it yeah
I like the pizza I like you like it okay
that's good it's very different than the
Italian one but I like it are you going
to have it again tonight mhm good and um
and and and why do we need wisdom te
when we don't need them for chewing why
do we have
them I I'm going to do I I don't think
I've talked about wisdom teeth I think
I'm going to do something and I'm going
to talk about before so soon enough
before I need to take I'm going to do I
think I'll do a podcast and I'll or I'll
do a live and I'll talk about wisdom te
I don't think I've ever talked about
yeah that would be great because I need
to make a decision it
it's okay I'll talk about them okay
thank you thank you all right you get
some good food and I'm proud of you
right this whole journey for me started
from my daugh being very very sick we
did all the regular stuff like went to
the doctor they said it was all in her
head tried different things nothing
really seemed to help but then as I
started discovering more medical medium
information and applying more of it it
started to help and then she hit a point
where she had like a trigger and it got
way worse as a mom like all you want is
your kids to be healthy and your family
to thrive and when you see your your
people suffering and you don't know how
to help them and the doctors don't know
how to help them it's just honestly one
of the worst feelings
possible we reached out to a
practitioner and worked with her and
over the course of almost 2 years she
went from being bed bound to now getting
back into her life so just beyond
[Music]
grateful this man has changed my life
Anthony William now I'm reading the
books I know that I was sick for a long
time since I was a baby my whole
childhood basically there was always
something wrong I'm the one with the
allergies I'm the one that had to be
going to the doctor all the time I'm the
one with the acne I was on like
medications that really messed me up and
I never knew why I was always the sick
one right and then I had my babies and
then boom like my whole world crashed
down because I got lupus it's been
something that I've been fighting and
looking for and I'm a biologist I study
biology I have a master's degree in
biology I was in biotech I couldn't find
the
answers and then when I found well my
friend told me about him and he said you
will love his book Because You Love
angels and I had been praying I've
always prayed to God I've always asked
his angels to help me finally when I got
the book and I read that one chapter on
the Angels I'm like this is the
information I was waiting for not the
science part not the explanation as soon
as I read that I
knew the meet and greet with aw just
finished and we hope that you're having
a fabulous time tuning into the live
stream at home we're going to take you
inside Cafe Gratitude right now
to enjoy some delicious food it is night
two of the medical medium pizza party
the energy in here is just
incredible e
[Applause]
same
e e
[Music]
[Applause]
if
watch
you e
second
[Applause]
it
than
[Music]
e e
[Applause]
you
yeah
[Applause]
e e
[Music]
that
[Applause]
think
spe
know
[Music]
[Applause]
Theon you
guys
food I see the Green Papaya kelp noodles
right there I mean that's an amazing
dish it really is it's so light and so
good for you you guys like it is it okay
you guys staying warm back here or what
I feel the heat right there whoa that's
that's a hot lamp right there what's
going on you guys you having fun back
here all right all right you're nice and
warm for sure I feel it this is amazing
all right good good good this is an
incredible restaurant by far oops sorry
about that it's an amazing restaurant
honestly I can't believe we're here
another night we're really blessed we're
really lucky um let's go back in here a
little bit
bit all right you guys you guys are
eating up are you get are
you are you get are you getting too
stuffed you guys getting too
full right come
on I I wouldn't be able to stop eating
all right I'd be eating all of this I'd
be like come on Bring it on Bring It On
how's it how's the food okay food's all
right okay all right the plates empty
right there
what's going on that's good that's good
all right good good everybody how's
everybody feeling
tonight right feeling good you guys okay
all right amazing some of you guys
traveled far away Germany all right
Austria all over the
place unbelievable it blows my mind to
think you guys have made it here that
far right that long of a journey
Christian what's up you guys it's so
great to see you guys seriously it's
amazing the medical medium Community is
mindblowing come on it just is there's
nothing like it out there I mean come on
think about the other communities oh
wait there are none really it's just one
big it's just one big pile of whatever
out there everybody clicks and likes and
then whatever and they're doing this and
doing that this is a real Community a
real one with the real Soul come on
right
think about it I know cuz every now and
then be like oh the other community is
like really come on no way nothing like
here it doesn't exist and there's a
reason for that people who are on
mattress Island know that people who
were sick for a long time know that
there's a reason I'm proud of all you
guys proud you guys got no idea how much
so every night I go to bed I send
prayers out all your way I know how hard
you guys worked and guess what though
we're partying tonight there's the
difference we're
partying I mean
right I mean come on come on did the
pizzas come out yet not yet oh they're
going to they're going to be amazing
wait to you guys taste them come on
anyway I'm excited to be here I'm
honored to be here I'm going to talk a
little later right we're going to do a
light blast God
willing yep yep yep yep yep we're good
we're gonna all right I don't have Dr
nesbet with me right now but a cousin of
Dr nesbet is kicking around somewhere
who is it there we go right there
exactly unbeliev if Dr nesbet is
watching tonight I'm telling you we'll
see we'll see you never know I don't
know he might be he might be sober
enough to see this tonight you guys
proud of all you guys proud of all you
guys out there seriously okay enjoy
enjoy eat mja a come on just e I'm
Italian you guys know that um all right
I'll catch you guys later right all
right
[Applause]
[Music]
three
e
[Applause]
for
e
[Applause]
for
[Music]
e for
tell
e e
[Music]
than
Pur
for
e
e e
[Music]
we're inside here at Cafe Gratitude
medical medium pizza party night two is
off to such an amazing start we're going
to join some guests here what's your
name Jennifer Jennifer and Gwen nice to
meet you Mary so lovely to meet you I
thought we were going to talk about all
the different meals but you've already
eaten most of the
food it's delicious it's it's delicious
you went through it very fast and look
at these pizzas you got one slice here
left what has the food been like
tonight amazing I wish I could replicate
it I'm going to I'm going to try
what has been your favorite bite of the
night this this one and it's different
this one tastes different than the
broccoli okay so for people watching at
home this one here that is the one's
gone but this one's
different in what
ways it's more intense maybe basil spicy
I'm not sure it's it's it's more
intense dried tomatoes so more flavor
yeah that one's really good yeah that
was my favorite
yeah what was your favorite of the night
well I haven't tasted that one yet so I
don't know that's your slice that's got
your name on it you're going to have
that one oh wait I lied I like the sushi
too I'm I died a little it it's like
better than any sushi I've ever had yeah
it's pretty incredible it's like a
little work of art the sushi too oh yeah
it was so
good and you're still with the pizza oh
yeah my favorite was definitely the
pizza and up next you have some
incredible cookies I just got a sneak
peek of the cookies the gingerbread
cookie brought me back to my childhood I
feel it was just it's so very homey and
that and then the tahini cookie I would
order a box of those cookies that's how
good it is I could eat a whole box I'm
excited yes yeah and then we have time
tea coming up as well I'm excited for
that
too how does it feel to be sitting here
in a restaurant that fully supports your
healing Journey it's weird it's wild to
go somewhere and be able to and I said
that after I ate the pizza I said I feel
like something bad's going to happen to
me now like I'm going to get sick
nothing bad's going to happen to you cuz
I haven't had pizza in like 10 years
yeah yeah feels very indulgent to be
having at a pizza potty right it was
amazing The
Amazing how's it feel for you it's great
I haven't had to ask the waiter does it
have canola oil does it have cheese on
it or whatever I'm just like I can eat
whatever is being served to me I love it
do you think having these uh items on
the menu uh a Cafe Gratitude will help
people's healing journey to be a bit
easier and more enjoyable absolutely
because I live in LA and I order it from
Cafe Gratitude and it's a wonderful
treat you know to receive it at home and
I don't have to worry like they said
it's just fantastic so you feel like a
night off in the kitchen you can order
some pizza delivered to your home that's
supports your medical medium healing
Journey so cool now they just need to
find a way to freeze it and ship it all
around the
world that's what they need to deal
that's true that's true well thank you
so much for talking to us for sharing uh
your table with me for a moment and
everyone for tuning in you know they got
to a glimpse at uh the food at your
table tonight so thank you so much
you're welcome thank you we're going to
head to our next table and see what
their dining experiences like
hello oh you're up to the tea already
scoot over for you you can scoot over
that would be lovely and then I can join
your table for a
moment now I would ask you to show us
these beautiful dishes but you've eaten
them all the food was that good it's
already gone guys empty dishes isn't
that the best compliment you can give a
chef it is so delicious yeah I she had
to give hers away because she got too
full did someone else ate it
yeah so favorite dish that you would
like to give a shout out to and give
some love to tonight um mine was that
pizza the pesto Pizza the is that the
pinco yes the Pesco oh my gosh delicious
it was divine Mediterranean pinco can we
for everyone watching at home could you
go through some of the toppings that
were on that pizza okay now I have my
glass on my age is
showing okay cherry tomato sundried
tomato chickpeas uh chickpea cheese
Capers basil pesto calamada oliv
um preserved lemon arugula and herbal
hemp hemp seeds yeah and also the
vegetable Sushi was oh my God the crunch
yeah mhm MH let's go around the table
I'd love to know what your favorite
dishes were for the
evening
salad I love the salad the papaya
yes and what were your favorite bites of
the night I loved the salad it was like
my favorite I don't know something
magical about this yes I also like the
cookie I was here yesterday so I know
what the cookie is like but it's coming
it's coming well I just tried the cookie
the gingerbread cookie is amazing the
tahini cookie they're both there oh yeah
that's what I was eating over there did
you see me I was I was having a lot of
fun I saw you eating yeah uh there's no
cookies left on the plate yeah okay yeah
cookie to me tastes like Girl Scouts
peanut butter sandwich cookie
which I cannot eat but this was just the
blast and now you can have something
delicious The Taste may be a little bit
indulgent you know but it's still
healthy and healing
right yes exactly that's what I thought
what was the time tea
like very good very good but we also
have this one which is I'm cozy it's a
ginger lemon and cayenne pepper which
was very good
we we all had it and we loved it
beautiful what was your favorite uh dish
this evening Pizza hands down it was
amazing it was like the one with the
pesto yeah this is uh it was salad as
well but uh this pizza had more flavor
more complex
flavor um yeah so that pizza I tried it
to do too today in the Mediterranean
Pesca oh so good yes yes and then I
liked the uh edge of the crust as well I
found it was like nice and crispy and
just oh had nice like that texture to it
yeah it was yummy very yummy okay we're
going to check out the next table thank
you so much for talking to us enjoy the
rest of your night thank you so much
okay hello everyone hello lovely to see
you everyone may I join your uh your
pizza party for a moment
yes okay so if we could have a look at
what you're eating here
you're mid you're mid bite but we'll
have a look at what you're eating there
if you could explain the food that you
have in front of you so this is see one
second I have to watch of course this is
the the uh the potato chicken pizza I am
healthy and I think this is
the uh one of both some one of the piz
say it is the veggie medley it's and
it's really really tasty and this this
one too yeah what would you give a shout
out to tonight that was your favorite
bite so my my favorite bite so so far
was for sure the pizza like like this
kind of where the where the where the
where the chickpea cheese is on yeah
this is a really really good treat a
nice treat uh I agree I think the pizza
is a nice treat cuz it's something we
don't get very often and it's not
anything that I can make myself without
a lot of
effort so I I've enjoyed it yes it's all
been good though I think the sushi was
really good the salad was phenomenal so
it's really hard to say what's good
what's the best yes the whole evening
has just been amazing amazing yeah
exactly lots of flavors what was yes
what was your favorite dish this evening
well all of them are delicious it's hard
to pick but I really like the sushi a
lot it was good it was really good me
too I like the sushi the most I like the
mediterranian pizza
too that the cookies are delicious
what I've heard uh they are delicious I
can't confirm the rumor uh I would order
a box if I could that's how good they
are I I like both of them the ginger uh
and also the tahini uh another lady was
saying it was like a a Girl Scout cookie
peanut butter Girl Scout cookie the
tahini uh just they they're full of
flavor they taste like they would be bad
for you but they're healing and it's
amazing what did you think of the
cookies last night so the cookies are I
dreamed about the cookies and how how to
put the cookies in the in the tea like
so a little bit that was like a time tea
to put it a little bit in and then ah to
get like this flavor in your mouth is
can we okay we we have we have to need
some uh some some really amazing cookies
yeah well I'm going to have to order
more cookies and some time tea and dunk
them in the time tea I think this
table's about to have a tea party as
well as the as the pizza party you know
thank you so much for talking to us
we're going to go to one more
table hello
hello you know what I'm asking everyone
to show us their delicious food but
here's the problem it's so delicious
there's none left on your Plage where
did it go where did it go only a tiny
bit
left and I was just saying I think this
is the biggest compliment to the chef is
having a Clean Plate would you mind if I
sit down next to
you thank you thank you for letting me
join your table oh thank you I'm good
loveely to see you yes yes so good to
see all of you how are you enjoying the
evening so far how is the pizza party oh
it has been absolutely amazing and these
three young people here are just
incredible and we're learning so much
from each other and it's so great to be
involved with other medical median
people did you just all meet at the
table yes we did you going to be
lifelong friends now absolutely they've
all been invited to my home and you can
come too thank you I'm invited as well
amazing yes thank you we'll continue the
pizza party yes absolutely yes well I've
got to ask you about the food what were
some of your highlights for the food
this evening and I'd love to go around
the table and get everyone's reactions
so we'll start here well I love the
sushi and I was so glad to see that
they're using pumpkin tofu because
people think of it as tofu it really is
not it's made out of pumpkin seed and I
was thrilled to see them using that as a
delicacy yes yeah I love the
Mediterranean pizza it was so good I
love camada olives and pesto so it was
so delicious yeah I loved that
yeah I love both pizzas so much um I
wish that I could share it with my
family back on the East Coast um they
were just absolutely delicious and uh I
wish I could have this every day and I
wish I could have
more I'm always a fan of the sushi um
I'm local so I come to Cafe Gratitude a
lot and I think I ordered the sushi
maybe like 30 times since it came out
yeah great that you're local do you
think that having these items on the
menu will help your healing journey and
be help it to be more enjoyable and a
bit easier as well definitely because
prior to this it's not like I was ever
able to order a takeout or anything um
so this is a really great option to have
for me to feel like I'm like partaking
in normal life while still on the
healing journey and now they have the
cleanse option that's available to order
as well I think that's great because it
makes it a little less daunting for some
people as well and it saves a lot of
time in the kitchen it's just very
convenient right definitely yeah I think
it's amazing yeah well you know what's
coming up next are these delicious
mouthwatering cookies oh I think we're
getting something else before the
cookies you're getting something else
before the cookies yes uh maybe the
potato burrito yeah the burrito we
haven't gotten that I am Noble oh so you
got that to go and the cookies and the
tea and the tea you have so much more
food to enjoy all of it is just
delicious how does it feel to be in this
environment with others that understand
your healing journey and then to eat
food that fully supports your healing
Journey as well well the energy is
unbelievable if I drank coffee I would
feel like I've had two or three pots oh
wow wow
yeah it's so wonderful to meet and talk
to other people who just get it they
just know what you've been through or
they understand a little bit of your
journey cuz they've been on a journey
too so it's just a really warm loving
environment with delicious food so it's
been wonderful yeah um yes it's just
been amazing positive energy tonight and
uh we all feel like we were meant to
meet each other and uh we've had
beautiful
conversations and um yeah we're I'm I'm
very grateful um that we have this
community yeah I love coming to these
events because I feel like I always end
up at a table with like complete
strangers and yet it feels like I've
like known them for a really long time
and it all feels very like faded yeah
medical medium family right yeah
exactly well we're going to finish up
here in the dining room up next I'm
going to have an interview with aw aw is
coming back as well you guys are going
to have a lecture tonight A Life block
fast and these cookies so much more to
go the night is just you know we're just
beginning the pizza party we've got a
lot more to go here so grateful for you
also doing this it's and you have such a
lovely accent oh thank you so much
should we say bye for now to everyone uh
bye for now from here in the dining room
but don't go anywhere cuz we've got that
interview with aw the light blast the
leure so much more and the energy in
here is incredible right it's electric
that was so much fun thank you thank you
you
[Applause]
e e
think
[Applause]
will
[Music]
oh yeah
it's probably about5
[Applause]
[Music]
mil
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
I
[Applause]
for
e
[Applause]
e e
[Music]
ask
hey guys to back here with aw we are
having such BL we're live right yes
that's the way that's the way I like to
do it yeah and it's incredible we're
just going with the flow here look last
night you spoke about your original
audio Angels demons and spiritual tools
can you tell us more about it you know
um you hear people all the time and I
said this last night people say you know
they talk about demons they say
something about demons or that person's
a demon or whatever it is you know it's
been in the verb for centuries it's been
in the verb of you know civilization
here right but yet no you know it's
really just nonsense it's just for the
movies it's just you know what I mean
it's just make believe but the
information that came down might have
you thinking a little different when you
hear about it when you hear about like
where the word demon really came from
what was the word before it how did it
start that's one thing on its own I mean
that piece of information is just to tip
the iceberg
look look I'm nervous even talking about
this audio this original audio because
the information is so mindblowing that
you know I'm probably going to take some
hits for you know there's going to be
probably some hate because you know
people like they want a good reason to
hate out there you know do there's a lot
of people that want a reason to hate and
there and there's and there's a lot of
people that don't want that obviously
but this information is controversial
controversial
that that's the difference but but
spiritually
controversial and it challenges belief
systems it challenges
religions and the one thing
about the one thing about angels demons
and spiritual tools the one thing about
this interesting is that I've
Incorporated information for my
spiritual belief system in there so it
doesn't matter what it doesn't matter
what belief system what religion what
you subscribe to what you believe in
what your faith is you can use this
information that's what's incredible
it's like medical medium information in
general for health right you can be
somebody that eats animal protein you
can be somebody that's vegan or
plant-based and still use the tools to
heal and still stay on your side of the
aisle whatever that is this
information Angels demons and spiritual
tools is similar it's information you
could bring into what your faith is what
you believe in and I've I've taken the
information I'm bringing it into what I
believe in what my spiritual you know
faith is my religious Faith whatever
that is and so I'm bringing that in
that's that's that's what's wonderful
you know wow and I can't wait that's
March 18 right March 18th I I and I just
want to prepare people little disclaimer
M it's it's intense information really
intense you got to be ready for it got
to be sitting down definitely talk about
after death I talk about the Grim reap
if there is a grim reaper I talk about
angels of course I talk about fallen
angels falling angels I talk about
ghosts I talk about tortured Souls evil
Souls I talk about people here than
people when they leave when they die
it's it's stuff that is really
challenging it challenges what people
believe but it's from s so and it's time
yeah I'm I'm ready I I can't wait for
this now what I've noticed over the last
couple of nights is a lot of people are
telling me medical medium information
gave them their life back so what is it
like to see so many people get their
lives back it's the greatest feeling in
the world I mean that's that's why I you
know do what I do obviously and it's
it's more than that I live and breathe
it you know Anthony go take a vacation
you know Aw take some time off you know
you should be focused on yourself you
should be focused on your self-care
that's what you should be doing you
should be taking you know baths with
salt and different you should be putting
you know you should be doing this and
that an exercise you should be in the
gym two hours a day like the influencers
that'll teach everybody you get in the
gym for two hours a day you know and
it's like uh okay let me go do that and
then drop the ball let me go do that and
just focus on myself and myself only and
drop the ball for the chronically ill
you know it takes self-sacrifice it
takes sacrifice on my part it it has all
these years it's just the way it is but
you know it's worth you see people here
they got their lives back and people get
out of wheelchairs people who actually
are living their lives now and they were
on mattress Island suffering it means
everything to me to see people heal like
this and this community like I said
before the most people healed around the
world hate me love me like the way I
dress hate the way I dress like the way
I look don't like my voice whatever it
is you know what I mean um more people
healed than anywhere in the world so
whether you like it or not that's just a
fact and that's how incredible this
community is and I I and I stand behind
them stand with them yeah it's such an
incredible community so much gratitude
for you so much gratitude for S so and
the medical medium information now
medical medium information has been
leading the way for over a decade why is
that the health movement is has been
changed because of medical medium
information all the way down to science
to fake science to real science to you
know um to the podcast world and health
they use medical medium information they
don't cite it they take medical medium
information every day I mean you see it
out there everywhere psoriasis is caused
by Metals really there's no science that
determines that it doesn't exist
anywhere it's been published in medical
medium books the sad part about that
there there's a positive about it in a
way and that positive is the has changed
the shape of Health right like fruit
fear everybody was afraid of fruit I
don't care what anybody says 10 years
ago everybody was fruits the devil it's
sugar it's bad for you you can't heal
when you're doing sugar that's what
everybody said everybody did and if you
don't know that you're just green and
you just started you're just young or
didn't know but it was like that medical
medium fought the battles already we
fought the wars and so that people are
eating fruit so much so carnivore diet
has fruit in it now keto has fruit in it
all the time like fruits in everything
now because of the work we did whether
anybody likes it or not it was the work
we did and it was it was a battle and we
did that and it's it's changed the world
but that's just one one thing like look
at collagen it was like you got to eat
collagen and that's how you build up
your collagen medical medium information
was like no you need the building blocks
to build collagen and now look you hear
it on you know there's podcasts out
there and podcast doctors people always
tell me like you wouldn't believe what
this person's saying they're they took
your info it's leading the way it has it
still is it just it just is you know and
that's what's incredible about it
because Spirit compassion is leading the
way with this and people they don't have
to believe in spirit they don't have to
have a spiritual belief they don't have
to think I hear a voice or not since age
four I have they just need to do the
information and heal and move forward
you know and that's okay with me but the
the you know the sad part is is that the
health movement has changed it is
completely the Whole Health movement has
altered because of medical medum
information it's gotten into every
aspect of of um the health world the sad
part is that's the good part the sad
part is people can't find their way to
the rest of the information they hear
tidbits here tidbits there you know bioh
hacks and biohackers are using it you
know what I mean but they're not they're
not getting the rest of it because
people aren't citing it back enough to
say oh that came from here now you can
heal your psoriasis that came from here
you can heal your multiple sceris you
can heal your chronic fatigue syndrome
you just need the rest of it it's not
just this or this you can do all of it
and that's a sad heart that um there's
enough people with Integrity out there
to say oh crap I stole that information
to try to get some more clicks and and
likes and more you know views but I
don't want to say where I got it from
and then you you got to think about
somebody who's chronically sick yeah how
can you have like how can you be that
way and not just be like look to be
honest this guy here he wrote all these
books it's changed all these lives
that's where you can find the rest of it
yeah but people don't have that
Integrity anymore maybe somebody does
but not a lot when it comes down to the
doggy dog world of Health it's it's
pretty sad well talking about people who
are sick if anyone's watching out there
tonight who is sick what would you like
to say to them look there is a way you
can heal it's possible there is a way to
heal I want people to know that it it it
is real if you're on mattress Island
maybe you're on mattress Island for an
hour a day 2 hours a day you could be on
on mattress Island for 20 hours a day
there is a way to heal and get better
and why wait until you actually get too
sick too if you got symptoms and
conditions think about getting into this
information take it to your doctor
whatever makes you comfortable and and
learn because you don't want to go
downhill and downhill cuz a lot of
people a lot of influencers and people
who are just sick they play with things
while they're sick they manage it do you
want to keep on managing your illness or
do you want to like heal finally and
that's what people do they manage and
they're just managing it managing it
managing it and then all of a sudden one
too many things hits Death By A Thousand
Cuts the scale tips and they're going
down and now they're like oh [__] I'm
sick now I am sick God what do I do what
do I do where do I go you know why let
it get to that point if you're somebody
you got symptoms and conditions learn
the medical medium information tell a
friend about it so they learn so they
can heal you
know and just and keep in mind that
information is there you know yeah you
can hail so I want to talk to you as
well what is the difference between
biohacking and medical maum because you
mentioned biohacking that's just musical
chairs you know biohacking is musical
chairs everybody wants a Magic Bullet
they wanted you know they want this
Magic Bullet and this one fish oil it
used to be fish oil medical medium
blasted that so bad that it was bad for
you that that's gone now very very few
people take fish oil supplements like
they used to because of mm info it's
like the biohacks oh maybe it's fish oil
maybe it's collagen maybe it's charcoal
maybe it's ionizer water which is
terrible for you maybe it's this maybe
it's that and that's how maybe it's
Pearl powder maybe it's this it's just
it's endless out there biohacking this
biohacking that you know put electrodes
on your brain and run on the treadmill
you know why some you know like some
neuroscientists is like oh wait a minute
there's a little more heat on this side
there's a little more heat on that side
you got the answers you know here's
longevity here's this it's just constant
biohacking crap but when you're sick
with chronic illness all that's
worthless it's musical chairs around and
around we go and then you lose time and
so the thing is the medical M Community
they know about this they're seasoned
they tried everything for 10 years 15 20
years they fought their way back and now
they're here they found something that
works and then they see they got eyes to
see now they're wise they look out and
they see all the bull and they see all
the tricks and they see all the gimmicks
and the ads and the advertisers and all
of that it's all just a game and they
feed off of the chronically ill that's
the point too you know they feed off the
chronically ill so it's it's scary and
medical medum communities is is has
Integrity it's people who care have
compassion and they've learned they've
learned what it's like out there they
know about the biohacking crap and and
they want the truth they want the truth
maybe I don't deliver it the best maybe
I'm not the best speaker maybe I'm not
the best at like getting the message out
I try my best Spirit of compassion
talked to me since age four you know and
I'm doing the best thing I can I see
people on social out there I hear about
them they got their act down they got
their stuff down and all that it's kind
of draws people in look I'm just me I'm
trying to get the word out but the
healing is healing and the the street
creds there and people are getting their
lives back that's what counts and look
people wouldn't travel from all around
the world to be here tonight just to say
thank you if it wasn't real you know and
and you know I held back some tears I'm
trying my best you know the minute I
start crying though you know it's just
in and then we're done I to go in the
back but it's it's um but I but honestly
I yeah I can't Than People enough for
even coming here taking the trip think
about it uh you know you're you're in
Austria I'm going to hop on a plane I'm
going to come down to Cafe Gratitude I'm
going to meet aw I'm going to get some
great food I mean have to take some
balls and it just very special very
special it's incredible there's no other
community like it no there isn't and
these pizza parties are so much fun
we're having so much fun here how do you
feel to have the medical medium pizza
now on the Cafe Cafe Gratitude menu look
I mean I love this restaurant um I used
to come in this restaurant years and
years ago um to get good food it's it's
an amazing place right and Cafe
Gratitude they haven't collaborated with
a pizza before with anybody else and
they stand behind our community and they
and they collaborated Chef Drew Patrick
the COO I mean they're just like no
let's make this happen we want people to
get the best of whatever we can possibly
offer and the support is amazing here I
mean anybody anybody so maybe you don't
do medical medium still get down here
and try it it doesn't matter just get
here and try it and if you're somebody
right now and you're watching this live
stream um you know you're missing out if
you if if you don't try it to be honest
and look I challenge you come down here
if you live in the area have a pizza and
guess what you're not going to feel like
crab afterwards you're not you go eat
one of those greasy salty Dairy filled
oil filled God knows what's in them
gluten and everything else with all
kinds of preservatives people don't even
know about that's in frozen dough and
everything else go ahead and have those
and you see the difference go ahead and
have these pizzas and wo I don't know
I'm just really really excited oh no I
can feel it I'm so excited to be here
the energy in here is just so uplifting
we're having so much fun eating this
healing food and to be surrounded in
enironment that supports people's
healing and having fun and having a
pizza party who could ask for anything
more it's amazing I know I know it's
incredible and there's so much more to
go tonight don't go anywhere guys we got
the lecture coming up the light blast
it's incredible up who knows what's
going to come out of my mouth flying out
of it so we'll see hopefully you know
and that's the thing though it's funny
because um you know I I do a lot of live
stuff I don't do a lot of video stuff
and then the video stuff gets post it
it's only if for some reason I couldn't
get a live done or whatever or whatever
it is so but I I I make this like who
would do this maybe maybe it's a crazy
thing to do but who would do this I just
want people to out there see that you
know you can heal so I want them to be
able to be a part of this because
someone's sitting out there and they're
sick even if it's just one person
they're sick and this is going to be a
moment where they're going to be like
you know what I I like this guy a little
bit um look at him he's he's live right
now I I'm going to do medical medium and
heal and you get one person better this
that every every person counts yeah
every person counts but I like to do
things live I don't care if I make
mistake I don't care if I fall in my
face it doesn't matter that's what I
like doing the the lives I do normally
all these years and that's why I like
doing this live stream here I like you
know it's it's it's risky I used to do
all the podcast live MH but it's worth
it because you want people to just know
that your heart's in it I'm willing to
take a risk I'm not trying to hide
anything I might say something I might
say a word that may not make sense for a
minute it doesn't matter whatever it is
it's just I'm in it with you that's the
whole point and that's the key I'm in it
with you I need people to know that I'm
dedicated because I am and that's the
key it's the dedication so yeah we're
live right now and I'm going to be doing
a lecture live and a light blast live
well we know you're dedicated we feel it
we feel how real you are and thank you
so so many people are grateful for you
it's such an amazing uh collaboration
Cafe Gratitude we're grateful for you so
thank you so much thanks so much Daniel
thank you thank you
spe
[Music]
for
e
[Applause]
[Music]
e
e for
[Music]
I
m yeah
all right look here here
[Applause]
years
spe
[Applause]
know e
[Music]
Med
Serv
[Applause]
[Music]
you e
[Applause]
it's e
t
together
[Music]
[Applause]
sh e
what
[Applause]
e e
to for
[Applause]
[Music]
spe e
[Applause]
moment said
you e
[Applause]
EX
e e
[Applause]
than
for for
know
[Applause]
I hear the cookies are really good
you guys you guys have the cookies out
here or
what
right I mean it's the best cookie
they're the best cookies
right but I know some of you guys make
your own cookies and you're probably
like well yeah okay I make good cookies
too but uh are you guys having
fun glad to hear that and you're warm
out here still right good good good
amazing
hey good to see you guys again you guys
ready for a little talk is that okay I
don't
want I don't want I don't want to
disturb you
guys well I just want to introduce first
off first of all Patrick over here I
want this man right here
okay he's a good man all right
truly truly and um he supports the
community he wants people to have the
best food and that's that's the whole
thing Cafe Gratitude has the best food
and now they got the me medical medium
food it's just mind-blowing really and I
really appreciate everything I just want
to tell you that okay thank you very
much
yeah yeah he makes it happen I get on
the phone with him I'm like Patrick
Patrick what about this and he's like
all right all
right y y he's like come calm down calm
down but anyway it's just it's a great
honor to be here so um you guys let's
talk a little bit for a minute okay okay
so I didn't come into this really easy I
came in kicking and screaming since I
was a child since I was younger okay
that's what I did I came in Kicking and
Screaming did you ever read the first
book medical medium
right okay I should have put even more
in there about how much I was Kicking
and
Screaming I kind of kept it out I was
like oh no I I can't talk about that I
can't talk about this no no do you
remember my dog right
August right you know that was a special
moment in my life right I I went into
the water it was a cold water in Maine
all right up north on the East Coast
okay and the water was frigid freezing
cold and basically I wanted to say my
dog that got caught in the
current
and when I jumped in spirit of
compassion said that's a death sentence
you're not coming back out of here
you're not you're not going to make it
back out of here you have to turn around
and I saw my dog way out there like
caught in a little bit of seaweed and
kind of going down and I said I don't
care what it takes because I need to do
this does it matter I have to do this I
remember when I got out there and I had
a few more more breaths left in me and I
went down in the water and I saw my dog
under the water okay and do you guys
remember what happened you
remember I opened my eyes in that water
down there that freezing cold water and
there was an angel holding on to my dog
underwater yeah all
right
yeah and I grabbed that dog out of the
Angel's hands and I just took my dog to
the surface
August and then Spirit of compassion
second time ever did it did did did you
read that part second time ever I saw
Spirit of compassion it's not like I see
Spirit of compassion it's rare it's it
was the second time and I got to that
water and spirit of compassion said you
got to get back
now you got to get back now because that
angel isn't going to be sticking around
because I was lucky that angel was there
but Angel wasn't going to stay around
and have me Meander because I was only
basically living off of that Angelic
light in that moment in that water
because I was already in
hypothermia
hypothermia so I came back to
shore I was alive and I knew I had to
make the commitment there and wasn't
going to kick and scream anymore and I
wasn't going to fight fight fight it and
fight hearing Spirit of compassion and I
knew this is the direction I had to go
it didn't matter what I really wanted to
do never was about that but I had to
make that commitment and I had to stand
strong and I had to be like no this is
it I'm committed now I am I can't unsee
what I saw under that water that angel
was there I hear a voice I saw a spirit
of compassion twice in my life can't
unsee
that so I have to work for the
chronically ill I have to work for the
people I have to do it no matter what
you know when we get sick sometimes we
kick and scream too
right we do I've heard of stories where
people are like I wanted to do medical
medium it just wasn't there it just
wasn't there yet do you ever hear of
anybody like that wanted to try medical
medium information and it just wasn't
there yet right kind of kicking and
screaming to get to the truth to get to
the information
right I've seen that out there well I
had a kick and scream to get to here and
I know that other people do too to get
to this
point and then they find the
information and now it's about
committing time and energy that takes a
kick in a scream you start with a little
bit of celery juice or you start with
maybe one of the meditations or you
start with something
right but you eventually get there and
then you're committed and now you're in
it and guess what happens then freedom
and you know what happened when I
rescued August in that cold ocean
water and I hit the shore it was Freedom
it was freedom I didn't have to fight it
anymore I was committed all the way
I wasn't just saying it
anymore before that I would say it yeah
yeah no I'm in I'm in I'm in but no
after that and I hit the shore I had my
dog in my
arms I was committed and freedom started
for me freedom of being like kind of on
the fence a little bit and fighting it
and that freedom you know when you find
medical medium information of Freedom
happens you're free from the fish oil
[__] you're free from the right the
protein protein protein Pro is that
insane the protein thing the protein
demon
unbelievable as if the world isn't
getting
protein everybody's sick they're dying
in hospitals all kinds of problems are
happening they're getting all the
protein you could ever even imagine do
you ever you ever see that you run into
somebody you're like yeah you're protein
efficient you're not getting enough
protein that's why you're sick you're
free from that think about it you're
free from that
Insanity ah it's
incredible but that
freedom that freedom is real and you
know what it takes too to
also experience that freedom is your
free will and the thing is what you guys
is you guys access your free will did
you hear that podcast I did about Free
Will at one point did some of you guys
hear that some of you guys heard it
right
right wasn't that a good one that was a
good one I listen to that one I listen
to that one you wouldn't believe it but
I do I turn it on and I listen to it I'm
like wow this is incredible oh my God I
can't believe it not because I'm trying
to like you know my head's all swelling
and I'm like egoed out it's because it's
not my words they're it's Spirit of
compassion's words so then when I'm away
from it a little bit I forget kind of
what Spirit of compassion said so then I
got to listen to the episode and be like
damn that's just oh my
God you didn't let me down you didn't
let me down you showed up for me man you
showed up for
me your free will is like no other Free
Will I can tell you that because you can
have free will and use it all the wrong
way you can have free will and screw up
sure that's life that's how it works
down here on planet Earth of course
everybody makes mistakes all all the
time they use their Free Will in doing
it but also they get blocked too so
they're on autopilot with their Free
Will and they start using their Free
Will without kind of realizing it it
gets used instantly like compulsion it's
free will that's not really in their
favor serving them it's not serving them
right I just got comfortable using that
word recently because in the New Age
movement it's like you know things that
serve you and stuff serve you okay but
yeah it wasn't serving people the way
the way it works with free will
sometimes but you guys you did something
different like you shifted your free
will into a whole different area like
you really are using your free will you
got control over your free will how
about that control over it that's
mindblowing right there all on its own
think about that okay there's a
difference because you guys are piloting
your
ships you are piloting your
ship you really are something to be said
it's something to know you guys have
committed yourselves you're in it you're
in it to heal your body and guess who
loves you for it who loves you for being
committed your body your body loves you
how many of you guys thought that it was
your fault you were sick that's what I
wanted to ask you guys you thought it
was your fault Tobias over there you
thought it was your
fault right yeah isn't that crazy how it
works you're not crazy the system set up
like that it's set up so that you think
you're the reason why you're sick it's
your fault you created it how many of
you guys searching while you were sick
came across the understanding that you
created your illness you manifested it
right through manifestation you actually
created it it's not just you're the
reason you're at fault and you're the
reason why you're sick you you made it
happen how about that one right there
I mean if that's not dark I don't know
what is what is in dark cuz that's not
the truth that's not the truth it's
Death By A Thousand Cuts out there there
lots of exposures there's lots of things
that make us sick and then the scale
gets tipped you guys know this
information right probably know it
better than I do at this point
right but you guys found freedom is what
you did even if you're still in your
healing process right now so I want to
take it to that level right
there healing works in mysterious ways
one way is the nervous system needs time
to heal after you've already healed
there's people that have already healed
they're healed they fixed their problem
they did they still have residuals they
still have their nerves that are need
time to heal that's always last it's
always last but it takes your free will
to just understand that and soak that up
a little bit and be like okay
okay it's not my fault I didn't create
it my nerves just need more time to heal
that's important to know all on its
own I think the one thing about us
thinking that we're the cause of our
sickness and illness and we manifested
it I think that brings you to a place of
hopelessness because you must be a bad
person if you're the reason why you're
sick and you caused
it truth is it's the opposite with you
guys and people out there who are sick
or just got sick it's not your fault you
didn't cause
it your body loves you unconditionally
you guys know the autoimmune Theory do
you guys remember that one the
autoimmune
Theory right your body's attacking
itself oh
no that's your immune system attacking
its glands attacking its organs that's
why you're sick it's your immune system
right attacking you it's another trap
out there and that's what I mean by
Freedom medical medium information is
true freedom because you learn and once
you learn hey my immune system didn't
attack my organs it didn't attack my
glands it's not attacking me but science
must know it truly must know they can't
be wrong all those smart people out
there in the world but they are wrong it
was a theory in the
1950s you know how it works you know how
it
rolls back to Freedom again you know the
ditch the fish oil tablets and capsules
or whatever you know to ditch the bad
stuff I'm just using that as one is one
example you know it's not Protein that's
not why you were sick you guys know that
you know your body's not attacking
itself you know that you know you didn't
create it or manifest it right you know
that you see all the traps I'm running
through them one trap after another one
one trap after another that's right
but don't worry some 22-year-old who's
never been sick
yet un social doing weights building
their muscles they know
everything till they're sick when
they're
39 and then they're like crap I I should
have read those medical medium
books and guess what those books will be
here they'll be here in 20 years be here
in 30 years they'll be here in 40 years
and there'll be a legacy
to save
lives I don't want you guys to feel like
you're super alone or anything I know
that you know with medical medium
information or medical medium I know
that I get I get ostracized out there I
get picked on have you guys ever seen me
picked
on it's actually kind of funny right
yeah it doesn't bother me did you guys
see me picked on but guess what medical
medium books more of them sold around
the world and the millions around the
world than any other health author any
other
anything weird really
weird no no wonder why the hate is so
big think about it right no wonder why
the hate is so big I mean there's a lot
of people out there doing the mm in
learning it they got the books they got
that Legacy it's in their hands you guys
got here early some of you guys 9 years
I 9 years seven years eight
years
mindblowing and that leads me to the
other
thing so you guys know Freedom even if
you still have some symptoms left even
though you're still in the process and I
don't want to ever disrespect anybody
who's a dabbler did you ever hear me say
dabbl
yeah right you could be a dabbler that's
fine do one tiny half teaspoon of celery
juice a day just do a half teaspoon
you're not going to hear any [__] from
me just do a half a
teaspoon don't tell me you're still sick
because of that half a teaspoon of
celery juice and that's doing
it but you can still tell me that and
I'm still going to be like look come on
come on
you can be a dabbler still do mm you're
going to get the highest respect for me
you are there's no doubt baby steps man
baby
steps that's all and that's fine that's
fine how many of you
guys how many of you guys feel like
you're
seasoned I want to know like I I say it
all the time but who who feels that way
you guys okay
all right Jess you you guys feel like
you're seasoned Nadine you feel like
you're seasoned right you
guys well you are you are there's
something to be said about that okay you
got you guys have to hold that you got
to hold that like a landmark you got to
know what the pillars are you got to
know what those landmarks are you got to
know what they are don't lose them
you're seasoned you're experienced you
understand the terrain you've seen it
all you've been there you done that
don't lose sight of that don't get
tricked it's nothing but mental mind
game crap out
there you got am I right you can tell me
I'm not and I'm I'm I'll humbly just bow
down like oh
[__] maybe I was wrong about
that but it's mental mind game craziness
out there and it's there to trick you
out fast so that you lo you lose your
experience in an instant because
somebody on social says something stupid
and just throws you in a different
direction for a second so you got to
keep your mind strong you got to know
where you come from you have to know
your experience and what you've been
through you got to know those pillars
and those landmarks man you have to hold
on to them you got to know what they
are you believe in God you don't have to
believe in God anybody believe in God in
here
medical medium book one was a little
difficult because I was putting God in
there every minute you
know I was I think back
then unless you were a
minister of
Faith right or a
priest or somebody you can use that word
God I don't know if you remember a
decade ago kind of well you weren't
allowed to use God too much you know
that right
and I was putting God all through the
medical medium book one wait a minute
though he's a medium why is he saying
God because it says in the Bible thou
who listens to some kind of voice in the
air or whatever who practices with the
crystal ball is damned to hell
right it's a funny
one you know when you hear a
voice that just wants people people to
heal and gives them tools to
heal I don't know anything closer to
[Applause]
God those pillars are critical you
believe in God that's a pillar that's
faith in your life that's a landmark in
your life you believe in God if you
don't believe in God that's okay Creator
the light maybe you believe in the
universe you've heard me say that all
these years right whatever it is that's
kind of a pillar in your life that's
your faith right well believe in the
fact that you're seasoned and you're
experienced and you've been there you
tried that you done this you guys are
the real deal hold that as a pillar so
you don't get rocked or
waver you hang tight to that it's
critical something you hold on
to cuz face it you guys probably don't
get enough credit do you guys get a ton
of
credit no you don't get a lot of credit
everywhere you go someone doesn't hand
you a
metal you laid in bed for 20 years you
went through hell and back here's a
metal
no oh you laid in bed for 20 years sure
you were sick
right what about that whole
thing people being sick and struggling
but you look fine right you look fine I
you know what I'm I'm glad that was
taken from medical medium there's some
things that are poached that I'm happy
about some things I'm poached that are
poached that I'm not happy about right
but when that was poached about the fact
that you can't see the illness but you
walk around with it and you suffer with
it with every single symptom but people
say you look fine there's nothing wrong
with you what are you talking about it
must be in your head you must be lazy or
bored something's just up with you you
got to see a psychiatrist maybe a
therapist you got a fear of
healing right but that invisible
illness that you can't see I didn't mind
when that was poached because you know
what it's doing a lot of people a lot of
good out there even if they don't know
medical medium
information but there's some things that
get poach it's sad because if they don't
know their way back to where it starts
they can't really get the rest of what
they need how many of you guys run into
people who have a tidbit for medical
medium they didn't know they had did you
ever see that you're talking to us all
the time all the time right you see that
and somebody has a tidbit and you're
like oh man this is annoying because
that comes from medical
medium you guys are seers I'm going to
say it again I said it last night you
guys I think I said it last night you
guys are
seers okay you know where the danger is
you know where the traps are you know
where the potholes are you guys can see
clear I don't care if you have brain fog
still or you had some brain fog you got
more clarity than people who don't have
brain fog you got more sight more
understanding more
compassion guys have to know this you
got to have this deep inside of you my
job is to make sure you know this and
you're aware of it that's my job Spirit
of compassion told me
that uh hope I'm doing a good
job I
hope that's all I can
[Music]
do you guys need to know who you are you
need to know who you are and I believe
you do I do I just want to support that
I want you to know deep down inside your
good people sickness doesn't Det
determine other in the sense where if
you got sick doesn't mean you're a bad
person it's the first place we go oh my
God it's a first place we go every
time yeah it's easy twisted ankle and
it's like I'm a bad
person it can happen but know where know
where you've come from you know you know
your life
experience you guys know your way I'm
proud of all of you I can't say it
enough
when I swam to the
shore and I landed on that Shore I
knew that I was granted a gift I did
something foolish I jumped in icy cold
water part of me knew there was no
coming
back but I
did thanks to an
angel I don't give Spirit of compassion
much credit me and him are have been
sparring since I was
four we've been
sparring you get kind of sick of hearing
them you
know but that's all right that's all
right I could deal with
it but I I came back it was a gift truly
a gift from above somebody was watching
so I got purpose and you got purpose too
cuz I'm in this room with you guys and
anybody out there in live stream land
wherever camera that is you got you got
purpose
too okay you do cuz the medical M
Community isn't just in here we know
that right in live stream land it's out
there it's
everywhere it's
everywhere it is it is you guys ready
for a light blast
all right where's the light going
remember that decide where it's going
maybe some of you thought about it
earlier tonight where you want to wanted
to
go okay is it going to your kidney is it
going to your liver it's going to your
heart going to your Consciousness is it
going to your soul is it going to your
brain where's it
heading right think about
it it matters it does and for some
reason you're like I can't make a
decision I just can't what am I going to
do it's okay because 1 2 3 boom it's
going to hit anyway and it's going to go
right through you and it'll find its way
it'll find out where it's going it will
okay that's okay so everybody take a
deep breath then
release then release remember it's not a
contest remember I told you it's not a
yoga studio it's not a hip Yoga Studio
in La where everybody's out breathing
each other right
yeah I know I know I know and they got
that new coffee drink in their hand
right
after and they're intermittent
fasting
right all right count of three one two 3
deep breath
in okay
release okay good you guys outside I see
you doing it too yep
exactly good good good we're going to do
one right here we're going to do an easy
Breezy one there's a little bit more
power Behind These because something's
happening with the Stars something's
happening with the moon right
now Spirit of compassion says there's
kind of a more open
Channel so it's not going to be doing
kind of a circle up here do a little bit
of a turn down it's going
straight like that
noise we're
live it's not scripted there's nothing
scripted about me
the funny thing I didn't even have one
word prepared for this I'm just waiting
on spirit's words and then I know where
to run and where to
go one two three deep breath in hold it
light light light light
release okay good good yeah it's a much
more powerful light so just look out
tonight take a deep breath and then
release you guys in
and release fantastic wonderful all
right we're going to do another one
right now and the count of three one two
three deep breath in hold it light light
light light release
release okay good good good we got a lot
of blockages and that's fine this next
one's going to be a lot stronger now get
ready for this on the count of three one
two three deep breath in hold it light
light light light
release we're at
like still 60% to go who felt it go
through them directly already there's a
bunch that it went through went through
you directly through you directly you
guys outside any of it did you go
through you okay that's good get ready
for this now one
two three deep breath in hold it light
light light light light light
release take a deep breath
release count of three one 2 3 deep
breath in hold it light
light light light light
release there's not a lot of people
left we got a couple more to do though
meaning a couple more light blasts all
right so it's Amplified even higher now
it's going to be straight hits right on
top of the head but really hard get
ready on the count of three you guys one
two three deep breath in hold it light
light light light light light light
release there's only like a few people
left where are they there's one
outside in this area here one outside in
this
area there's two here there's one here
and there's somebody just adjacent on
the edge of this the the restaurant
outside
somewhere they're just getting it cuz
they're so close
hope they're not driving immediately
right after this a second later I
wouldn't add if somebody had a stop sign
isn't getting a hit a little bit ready
count of three this is a big one one two
three deep breath
in hold it release release hold
on I went a little too early spirit says
now ready one two three deep breath
in hold it light light light light light
light light light light
release we're good you guys all the way
through just want to thank everybody who
came far and wide who got here who came
from far
away I want to thank everybody okay I
want to thank the staff all right you
guys are amazing
seriously okay
and um I want to thank everybody outside
here for a second
too you guys I'm proud of
you you guys feel the light go through
you all right how you guys doing over
there amazing you guys I appreciate you
coming out taking the trip all right you
know I love you for it
truly remember those words okay remember
all those
words keep it to your heart I love you
guys love you
all
[Applause]
right I recognized the medical medium I
had read like a little blog about him
and yeah just like a little seed was
planted I started listening and then a
couple years later is when I started
using his tools because I got desperate
with my symptoms I struggled with
chronic UTI for about 20 years and I was
on antibiotic every month sometimes
every week I probably took hundreds of
rounds of antibiotics throughout those
15 to 20 years and it wasn't until I
found his information that I was able to
clear those on my own and I've been UTI
free for probably 3 or 4 years and
antibiotic free for 5 years but I just
wanted to meet Anthony and thank him for
just giving me a new life really when I
was pregnant with my son I started to
feel these symptoms with like difficulty
digesting I pretty much couldn't eat
anything it just kept getting worse and
worse and my symptoms were out of
control and I you know went to all the
doctors and naturopaths and nobody
really had an answer and I was really
desperate one time I went to a bookstore
I saw his book his first book and I was
curious about it I read a little bit and
I was like I'm not sure so I just kind
of put it back a few weeks later through
a friend I was telling her you know that
I'm feeling these symptoms I can't eat
anything I felt like I was slowly dying
and she said you should check out
medical medium and I was like what I
just saw his book and she's like yeah
you should read it and I did and I mean
everything changed for me after that
everything I mean the fact that I can
come here and eat eat this food and
whereas before it was impossible
impossible so that's kind of what drew
me and I'm so grateful I would say I
am such a stronger mother
I just asked my 14-year-old son I said
when was last time you were sick and it
was just a long
pause we realized it was over 2 years
ago before learning mm I never knew
which supplement to buy I didn't know
what to stay away from I didn't know how
much to give a child that is
huge so I would say you know do I give
him 1,5 what's too much am I going to
hurt him you know so now I know I have
the power
I've been using medical medium
information for 8 years and I started
off kind of slow and needed to build my
trust with the information and the new
mentality of how to eat and heal but
just step by step I slowly implemented
one item at a time pretty much every two
weeks and each time it blew me away so I
kept going and it would took me about 3
years to fully dive in my biggest change
I would say was healing dyslexia add um
depression anxiety OCD thoughts and it
still took me maybe a year to really get
out of that but once I did it was like a
breath of fresh air to lead a normal
life to have new opportunities to feel
confident and you know feel like
yourself again so I yeah I was lucky
that I found this information and
[Music]
healed I was diagnosed with hypothyroid
about 4 years later I kind of I found
medical medium's advice and I said
finally there's an answer of why because
I've always said why why do I get this
why do you have this what's this and
there's a reason and he gives a reason
and that's kind of what I was always
looking for so Through The Years just I
would say um having energy being alive
not on at my age any medication I'm
super thrilled about that and never want
to be and I just believe the body
naturally does want to heal if you give
it the the right things well I was
diagnosed with Graves sometime last year
and after being on medical median for
like 6 months my doctor finally told me
that I'm in remission when we got the
news last year was like spring uh it hit
her really hard it's just like you have
to be on medicine your whole life or
remove your thyroid ready she wasn't
having it she was searching for answers
and then eventually came across
Anthony's book beforehand she tried
going off the medicine symptoms came
back like within a couple weeks and we
were both kind of disappointed cuz it
was doing well when she was on the
medicine and then the summer she took
herself off and like you know nothing
really changed too much and she just
kept with the diet and then yeah went to
the the doctor and they told her that it
was in remission did blood work and all
of that and I was thrilled naturally I
just wanted her to be happy and she is
she's happy and healthy I would say what
predominantly brought me to the
information was I had really bad mental
health struggles very severe depression
to where
I'd wake up and I couldn't pinpoint why
I felt that way but I was just so low
and for most of my life I struggled with
depression and anxiety um among other
struggles and it's symptoms I've made
like a lot of traction with I feel
amazing that I'm able to cope with
things in a lot more resilient of a way
so it feels very freeing I came about
the information to help my patients and
family I think that as doctors we can
see what we are actually doing to
patients because a lot of patients are
suffering some side effects and when
they come back we put them on more
medications to help with the side
effects and they end up with more and
more medications and the procedures we
see a lot of um negative effect from
procedures that we perform really
witnessing that should alert us are we
really helping patients with those
things that we do to
them wow what a great lecture and that
life blast tonight was so powerful did
you guys feel that powerful light blast
like we were feeling it here in Venice
at home it was just incredible we're
going to talk to some of the guests
about their pizza party experience here
I have my first guest would you like to
join me over here hi hello I don't know
if you remember me I do how are you it's
so good to see you I'm good how are you
it's so lovely to see you give you hug
oh thank you yes yes how has your night
been so far it's been fantastic so this
is my identical twin sister so hi hi
good to see you it's been amazing I've
never done a medical medium event before
and to share this with my sister who's
recovered so much from medical medium
means the world to us what is your
favorite part of the evening so far it's
been really emotional to see her you
know I've had my health struggles and
I've healed completely with medical
medium and she's on a health Journey now
suffering with some symptoms of vertigo
and to share this together was very
hopeful uplifting ing cathartic
spiritual emotional everything so it's
great what beautiful people like we have
a a table full of women telling stories
of like hope recovery things they've
been through and you feel a sense of
community and um how food can heal you
it's like gosh I wish there were more
moments like this in life but it feels
really special and lovely how was your
experience like with tonight's life
blast it was amazing I felt it
immediately I actually had like a
toothache and it's kind of gone um and
we were actually holding hands she like
I'm more ingratiated into medical medium
she's a little bit like slowly getting
into it so I made her hold my hand
because I was like you you know got to
send that energy to her but I don't know
it was great I loved it what did you
feel during that Li Bloss well I you
know like I'm I am not that spiritual of
a person but I felt like this is really
fun and quirky and different and maybe
you know like I don't know there's
there's positive energy and I feel that
Virgo is going to be gone now and then
yeah maybe I'll change my mind yeah when
I'm like reverse aging I'll I'll change
my mind on it and what is it about the
medical medium protocol that You' first
started now and what what are some of
your favorite uh you know smoothies
juices and what health benefits have you
found so I've been dealing with ver for
the past 6 months and I had I quit
caffeine I've taken a lot of cues from
Lauren um the C juice in the morning is
so important the heavy metal detex
smoothie and I'm not always perfect but
for me it's like ginger is great for
inflammation there's certain elements
that I you know Ginger and turmeric and
spirulina and it's like adding these
things in and slowly over time taking
things out and I like that Anthony talks
about maybe you just change one thing
that that's me I'm not you know Lauren
has has gotten to the point where she
can live a really clean protocol I'm
just doing it step by step but I see
enough Improvement in how I feel and my
energy to keep going and I hope to just
keep getting better at it what a
beautiful way to do the protocol
together is it inspiring watching each
other heal it's so inspiring she
inspires me every day we Inspire each
other it's it's
great do you ever get in the kitchen
together and make some of the recipes oh
yeah she's a better cook than me
actually like I mean I've done it so
long I'm a grizzled vet like I do the
same things over and over she'll like
get creative I'm like oh man this tastes
good but she is like very strict I'll be
like do you want to put like a Parmesan
R and she's like so she's like very
medical medium seasoned but um I'm
better for it so she's a good influence
yeah she's doing it out of love yeah
absolutely what did you think of the
food tonight what was your favorite dish
um the pizza was incredible I haven't
had pizza in so long and the
Mediterranean pizza sorry I ate both
Pizza is but it was so good it just like
had it was analogous to pepperoni in an
interesting way and I thought it was
really good well I loved all the food
but for me you know Lauren's been doing
this for 9 years uh this is the first
time in 9 years where I've gotten to go
out to eat with Lauren and she hasn't
had to bring her own food that means the
world to see my sister sit down and eat
a full meal and be taken care of and not
be judged um so to me the food's
excellent but it's also someone created
this environment where you can feel
included and
seen it makes me emotional but it's
beautiful she deserves that all the time
but to get it like this is so special
yeah so special do you enjoy hanging out
with the medical maum community in this
environment like like your sister saying
it's a beautiful environment everybody
understands one another there's a quiet
understanding you don't even have to
really explain yourself to someone and
we all look fine but we've all been
through a lot and it's just a beautiful
thing to share no we spoke to someone
who she was like my goal was to just
walk at my friend's wedding and she got
to do that and I think like when you
think of Cafe Gratitude it's like that's
it it's gratitude like you get gratitude
for the smallest thing that we take for
granted in life to walk at your friend's
wedding to see your sister eat a meal
that she couldn't eat that's so
beautiful and Powerful yeah are you
excited for Cafe Gratitude to continue
offering these dishes on the menu yeah
because if we can build more more
communities like this people can heal
and I'm not saying it's for everybody
but there should be a space for all the
people who want to heal or aren't
getting answers and want to empower
themselves you know there's there's
things that your doctor can tell you but
if you if you want to believe you can
heal yourself this is how you start with
how you eat and we need more places like
this for sure and finally do you have an
encouraging message you'd like to share
with the community watching tonight I
would say just start small wherever
you're at every day sometimes it's just
one little thing go through one minute 1
second one hour I know everyone's going
through tough things we get setbacks
just keep going there's light at the end
of the tunnel There's Hope yeah and if
you don't believe in this stuff just
talk to one person who's experienced it
because you know Lauren gets a message
from people all the time who are looking
for answers like you're the living proof
there's so many people that are living
proof that you know they got an
infection they use this protocol they
got better like it's these people are
all recovering and if you're searching
for answers reach out it's I don't know
it's a beautiful thing pick up a book
try it you have nothing to lose exactly
nothing to lose thank you so much I hope
you had a beautiful evening so great to
see you too enjoy the rest of your night
bye-bye now we're going to talk to our
next
guest hello and for everyone watching
online what is your name my name is Alas
and I'm coming from Germany from Germany
traveled all the way here with family to
be here for medical medium Cafe
Gratitude pizza party yes so what was it
that made you you and your family want
to attend
tonight uh I don't know why did you want
to be here um cuz my mother is a big
friend from Anthony William andum and he
want to come here CU this will be um the
first time he see Anthony mhm and uh he
want to come here with me
because I made um much light blast with
her but
online and um then he then I come with
her mhm and uh I don't know what did you
think of the light blast tonight what
was your exper what did you
feel I don't know I don't feel
some so much things or a big update yeah
but it's pretty incredible so much
healing happening here what do you think
of the food uh the food uh it was was
good it was good yes do you like eating
the pizza uh yes but I um it's not so
super mhm what about the cookies the
cookies the cookies were the cookies was
very yummy yes yeah I loved them the
gingerbread cookie oh my God that was
amazing that was amazing where's your
mom my mom is uh in the coffee oh okay
yes well you having fun evening yes a
lot of fun well thank you so much for
talking to us enjoy the rest of your
night and uh yeah it was great talking
to you thank you so much you're such a
trooper love it okay we're going to talk
to our next
guest hello are you having a good night
absolutely yes beautiful what is your
name Karen poer so nice to meet you my
name is Danielle to meet you so what was
it that made you want to attend this
night um just get more interaction with
Anthony and the light blast and hearing
him speak being in person being around
the community it's such a beautiful
Community do you enjoy being around this
community absolutely yeah everybody's
wonderful compassionate
caring yeah it's beautiful it's very
unique yes it is what did you think of
the life blast tonight what was your
experience like with that it was it was
more intense I've been to several I've
had several and you just feel the like
my nervous system is the last to kind of
heal so I it feel shocks all through my
body wow that's incredible yeah it's
intense tonight and what was your
meeting like with aw
tonight it was a little quick I just
kind
of just it was just a quick one I know
it does fly by right it does yeah yeah
you have to watch the live stream back
again yeah for sure
yeah yeah did you have a favorite dish
from
tonight I actually like the sushi I I
don't usually eat sushi you ever so yeah
that was that was a nice surprise did
you like the thyme tea and the cookies
absolutely absolutely yeah those were
yeah fantastic so would you like to
share a little bit of your healing
Journey with medical medium
information um sure um I was on mattress
Island about 13 well I started 14 years
ago I had a bad Hemorrhage so that put
me in UN in a bad place and so I don't
know how long after that it's kind of a
blur how long it took to find medical
medium but he was an answer to my
prayers and I just started slowly and
here I am wow so you say you started
slowly what things did you first bring
into to your with the medical medium
information to start your healing
journey I cut out the no foods and I did
celery juice and then the heavy metal
detox smoothie was
just a little bit at a time MH yeah when
did you really start noticing your
health moving forward your healing
Journey
progressing oh I would say probably
pretty much right away um I was in such
a bad place though it took a while to
feel like I was functioning as a normal
person but um it was it was pretty
quick that's incredible what other
health benefits now have you experienced
using the information
H gosh I had almost 40 symptoms so it's
hard
to it's just been a lot I mean all of
the a lot of the symptoms were
debilitating and now if I have a little
symptom it just it's minor it doesn't
affect me it doesn't knock me out so
much that's pretty incredible now you're
here at Cafe Gratitude are you excited
for them to to continue offering the
medical medium uh menu items and cleanse
options yes yes yes we did the cleanse I
don't remember what it's called the one
that they have here yes yeah the medical
medium cleans yep we did that that was
what a treat you know to get treated but
not having to do it all yourself and do
you love having a a meal tonight this
pizza party that fully supports your
healing Journey absolutely yeah just to
have not have to prepare it yourself is
such a treat M yes do you have an
encouraging message you would like to
share with those people online that are
watching the live stream
keep the faith the first radio show I
listened to with Anthony was about faith
and yeah that turned it around for me
was just knowing that if you have faith
starts somewhere and every little bit
does matter so I want to ask you then
during your healing Journey did you
encounter any spiritual lessons from
medical medium
information
oh the
Angels the
meditations um um strengthen my my
beliefs
um yeah a
lot yeah I it's hard to explain
incredible yeah yeah no it's okay words
to it it's just difficult it's just
something just you can't explain it it's
quite beautiful cuz a lot of people
mentioned during their healing Journey
that it's not only just Health but it's
an all like health and also spiritual
and you know it's a combin
yeah I think cuz when you're when you're
in such a l place you start to question
a lot and so as that builds every it's
like the cloud lifts
and yeah yeah yeah well thank you so
much for talking to us tonight it's been
such a pleasure talking to you I really
appreciate it thank you so much well
guys that is everything from night two
of the medical medium pizza party we
have had a blast and I can't wait to do
it all again tomorrow night it's the
final night night three thank you so
much for tuning in and watching this I'm
Danielle delate I've had so much fun
this evening and haven't those healing
Journeys been incredible that everyone
is sharing with us I can't wait to see
you all again tomorrow