our brains are under attack
that's what's happening I want to read a
quote we're doing the brain saver books
right here you guys check this out
if you're someone who wakes up in the
morning and shakes their head wondering
why there's a lack of answers out there
for the chronically suffering
now you understand why because you've
read the brand saver books
you're learning the answers you're
learning the truth so you can do
something about your health and your
family's health because your family's
health is critical it's important by
knowing what that critical truth is that
for one toxic heavy metals are
saturating our brains and we can remove
them to enjoy a better quality of life
we supersede the machine
We rise above the so-called authority of
our well-being so that well-being is in
our own hands
We rise above the machine
so I want to talk a little bit about
some we're in the brain saver books you
guys and we'll pop these down right here
really quick
so I'm in a section right here chapter
15 The Brain saver book both of these
brain saver books are just absolutely
phenomenal
packed with information you guys know
and you've got the brain shot therapies
and everything else this section is
called evolving backwards and I was
talking a little bit about our brain and
our immune system earlier before right
but now I'm talking about a couple of
other things so let's go into it a
little bit we think humans are evolving
and advancing right we think humans are
advancing and evolving
we know that's not true
what's really evolving are the toxic
chemicals we're exposed to
the EMF were exposed to that's what's
evolving we're up against the pathogens
we're exposed to that's what's evolving
we're up against
brain betrayers our brain becomes
betrayed designed by Industries to
supposedly make our lives better so they
say they're trying to make our lives
better but yet they betray us we confuse
the long-standing theory that humankind
is evolving with the advancements in
technology that we see all around us so
we're thinking there's so much
technology I'm here talking to you
because of technology technology means
whoa technology is advancing then
everything's advancing that we're but
we're getting more chronically ill and
chronically sick that's what's
incredible about it all we see
advancements in life-saving surgical
medicine too right advancements in how
far we can reach into space with our
telescope whoa that's all technology it
gives us the misperception that
humankind is getting ahead by Leaps and
Bounds in some ways that we may be true
some ways that may be true when it comes
to technology
but what about our physical brain so
let's go into that what about our
physical brains and bodies what about
the physical existence of humankind is
that evolving
just want to ask you like is humankind
evolving
life expectancy will decrease did you
know I was the only oh my God I hate
saying this
I was the only one that said it was
decreasing all these decades
and they're like no life expectancy is
better than ever it's better than ever
all the clinics are saying so medical
research and science is saying life
expectancy is incredible it's only
getting better and I was like no it's
not they're just not telling anybody
they're not telling anybody that
actually it's not
it was decreasing all along and now it
is decreasing it has dropped it's out
there it has dropped
life expectancy will decrease at a
gradual Pace during this decade and then
life expectancy will decrease at an
unprecedental drastic Pace over the next
decade and Beyond what's going to happen
here and reading on the brain saver
books
life expectancy I hate being kind of a
bummer
but after 10 years it's gonna
decrease
at a drastic Pace a drastic pace
over the next decade and Beyond at
drastic Pace already The New Normal is
to struggle with symptoms whether you
identify a sick or not everybody has a
symptom everybody has a symptom
everybody has something
acne stuffy nose all the time an allergy
asthma aches and pains stomach problem
acid reflux everybody has a symptom
tiredness fatigue headaches whatever it
is they have a symptom
Eating Disorders whatever it is they
have a symptom
virtually every human being on the
planet experiences at least one symptom
at
this point where we stand right now in
history so right now in history at this
point every single human being on the
planet does experience at least one
symptom
there are different levels from very
mild to devastatingly severe symptoms
you guys know about that there's The Not
So Sick group those who are experiencing
symptoms and still functioning you see
them out there they're all at the stores
they're filing into the drug stores
they're in the grocery store you think
everybody is fine and dandy in the
grocery store everybody's got a symptom
I know so they all have a symptom or or
more
those who are experiencing symptoms and
still functioning working being
productive even playing all day if they
have that privilege of playing all day
there's people out there that have the
privilege of playing all day
they could play play play it doesn't
matter they could be big trust funders
they can play so either way they still
have a symptom then there's the sick
group those who are frightfully ill out
there those for whom each day is about
surviving then there's a people there's
people that are really struggling and
suffering and they're just trying to
survive
this increase in sickness like never
before is only going to keep developing
over time in the next 10 years in this
10 years here worse than the next 10
years drastic
so are we evolving in that in the right
direction or backwards that's the
question right here the book's asking
are our physical bodies any different
than they were in ancient Rome 2500
years ago and if you believe that we
have evolved since then are we evolving
faster than what's evolving around us
now that's destroying us
so we're up against so much
toxins more than ever before the
pathogens more than ever before heavy
metals more than ever before
and the list goes on we need to be aware
that we are going backwards not forwards
but nobody cares
you guys do with their physical health
in the next one to five years
we're going to see chronic illness rise
to levels no one could ever imagine so
in the next one to five years we're
going to see chronic illness rise to a
level no one ever ever imagined before
you guys I'm reading on the brain saver
books brain saver and brain saver
protocols two very heavy books I'm sorry
about that about them being so heavy and
everything I'm going to bring this over
a little bit
so and that's because instead of our
bodies advancing everything wrong about
the world is evolving
you guys know what's out there
environmental pollution is involved is
evolving the ocean is becoming more
toxic the Great Pacific Garbage Patch is
becoming bigger the chemical industry is
evolving creating new chemical soups by
the hour Around the World Around the
Clock the pharmaceutical industry is
evolving even overreaching and
controlling the nutraceutical industry
and not always evolving in our best
interests
pathogens are evolving more and more new
strains of pathogens that have been
released from Labs over the last hundred
years and keep people sick with chronic
illness or mutating and strengthening as
we pass those pathogens around to each
other whether through our family line or
any other means of exposure
everything's evolving around us
but the industry is in and the world of
health is not saying hey hey we have to
do something about it we got to protect
our brain
we have to take care of our brain we
have to look out for our health not
doing that instead it's all gimmicky
trendy stuff it's like take your
Omega-3s make sure you do your
probiotics
make sure you make sure you take your
vitamin D right and it's all about that
and it's not it's not medicine is not
evolving enough to keep up with
everything that's why there's hundreds
of symptoms with no answers and there's
hundreds of symptoms where people are
struggling and suffering and it's like
the lotto in a way to get some relief
out there maybe you'll get relief for a
second maybe you won't
that's very difficult
so the world of sicknesses is getting
worse the the attack on our brains is
evolving but our brains are not evolving
enough to override the attack so we need
help and support the brain saver books
are that
foreign
look I want to go into this a little bit
I could go on there's so many different
things in here there's your pain and
suffering enlightened as I was talking
about the other day there's over 300
symptoms conditions in these books
right there's recipes so I didn't talk
about the recipes yet I talked about the
brain shot therapy but I do want to get
into the recipes a little bit so let me
grab
the book here and take a look
so what you'll find in these books is a
massive recipe book inside these
incredible books so we have a lot of
information so you got over a hundred
recipes in here that's a brain detox
tonic right there I just opened up to
which is incredible all on its own so if
anything if you just worked off the
recipes it can better your life
because the recipes are geared for the
brain for healing the brain and body
specifically geared towards the brain
getting the brain what it needs this
one's called the brain armor salad which
is really incredible on its own the
brain armor salad which is really
exciting too I'm just giving you a
rundown in just some of the stuff that's
inside here
these are the brain saver wraps and
you'll notice the wrap is lettuce right
instead of something else instead of
something like corn or wheat or
something else there's so many
incredible recipes that I'm going to be
making some of these recipes with you
guys which I'm really excited about so
when you have your brain saver books
it's going to be really fun to make the
recipes together so I'm excited about
that I want you to know that that's one
of my goals is actually to cook with you
guys make the recipes out of the brain
saver books and while you guys are
making the recipes out of the brain
saver books so that's going to be really
fun all on its own so I wanted to give
you guys a little heads up is where
we're going
which is really cool so the recipes are
really incredible all on their own and
then there's a soul healing like a soul
brain and soul rehabbing section in the
protocols book
so brain and soul rehabbing in here so
there's meditations in here and I'm so
excited because I can't wait for you
guys to try those meditations which are
really powerful it's really exciting so
the protocols book I didn't show you
enough of the produce call protocols
book right over 300 symptoms conditions
with protocols
which is incredible so the whole point
is is allowing you to be able to choose
what you need because you're different
than someone else customize what you
need to move yourself forward now
I'm gonna go into the heavy metal detox
cleanses a little bit you guys know
about the heavy metal detox cleanse
medical medium heavy metal detox cleanse
now we have seven levels the brain books
have the heavy metal detox cleanses
which is really exciting in the seven
different levels
then there's an extractor smoothie too
so there's also an advanced extractor
and an extractor
these are incredible tools that are
going to be so helpful valoris's rehabs
need them
um Patty says ordered both books can't
wait for them to arrive
so now I'm in the brain shot therapies
I'm just giving you guys quick a quick
look through there a little quick tour
so I'm gonna put
the sign up here for a little bit scene
see the books right so I'll give you a
quick little Tour on the books
so now I'm going to brain shot therapies
I know everybody's starting to try the
brain shot Therapies
so I just want to give you that
forewarning if you just got here it's
the first live view caught talking about
brain saver the brain shot therapies are
quick acting fast acting for quick
relief
but they're intense and you'll
experience that now people are not used
to immediate relief in alternative
medicine
it's really really rare
and medical meeting books creates this
situation where you heal and you get
relief where you get relief and heal but
the brain shot therapies are even more
intense
and so when you do experience them this
one's a trauma shock and loss stabilizer
when you do experience them I don't want
you caught off guard
because you're gonna feel it when you
actually use these brain shot therapies
so I just don't want you caught totally
off guard I want you to be just
in The Knowing of what's Happening
so Allison has question extractor is
that better than the heavy metal detox
smoothie no it's not better than the
heavy metal detox smoothie it's part of
the heavy metal detox cleanse you can
actually choose to do the extractor you
don't have to there's seven levels and
you can do the extractor if you want
that's what's incredible about it
someone else may not need the extractor
somebody else can use the extractor what
happens is when you'll see reading in
here that Spirit of compassion was
basically trying to get a sense from a
billion people on the planet
because it's not MediCal medium was
never one size fits all it's not like
all the different programs out there or
whatever Health trendy diets those are
all one size fits all you go into it
it's one size fits all right
these are for everybody to be able to
customize you can do the extractor you
don't have to do the extractor but it's
there for you to move that needle if you
need it you got the heavy metal detox
smoothie you can just do that but you
can also do the advanced heavy metal
detox movie and then the seven levels of
heavy metal detox where there's other
things to do that are recommended in
that level so it's really comprehensive
and you can find your way and find what
feels and works best for you
because you're different than another
person and why are you different because
you have different things going on so
there's something called the nerve gut
acid stabilizer that's one of the brain
shot Therapies
I love that one for people I know people
are going to benefit so much
for that
centauri's healing you actually uh did
that stabilizer you did the trauma shock
and loss stabilizer
incredible um relationship breakups
stabilizer is a great one all on its own
so that one there I'm just showing you
really quick what they look like
so that's the relationship breakup
stable like sleeping recharging
stabilizer that's a great one Speaking
Your Truth stabilizers so many people
that feel like
there's so many people
who feel like they they have a difficult
time speaking their truth and they're
looking to actually
hone their purpose there's a wisdom and
intuition stabilizer
which is really powerful
and so
the dream shifter that's incredible all
on its own so I don't know if you guys
keep track of your dreams if your dreams
mean anything to you A lot of people
don't dream and then there's a lot of
people who have nightmares and a lot of
people that
wish they had better dreams and there's
also people that want to find messages
in their dreams too there's also people
that want to be reached by loved ones in
their dreams they want to be reached by
people
in their dreams too they want to connect
spiritually in their dreams their dreams
mean a lot because dreams do mean a lot
for sure so this is the dream shifter
I recommend trying the dream shifter
someday
because get ready for that
I mean that's a really that's a really
incredible one all in its own
so there's over there's sorry there's 30
brain shots but there's seven brain shot
therapy cleanses
so the craving shifter I know so many of
you struggled now we're going into the
holidays and I want to talk about this
for a little bit we're heading into the
holidays got the Halloween candy coming
up
and then we got Thanksgiving coming up
depending on where you are in the world
and such and then you got Christmas
coming up
and then you know so either way
the holidays are on and then New Year's
right you got the new year so you got
the holidays coming up for everybody
and there's a bunch of holidays I
haven't even mentioned that I haven't
got the chance but the point is is
there's holidays all over the world
everywhere and what happens is we end up
having like craving problems
so we end up like eating whatever we can
like Cake's cookie Donuts whatever it is
or overeating or eating things that
we're not supposed to eating so much
especially for struggling we're
chronically sick and we know we're maybe
not supposed to eat certain things
because we've learned but the craving
shifter is something that I recommend
for the holidays so that alone is
incredible in the book and the Brain
saver books is the craving shifter
I mean be the judge of that one try that
one and whoa you know
a friend of mine right now is doing that
one like on and off all day now a lot of
people have food fear
they've developed it along the way they
have food fear for a lot of reasons so
maybe Eating Disorders or food fear that
one right there is something that you
might want to try if you're a food for
your kind of you know like if you're in
that zone where you're kind of stuck
a lot of people need their energy
shifted
so it's not just about fatigue that's a
whole other thing too you could use it
for that but the point is this energy
shifter that's a great one too so it
says at the midpoint of a long day when
you're desperate for an energy boost you
know that like long name it's hitting
you or when you feel unbalanced as if
you don't have enough energy the energy
shifter is good for that if you're
feeling that your energy is off
then you're not on point right or
someone says something to you and you're
like why are you like you are right now
like what's going on are you okay are
you okay do the energy shifter if you
feel like you have too much energy and
you're hoping to calm down and you know
kind of like de-escalate right so
there's that thing too where you're just
like the the energy is like going going
but then you're gonna burn out so you
might want the energy shifter so you can
like burn it just right so you don't
just blow all your energy in one shot
if you're removing caffeine from your
life do the energy shifter so that's one
right there so if you're trying to get
rid of the caffeine trying to break the
coffee addiction you're trying to break
the cacao addiction the chocolate
addiction
when you want to wind down at the end of
the day so you can recalibrate because
you come home or you're it's the end of
the day and you're already home but
you're feeling really weird so it's the
end of the day you feel kind of like
confused or lost or you're not kind of
feeling quite right or your Energy's low
at the end of the day you want to
recalibrate before the night moves on
that's another time to use it
the energy shifter is also ideal for
overreactive or under reactive adrenals
so if you got some like overreacting
adrenals under reacting you know
adrenals sorry
got a lot of words going on in my brain
and mouth right here and
so low blood sugar that's another one
too hypoglycemia Sensations such as
edginess exhaustion feeling emotional
for unexplained reasons or you're
getting triggered really easily so check
that out so the energy shift is great if
you're feeling like you're getting
triggered
like easily triggered like you're just
like oh my God I can't handle this
everybody's triggering me
so that's a whole another reason to use
that
these are so great then there's the
nerve shifter so I want to talk about
the nerve shifter just for a couple of
minutes which is really powerful on its
own I don't know if you guys had a
chance to try this one
when you're feeling shaky or anxious
like have you ever felt anxious or shaky
so it's not just the normal anxiety
you're dealing with anxiety too but
you're shaky you're shaky you got like
the shakes If you experience random
spasms Twitches ticks are shifting and
moving pain throughout your body
like you know the random spasms and the
Twitches and the ticks and all of that
when you're struggling with any kind of
neurological onset or episode so the
nerve shifter a lot of people that
they'll have their neurological symptoms
neurological problems
maybe you know you're just you're just
in a place where you have all the stuff
going on and you want to do something
because you're getting into an episode
so there's a nerve episode coming on and
you want to use the nerve shifter that's
a big deal right there on its own
to break a nervous feeling about the
moment you're in so if you're in this
moment you've got this nervous feeling
going on just get the nerve shifter out
the future or something that happened in
the past if you're thinking about
something that happened in the past and
it's bothering you like why did I say
that why did I say that to that person
like what was I thinking I don't know
how it even came out of my mouth but it
did get the nerve shifter out because
now you're focused on that you're really
upset you're worried about it
to calm restless leg syndrome so if
you've got restless leg syndrome if you
can't you know deal with like if you
can't deal with the restless legs
because it's getting out of control
you're having an episode you're trying
to get to sleep do the nerve shifter
and then if you're gonna take a flight
somewhere or you're taking a trip that's
another time to use the Nerf shifter too
that's incredible the nerve shifter is
also an excellent tool to use for
weddings and other events that have
great meaning to you so it's like send
out a nerve shifter before you go to
your friend's party or whatever it is
so these are really potent these are
really powerful and what you're going to
find is you're gonna like you're gonna
like some
so much that you're gonna just keep them
there but always know that there's these
other ones you can always try and then
you might be surprised like whoa that
just hit me like it did this is a big
one I talked about a little bit the
other day obsessive thoughts shifter
this is a huge one right here mind
racing thoughts you can't fall asleep
you can't rest you don't feel at peace
because the thoughts are coming in and
they keep on coming in or they're doing
this the Vicious Cycle they're just
spinning around in your head the
thoughts are moving around in your head
they're just in your brain going
swimming around or they feel like it's
painful and it's repetitive it's just
repetitive and you can't get rid of
those thoughts if you're stuck with them
could be anything and maybe somebody or
something triggered you so it became
worse and now you got those obsessive
thoughts and it's much worse and you're
struggling with it that can happen too
the obsessive thoughts shifter love it
so let me give you a couple of things
about it right here that's really
incredible because this is one of my
favorites for people because I see so
many people struggle out there
try this shot when you're trying to
break repeated painful thought patterns
resulting from a difficult situation or
hardship if you're under a hardship
stressful situations anything like that
this can help break that pattern there's
a question I want to read here
um meditation and breathing are proven
to reduce long-term nerve feelings it
would be nice if he discussed all
strategies instead of just a drink okay
so first of all
something you have to understand when
people have neurological problems
tightness in the chest
Skin's burning
they're having panic attacks
the last thing they need to be doing is
intense breathing exercises so
I'm not trying to say you're not
experienced I'm not trying to say you
don't have experience whatever it is I'm
not trying to
be judgmental or anything
but it's critical to know that people
who have asthma
people that have neurological asthma
people that have gastroparesis nerve
related
people who have trigeminal neuralgia
people that have vertigo and dizziness
people that have balance issues are you
following me because I saw that question
I wanted to read that balance issues
dizziness
vertigo
people that are struggling where they're
very weak and they're fatigued with
neurological fatigue let's keep on going
people that have numbness in their
fingers and hands
real physical neurological problems
which the Chronicles suffer from you
can't sit there and do all that intense
breathing exercise you'll end up a
possibly in the hospital with a massive
panic attack up all night because your
nerves are jacked up now
and then you'll also create too much
brain Heat
so when you read the book you'll read
about that it's not that I don't want
you to breathe if you don't want to
breathe that's not it at all and it's
not that a deep breath in a meditation
is a bad thing
but breathing exercises are for the not
so sick or the people who aren't sick
yet
that's what that's for
if you have experience with health
experience with other ones that are sick
and I have
Decades of experience here
I know for a fact through Decades of
experience tingles numbness dizziness
balance issues
asthma neurological asthma tightness in
the chest tightness in the throat
trigeminal neuralgia
gastroparesis stomach problems you can't
sit there and do all that breathing
exercise stuff you do it you're going to
be hurting
so I just want you to think before you
throw stuff out there because it sounded
like it was a little snarky like I don't
know what I'm talking about and I'm just
trying to get you to drink a drink and
you know and you're gonna teach me
something here you're gonna teach me
that why doesn't he just have all that
great breathing exercise stuff if it was
that great I'd be tooting it and tooting
it for decades for people
when you read the books you will learn
about how the balances go off when you
do the heavy heavy breathing exercises
how your oxygen levels go off the chart
and start to eat up neurons you have to
understand very important information is
in these brain books helping you and
protecting you from serious breathing
exercises when you're not feeling well
it's critical to know
I'm not anti-taking breath some breaths
in I'm not anti-breathing deeply I'm not
anti-breathing in a meditation but heavy
breathing exercises does not work with
the chronically sick with neurological
problems and in 10 years there's so many
people they're going to have
neurological problems
and they're going to learn as they try
breath work that it's going to tank them
and send them down the drain
so and I I get it I'll probably lose a
couple of followers that aren't really
sick and they don't have the
neurological problems they don't have
the true vagus nerve issues and
trigeminal nerve issues and facial nerve
issues and I get it they'll probably be
like oh he doesn't know what he's
talking about but when you get sick
someday really sick and you got
neurological symptoms mark my words here
you'll be picking up the brain saver
book and you'll be reading it and being
like why didn't I know this five years
ago and why did I think I knew
everything
foreign
I'm going to read you a little section
right here on page 84. let me see it's
84. I think it's in the brain saber book
so I want to read a little something for
you so let me go to page 84.
maybe 484 let's go let's go I think it's
in here
and it is
so if you got a second the person who
was complaining that there's not enough
breath work in the books there's only
life-saving information in the medical
medium books that have saved people's
lives
okay
taking care with breath work get ready I
want to read a little something here
so let me just find it here
okay
here's what an imbalance of electrical
brain supplies in the bloodstream looks
like in practice
I'll just go one more time you ready
this is Advanced information
the person who was throwing the breath
work at me can you follow along
here's what an imbalance of electrical
brain supplies in the bloodstream looks
like in practice
in the bloodstream
ready if someone already has crippling
anxiety
and they're not eating an even close to
the balance of foods and liquids they
need to keep their glucose and water
levels high in the bloodstream
you following me with that and then they
go through some type of emotional
turmoil
their adrenaline will be elevated
get this
their glucose in water will be reduced
and their breathing will be increased
fondly
driving in more oxygen to the brain
heightened oxygen and heightened
adrenaline creating elevated heat on the
brain's electrical grid without glucose
and water to suppress the heat can even
lead to hyperventilation in some
situations it's why people who do breath
work who have neurological problems end
up in a big problem a massive big
problem I hope the person with the
breath won't work uh Judgment at me is
still listening and if they're not I
don't know what to tell you maybe you
know maybe you'll just leave because
it's all free because we do everything
free so it's probably not valuable
okay
so let's go into this height and oxygen
and heightened adrenaline creating
elevated heat on the brain's electrical
grid without glucose and water to
suppress the heat can even lead to
hyperventilation in some situations the
electrical Sparks check this out
the electrical Sparks on the grid run
hotter and more sporadically and can
even go Rogue with brain electricity
becoming Reckless the electrical grid
becomes extra hot and travels to places
it's not supposed to travel in the brain
for what is occurring in the person's
life this can take a person to the level
of being completely overwhelmed push
them into a panic attack or shut them
down so they're less responsive lying
curled up in bed feeling wrecked I'm
trying to talk about what happens with
breath work where literally it can throw
somebody into a horrible panic attack
I'm giving you the actual medical medium
science into how that can happen that's
so farther ex that's so far Advanced
past science and past anybody who's into
breath work
I always told you guys I'm not smart I'm
just a messenger with this Advanced
information
the balances get off when someone
doesn't have enough electrolytes and
glucose in their brain so the balance
goes off and they don't have enough
water electrolyte and glucose in the
brain and that's what happens people
with chronic that are chronically ill
don't have enough of that in them and
people who aren't chronically ill don't
have enough of that in them either
taking care with breath work so let's
walk down that aisle a little bit if you
guys got a second we're often taught to
use breath work to help regulate
emotions deep breathing and breath work
certain types of it
do have some value I'm not negating
breathing I'm not saying breathing's bad
I'm not saying you can't do a little
breath work
but at the same time breath work is not
what people think it is
what people don't realize is that there
is such a thing as too much oxygen
uh-huh
even though we're in a world lacking
oxygen
we're also in a world where people are
lacking what they need in their diet if
you're not keeping a balance with other
brain supplies such as glucose Trace
mineral salts and water then driving up
oxygen to your brain heats up your
electrical grid and that can be
traumatizing to the brain and body on
top of which people are often doing
breath work while also consuming
caffeine which dries up adrenaline
putting their brain and bloodstream
further out of balance what I'm trying
to say this is really like incredible
information here
is that
it's Advanced information if you don't
have what your brain needs
and you're chronically sick and you're
sitting there trying to drive an oxygen
to the brain through breath work
the nerves can't handle it the brain
heats up and the nerves can handle it
throws you into panic attacks throws you
into anxiety makes the skin burn worse
can cause a lot of Tremors ticks and
spasms everywhere
It's Like Oxygen to a fire
and you don't want the fire burning that
hot while you're doing your breath work
especially if you're suffering with any
kind of symptom or condition
ready if you guys got a second like many
Trends in health breath work is a tool
for the not so sick did you hear that
like many Trends in health breath work
is a tool for the not so sick
if symptoms haven't sidelined you in
life that means you're not so sick yet
you're just not so sick if symptoms
haven't sidelined you in life you can
bring breath work in and have fun with
it I'm not and tie it to the point where
I'm anti-it if you if you haven't been
sick yet
and you want to play with it be my guest
you can bring breath work in and have
fun with it if you're really sick or
struggling and here's a key fact and
that person is one size fits all I hate
to say it but everybody seems to be the
one size fits all out there
it's really sad because we got a whole
bunch of people on here watching this
that aren't one size fits all they're
sick their problems aren't one size fits
all
if you're really sick or struggling
breath work isn't going to fix you
that's a fact
if you're really sick and struggling and
you've got bad fibromyalgia and you got
chronic fatigue syndrome and you got
mecfs and you got lupus and you got
neurological Lyme and you got 20
neurological symptoms and you're really
sick and your life has been derailed
breath work is not gonna fix you I'm
sorry but it won't
it's amazing when I see people out there
like teaching us if it's going to fix
people it doesn't breath work isn't
going to fix you breath work is really
difficult for people with anxiety and
even worsens it for most anxiety
sufferers
Heidi M says I signed up for a breath
work class webinar and realized halfway
through it was not for me thank you
Anthony and SOC Valerie I taught yoga
and breath work and had someone have a
panic attack in my class
but remember the person that was judging
me on this
was going for one size if it's all Lynn
Lynn Goss I had a breath work
practitioner come to my home and I
passed out he said it was out for over
five minutes because the brain got
intensely hot and the neurons had an
attack
this is Advanced information this is the
brain saver books this is information
isn't out there this is Advanced info no
one's ever heard of it it's going to get
stolen in poached tonight with me just
talking about it I'm sure there's
someone that's got a devious devious
heart sitting behind here watching this
free information that I'm not charging
for and they're probably watching and
they're going to go out and next thing
you know it'll be on some invited on
somebody's podcast and spreading it
around and not citing it back to Medical
medium it's a sick world I never
expected it to be that sick meaning
demented
and evil and dark I never expected that
when I was a kid I thought everybody was
going to be happy and loving and want
the info and do the right thing doesn't
work that way they'll poach it so no one
else can find their way backward to heal
breath work is really difficult for
people with anxiety and even worsens it
for most anxiety sufferers it worsens it
for anxiety sufferers stick a bunch of
people who aren't feeling well in a
breath work class and you got a whole
bunch of sick people
Holly's health I almost passed out from
it and I was crying I've seen people
damaged and injured by it that's why you
don't see me recommending breath work
out there
Allison star holy crap so true
explanation points I struggle with
anxiety and breath work it makes me feel
awful it actually hurts people more than
helps them
people who are not so sick who don't get
affected by it yet it's still hurting
them they're just not feeling the hurt
yet but they will later down the road so
the person who judged me on this I hope
they're still watching you'll see the
people there's a lot of people they're
gonna get hurt down the road by it
really great you know better you know
more than me
breath work is really difficult for
people with anxiety and even worsens it
for most anxiety suffers especially
those with sensitive vagus nerves
sensitive vagus nerves reading out a
brain saver you guys
do you know how many people have
sensitive Vegas nerves so let's go do a
breath work class and let's just make
our Vegas nerves freak out and so we end
up in the hospital overnight
causing neurological symptoms such as
tightness of the chest and remember
breath work was something that came
about over a dude that was never well
not had symptoms but not sick
neurologically
so it's like a dude thing
breath work was initially a dude thing
it was a dude thing
and then it eventually got into the yoga
community and everything else yoga
wasn't really all breath work
30 years ago yoga wasn't all about
breath work yes breath work was involved
but now they've like they're they're
mixing it now it's like breath work and
they get all these people that are just
like they can't handle it so they quit
yoga because they're confused you don't
have to do all that intense breath work
to do a little bit of yoga
breath work is not going to make lupus
neurological Lyme eczema fibromyalgia
Parkinson's or Ms go away you can bring
in simple gentle breathing whoa on Pro
breath work for a second check this out
you guys in the brain saver book
check this out
you can bring in simple gentle breathing
techniques if they feel supportive and
you're and you're also staying hydrated
and getting enough glucose electrolytes
trace minerals and macro minerals such
as magnesium and trying to stay off
caffeine if you're staying off caffeine
and you bring in trace minerals and
macro minerals and you're getting enough
glucose and electrolytes and you're
staying hydrated you can enjoy a little
bit of breath work but no one's talking
about how to do it right or how you can
do it if you're sick
the books are packed with life-saving
information and brain protecting
information
anyone who just got to health like a few
years ago and now they're an expert and
they want to try to school me get the
brain books
because you can't make this stuff up
this is complicated
critical information
comprehensive information from above
brain shot therapy is a physical tool to
assist fit the physical body
the body doesn't only survive on oxygen
so you want to be a breatharian and just
die somewhere in a desert
so oxygen is how we only survive we only
survive with oxygen
that's it so quit your quitcher than
your your tonics
quit your don't do brain shot therapy
don't do heavy metal detox cleanses
don't do celery juice don't do any kind
of supplementation just do oxygen and
just die in a desert somewhere
Michelle L none of that crap helped me
ever and you went through a lot Michelle
I've seen comments before
sunrid yes that's me my Vegas nerve
stress out with breath work and that's
what they don't understand the breath
work
the breath work trashes the vagus nerves
but don't be afraid to breathe or do
gentle breathing exercises if you want
to incorporate that into your life I
talk about it in the brain saver books
yeah but there's a difference of what is
happening here
very important
but I love being schooled
35 years of getting people better eight
books that have saved millions of lives
around the planet
but you you want to school me
people get adrenaline high from heavy
breath work and that's the next thing I
want to talk about read the books I talk
about it inside the books people go on
adrenaline highs when they do intense
breath work and they're not sick or
suffering with all kinds of problems yet
I know people that actually weren't sick
doing breath work for a few years
feeling great but then they got sick and
then they went to their old staple I'm
going to do my breath work and get
myself better but they were sick and
they didn't realize you can't mix the
both the two and they start doing their
breath work and they started doing it
all and started following all the breath
word Kings and they're doing it and they
ended up like this seizuring on the
ground wondering why and that they're
literally at the doctor's office the
next day going what's wrong with me and
the doctor's like what were you doing
it's like I was doing breath because I
wasn't the reason they were sick the
breath work just ignited the fire
you have to smother a fire
take the oxygen down
too much oxygen to a fire makes it
hotter and faster and spreads
and so what happens is when you have
electricity in your brain so let's go
into it a little bit this turned out to
be a breath work talk when you have
electricity in your brain swimming
around you got the match that's your
fire
if you don't have enough glucose in
electrolytes and hydration inside the
brain and glycogen storages inside the
brain and you want to bring in all that
oxygen but you don't have anything else
in there to keep the fire down and you
want to bring in the oxygen you're going
to blow that fire up and your Vegas
nerves are going to be spasming out
you're going to be tightness to the
chest you're going to be all whacked out
you're going to be in a bad situation
and don't you know don't if you don't
have the brain saver books
and you're sitting here judging me and
you want to throw breath work nonsense
at me like you know and and judge me on
that you don't even have these credible
books with all the life-saving medical
information and stuff you read 10 lines
in just the first chapter and it's
unbelievable how much info's in here
what people notice is Medical
medium info makes sense it's very
complex information but it makes sense
so people don't realize that medical
meme information makes so much sense all
the time so all you have to do is just
read it or be open to it
foreign
I'm not picking on anybody for schooling
me
but you gotta kind of you know know what
you're talking about if you're going to
school me
little medium information is not common
sense it's
not common sense it sense that nobody
knew
and then they learn and it makes sense
common sense is just crap out there oh
it's Common Sense oh really
and then someone you know gets hurt Oh I
thought I was doing it right
the truth hits you when you read the
brain saver books truth just hits you
it's just whoa it's there
Michelle L says it's insulting aw to you
and to us
yeah but here's how it works Michelle
that person or that per or another
person or another person you're just
gonna leave their comfort zone of not so
sick and they're gonna get sick someday
and then they're going to get the
medical medium books after they visit
their 10th neurologist and 10th
functional medicine doctor they're going
to get to the medical medium books and
you know what's going to happen they're
going to heal themselves and they're
still going to on the medical
medium name and the medical medium
Community because they're just going to
do it spitefully they're going to do it
behind the scenes and they're not going
to come clean on their mistakes and
they're just going to like take the info
and poach it for themselves heal
themselves and still tote how apple
cider vinegar did it or some collagen
did it or some charcoal did it or
something else
Kerry Rose said this happened to me my
chiropractor told me to do these big
breath work exercises I ended up
crippled in pain in my neck and
shoulders anxiety was so much worse it's
real
it's real you guys
it's real I've seen it mess people up
I've seen it mess people up for years
but it tells me that people don't have
experience with the chronic wheel then
how come I have to know all these things
it's like people don't have the
experience then when they say things
they don't have the experience with the
chronically all these years it's obvious
they got into Health who knows how many
years ago played arounds bought an eat
better diet book from some podcast
doctor and just got rid of their junk
and processed food
they already had they didn't have a lot
of exposure a lot of bugs in them and
they were like okay I got a free ride in
life right now I'm a health expert let's
go you know but it's insulting because
it's real this information of what's
Happening
laughs
yeah I can't even understand how anyone
can do that I know but they do it by the
hundreds and thousands out there
Death By A Thousand Cuts it's what they
try to do out there oh quick
just cleaning your book kind of thing
Amazon has grease on their conveyor
belts it happens every book launch every
single book release and everybody gets
their books and they see because these
beautiful white covers and stuff like
that right they see
that there's marks all over it and they
think they have a used book and then
they give me a one star review saying he
gave me a used book gave me a used book
a publisher
gave pristine books to Amazon and other
um you know other warehouses and the
conveyor belt got them dirty so I wanted
to say you can take a little dish soap
with a damp towel and clean off your
covers creative heart says a lot of
people wonder why they don't feel good
after doing breath work thanks for
explaining
look
I like explaining I like meaning like
explaining what's in here because this
is where it's all at
that's what's incredible so what I do is
I take like a handy wipe
handy wipes tend to work good too
I gotta kick me sign on my back is what
I have you guys know that
and all we you know which is terrible
anyway but s life right
boom Handi wipe cleans the grease off
wow medical medium books come out nice
and clean
quality of medical media books equality
is incredible because I don't want any
cheap stuff you guys can you leave some
reviews for the protocols book and for
brain saver just so the trolls don't get
ahead of us
and leave the illegal reviews they don't
buy the books they don't purchase them
and they leave reviews it's evil
so if you can leave some reviews if you
like the books right just doing a quick
little cleanup right here
and a reminder
that these books
were stored in a warehouse that had no
plug-in air fresheners no chemical
toxins none of that kind of stuff and
the publisher did that for me and my
people
so if you do get a book that smells and
needs to air out for a little while it's
not because of us it's because of the
scented candles in a warehouse
um somewhere else
maybe a you know whatever the the chain
that you got the store from whatever it
is
you know that's another story so I'm
just letting you know air them out but
the books are pristine and we're stored
without that chemical that's always in
those warehouses
laundry detergents and stuff like that
none of that was stored around the
medical medium books like everybody
else's books
and it was done
purposely to look out for you guys
a lot of thought goes into these
incredible books I just want you to know
a lot of thoughts go into it
um I know I do a lot of like lives and
stuff like that and a lot of I do the
podcasts and lives and I do everything
and there's no pay walls and stuff like
that I just don't want to recreate that
there's no courses there's no this and
that I know that people poached bits and
pieces from the medical medium books and
they create their own courses out there
in the world and add in all this bad
stuff it's really a sad world out there
I think people are just desperate to be
somebody
um
whatever I don't know all I'm saying is
that I'm keeping this stuff free
I hear every time I have people tell me
all the time that if you make everything
for free people think it doesn't have
value I know you guys don't believe that
but that's what I'm told anyway I'm
keeping it free like I do it's free
wherever I can
if you need to wait someday down the
road for the book to get into the
library which takes me time to get them
into a library then wait for that day
but these books are on sale right now on
amazon.com and Walmart
so that's another place right there by
the way right now Walmart's a great
place to get the books right now a
fantastic place I think the books are
they they got a great sale on the books
right now so if you want a second book
if you guys want a second or third like
a second set for other people or for
gifts
go to Walmart right now
Walmart online or whatever or go in
Walmart they got the medical mean and
brain saver books and they're reduced in
price in Walmart right now so if you
want a second set for friends for
Christmas for the holidays for anything
that you're doing for somebody's
birthday whatever if you want a second
set
the Walmart has a reduced price on the
brain saver books right now so you can
order online there too
senia says how can we consult you I
don't do consults
I don't oh look out for imposters you
guys and there's imposters
and the imposters are getting people
upset out there because they take their
money and they say terrible things and
they do terrible things so there's
imposters out there that do terrible
things and so then people go out and
they'll say they they use the imposters
use my name Anthony William the medical
medium and then they try to get a
consult with somebody they tell the
person I'm gonna fix you and the person
then does a consult with them and then
they do terrible horrible things
and then the person who's been wrong
goes online and says terrible horrible
things about me when I had nothing to do
with it and I don't do consults
so
keep an eye out for that it's really sad
it's
pretty sick Beyond actually words and
please let others know
right
so
on that note I don't know what else
there is to talk well there's tons to
talk about lots of stuff but I hope you
guys enjoy the books and you know when
you get them in your hands
just know they're living words inside
these books the energy is in these books
you can feel it
you can feel it it's there and they're
not dead books with dead words on the
pages
and that is obvious when you hold them
keep in mind though it's a lot of
information in every single line is
packed with a message
for everybody cold white spring I told
somebody they were talking to a fake
they thought it was you
yep and then when someone gets wronged
by that fake
they end up saying bad things about me
and then a whole bunch of people who are
haters go I knew he was bad exactly we
got something else on aw
look what he did he wronged this person
uh-huh
sure
anyway I love you guys
and I will see you next time look out
keep your notifications on I don't know
if that helps but keep in mind
and I will talk to you guys again just
know I care about you guys I love you
guys and I know so many of you guys are
suffering like I want you to know that I
want to say one more thing before I go
if that's okay
I know I'm busy with trying to get you
the information to show you the books
and talk about it and give you whatever
I can
but I also know you guys are struggling
many of you mattress Island you've been
through hell and back
and
I know that a lot of people don't
understand what it's like to be in your
shoes
and when you feel hopeless and you feel
like you have no answers and you're
struggling
and you've been through a lot and no one
can relate to the hurt you have in your
life and all that
just know that I think about that all
the time I wake up in the morning
thinking about that I go to bed thinking
about that for you guys and I know so
many of you struggle and it breaks my
heart it actually breaks my heart I tell
my family members how it breaks my heart
all the time and Anyway by the way we're
brain saver day three right now the
challenge brain saver challenge day
three day four is tomorrow and we're
doing the light infusion meditation
I'm gonna be a little breathing in there
if you want to but you don't have to but
the little touch of it it's not breath
work
it's an incredible meditation check the
link out in the description if you want
to sign up so there is a link I saw
somebody leave a comment saying I can't
sign up to the brain saver challenge
it's too late no it's not too late sign
up for the brain saver Challenge and be
there tomorrow for the light infusion
meditation be there for the light
infusion meditation
for sure
incredible
Courtney EMA gonna make me cry
and I will see you tomorrow here because
I am going to do another live and we'll
just talk about the brain books
it's a lot a Brain book right there
it's a lot of rain book right there
there's a lot of brain book right there
I was sitting here before I went on and
I was kind of playing with the brain
books and I was kind of like doing this
a little bit I was sitting here kind of
playing around with the brain books and
I was just like
we were getting ready to do the show and
I was just having fun with my brain
books here
where's fly on the wall these days
where is fly on the wall Michelle L
burned out brain was outstanding oh my
God you read the chapter
right burnout
incredible
um oh no you're talking about the brain
saver challenge really that's what
you're talking about yeah that was
incredible that was incredible that was
Challenge three challenge four tomorrow
is the light infusion meditation
anyway
and you guys medical meme podcast
check it out at Apple podcast
I released a new one last night was it
last night I'm trying to remember now
so much going on I'm juggling 20 billion
things Kenny says I feel a robot coming
I do too I do I do
wait a minute guys I have to I'll just
keep you guys on while I clean up
everything and put everything away put
everything I'm just gonna put everything
away while you guys are hanging out in
the kitchen because I gotta make some
dinner soon and everything and I'm just
up the brook box
worst robot ever but guess what I had to
do it love you guys greatly
I will see you tomorrow I'm going to do
the real robot tomorrow