heard it yet but it's a mind blower i
know that chemtrails blew people's minds
i know that
fruit fear did too air fresheners
scented candles episode did
but this episode eggs eaters lose all
is a mind blower blower it's an eye
opener
it's an awakener you know and the thing
is it's like and look i got nothing
against
eggs at all i don't have anything
against eggs i'm just a messenger
of what nobody wants to believe that's
the whole point
and it's fine you can still eat your
eggs that's fine but i wanted you to
hear what's going on what happened
why eggs play a role in why everybody's
sick now
that's what i talked about inside this
episode is how eggs played a role
going back to why everybody is sick
now really really important to know like
if you got
reproductive system conditions like pcos
and fibroids and
you know and aches and pains if you've
got some other kind of condition if you
have
fibromyalgia chronic fatigue syndrome
hashimoto's thyroiditis
lime just lime all of this eggs
are the reason why we have these
problems but i tell you
why and how in the episode it's
every line in this episode
is mind-blowing so it's just so you know
the link is in description so check that
out the link is in the description
make sure you check that out i see your
comments coming up um
kathy says oh my god love eggs but i
can't have them
you know it's it's really everybody
loves eggs most people love
eggs and it's really a hard episode for
me to do
but it's jam-packed so much information
in this episode
so much so much shelly says if you eat
eggs you'll stay sick it's true
shelly it's true if you really are sick
if you're someone with symptoms if
you're someone with
ms or als any kind of condition you name
it
any kind of problem yes it will keep you
sick
or chronic fatigue syndrome hashimoto's
thyroiditis
anxiety depression what kind of
condition are you dealing with
acne that's one right there what kind of
condition are you struggling with i want
to answer questions tonight too a little
bit
talk about this but eggs are the whole
reason
a big part of it of how we're sick today
i'm not saying that you're going to get
sick from eating one egg that's not
it i'm telling you about how we got here
today why we're sick why chronic illness
is so bad and if you are sick with a
symptom or condition you guys
how you want to get rid of eggs out of
your diet you want them out of your diet
you definitely do it's so important to
know
um liliana said his cheese bad too but
if this but eggs you gotta know about
eggs and everything about it
um and it's really important how it
works and wait till you guys hear this
episode
so so eggs eaters lose all
episode 5 of the medical medium podcast
so let me just tell you
medical medium podcast is that apple
podcast that's the platform the official
platform
that this podcast has launched it's the
uncensored
platform so this is an uncensored
podcast
and you you're going to want to listen
to it at apple podcast now if you don't
have an apple device
then just go to medicalmedium.com
go to the menu see podcast on the menu
and just listen to it if you have an
android or some other device
but apple podcast is the uncensored
platform for it
share share the episodes so the egg
episode
it's just when you hear this it's not
for the faint of heart i said that about
chemtrail episode
i said that about fruit fear of course
but this is not for the faint of heart
this is a shocker when you hear this
episode
about eggs a real big shot real big
shopper michelle
michelle l says eggs are the worst they
are because what happens is that they
used our eggs long ago
and i'll tell you how in the episode so
you're gonna have to hear it you're
gonna have to hear it on the episode
it's just i couldn't do it justice right
now
it's packed with information line for
line for line
so important to know okay and and i got
nothing against eggs
that's it that's the whole thing i'm
just sharing information that nobody
knows about eggs secret information that
nobody knows about eggs
it's important and i talk about like
whether if the eggs if it's like you
know organic eggs or if they're free
range or if you're raising eggs in your
backyard do your own
your own chicken shed all of that but i
talk about how viruses
do eat food and somatical medium
information how viruses do eat food
and they eat food so when we eat food
and we
are sick so if we have fibromyalgia we
have hashimoto's thyroiditis chronic
fatigue syndrome
lupus whatever we have and if we're sick
and we have
the reason why we're sick is we have
these pathogens in us that's i've always
talked about that
and but when we feed these bugs that are
inside of us
certain foods we stay sick over time our
acne comes back
that's why acne comes and goes in a lot
of people they're eating eggs in between
it's all this a detailed information is
in this
episode on how viruses eat information i
never released before really really
advanced information
groundbreaking information and you can
learn this in the episode on how
viruses eat and how how the process
works um so yeah so so important so the
information in there is is really
important so make sure
it's medical medium podcast at apple
podcast okay
and subscribe so you get notified to
each episode coming out are you guys
sick of the episodes yet
or did i give you too many episodes
because i'm just pouring them on
the description is in the link the
description is in the link okay
i mean sorry the scripts the link is in
the description of course
it's funny had that one back back yeah
um
so this is the platform that i
officially launched it on is apple
podcast because there
it's on sensor that's the one i can
guarantee that all the other platforms
whatever the platforms are i can't
guarantee that even though the minutes
may look the same
doesn't mean they're the same doesn't
mean they're the same at all so very
important to know
because little bits and pieces are taken
out it's censored the whole bit
it's really really important to know
it's why it's launched there
um allison says why do you need an
uncensored platform
because the information is shocking the
information is groundbreaking the
information
you can't get anywhere else and there's
a reason for that so wait to check it
out chemtrails episode fruit fear
episode
brain meditation have you guys done the
brain meditation
so i want to talk about that for a
minute too is the brain meditation
it's changing lives right now people's
lives are being changed
fear is getting out of their body out of
their system
they're releasing fear they're releasing
broken trust so the brain meditation
share that episode that's on the medical
medium podcast the brain meditation
people are using the fall asleep at
night
they're using the heel they're doing it
once a day try the brain meditation if
you haven't tried it yet
many of the people on here tonight have
tried the brain meditation they're doing
like once a day
um once you want to twice a day or
they're doing it every night
but the brain meditation is an important
one to do so that's in the medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast check
that out
okay the link is in the description
so check that out um did you catch
episode four
air fresheners scented candles colognes
perfumes it's incredible for chemical
sensitive people
it's called killing you smelly check
that one out
uh it's just really these episodes are
packed with information
and you know here's the cool part you
guys check this out
there's no infomercials there's no
sponsorships there's no advertisements
so none of that's there it's a free
resource without you being bombarded by
nothing but all that stuff these
episodes
in the medical meeting podcast are not
like other podcasts where it's like some
talking heads and they're talking about
collagen and matcha tea
and they're talking about the keto diet
or something and they're just but they
don't know why anybody's sick and it's
just
it's just kind of like a little talk
show and that's what usual podcasts are
in health
that's not what this is this is
groundbreaking information
line for line you never you'll never
hear this information
anywhere else and it's got healing tools
in it like the brain meditation
and then episodes that are packed with
information that's
mind-blowing shocking the only thing i
got to forewarn you got to give you a
forewarning
straight out straight out okay it's not
for the faint of heart some of these
episodes
they are shockingly scary to some degree
eye-opening awakening the whole bit so
on the uncensored platforms apple
podcast
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
check it out um
so uh fontana says i've done your brain
meditation
six times and you love it incredible i'm
so proud of you that you're doing it
that's amazing and it's really a
powerful meditation to brain meditation
because what happens is when we go
through hardships like losses
heartache betrayal broken trust when we
have hard times in our life when we have
struggles when we have all kinds of
emotional hardships of different kinds
when we go through things what happens
is we get this out of body experience
where it's not a good experience but we
get kicked out of her body our soul gets
kicked out of her body for a second
and or for a day and we're just numb
from it we get
injured from say someone broke up with
someone and say there's a
relationship problem or somebody cheated
on somebody or a
work partner something went wrong with a
work partner confrontation or
something's just so stressful
some kind of struggle some kind of
hardship you know feelings of fear and
loss and shame and guilt and
struggles inside our heart all these
things what happens is we get
disconnected because of these
experiences
and it creates a little bit of anxiety
or depression depersonalization
and our soul just gets kicked out of her
body like the crap gets kicked out of it
it just boom gets kicked out of her body
and then fear fills in and we walk
around fearful we walk around
broken trust we walk we don't trust
we're afraid to trust we're afraid to
you know whatever it is and we're all
these different things and so
the brain meditation is to repair the
damage done
because in this in the emotional center
of the brain the emotional center of the
brain these neurons they fry when you
get bad news
so when you get bad news like what what
happened
someone did what or what's going on the
emotional center of the brain just all
of a sudden gets boom like a shot of
lightning bolts go through like
electricity and then our soul just gets
kicked out for a little bit
and those those neurons get chewed up
and we end up getting post-traumatic
stress syndrome we can end up getting
ptsd
and so the brain meditation bridges the
gap it heals the neurons in the
emotional center of the brain
bridges the gap so the soul and the and
the brain connect
i mean it's really powerful you can only
experience it if you do it
um so yeah you can use both there's
messaging
with message messaging with angels does
that apply to itunes too you can use
both or is it the same as apple podcast
you could
use both and that's the uncensored
version right there
so very very good that you know about
that and know where to go
so the medical meeting podcast make sure
you check that out um
powerful episodes but the episode today
that was launched
eggs eaters lose all so important
melissa larkin says the brain meditation
is helping my lifelong insomnia
incredible and you know what when fear
is trapped in there and broken trust and
ptsd and
any kind of hurt that's somewhere deep
down inside there and a soul
that meditation helps to clear that out
and bring that out
the power of that in in you guys have to
know something
okay this is really important right here
check this out okay
meditations are man-made and there's
nothing wrong with that but they're
man-made
that's what meditations are it's like
some guy's trying one thing
he some other guy tries it in 1960 and
then another try
1970 and another guy tries it another
guy tries it and then
there's a style of meditation and then
it gets plugged into yoga then it gets
plugged into
and it's all man-made and that's all
great but but
the medical medium meditations they're
not man-made i can't make that
meditation
no one can make the brain meditation
really important to know
that you just can't make a meditation
like that it's not something you could
just
make or man-made come up with it it
doesn't work that way it came from above
so the brain meditation comes from above
that came to me when i was younger and i
coveted that brain meditation
i covered a lot of the meditations but
that when i coveted it meaning
it was just for friends it was just for
family when i was younger
and to heal their their wounds and then
i realized why don't i just
podcast this brain meditation so
millions can heal because millions have
healed from medical medium books already
with other meditations why am i not
releasing the brain meditation
and it was like a friend of mine said
why aren't you releasing this
what are you doing i'm like oh my god i
will start a podcast tomorrow
let me get working on it and figure it
out trisha says
you could never give us too many
podcasts trisha you know what's funny
is that's what i was worried about like
did i give you guys too many and
now you're just you're buried in all
these podcasts and you say i want to i
actually want to thank you for
for how much you're spoiling us with i i
could listen
listen to as much as you want to share
trisha marie thank you
you're awesome you're absolutely awesome
thanks for you know just
thanks for being there thanks for loving
the information
thanks for caring and thanks for sharing
it with others i bet you're sharing with
others
bethany denise hey bethany i trust the
mm information and that is saying
something since there are
very few other things that i trust
everything else made me sicker and
sicker and implementing the mm info is
the only
reason i'm healing you know what's
what's amazing is that
the protocols are in there you can
customize it to heal you can
you can do 32 ounces of celery juice you
can do you know
you can learn how to use the supplement
protocols you can learn how to do the
different foods in the cleanses it's
and medical medium information isn't
fruits and vegetables
it's it's not it's it's it's fruits
leafy greens
herbs wild foods vegetables and how to
use them all
as tools and so you can heal so i'm so
glad you're doing that
so proud of you donya says thank you for
the brain meditation it has been a
lifesaver for me i finally able to sleep
again
thinking anthony and spirit of
compassion the brain meditation
is from above as i was saying before
it's from above
and when you're dealing with meditations
that are from above
life changing things happen
they happen and and that's what it's
about
it's i'm just a messenger to the
information i'm the messenger to the
brain meditation
and i'm a messenger to cleanse the heal
the book medical means cleansing heel
that you see over here i'm a messenger
to that book over here behind me
which is saving lives right now um which
you can get free at the library it's
also
on sale 51 off at amazon.com in the us
it's got a killer sale on that book
right now and
but it's you know it was which makes it
affordable but you could also get it
free at the library
the point is is that it's about making
sure you guys have the healing tools
and i wanted this podcast to be
something that
you just we're getting so much
information and
so much healing information and there's
so many episodes to come
different conditions different symptoms
i got a surprise for you this week
okay so big surprise okay so eggs is out
today
eggs eat or lose all eaters lose all
okay
it's just really an unbelievable episode
wait do you hear
it i know trisha heard it she listened
to it i know a bunch of guys listen to
it already
right um francis the chemtrails are
scary
that episode is scary if you're if
you're if somebody
you know is a faint of heart you might
not want to listen i know you can handle
it
francis but that's a really intense
intense episode
um ken says hey ken ken spirali says the
brain meditation is simple but
incredibly effective thank you for
sharing
it really is powerful and effective it
really is it's changing lives out there
um so i'm glad you guys are sharing too
because i hope you guys share
and post about it so people can hear
about it post about it and
leave a review at apple podcast if you
can please because then you'll
then you'll override the trolls you know
with the fake stories and the trolls
that just don't want
don't want this information out there
where they're just they're just whatever
they are this you know so then you'll
override the trolls because you'll be
helping the support
it's important um trisha said it wept
last night during my brain meditation
it's
really does pull those old wounds out
and
gets them out of the body um
helene says where's the brain meditation
brain meditation check out
check out the uh the link is in the
description
so just so you know the link is in the
description it's the medical medium
podcast
the link is in the description it's at
apple podcast just so you know
now if you don't have an apple device
then just go to medicalmedium.com go to
the menu
see podcasts in the menu and just listen
to it just listen to it
it's a free resource you guys it's free
no
advertising no sponsorships uh no
infomercials um there isn't just talking
heads on there talking about whatever
like a talk show a health talk show 24 7
with nothing that gets anybody to really
move forward
um it's packed with information it's
made for you guys
uh i did everything i could to make this
work i'm not sponsored
it's so important to know um
michelle says celery juice is killing
off pathogens
absolutely that's what it does it breaks
the membrane down on the pathogen
that's why so many people are healing
around the world um
so proud of all you guys i really am
ichota
she's there tonight my son my husband
and i have been doing the brain
meditation every night together
and oh also do it when you wake up
on my own 10 10 i really highly
recommend
10 out of 10. incredible thanks each
other for doing the meditation
and look it's free the medical medium
podcast is free it's a free resource if
you're you know if you're using an
android
it's free resource but but here's the
thing remember this
uh gemma this is important gemma it's
censored on any other platform
unless it's on apple podcast so apple
podcast it's uncensored
so if you're listening to it on another
pod on another platform
that's going to be censored it's going
to be having little tidbits missing
without you knowing or it's not going to
upload right
and piece is missing or whatever i can't
guarantee if the apple podcast
is the platform that's uncensored for
this medical medium podcast
if you don't have an apple device just
go to medicalmeeting.com
look at the menu see a podcast in the
menu and just listen to it if you don't
have an apple device so what it's all
free
um ryan france episode was so good
aw the more info the better the more
reasons to stay away from eggs
also finally experiencing deep sleep
since listening to the brain meditation
every night
share the brain meditation post about it
you guys so it can get out there
and just so you know when you post about
it and you share the brain meditation
and share these episodes it's not going
to do anything for me because i don't
have advertisements
i don't have uh sponsorships with it i
don't have
infomercials in it so you're not going
to be making me any dollars
share it to help people heal that's the
whole point it's a free resource
with no one with no none of that
advertised ads in there
so you can literally help people heal
and get it out there
share it for me so we can help others i
mean what else are we gonna do
right are we trying to help people
that's the whole thing
and but yeah um ashley says love the
brain meditation
the brain meditation really is a mind
blower and it works
just as powerful every time you do it
and only does more for you over time and
over time and over time
um so omar says how do you heal acne one
more
did you check out cleans the heel can
you get a copy wherever you are in the
world can you find a copy
um cleanse the heel the book depository
overseas out there uh you know
you can try to if you can get the book
there
if you're in the u.s get at amazon 51
off right now
um thelma says i'm loving your brain
meditation thank you for sharing most
days morning and night you're doing it
most days morning and night
incredible incredible tammy says bless
you
in spirit for helping us the day after i
listened to the brain meditation i felt
happier
i shared it in ca in case others could
benefit
thank you tammy thank you thank you for
sharing it thank you
sharing it with people telling them to
hit the link so they can
find tell them where to find the link
the link is in description
tammy just you know share it wherever
you can or send them the link or
something
thank you incredible so important um
make sure you subscribe to medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast so
you're the first to get the notification
when each episode comes out
i was ecstatic i was so excited
when the egg episode went live
so excited i don't even know what to say
if you guys
heard that episode uh michelle said i
tried brain meditation for the first
time and i cried reuniting with my soul
that's what it does you're bridging the
gap
healing the wounds your your soul comes
back
and it's just boom it just happens a
homer i love all your podcasts so much
hey thanks thanks thanks man i really
appreciate it love all your podcasts so
much brain meditation especially thank
you for doing the brain meditation
thank you can you please do an episode
on hiv i will eventually
i will uh i will i will because it's
important
very important um pressing prince how
you doing tonight
never really done meditations before
until now your brain meditation has
become a daily ritual for me
morning and night amazing can't believe
how much it's
how much um can't believe how powerful
it actually is you're a truly gem
amazing human thanks for so much for
everything you do keep them coming i'm
going to keep the episodes coming that's
the whole point
you know and that's what i want to do um
i want to make sure they keep on coming
coming so you guys you guys
have that information so
hey hello hello hello everybody so look
the egg episode have you heard it it's
packed with information even if you love
eggs
you want to listen