many of you are aware of the massive
fires that are happening right now out
there and so many people are breathing
in a lot of smoke I have family that's
calling me and they're saying what do I
do how do I deal with this so I got a
couple of tips one I'm going to show you
in a little bit with is water and a
cloth
the other is immune system and
antioxidant support and I'll tell you
why because what's in the air is a
massive trigger for a lot of people with
chronic illness that's my main concern
people who are struggling with different
health conditions autoimmune other types
of health conditions they can be
triggered easier than other people
overall everybody should be concerned
about breathing in too much smoke but
it's not just the smoke itself like if
you had a fire pit going or if you were
breathing in some wood that was burning
the smoke has chemicals in it because
they're using fire retardants to
actually Calm the Fire down or try to
Die the fire out so they're dumping a
lot of chemicals on the fire it becomes
dust those particles float around and
travel hundreds and hundreds thousands
of vials so I just want to cover a few
critical tips to start with right here
glutathione
that's one right there I endorse of
energy that's the products I use it's
the products I recommend my friends and
family glutathione right there
detoxification you gotta remember that
whenever you see glutathione it's
detoxification so it helps the body
naturally
detoxify and what happens is when you're
breathing in smoke filled with chemicals
and you're getting that inside your
lungs inside your body it has to go
somewhere it can't just sit inside the
body we want to get it out eventually so
that's glutathione right there it also
supports your immune system glutathione
as well so that's the best one I've ever
seen right there because of energy and
the four things they do with their
purity which is incredible anyway micro
C
so vitamin C that's another one right
there the energy micro C is an
incredible antioxidant too so these are
the ones I'm taking right now and I'm
telling family and friends so let's move
on to another one there's the propolis
which is immune system now if you're
wondering why immune system like why is
he talking about immune system because
chemicals and smoke in the air lowers
our immune system it's a trigger and
when it triggers us and triggers our
immune system then we're open to other
problems and so many people have healed
so many problems out there and so many
people have they're struggling with
their health and so when we're dealing
with triggers we're dealing with
possible Avalanches with our health so
these are things that are critical and
this is what I'm telling friends and
family
propolis is another one that's the
immune system right there zinc that's
the immune system as well B12 that's for
your cells overall and that's what your
cells the thing is what happens with B12
it supports a lot of different parts of
the body like every part of the body so
when you're dealing with smoke
inhalation toxins in the air it's also a
critical thing too so let's go into this
part here what you see is a bowl of
water
now if you're going from your house to
your car a lot of people are traveling a
lot of people are on the road they may
not be able to get some things they need
because the time of year so what you're
seeing right here is a quick easy tip
which I really love so what I'm doing
here so I just have a simple bowl of
water I have a cloth right here now this
is a dish cloth a dish towel I'm
squeezing out excess water but I'm
leaving the towel damp now if you have
to be outside for some reason in this
smoke you have to leave the house you
have to go from your house to your car
what you want to do is take a a damp
cloth like this that you just squeeze
the water out and you want to make like
a cup
and you take your hands like this see
and you give yourself enough space you
don't want it like this where your hands
are just really close like that you want
to give yourself enough space so there's
air
inside of here so you have a gap and
then you take that and you put this over
your mouth like this over your face like
this and you breathe and what you're
doing is it's not about whoa that's not
as good as a mask or is that is a mask
better is it not that's not what this is
about because you can't soak a mask so
that's one thing right there they just
it doesn't really work you have to take
a cloth like this get it wet you know do
this like I said before get it in there
nice and
you don't want it dry in one part and
that's a mistake that can happen where
you only have it moist in one area
dry in another you you don't want to do
it that way you want to have the entire
cloth wet
not sopping wet where it's dripping all
over you but you want it wet so I'm just
going to squeeze it out a little bit
more
there we go you're trapping some of the
smoke within it but the key is you're
trapping chemicals dust particles dust
that's being dropped onto the fire so
the helicopters and the planes are
dropping all that fire retardant onto
the flames and so that dust those
particles are what's in the air it makes
it more difficult for people to breathe
it gives people more complications it's
a bigger trigger so if you're outside if
you have to travel if you have to go to
your car this is a simple easy way to do
it now don't get too wrapped up with
what kind of cloth if you have a dish
towel a washcloth if you have anything
like that and you take it you put it
right up to your face and you make a
really nice
Wide Cup and you can breathe through
that towel right there and you're
breathing air and that air has all the
dust particles chemical particles and it
gets trapped easily within the moisture
of the cloth now that's really effective
I'm not saying that is like
the end-all to what you're doing like
that's going to fix it all you're still
going to get some smoke in there you're
still going to get some particles in
there it's not something you want to use
and go up to a fire with nothing like
that this is just a quick tip from
dealing with running from your house to
your car dealing with being out there
trapped in it maybe you're at a family
event and you're Outdoors anything like
that and you can just you know get a
dish towel or a washcloth and do that
it's helpful it helps to to minimize
that smoke and those chemicals and the
particles and the Dust
and then once again important critical
supplement like the glutathione which is
a big one so right now I'm telling
family and friends glutathione that's a
big one right there and the micro C the
antioxidants immune system immune system
the immune system all the cells in your
body so and if you can only get a few of
these if you only have an opportunity to
get three of them I would get the micro
C the glutathione I would probably get
those two and maybe the propolis but all
of them are important and it's the
quality of these you guys know I endorse
these guys for a reason because it's the
best stuff out there I've talked about
the four reasons why there's nothing in
these supplements that shouldn't be in
there and other supplements and
supplement companies they deal with
there's a there's always things in
people's supplements that they don't
know about because legally you're
allowed to have a certain percentage of
ingredients that you don't disclose to
the the actual consumer dimmers you
won't do that it's actually the purest I
can find out there but anyway you guys
just a couple of tips right here for so
many of you that are dealing with this
issue that's happening right now I'm so
sorry if you are dealing with this so
sorry if you're actually in a place
right now where the smoke is thick and
it's in the air and you're having a hard
time with it my heart pours out to you
truly because I know that this is a
difficult situation and when our air
gets poisoned and problematic that is
really hard for so many people and it's
a trigger and I want to support any way
possible just know I care about you guys
hang in there if you're going through
any of this and
bye