strong i'm cooking
healing broth which i'm excited about i
got the water on right now
got my time right here because guess
what everybody is coughing their brains
out right now everybody out there i mean
if it hasn't hit you yet or hit your
area yet just you know i mean i don't
know what to say but it's like it's
everybody's getting the sniffles the
coughs and all that the fever everything
else so
the stuff is running through everybody
it's everywhere so what do we do to stay
strong because what happens is that
it's the bugs that go around
knock
everyone's immune system down
and then
you can't get back off the ground
because something else inside of you
is creeping up even if you don't hear it
because it makes no sense you know the
funny thing is is that
people walk around people walk right now
it's no big deal it's good good you can
get over a cold get over a cold whatever
but for a lot of people it knocks them
down
so then something else creeps up like
epstein barr and shingles and all these
other things and they're fever blisters
and also now they got neurological
fatigue and everything because the body
just it's just getting slammed slammed
by all the stuff going around so how do
we stay strong good to see you guys
glad you guys are coming on right now
making healing broth
talking about also how to keep ourselves
strong which is really important right
right there i'm telling everybody it's
like
vitamin c vitamin c it's just like a
broken record any friend that contacts
me i got a cough i got the sniffles i
got whatever how much vitamin c are you
doing it's critical how much making the
healing broth if you guys just came on
here so i'm going to cut up an onion in
a second and make some food
so i'm excited about that michelle else
is slammed i know right that's what
happens it's it's going on out there so
everybody's like oh no no it'll make me
stronger it'll make me stronger that
next cold will make me stronger the next
flu will make me stronger
uh no
no
unless you're doing something to take
care of yourself protect yourself unless
you're doing something because it
doesn't necessarily make you stronger it
beats you down
and now you're like dragging or six
months later now all of a sudden you're
like why am i having these other
problems like what's going on it's
chipping away
at your
strength chipping away at the strength
so you want to be on this stuff
you want to be on
what you don't want to be doing things
like the healing broth is like that
that's running
all the time like i have that running
all the time like every other day making
healing broth
because i just want it on hand so it's
like even if i don't consume it even if
i don't consume it because things are
going crazy i put it in the fridge
and then i reheat it or something but
the healing broth is a great thing to
have right now especially if you're
feeling like
wait a minute
and is that a sore throat i'm losing my
taste and smell
wait a minute i can't taste anything i
can't smell anything and i got the sore
throat and
got a cough coming on all of that so how
do we stay strong you guys so we're not
getting kicked down kick down that
rabbit hole you can get kicked down that
rabbit hole really far really far
really far the flu's come every two
months there's a new flu every two
months there's a new flu call it what
you want
call it what you want
you know what i'm talking about every
two months there's a new flu
that's what it is basically right one
coming out of the running gate
and just you know just when you thought
you're recovering you're doing okay okay
no big deal with that one you get
slammed again boom another one
right
so how do we protect ourselves keep
ourselves strong during all this so
important to know
healing broth let's just get that going
right now wait before i go into the
healing broth
you guys it's january it's a new year
happy new year
and
morning cleanse challenge coming up
look out you know sign up to my
newsletter just so you know
medicalmedium.com sign up to my
newsletter so you know when it is
but we're going to be doing the medical
media morning cleanse challenge make
sure you have a cleanse the heel book if
you don't have a clean skill book pick
one up get one free at the library it's
a medical textbook
it's got the morning cleanse in here you
want to have the book on hand if you've
never had the book before pick it up
it's 51 off amazon.com us so that's
incredible it's 16.99
so
you can get that there 75 recipes
200 symptoms conditions all the
different protocols
and it's got the cold and flu
protocols
that means
the cold and flu protocols the things
that we're dealing with right now right
call it what you want as i was saying
before call what you want if you want to
call it something you call it what you
want right whether it's the bug going
around hey whatever that bug is going
around
you got the protocols in here for the
bug that's going around
okay so
but that medical medium morning cleanse
challenge is coming up
but every time a friend's calling me
like i'm sick
i got hit with it i'm in bed how much
vitamin c are you doing how much
how much z i n c are you doing like how
much
do you what you don't have
you don't have zinc
it's like too bad
too bad because it would be really great
if you had the zeons that's what i tell
my friends if you had the zinc
right
so these things are important do you
have the olive leaf right there you have
the olive leaf have that on hand what do
you have do you have the best elderberry
syrup i've ever seen
come today like there's nothing else on
the forefront that can touch the
elderberry syrup this this one right
here the vimergy one this is vermicy
supplements i'm not sponsored
very important to know not sponsored but
the stuff is that good so this is the
elderberry syrup like when you're coming
down with something
not even coming down with something
if you're exposed
or you're just yeah around people
what i tell my family
is you do a tablespoon of elderberry
syrup every single day right now in this
day and age when the world is freaking
out and the bugs are going around
that's what you do even if it's two
teaspoons or a teaspoon of the
elderberry syrup right now it's so
important to know like it's an important
time for it that's juiced elderberry
there's no product on the planet that
can touch this like when i look at other
elderberry syrups now it's garbage
that's how superseded like this is
superseded any elderberry syrup i've
ever seen anyhow anywhere
it's just unbelievable
and so when i look at other elderberry
syrups i'm like oh yeah that's right
that's the old way of doing things um
that's just
a dried elderberry basically and then a
whole bunch of cane sugar in there
low quality everything citric acid and
everything else in there oh that's the
old way
you know this is the new way right here
no one's ever done it before that's the
most powerful way right what's the name
of the elderberry syrup it's vimergy v
is in victor i m as
and i'm making the healing broth
so i got the water heating up so let's
chop some stuff up let's get an onion in
here
onions and garlic baby
onions and garlic
get the onions and garlic in you really
important right there
medicinal medicine
onions and garlic
is medicine right
you need every edge you can get
i'm using whatever ingredients i have on
hand right now you guys
right
so i don't have all the perfect
ingredients for
medical medium healing broth right
but i have close enough
and if that's happening in your house
and look all you have is certain things
then then use it do it i'm getting the
onion in there that's first off
let's get that going in there
right
onion and garlic is the critical
component when you're doing healing
broth
i know that everybody loves your chicken
soup i'm not ranking on chicken soup
it's just that the fat
from the chicken
stops your immune
system
you know from doing its job
the reason why chicken soup
is something that went down in history
as being helpful for bugs going around
is because it takes people off of
sausage
bacon
ham
pizza
lots of cheese
it takes them off of all that
so they end up getting sick with the flu
or cold and they find that they eat some
chicken broth which is lighter than how
they've been eating for probably years
and that's why people got like a bump up
from having chicken broth i'm not i'm
not harping on it that's something you
do
no disrespect i'm not judging anybody
that's not it i'm showing you guys a
different way
your white blood cells
cannot easily clobber
the bug you're fighting when there's fat
in the bloodstream
bottom line
so when you're doing chicken soup you
got all that chicken fat
in the soup the chicken fat gets into
your bloodstream and your immune system
struggles yes it's better than your
normal standard fare whatever you're
doing processed foods fast food
restaurants pizzas whatever it is and
then you get sick and now you're eating
chicken soup and it gives your body a
little bit more of an edge to heal
because it is lighter than what someone
else might be already eating every day
because first of all they get sick with
food they're coughing they got no
appetite for a while they go a day
without really eating much of anything
maybe a dry piece of toast
and then they have some chicken soup
it's the first time someone stopped
eating the usual fare they usually eat
for a long time so they get an edge
but that's not enough especially with
the bugs going around today the bugs
going around today you guys gotta have
more of an edge you don't want fat in
the soup so just like chicken soup has a
fat in it if i put oil in this healing
broth i'm doing the same thing as if
someone was having chicken soup
how can you
give your immune system the strength it
needs when you got fat in the way
stopping your white blood cells
from going after the bugs
and that's what happens all the fat in
your bloodstream it's like becomes a big
smokescreen
and that's what goes wrong right
so i got some
onion in there let's get some garlic in
there now
best thing you can do
when you're sick with what's happening
right now stay off of the avocado the
oils the nuts the seeds if you're vegan
stay off of the animal products if
you're animal protein if you're sick
you're coughing you've got congestion in
your lungs and chest stay off of it keep
the fats out of there
jeanette says chicken soup without the
chicken is my new soup incredible
incredible
so what i'm doing is i'm peeling some
garlic back because
this is what we're doing you love garlic
bobby
yeah i do too love garlic
now if you're if you're not a fan of
garlic
you can keep it out
you can but it's really important to
have it in there so if you can tolerate
it on any level
try to keep it in that's what i would
say
try to keep it
ren says i got your juicer for xmas gift
amazing
i'm so happy for you i really am that's
so great right i'm using a whole bulb of
garlic pretty much
you can do two bulbs of garlic you feel
something coming on
do more than
a bulb of garlic do too
you guys just came on here
we're doing the medical medium morning
cleanse challenge it's coming up i think
it's in a week or so like it's coming up
maybe a week
so i'm just giving the four warnings
it's free
the medical media morning challenge is
free make sure you have the book go to
the library and get the book for free
with that or go to amazon.com 51 off
we're doing the morning cleanse
challenge it's a new year let's get
healthy let's get strong
let's build ourselves back up
go to medicalmeme.com sign up for my
newsletter so you know where i'm at like
where the challenge is going to be where
everything's at
so i'm just throwing this garlic right
in here you don't even have to
you don't even have to uh
you know cut it up you don't have to
chop it up you can just
pop it right out
if you see me hammering on this knife
right i just said this earlier too if
you see me hammering on this knife
don't do it
don't do it if you hammer on a knife
like this
the blade can't be angled to the inside
so the blade the sharp part of the blade
can't be angled to you so you can't put
it down like that
and hammer it
see with the blade pointing to me you
don't want to do that here's what
happens you ready
you have it's easy to flip up this way
and go right on the knife i've seen
people do it okay
you want to have it flipped outward you
want the sharp part going out
going outward and then you put it down
the knife doesn't flip easier up like
that it doesn't it actually the weight
of the knife does keep it down for some
reason so you want to do
it's the safest way to go
if you're popping like
the skins off the garlic
if you guys just came out you'll put
more in your broth amazing
you guys
cold white spring sauna rumble he chodes
on rubble
right
daisy power house is on rumble aware is
on a rumble
kaylee girl is on rumble
g delicious is on rumble
gee delarius is on rumble
we're getting some garlic in here
we're live on youtube probably got a few
people on there right now we're live on
facebook live on tick tock got a few
people on there too and telegram don't
forget telegram
melton says she loves the healing broth
incredible
so you want to keep the oil you want to
keep
the fat out of the healing broth you
want it fat free
overt fat free radical fat free you
don't want anything in there
that's an overt fat
you're not going to be able to recover
fast enough when you get hit with the
bug going around all right we got some
garlic in there which is great
give my hand a little rinse
so let's put some other things in here
we can put anything in here i got some
carrots why not pop some carrots in
there right miss that one
try there we go
oh go
all right
one more time
oh
i don't know
so we're gonna pop some carrots in there
you can chop them up
a little bigger if you want remember
this is the healing broth
you don't have to eat the vegetables if
you want to eat some of the vegetables
and you're really hungry then eat some
of the vegetables that's okay
so i'm doing some chopping right here
you guys
if you guys just came on you might want
to sign up to my newsletter so you know
what's going on
i give out a lot of information that way
i'm doing the healing broth because
everybody's sick
everybody
is sick
it's insane actually
and in two months
or another month
it's gonna be like that all over again
a new bug
every
other month
so with that
the healing broth is incredible because
what it does it helps as an expectorant
it gets mucus out of the chest
it gets that phytochemical compounds
from the garlic and onion in the sinuses
right
it's got antiviral compounds
really important
so you want to have
a good healing broth going on
you really do
really important
i'm going to throw some time in here i'm
going to do some time water too but i'm
throwing time in here
look at this i don't know if you guys
can see this
medicine
hey man this is medicine
uh huh
can i roll this into a paper
it's time
this is like
this stuff is this is the real
the real stuff
incredible it's good stuff
love it all right i'm putting a little
bit more in there
time is so good for you
let's get some ginger in here
there we go
keep the skins on
and just do this right here just cut it
up
put a put a decent amount of ginger in
there if you don't like ginger just get
some in there then
just get some in there
awesome
that's fresh thyme claudia that's fresh
time indeed that's what it is
let's put some potato in here you can do
some potato in your healing broth
you definitely could there's nothing
wrong with that this is a beautiful red
potato it's not a sweet potato it's red
potato let's get that in the healing
broth that's awesome it's a great thing
to get in there
guess what
potatoes are high in lysine
they're anti-viral against the fever
blister against the ebv
against cytomegalovirus
against all the different bugs right
potatoes are anti-viral and yeah and the
bugs that are going around right now and
the flu and cold bugs or whatever you
want to name it
is
really afraid
of potato
potatoes a great weapon against it i'm
going to throw red bell pepper in here
you guys
you don't mind
let's get a red bell pepper in
pop that in we're making the healing
broth we're going to make some time
water
we're going to talk about powerful
supplementation that's critical right
now
i mean when you have the medical medium
z-i and c-shock therapy
available
when you start getting sick
it's like one of those
one of those protection methods that's
so amazing
it's there to cut it down in half if
someone was going to get real sick
they're going to get less sick maybe you
can even forward it all together okay
let's get the red bell pepper in there
so let's talk about z-shock therapy
so anybody wants to know what z-shock
therapy is right there it is
so that's the vimer g1
it's a liquid zinc sulfate right there
okay it's the only stable
z
on the market
the other z's are not stable so right
now when people say oh yeah okay i'll go
get z
okay well you're only going to probably
get a fraction
of
of what can help you compare to what you
can get out of the right product right
if we came on here i'm not sponsored by
vimergy i know them
i've become friends with them
um over the years just like i've become
friends with probably
many many other
supplement company people because i want
to make sure they can offer things and i
could put like a little bug in there
like hey can you keep out the natural
flavors so you don't poison my people
hey can you keep out the citric acid so
you don't poison my people
can you keep out the fillers that nobody
knows about that are hidden in every
supplement company and nobody realizes
it so i try to make friends with
everybody that's what i've done for
20 plus years
and and any company that has even a
partial quality product i want to know
them
i want to meet up
i want to see how they do it
because if i'm going to recommend
something to my people or my family my
friends or whatever i want to know it's
incredible
and that's the vimorgy product right
there
so
z shock therapy right
is what i've used all these years i've
learned that from spirit of compassion
where you can head off
stave off that cold or that flu bug you
can stave it off you can head it off the
path right
head it off at the pass right
and that's that's what i love about z
shock therapy so z shock therapy is
every three hours
two dropper pulls
two dropper fulls
every three hours waking hours veronica
samara says mmm i'm the only one not
sick at home from the bug dot dot
following flu and cold protocols lemon
water and celery juice incredible
incredible
and and then you still have z-shock
therapy too if you need it right
two dropper fulls
every three hours
this is cooking up right here you guys
and you can put in a little bit of water
that's all you put in a little bit of
water like a shot glass let me go get a
shot glass you could put it in there and
add a little bit of water to it and then
you've got yourself the z-shock therapy
right
you do it for a couple of days if you're
really sick if you're coming down with
something you do it for two or three
days
and you get ahead of it
that's a weapon man that's a weapon i
can't tell you
if i had a feather for any every time a
feather every time
someone said aw that saved my life
aw
i was half as sick as i would have been
aw i never even got sick aw my sore
throat went away aw i caught it in time
and i did that z shock therapy if i had
a feather
i'd be flying i wouldn't have to i
wouldn't have to book plane tickets
i just literally
just grab my
million feathers stick them on me and
try to fly
you know so jacqueline says i love how
tolerable the vimergy zinc is on the
stomach it's the only one that i know
people with sensitive stomachs can
tolerate so that's the other thing
because it's stabilized right
unstabilizing
which is all the other companies right
now unfortunately i don't know why
people can't get it right out there
but it's unstabilized and then they they
have to use terrible things like citric
acid or whatever in there right
and and it just burns a hole in your
stomach so when people get sick
from z
they're just like they're just do they
feel like they're getting a hole burned
in your stomach right
and like i said if i mean seriously
so many people with with
the z shock therapy what it's done
zinc shock vitamin c and goldenseal have
saved me
cindy says
incredible right
so that's an important thing right now
and look
stomach flu is on its way that one's
going to come through this winter
on top of all the other stuff that's
happening
right and these bugs are
virulent
they're just that's just the way they
are and it's about taking control having
some empowerment empowering yourself be
like you know what
i'm going to have this on hand i'm going
to have the ingredients on hand when i
need it or go go out and get what i need
if something's happening i'm going to
have the healing broth i'm going to have
the time water i'm going to have the
time t i'm going to have lots of oranges
on hand right lots of oranges all that
incredible vitamin c
all that matters too right
you want your oranges on hand lots of
those
because what you can do
is you can make yourself some fresh
squeezed orange juice
how about that for your white blood
cells that's incredible right there
right
and you always keep some thyme in stock
maybe grow it someday too in a pot right
outside your porch or your window or on
your windowsill something like that but
having lots of time is really important
having ginger on hand for ginger tea
that's another one all on its own
right
so
so having ginger tea on its own that's a
great one you got your ginger
so let's talk about time water for a
minute
you ready
i put water
in this jug
right
and then
i take this time
then i drop it in
someone told me the other day it's too
hard to do all this stuff
that's what they said it's too hard
you said hey i just want to tell you
something i i i can't do this stuff
i said what are you talking about
i can't do the time whatever i'm like
what
i put water in the jug and i dropped
fresh thyme in that's all i did
now it goes in my fridge
now it's a weapon
against the bad guys
goes in the fridge
it's steeping
drink it on and off all day long
it's just really great
simple simplicity
lydia hi please let me know the brand of
vitamin z
that's it right there it's the bimergy
these and victor i m as in mary ergy
that's a big deal and if you're somebody
and you don't have the right z if you
don't have the right something if you
don't have the right vitamin c or you
don't have any at all you got the
healing broth
there's still tools you can do in your
power in that moment when you start
getting sick and something starts going
wrong you can
still do life-changing things so let's
make a time t so we're gonna do i'm
gonna heat up some water right now
so i'm gonna heat up some water we're
gonna make some thyme tea that's the
next thing you can put honey in your
thyme tea you can do all kinds of stuff
right
you can put lemon in your time tea you
can put lime in your time tea if you
really want
they haven't got time for time dino says
can you show us your broth linda would
love to thank you for being here i'm so
happy
that you want to see the broth
is there a way to show you guys this way
i think there might be can you see that
that well the broth is about to spill
you guys see that on telegram
you see that on
rumble youtube you guys see that on tick
tock
that's the healing broth cooking up real
nice
i got a cabbage here from earlier but
you don't have to put that in there if
it's all you got you could
so let's make some time t
let's go you guys
we're having some fun hot water
right
you can go with honey
you can do that
if you really want
put a little honey in there you can put
a lemon and you know some lemon in there
too right
you can do that let's get some time in
there so it's steeping
all right
you can mix it up with a spoon
got a little spoon you can mix it up
with
i'm going to pop a little bit of lime in
there
i'm going to talk about vitamin c shock
therapy it's in cleanse the heel
put a little lime
okay
so in cleanse the heel if you really
want to know if you want to have these
tools
the z-shock therapy
for your white blood cells so you can
clobber the bugs that are going around
is in here and cleanse the heel
right here the vitamin c shock therapy
is also in here too we'll do that too i
gotta i got a couple of mugs over here
we can do it
i'm letting the time tea
do its thing right there
time
sits in your bloodstream
longer than other herbs
so when you drink your thyme tea
the phytochemical compounds in time
float around your bloodstream
staying there longer so it can keep the
bad bugs away
and that's what i love about it so
powerful let's make a vitamin c shock
therapy let's do that now
vitamin c shock therapy you put some
water in here
right
two capsules
every two hours two capsules every two
hours that are waking if you're up
take it
right what i'll do sometimes i'll do
three
if i was exposed
i'll do three
right
so we got that
let's get an orange in here
so vitamin c shock therapy
takes an orange
you can strain the seeds
get a strainer out
squeeze it in
this is the vitamin c shock therapy
every two hours what a powerful tool
you guys if none of this stuff ever
worked or ever helped anybody
be a different story i'd be here like
hey try this
but these things work
like work
for real because in alternative medicine
it's smoke and mirrors and a lot of
alternative medicine is so much
bull
it's unbelievable
so
the book is in the profile just on tick
tock they said what about the book lens
the heel it's it it's right there
the link is there and guess what a free
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
is coming up like real soon make sure
you sign up to the newsletter so the
medical media newsletter go to
medicalmedium.com you'll find the
newsletter sign up so that we can send
you an email saying hey are you ready
for the cleanse the free cleanse the
link is in the description for the
newsletter
in the bio too in the bio
and the book is there too
thumbs up if you guys can thumbs up and
youtube thumbs up wherever you can you
know youtube and
and and um if you and subscribe
right
thumbs up
like whatever whatever options you have
so what i'm doing here is i have to get
some honey in here so i like honey in
here so this is vitamin c
shock therapy
every two hours
two capsules
the best vitamin c that's easy on the
stomach so what happens when everybody
gets the flu and they get the cold bugs
their stomach goes south
their stomachs just go sour a lot of
people half the people who get the flu
bugs end up throwing up all the mucus
and their sinus congestion their sinus
congestion and mucus their lungs and
everything it's going into their stomach
so what happens when someone catches a
bug
they're swallowing all the mucus all
night long and their stomach gets sick
that's why a lot of kids throw up that's
like a lot of people throw up when they
get the flu or the cold or they get the
bug going around they're vomiting
because
their stomach is filled with mucus
another reason why they're vomiting is
because all the sinus pressure from the
bug that's going around right now and
i'm seeing it out there the sinus
pressure
is putting pressure on their vagus
nerves
so everybody has this pressure on the
vagus nerves the sinus pressures are the
sinus pressure is putting pressure on
their facial nerve trigeminal nerve
vagus nerves and optic nerves and that
makes people throw up to you or get sick
in the stomach so how am i going to take
vitamin c aw if i'm so sick i can't even
i i'm coughing i just have no appetite
i can only get a piece of dry toast down
like what do i do i'm like dude
get the micro c because it's really
gentle on the stomach so you can do
something about it while you're trying
to heal
so that's the vitamin c shock therapy
medical mean vitamin c vitamin c shock
therapy right there
two capsules
every two waking hours you got some
orange in there
you got a little bit of honey in there
that's a weapon
you gotta have some
tools that can do some damage to the bad
guys
deborah says the shock therapies really
do work exclamation point
been there done that
amazing
in alternative medicine the smoke and
mirrors is just incredible that's how
it's always been right this promotes
this
i'm dr michelle and zoe hudson i'm
doctor
try my
try my little supplement it promotes
well-being
it promotes good health
it's like yeah okay i'll buy that i'll
buy that another sucker born every
second i'll buy that i'll buy that i'll
buy that
but this stuff never works you have to
use things that work you
health is nothing to fool around with
life is precious
and the amount of crap that's piled high
so high out there that people have to
swim through i don't know how anybody
gets by you get sick and sick and sick
and sicker sure
if you're not so sick i get it if you're
not so sick and you're young and you're
indestructible and you only have a
little rash or a little bit like a
pimple
you get three pimples and you run to a
functional medicine doctor because your
tummy is a little funny and you got
three pimples you got a little bit of
bloating you you yep you got it under
control with your functional medicine
doctors and everything else right
because you're not really sick you're
you got a couple of little things but
you're in the not so sick group right
but man when you're sick
it's like land mine land mine stab in
the back land mine
pitfall pitfall pothole pothole it's
like it's crazy how do you how does
anybody even survive they don't they go
downhill downhill downhill downhill
until no one no one everybody forgets
about them
you know how many people are just you
dropping like flies out there all around
the world and then they just disappear
oh yeah that person used to work here i
don't know what happened to them two
years ago who cares
jeanette i see medical medium
information all the time taken by
doctors on ads oh my god jeanette
i just had a a meeting about that
here's what's happening
all the doctors have taken medical
medium original unique information out
of the books
that's only been put in the books
nowhere else right
they've taken it they've hijacked it
they have no studies to show where it
comes from because they don't come from
studies they come from medical medium
literature
and they're they're banking off it right
that's what they're doing right but
that's just one area
i'm seeing it everywhere we see it
everywhere medical medium information so
the goal is
censor medical medium wherever we can
so medical medium doesn't take credit
so that his people people who find them
can't find him and get better so that
they take the medical media information
they chop it up dice it up they put it
out there they add their other stuff to
it people don't really get better from
it they don't give credit to the good
stuff they're using
from medical media
it's just it's sad
i don't care about the credit
i could care less i didn't go into this
if i wanted credit i would have done 10
shows tv series because i've been
offered all the tv series for the
medical medium tv series all on
mainstream tv all the different networks
for the last 20 years have been offering
me tv series right reaching out to me
and everybody and network's reaching out
and being like let's do a medical medium
series where you're working on people
right
i didn't want to get credit i just want
people to have the information
so someone can heal
it's just somebody can heal
so this is cooking up nice we got the
vitamin c shock therapy we got the z
shock therapy right there
that's that's a big one all on its own
we have the thyme tea
we got the healing broth
simple
powerful right simple powerful
such a good thing all right so talk
about cat's claw a little bit so what i
recommend friends and family is to do
cats cloth they get hit with something
ask your doctor what's right for you you
guys know that you can ask your doctor
what's right for you
but i tell friends and family you've got
something going on you think you're
getting something boom let's get the
cat's claw going
here's what's really sad and people
don't realize this so he you guys hear
me out if you just if you have a second
please right
it's one thing
to be okay with no real problems with
your health yet
and then you catch the flu or a cold or
a bug going around it's another where
you've struggled with fibromyalgia
hashimoto's thyroiditis multiple
sclerosis symptoms neurological lyme
lupus terrible digestive problems
neurological symptoms left and right
trigeminal neuralgia migraines or
anything else
and then you get the flu or the bug
going around and everything you see see
how that works
so someone can be like well i'm not you
know i'm young i'm indestructible oh i
got i got it i'm sick for a week okay
get back on track right and still it
could knock them down but they have
people who they've already had problems
they already have problems a lot of
people you guys know how it is
they got eczema psoriasis they got
vitiligo they got lupus they got ms they
got you know neurological lyme they have
all these other conditions they got
problems with the thyroids whatever
and then they get hit with it
that's why it's important to take care
of yourself like having these tools
that's why it's so important
michelle fromm says you inspired me to
make healing broth right now thank you
yay
incredible
make sure you get the book get it free
of the library too so you have all these
other tools the z shock therapy the
vitamin c shock therapy the
flu and cold protocols
right
you guys i did an amazon live cooking
show today just letting you know i did
an amazon live cooking show i made these
incredible spring rolls
and it was really fun
so make sure you sign up to my amazon
live like sign up or follow me on amazon
live
so look for me there so you don't miss
out because the medical media cooking
show is really cool we do a lot of
cooking tips and stuff like that just
letting everybody know link is in the
description link is in the bio tick tock
telegram
you know where to get the link
so your live was amazing so darlene you
watched it incredible
limbo love says the amazon live was
amazing loved it
emily marshall oh my god cooking show
was awesome
thanks emily amazing
incredible
courtney said whenever i see you i'm
reminded of the mm tools amazing
lorraine says it made you so hungry
yeah i downed them i made all these
spring rolls and just scoffed them down
i was just
in between everything i was walking
around
just eating them
it was great it was great i used the
dipping sauces terry says what kind of
broth this is the healing broth so i got
lots of garlic in there i got onions in
there right got some carrots in there
too okay
and i got some potato in there as well i
threw some fresh thyme in there
that's a medical medium healing broth
for the moment i use what i have and
there's lots of ginger in there too
happy new year's back to you joe
happy new years to everybody seriously
isabella says those spring rolls look so
good i want to make them all that
they're really fun
so many cool ones there
so
give you a little reminder
good protection method right there the
elderberry syrup there's nothing like
that out there i'm letting you guys know
process the way they do this process is
incredible it's a juiced elderberry the
whole thing's incredible right it's got
vitamin c in here so that actually has
vitamin c in it which is who does that
in an elderberry syrup
is there water in the broth yeah i did
put eight cups of water in the in there
somewhere around there i wasn't actually
counting perfectly and this is done this
broth is done by the way
b12 is critical for recovery especially
with neurological symptoms when we get
sick with a cold flu which is really
important
and
lemon balm is a great one right there
you've got the vitamin c shock therapy
you've got the other various cells all
these things are important
i'm not sponsored by them by the
emergencies vimrgy.com v isn't victor i
am as mary e rgy.com the stuff is
superior
which is unbelievable it's just
incredible we talked about time t we got
time water right here on recap you guys
we got that we got the healing broth
let's get a little bit of healing broth
out
get the lid off of this
now i'm not straining this right now
i'm just actually using this just to get
the broth out see you guys i'm sure
you've done this before right
okay
so basically i'm pushing this down in
there and i'm just getting the broth
i think what i'm going to do is use a
see-through
bowl
how's this
does that work
might get a little piece of carrot in
there because what i'm doing is just
bringing this down into the bra you know
i'm kind of letting the
the broth
spill on to the spoon i mean to the
ladle
and that's what i'm doing right now so
i'm getting this broth
all that congestion in the lungs all
that congestion in the sinuses
and you sit over this thing and you
breathe in the steamy hot broth and then
you
blow on the spoon and you you suck it
right in and all those chemical
compounds get driven into the body how
incredible is that
is it okay to freeze the broth yes it is
yes it is
so that's the broth right there
how long does the broth keep
i keep it in the fridge for a couple
days
a couple days easy to reheat it
to freeze it too if you want
gail says i've only known you for a week
yay and i love you already thanks for
all you do
don't worry ladies i'm 72.
well thank you listen it's i mean
honestly i'm honored you're here truly
okay it's so great i'm glad you weren't
scared away
it's an amazing community
and i'm glad you weren't scared away by
all the stuff i do like when i'm like
doing all the different stuff on
instagram the fun stuff
which
we're gonna go and do
we're gonna do that in a little bit
i'm gonna make another healing broth i
think on instagram
and then
i don't know
i'm not going to be dressed up like the
pirate today
but who knows
it's the best community
you guys i love you much
and i'll see you soon i'm just going to
straighten up a little bit for a few
minutes tick tock i'm turning you guys
back on and telegram i'm turning you
back on
right
and we're going to do it and i'm heading
off to ig with you guys back on so come
to instagram we're gonna have some fun
can't wait cold white spring says pirate
all right