all right so we're talking about a
couple things today we're talking about
processed food propaganda processed food
you're probably thinking oh he's going
to just be all angry about processed
food and fried greasy fast food
restaurants and how bad it is in the
United States and everywhere else or
anywhere else and that's the reason for
chronic illness and disease no we're not
going to talk about that because that's
[ __ ] that's [ __ ] I'm not for
processed foods if you read medical
medium books I don't know if you can
even see them over there I talk about it
not being a great idea obviously
processed foods are not a great idea but
what's happening right now it's a
distraction it is a distraction that's
happening and occurring and influencers
and people in the health movement are
falling for it they're kind of they're
falling for that distraction forever
chemicals processed foods food chemicals
and they're they're falling for that
right because that's what the evildoers
want them to fall for that's the whole
point so now it's going to be all about
that right that's going to be the trend
but people don't realize I'm going to go
into great depth into
this but people don't realize what the
distraction is for is so nobody knows
the real reasons no one learns the real
reasons why people have chronic illness
people are sick they are suffering the
people that came to the medical medium
information and medical medium books
know this they've been there they've
done that you don't eat processed foods
right but I'm going to go into it a
little bit more in a little bit we're
going to get there so this is going to
be a really interesting episode real
interesting talk about processed foods
you're going to want to stick around if
you don't mind I would like to make
something and I might even work on the
board a little bit and do some other
stuff too so I am here I got my oven on
right there and let me just get started
okay you guys today I'm making something
called potato and cherry tomato bake
right here so there it is I'm going to
make this you guys want to see over
there on you guys want to see on Tik Tok
right there on YouTube Rumble there you
are so I'm making this so delicious it's
going to be great I'm going to make it
in this pie dish right here as you can
see here it is take a look and I have
steamed potatoes right here these are
got raw
potatoes by the way that's a protocols a
life saving protocols book right there
you read this book your mind will be
blown away that's the Brain saer book so
let's get started okay I got my tea over
here if you don't mind Maria over there
on YouTube says I'm having a hard day I
hope this will make it better I hope so
maybe I can make you laugh cuz you never
know because if you've seen me in the
kitchen before um anything can go wrong
like something could hit the floor um
the oven can stop working I mean
anything can happen so maybe that'll
cheer you up I will certainly not do it
on purpose because I don't want to make
a big mess but you never know so I'm
going to get a bowl right
here and I'm going to put this in the
bowl so what I'm doing is peeling back
these steamed potatoes right now okay so
that is what I'm doing and I'm going to
grab a dish towel as well going to
moisten the dish towel right here okay
so I'm going to peel these back a little
bit is what I'm going to do and I'm
going to stick this dish towel in my
back pocket okay how's this tutorial
going right now now right so I'm going
to peel these a little bit
better um they'll just look better
they're better you don't want to keep
the the peels in
this cuz you get a different look you
get a different vibe it's not the best
most funnest thing so while I'm doing
this I want to talk about processed
foods for a little bit if you guys got a
minute and so right now what's happening
is we're taking a thousand steps back in
the health world right so we're back to
process foods again that's where we are
that's where the health food is that's
where the health world is going with
their health food it's all about
processed food so we're going back in
the dark ages of the health movement I
mean seriously that's where it's going
and fine Let It Go that direction right
I mean hey it happens it happens but
that's not the reason for chronic
illness I'm sorry but processed food is
not the reason for chronic illness
sure somebody can eat a processed food
diet they can go to fast food
restaurants they can eat a lot of these
right here a lot of these right there
double bacon cheeseburgers you know
what's going to happen over time they
arteries will slowly fill up with a
whole bunch of plaque and junk and
garbage over time depending everybody's
a little different the livers are going
to get a little bit of a fatty liver and
clogged up over time they're going to
get the pre-diabetes eventually to type
two diabetes is what they're going to
get and maybe some blood sugar
inabilities in general outside of uh
pre-diabetes and so forth and maybe some
other things will happen and maybe
eventually at some point if their
arteries get filled enough with a bunch
of junk and plaque they'll die of a
heart attack that is not chronic illness
that is
not it's very important to
know so Spence over there in IG says are
those potatoes steamed or uncooked right
now they are steamed potatoes I steam
them
prior and they are now going in here and
I'm going to mash them I'm going to make
this really fun dish right here and I'm
going to try not to make a mess but I
always do make a mess I just
do okay so let's go back into processed
foods if you guys are open to
this so yeah processed foods are not a
good thing I've talked about it in the
medical medium books okay
there's a lot of people unprocessed
fried greasy fast foods a lot of people
and they're not bedridden on couch
Island and Mattress Island but a
20-year-old is a 19-year-old is a
25-year-old is a baby boomer will have a
heart attack eventually at age 65 a baby
boomer will have some other
problem they'll have all these stints
and shunts put in they'll have maybe a
heart surgery
maybe they'll they'll get eventually
something going on with their pancreas
and so forth they'll get obese their
weight will go up baby boomer right
they're eating processed foods and
everything else but what about the
16-year-old that's in their bed dying
and the 9-year-old that can't function
and has fatigue and they don't know why
and they think it's psychological and
what about the 26-year-old that can't
get out of bed and feed her children and
take care of her children is she at
McDonald's is she at Burger King every
every single day no probably eating
healthy food probably watching what
she's eating probably seeing 20
alternative doctors but she's sick
because she's got this internal problem
nobody knows about but once again we get
these people that have loud mouths and
they they end up you know going around
they connect with other people in the
industry and they're like processed
foods processed foods let's save our
children let's save the planet process
foods let's make sure that that there's
no forever chemicals in there make sure
there's no food chemicals any anymore
make sure there's no high fructose corn
syrup in there anymore that's the real
problem that's why the whole world's
falling apart it's because of processed
foods which is [ __ ] it's
[ __ ] Jack Lynn over there Jackie
says oh my God all over Tik Tok food
vloggers yep it's all about processed
foods and that is a setup that's a setup
by a higher Archy in the industry making
sure that everybody's talking processed
food [ __ ] that is a cover up is
what's happening in the industry I'm
just letting you guys no it is you'll
see It'll come out down the road just
like all the other medical meme
information comes out down the road just
like the you know life expectancy was
dropping all this time just like medical
medium information published a long time
ago now down the road they're talking
about it it's going to happen just like
this with processed foods it is a
coverup for a bigger picture and people
are falling for it
everywhere and here's the funny thing
you can take processed foods away from
people and they'll still find them
somewhere if someone wants to eat a
processed food they're going to freaking
eat the processed food it's like alcohol
prohibition taking alcohol away taking
liquor away only made the Moonshiners
make liquor in the freaking woods and
that's what happened you had hundreds of
thousands of
Moonshiners making alcohol in the woods
is what you
had every everybody still drank there
were speak easys everywhere there were
hidden joints where everybody was
drinking themselves to death everybody
had a hidden bottle under their pillow
you can't take away alcohol they'll find
a way to drink it you can't take away
processed foods they'll find a way to
make it and they'll find a way to eat
it got a lot more to talk about with it
are you guys with me or or what steamed
potato in my hand right here Susan blond
over there on YouTube happy to be able
to hear you IG cut the volume because
they do cut the volume yes they do and
um they also cut the people too long
time ago that's what they did they cut
the people as
well um but you can actually come on
here I'm on YouTube I'm on Rumble you
can see me even on Tik Tok right now Tik
tok's actually not uh Banning me right
now you'll see probably in a minute
they'll just give me a forewarning the
minute I start telling more truth more
truth they'll just they'll give me the
warning so over there in IG which te are
you drinking lemon balm with a dropper
full of the vimergy lemon balm in the
lemon balm tea because I feel like you
know if you're going to do lemon bomb do
it right so I put extra lemon bomb in
there there's one thing on planet Earth
is you're always going to get assistance
to hurt yourself and self-sabotage
yourself please understand that there's
always going to be a lot of assistance
the waiter is going to bring the tray of
shots and alcohol there's always going
to be assistance there's always going to
be a fast food restaurant I don't care
in Europe I don't care in the US I don't
care there's always going to be
somewhere where there's going to be
someone's going to be able to eat
something that they probably shouldn't
be eating and it's always going to be
here on planet Earth so we can talk the
stupid [ __ ] game over over and over
again process foods process foods we can
do all that but we're missing the point
of what really causes chronic illness
and why people are really sick and why
you're 25 years old and you're bedridden
is it really from processed foods I'm
curious is it is that why a 25-year old
can't get out of bed and they're so sick
they got vertigo and dizziness and they
can't even function and put two words
together and they got herpes breaking
out everywhere and they're sick as a
goat is it because of processed foods
cuz I'm scratching my head here and I'm
kind of confused a little bit there
that's how ridiculous it really is all
of
it all right I'm going to get this dish
going I'm just probably going to go with
one more potato here I'm going to peel
back what's the answer to remove
processed food put everybody on clean
keto put everybody on a clean keto diet
put everybody on a a diet that's that's
uh clear from of food chemicals is
that's what what it is everybody's just
going to get a steak stay away from
potato is that what it is everybody's
going to be a steak and salad person is
that what they're doing that's the
answer to get everybody better because
there's so many people sick and bed that
have done that they tried it they're not
better pepper seed good to see you by
the way over there in IG okay and IG
what are your thoughts about the
carnivore diet or meat-based Diet so
let's get into that a little bit why not
I think it's a good
idea I do
I'll let you know my thoughts see what
you think okay I'm just going to mash
this though bear with me for a second
I'm going to move this cheeseburger
bacon double cheeseburger and I'm Mash
this up a little bit
here over on IG I'm going to answer the
question about the card War stuff too my
thoughts are just give me give me a
second here Shamrock over there in IG
says I atat a whole food plant-based
diet for 20 years and still had painful
IC and MCAS thank you for Shining Light
on this it's very important to know and
you can have that for 20 years and you
can be 18 years old and have that at 18
years old is it processed foods that did
it but no they're going to make it look
like it is they're literally going to
pollute the industry with the processed
food propaganda to the point where even
the influencers that are so-called in
the health rub that are experts are
going to be all over the TV channels
talking about it everybody's going to be
on Tik Tok talking about it and the
whole things of Roose the whole things a
setup whole things a setup
yep the whole thing is the setup let's
go into carnivore for a little bit if
you just got here I'm making the uh
potato and tomato cherry tomato bake
okay so what I'm going to do is cut
these cherry tomatoes right here I'm
going to cut them in half I'm going to
put them on top of this little kiche pie
dish right right now I'm just kind of
mashing these up you can roughly mash
them I'm going to kind of give them a
really good you know break them apart
and give them a really good mash um
um my cutting board sticks out a little
F further than the the counter so I have
to be careful if I put all my weight and
all my strength down on this I might
pull my cutting board down so I'm just
going to break it up a little
bit
so there we go and I'm going to mash it
up okay carnivore let's hit it well
carnivore originally was a mono diet of
meat I they didn't actually even eat
eggs to start with right off the running
those came late
so it's really just carnivore diet was
just people being like just eat meat and
you'll be
fine I called the shots many years ago
that any carnivore expert is eventually
not going to be a carnivore diet expert
they're going to be a carnivore diet
idiot and I'm not saying that in a dis
you know a disrespectful way just in the
mere fact that they're just
experimenting on people who are
following them just eat meat and beat
only just eat chicken or chicken only or
just eat meat maybe bring in eggs and
that's it what happens is
women don't do good on just meat chicken
and Eggs only they don't they don't do
good their body systems will start
falling apart this isn't an anti- meat
talk uh I'm not against people eating
meat this isn't a vegan Channel but I'm
going to tell you right now it was
terrifying for women so it became more
of a guys thing just eat meat and work
out what happened where what happened
was guys were hitting the walls I
predicted it and there's a whole bunch
of guys that used to be carnivore where
they ate meat now they're not car now
they're eating fruit meat and fruit and
then they're talking stupid about
vegetables how vegetables are all bad
for you but then now they're eating
vegetables so really what happened was
all the carnivore people I don't know if
you guys know unless it's a newbie
that's starting on just meet all the
carnivore people all left carnivore so I
don't know what carnivore you're talking
about that's another thing you asked
what I thought about the carnivore diet
what carnivore diet they all left
carnivore they all brought honey in and
lemons they didn't have honey and lemons
in it before they all brought fruit in
there they didn't have fruit in the
carnivore Diet before they all brought
berries in they didn't have berries they
brought green apples in so now they're
kind of on the low sugar low glycemic
keto diet is what they're really on
Paleo diet is what they're really on
there are no carnivore diets anymore
they shape shifted it they started out
you know hey this is what you do you
just eat meat and this is what you do
women copycatted and just the
reproductive systems just fell apart
their brains fell apart they hit the
wall they were gone that was it onto
something else or half dead and then the
guys that were actually doing the
carnivore diet and they were up in the
front running and social media making it
look interesting great they were trying
to stick with it stick with it finally
they knew that they couldn't lie much
longer to the crowd they were bringing
in Honey because their brain wouldn't
think they couldn't think at all they
had no their intelligence level their IQ
just dropped tremendously they were just
literally bumping into walls cuz they
had no gluc glucose to feed their
neurons and feed their brain electrical
activity went down because when you go
carnivore where you're just mono eating
meat your electrical activity just drops
and goes down and falls apart and your
short circuit so what happened was um so
what happened was
that the carnivore
movement turned in basically to a
bringing one thing at a time the
carnivore movement turned in to bring in
some honey the carnivore movement went
okay bring in some fruit now bring in
some lemons now and remember there's
glucose and lemons so they were trying
to get sugar they were dying for sugar
you need glucose or you're just bad you
have to have glucose or you can't
function and so the carnivore diet is no
more it doesn't even exist anymore
unless a new person comes on social
media and says this is what I'm doing
meat only Eggs only chicken only good
let's see what you do in 2 years you'll
be eating honey berries lemons and then
in newbie another guy will come into the
mix and be like okay I'm on the cardiv
war diet again doing it again be like
dude that's been done over and over and
over again and soon as you get popular
enough getting enough people just to eat
meat by itself you're screwed and you're
going to be doing nothing but honey
lemon and berries and you basically
you're just experimenting on yourself
and the people around you getting them
to experiment and then that's where you
are so that's the card of
D so I'm just going to mash this up a
little
bit sure you eat a whole bunch of these
every single day for years and you're a
baby boomer and now you're 65 years old
or whatever you are and you ate a ton of
these and a ton of hot dogs and a ton of
processed meat and a ton of garbage and
a ton of everything else and yeah your
your veins are going to be filled up
your Aries are going to filled up your
heart valves are going to be filled up
probably going to need heart surgeries
and all kinds of other things you're
going to have the diabetes you're going
to have the weight gain and obesity and
you're going to be fighting it trying to
exercise and that's going to be your
life but that is not the reason for
chronic illness and it isn't why people
are sick and it's not why college
students can't function anymore they
have to be on Aderall how come right
processed food that's the reason all
right so I'm making um the potato and
cherry tomato bake right now so I'm
mashing this this
up and giving it a good mash and it
doesn't have to be perfectly mashed
but forgetting that I have to make a
recipe
here there you
go when you go carnivore you may get
results off the bat reason why you get
results is cu you're mono
eating not just mono eating you're
getting rid of the gluten doesn't mean
it's a panace and it doesn't mean it's
an answer to heal chronic illness you
can take somebody they never had a
problem yet they're 25 years old they're
exercising and they go completely
carnivore mono eating meat only and you
give them a year you give them two years
and they'll be off of it the reason why
they be off of it is because their
muscles won't build properly anymore
they don't have any glucose to feed
their
muscles they'll start aging and look way
older before their
time they'll have the meat age the meat
aging where your skin just starts to
fall apart over time when you're young
you look like you're 40 when you're
20 carnivore diets that's what it does
you don't have any antioxidants in your
diet
another thing with people that have done
carnivores they'll take a ton of
supplements of all kinds they're just
looking for anything whey protein powder
creatine they're just looking for
anything they can find lcarnitine
they're taking everything under the sun
because they're so so jonesen for
anything because really they're starving
themselves of like real nutrients and
everything else I'm not saying meat's
bad that's you want to eat meat fine but
I'm just telling you what's going on
with carnivore so many people lie on
social media too they're telling you one
thing but it's It's Not What It Seems
they're telling you one thing but it's
not what it seems they're actually doing
something entirely different they they
don't want to lose their like mojo on
the set they're doing their social media
and their reals and everything else and
they're not going to tell you they
cheated on this a little to survive they
ate a little of this over here they were
over here at their family's house they
had a bite of this and then they're
going back on saying I'm carnivore I'm
carnivore this is how I
eat rise with melum over there on
YouTube says my hairdresser is on a keto
diet and he had to fill up with honey
during our session cuz he couldn't
function anymore he told me how he feels
more awake
now so here's the thing let's go into
this a little
bit talking so fast I think I need to
slow down my
talk all right so I'm going to add
spices and everything I need to put in
here putting a tablespoon of garlic
powder in here
that's what I'm
doing get that in there that's the onion
powder now I'm going to put a um two
table two teaspoons of garlic
powder there we go got that in there
okay I'm going to squeeze some lemons in
here as well I mean you can do a little
bit more lemon if you really want to
it's a half tablespoon of freshly
squeezed lemon juice I'm going to do
probably I don't know a little more
maybe I'm going to cut a couple lemons
up right here
let me get a strainer if you guys don't
mind I'm going to drop some lemon juice
in here now this is the potato and
cherry tomato bake so I'm going to drop
a little bit of lemon juice in here you
guys this is a medical mean recipe
that's really great it's a fun one it's
going to be so fun to eat so great to
eat okay so I'm going to drop some lemon
in here and then going to add some thyme
and some oregano so that's the plan
right here
yep so I'll give you the Europe talk too
about Europe right so everybody saying
Europe food so much cleaner so much
better but we got to keep in mind they
are so sick over there they are so sick
in Europe and I'm going to go into that
a little bit
too so what the take away from this is
the setup that's happening the
distraction
purposely they're actually like you know
acting like Europe is healthy because
they have better food there and they
don't do fast food like we do
here really ignorant thing to say um and
really what is it called freshman thing
to say you know definitely somebody
that's not seasoned in the health real
but you'll see people out there
talking and I guess it makes sense of
somebody who's not seasoned either it's
easy to fall into that all right so
let's pop some fresh time in
there people are sick all the same in
Europe they're all the same in France
Italy
Netherlands they're sick everywhere
Germany they're
sick not even eating fast food and
they're
sick people growing their own food out
of their garden and they're
sick and they're growing their own food
out of their garden and they're sick
okay all right let me get some fresh
time some fresh oregano in here that's
going to get mixed up in here
too so I'm kind of taking the Twigs out
of the oregano for the most part any
real hard twig but I'm going to leave
some of of the softer Twigs in here so
I'm get some oregano going right
here but when you hear the rhetoric it's
the same old [ __ ] it's like in Europe
they're so much cleaner with their food
that you don't have to worry in the US
they're killing everybody with the fast
food it's the same talk and now they
just bring it back out again
okay got some oregano here I'm going to
chop up let me get some fresh time in
here too got some right out of the
garden right
here there we
go so I don't want it too Twiggy because
this isn't a stew or a soup so what
happens is with thyme thyme twigs and
everything if you put it in something
like this it it's going to be a little
bit more Twiggy when you're baking it
like that so let me get a little bit
more here there we go getting a lot of
little T little th leaves right there
that's a big stem there get that out and
a little bit more oregano too I want to
make this taste
great there we
go give this a little
chop guys don't mind that's a twig right
there I got to get that out that's going
to end up in there someone's going to
have some be like what is this it's a
big twig aw not good so right there
rising out of the ashes over there on IG
we are so sick especially in my country
Norway
yeah is everybody lined up at the fast
food joint in nor Norway but I heard the
fast food joint in in Norway is a lot
healthier than ours but everybody's
still sick people in Germany are so sick
absolutely they always have been yes and
they still
are they're sick absolutely right but
see the setup you guys the
setup is tricking enough people to
believe they're making a difference and
they're doing something by attacking
processed foods like I said you take
away processed foods you take away fast
food restaurants and how they do things
people will find a way to still eat that
they'll still eat it if they want to eat
that that's just the bottom line you
can't take it away you can't take their
their weed away in the states that are
you know that whatever it's legal you
can't take their alcohol away you can't
take their pills away you can't take
their crap away they want to eat their
fast greasy food fried food with
chemicals in it you can't take it away
they'll find it and eat it
duh Emma over there in IG I'm in Europe
and there are stricter regulations than
us I know that on what is allowed to be
added yes it's true in genetically
modified IED food as well absolutely and
that's true it still doesn't change
anything it still doesn't change
anything I know people in Europe and
they're growing food out of their Garden
they never even eat a processed food and
they've suffered for 20 years with brain
inflammation that no one can
explain I get it in Europe they do have
regulations absolutely fast food
restaurants have to keep some of the
food chemicals out absolutely is that
the reason why everybody's sick in
Europe is that the reason why every how
come everybody's still sick in Europe is
that the reason why everybody's sick in
the US it's not the reason why yes it's
not good it contributes to some degree
if you eat enough of this you will have
a hyper a hyper fatty liver also
processed foods you know like like are
stricter I the processed foods are
stricter there too in regulations
absolutely but people are just as sick
they're just as sick getting just as
much much cancer the heart disease the
brain diseases the Parkinson's the ALS
it's
rampant so true just spoke to a woman
over here on IG so so true just spoke to
a woman who came back from Europe and
said she started feeling neurological
symptoms again and needed to get on the
medical medum 369 cleans Europe is not
the answer to heal as far as the s is
meaning meaning like you can heal
anywhere us Europe you can heal anywhere
that's not what I mean Europe's not the
answer just because the pizza in Italy
is missing some of the chemicals that
are in the dough here it's it's not the
answer to stop chronic illness it just
isn't you go to Italy you go to Sardinia
you go to somewhere and you actually eat
the freshest most delicious pizza you've
ever had no process whatever the dough
was made they ground up the wheat they
did whatever right they you like you
name it or forget Pizza you had the best
salad mesculin mix ever grown you find
it in Italy and they put the most
beautiful extra virgin olive oil there
was Millstone the olive oil is Millstone
it's not the answer still someone will
get sick someone will be
sick and they'll be they'll just be
suffering I'm not and I'm not dissing
any of that that's awesome that's
awesome I'm not dissing any of that my
rash clear so over on IG uh Porsche my
rash cleared up while in Europe on
vacation and when I came back to the US
my rash came back I'm grateful I I I ate
great food while away and now back on my
cleanse you had fun food while while out
there okay so I want to get into that a
little bit what happens is when you go
on vacation and your stress goes from
here to here you go on your European
vacation your stress goes from here to
here you're going to start healing try
living out there see what your rash
does okay try living out there if you
have the ability resources money time go
out there to Europe and live out there
tell me if your rash comes back after 3
months or four
months let me know because it happens
every day to everybody else yeah you
want to go on a vacation and you want to
shift gears and go on a vacation you'll
see an improvement with your health in
general cuz you're you're self-caring to
such a degree you go on a vacation you
go take walks you're out there you're
breathing in some air you're you're
looking at things you're happy you see
things you never saw before you're
getting like you're getting ignited
right you're feeling happy happy your
stress levels go from here to here your
adrenals go from here to here and then
you start feeling a little
better and then you come back home it's
like I don't feel good anymore stay out
and Europe up and watch your rash come
back
watch your fat watch your fatigue come
back six months you'll have your C CF
you your CFS back Jess elain I am from
Europe and they are very heavy in bread
cheese Beer chocolate and more they are
indeed hey Jess by the way just
aaine it was it was mind-blowing to see
you at the event mind-blowing to see you
at the event man thank you brother for
coming it was incredible just to get a
chance to shake your hand and to meet
you
uh still in my Consciousness man still
in my Consciousness all
right we got everything we need in here
let's mix this
up and let's get this on the uh we'll
get this in here and we'll get going
with
this you know what s so just said Spirit
of compassion if you don't know s so is
so said why don't you tell them about
the people who live in Europe who are
sick and take a vacation to the US and
end up clearing up symptoms a little bit
too because it happens all the time
that's interesting I didn't even realize
that I don't think I ever knew
that but s so's telling me tell them
about the amount of
people that are sick in Europe that come
to the US to experience a vacation here
for a month how their symptoms start to
dive down a little bit meaning they
start to calm down and skin even starts
to calm down because they're on their
vacation then they go back to Europe and
it flares up again and they're all sick
explain that to me
please all right Margie over there on
YouTube Details Matter and there are so
many details so many like the one I just
said just now from so that detail was
huge
huge Jess says was awesome to see you
Anthony was awesome to see you too it
really
was herbal girl over there on YouTube
that's so funny s see good
point really it really was a good point
I don't think I've ever said that point
before I don't think I've ever said it
in any live in any podcast and I don't
think I've ever said it before so yeah
that was a really good point chelini
over there on Facebook I can't believe
someone can even see me on
Facebook Selen on Facebook but overall
the quality of Foods is much better in
Europe they have better standards
absolutely will not argue that one bit
but I can tell you right now you can
even live above those standards in
Europe and grow your own food only
literally grow your own grapes only and
still be
chronically bedridden in Europe you have
to understand what I'm trying to
say yeah the standards are better
good jaro Slava says over there on
Facebook yes my symptoms got much better
when I went to the US because I saw you
in Culver City and got the light blast
there we
go Culver City basically shut down so
the numbers came in 24,000 people came
to see medical medium in Culver City
24,000 people the largest book signing
on the planet and the largest the
largest crowd to come to a grocery store
to see me in a park and so forth and I'm
laughing because the whole fire
department was there the entire police
department was there the state police
came from what I heard and like
literally it was the craziest thing but
everybody was calm and everybody was
happy but what I'm saying is there were
so many people in the city the line went
four miles and and it was just it was
unbelievable
unbelievable from all over the world
and I'll never forget it it was the most
beautiful thing all right this is all
good so I just wanted to mix this up
just just a little bit better and then
that's it I got the onion powder in here
I got the lemon juice the garlic powder
the thyme I got the oregano in here so
what I'm going to do is pop this in this
little dish
here but even the recent expert
carnivore guys are all eating fruit now
and honey they're guzzling honey
guzzling it it was off limits the
original carnivore diet was off limits
they were bumping into the walls I
predicted it I predicted it 5 years ago
I predicted it years before that and the
guys I even predicted would be bumping
against the walls and actually eating
honey and fruit are eating honey and
fruit all right so what I'm going to do
is pop this in this dish right
here just like we speak just like this
there we
go
okay SD Goodman over there Facebook what
are you
making you're from Maine
amazing say hi to everybody up there for
me
please including my
family say hi to everybody up there for
me including my
family all right so uh
this is coming out great I think what
I'm going to do is I have it at 350 the
oven but I might put it even touch
higher you can do it at 350 but I don't
think you I'll have the time to really
give this a you know super big so there
we go all right now I'm going to do the
cherry tomatoes I just want to round
this off like this okay now the cherry
tomatoes come
in so I'm going to talk about Pro
process Foods a little bit more and we
going talk about the critical parts of
chronic illness and how processed
foods you
know are not what it seems I do not
recommend eating them I've been talking
about processed foods too for many years
all right can I get the cheeseburger out
of the
way I don't want to accidentally chop
that up and throw that in here so I'm
going to do is I'm going to cut these
cherry tomatoes right here and I'm just
going to place them like this I'm going
to cut them this way
though I'm going to cut him that
way and I'm going to clean this knife as
well so yeah there we
go so I'm doing some cherry tomatoes
these cherry tomatoes are
insane for some reason they're really
good I mean they're extra good they're
not tart right and I'm pressing these in
see yep pressing these
in and I'm going to spread them out as
well all
right
yeah going to press them in like this
this is going to be really good so let's
talk a little bit more while we're doing
this if you guys have a have a minute if
that's okay if you're interested in the
processed food talk marger says I hear
people coming again from all over the
world to eat together with you at Cafe
Gratitude it's really an incredible
thing that has happened right the Cafe
Gratitude um nights are going to be
amazing they're going to be amazing Cafe
Gratitude collaborated with medical
medium and they're putting medical
medium dishes on the menu right but but
they've also they've also wanted to
do um a a you know a popup dinner and so
I wanted everybody to
come so anybody who's coming it's going
to be a blast and you know what it might
not be the only one I do so if you feel
like you missed it or you're going to
miss this then you know hey
look just look out for the next one you
know but there are four dinners there
are four four dinners is what there are
four
dinners four four
nights it's going to be so cool they
sold
out and two nights sold out in 12
seconds that's what we were told so two
nights Cafe Gratitude said sold out in
12 seconds it was so confusing cuz they
sold out so fast like it was
baffling um so I'm really excited about
it it just added even more seats and
that was sold out instantly too so they
added 60 more seats and that was sold
out so it's going to be a meet and greet
it's not just a I'm going to be there
and it's more intimate right I mean I'm
right there in the restaurant with you
it it's going to be it's going to be
great and who knows what's going to
happen all right some just pressing
these in making sure I don't know if you
guys can see this over here I hope so
I'm pressing these in it's looking
really good let's get into some
processed food talk once this goes in
the
oven here we
go hang in there for you processed food
but this isn't processed
food but for you process food Buffs
we're going to have a talk
all right okay lo and behold I think we
got it now you can put some fresh herbs
on there um on the recipe in the book
right here you see fresh oregano right
on top I'm not going to put it on now
that's going to go on a little later cuz
all that's going to do is just you know
like toast up in here can I show you
this is ready take a look there you go
going in the oven now you guys I'm over
here I'm over here
here yep over here that's in
there I might cck this up a little
bit I think I'm going to do that now SP
with me I'm going to put it to
375 boom boom
okay
woo we got it in there eat don't mind
right love those cherry
tomatoes a good one too a sweet one
so
good it's crazy so
good
okay and a little lemon bomb tea with
honey in am I allowed honey am I allowed
honey Lord over there which recipe is
this please thank you for asking it is
potato and cherry tomato bake that's it
right there it's in the brainsaver
protocols books book right there it's in
this book
okay processed
food
ah processed
food okay let's go all
right guess what eating really really
high fat diets that are also not
processed to guess what it does it still
clogs up the liver still gives you a
fatty liver still kills your gallbladder
in the end still gives you sluggish
bloodstream dirty blood syndrome still
clogs up your lymphatic system still
starves your brain of oxygen and glucose
and still brings you to pre-diabetic and
diabetes type two
that's what the keto diet can bring to
you you ready processed food sluggish
liver fatty liver
right all the same like I was saying
before so keep in mind that the keto
diet can still do the same thing over
time as a processed food diet the
difference with the processed food diet
you'll probably have some more chemicals
in there obviously you'll have maybe
you'll have uh you know a little bit of
a fried grease every now and then you'll
have some other things too maybe you'll
be on more bacon than you were supposed
to be on with nitrates and stuff so
maybe you'll have nitrates and some
extra chemicals and maybe overall if
you're eating processed food too much
fried food and fast food restaurant food
you'll probably just get there a little
quicker you'll get there a little
quicker you'll still get the stuff in
the arteries in the heart you'll still
get everything else you'll just get
there a little quicker maybe a little
bit more than a little quicker but you
still get there but keep in mind that an
actual keto diet that's free from proc
processed foods will still get you to
pre-diabetic type 2 diabetes will still
get you to brain function problems still
get give you a fatty liver a sluggish
liver still give you arteries that have
plaque in them and all kinds of junk and
fat in them and still get you to get a
heart valve replacement or a heart
attack by the time whatever 60 70 and so
forth on a keto diet that's not
processed so all they're doing is
they're basically saying what they're
fighting for is they're fighting for not
getting you there as
quick that's what they're basically
doing but that has nothing to do with
real chronic illness and why that
8-year-old died that 9-year-old died of
some kind of terrible disease where they
just said you know the child's you know
life just didn't want to live
anymore they have actually terms for it
but that's what it
means you know like a thriving problem
the child can't thrive so all these
children are dying every day at 99 years
old 10 years old 11 years old of
physical body pain and fatigue and
they're calling it like the child can't
Thrive that's what they're calling it
I'm not talking about cancers I'm
talking about like they're calling it
like the child can't
Thrive and they got 10 terms for it got
look it up Susan says why are people
saying they're healing chronic illnesses
and cancer on
Carnivore okay so here's how it works
okay you take somebody that's been on a
processed food diet right and they're
really overweight you put them on a mono
diet and you starve them of
calories you starve them of calories and
you put them on a mono diet like just
meat only okay what's going to happen is
at first they're going to get some
results just like if somebody goes on a
sardine diet where it's sardines only or
they go on a tuna diet where it's just
tuna only or they go on a salmon diet
where it's just salmon only the same
thing happens their obesity comes down
they start losing their weight they
start shedding some pounds their liver
gets a little bit better things get a
little bit better they're not eating
chocolate cake all the time they're not
eating all the different Donuts cakes
and cookies filled with all that extra
fat and they're not eating all of that
and what's happening is their body
saying you're giving me a breather but
here's the problem okay here's the
problem you're eventually going to have
to leave that diet you can only do it
for a short time short time only your
brain stops working your body starts for
starts to starve with you know glucose
deficiency and you start binging over
time eventually you get so severely
nutrient deficient that you get problems
that you never even thought you would
get later on on the ladder and which
just so you know those people are doing
cancer therapies people just don't go on
Carnivore and don't do cancer therapies
So when you say how come people are just
throwing that blatant statement out
there like that scratch the surface
they're doing cancer therapies they're
getting surgeries and then they're going
on Carnivore they're getting
chemotherapy they're getting radiation
they're getting all kinds of alternative
therapies and conventional therapies
both fused together like in bed together
they're in clinics they're getting stem
cell therapy they're getting all this
crazy stuff right they're getting all
this stuff and then they're eating
carnivore and then they're telling you
the carnivore got their cancer better or
they cancer into remission or they
cancer
reduced you scratch the surface you got
to understand what the details are the
details are there they're there
okay nobody gets this big old diagnosis
of cancer and then now they're saying
well I'll just go carnivore and just
ignore everything the 20 oncologists are
telling me every single day they don't
do that they listen to their oncologist
and they work with all their doctors on
their cancer therapies on all their
cancer therapies and meanwhile their
doctors are helping them heal their
cancer or putting it into remission
whatever a blood cancer or some kind of
lymphatic cancer that they did surgery
on they're putting them into remission
and then the person's saying it was
carnivore that cured my
cancer the people who were carnivore
eventually at honey and fruit and fruit
juice interesting
interesting so I don't know who's going
on straight carnivore any any anymore
there is no carnivore anymore
the carnivore experts are drinking fruit
juice they're not carnivore anymore
carnivore is just a slab of meat in
front of you and that's what it was and
that's what it
is I don't know why they're calling now
a keto diet
carnivore because now they're doing a a
low glycemic keto diet and they're
calling it carnivore with a ton of Honey
added to it and they might do a slab a
bee for a little while for a long time
like for a short time for a little while
and they do that but if you do it long
term or a long time you hit the wall and
your brain bends and you fall the heck
apart you actually fall apart just fact
that's just a fact you fall apart you
hit the wall you hit the pavement and
you're done that's what happens when you
just do carnivore like it was meant to
be at the beginning when people first
started doing it where there where it
was dudes not women dudes you put women
just on meat and meat alone their bodies
will fall so apart so fast sure they
might get a month where they're dropping
weight cuz they're starving themselves
with calories they're dropping weight
dropping weight starving themselves with
calories they're dropping weight oh my
God this is like the answer and then
everything goes to [ __ ] 6 months later a
year later their health is disastrous
from going carnivore where they're just
eating a piece of meat they're done
they're done they got nut their nails
fall apart everything falls apart their
skin looks like it's 100 years old and
they start falling apart they got no
antioxidants they get no vitamin C in
them and they start falling apart that's
carnivore and their breath smells like
rotten meat and their bowels are filled
with rotten meat because their their
their digestive system and their HCL
won't even break it down anymore they're
filled with rotten putrifying meat in
their guts and it stinks coming out of
them and their skin gets old looking 6
months into it they're screwed they got
to go on honey like the like the dudes
did when the dudes started this this
whole bad
idea maybe some people can get away with
it for a couple of years dudes a couple
of years but you don't know what they're
eating you don't know what they're
eating they're showing you what they eat
on social but you don't think anybody
lies nobody lies out there nobody's a
liar on social nobody
lies nobody's showing you something
different than what they might
do if you actually think nobody lies on
social and everybody's telling the truth
on social
oh man get me in that bubble I want to
be in that bubble can you put me in that
bubble too I would love to just slide
into that bubble with you and be like
nobody lies nobody lies at all in this
world this world has no Darkness
nobody's nobody's a sick liar nobody's a
everybody just wants good things for
everybody nobody wants people poor
everybody wants everybody happy let me
slide into that bubble with you that
would be great place to live
Susan Janet over there on Facebook
there's an 83-year-old woman has been
carnivore since a teenager and seems
healthy she hasn't been carnivore since
she was a
teenager she'd be
dead where's the glucose for her brain
her brain would have atrophied and
shrunk Susan Susan there isn't an
83-year-old woman who's been Carnival
since she was a
teenager you were lied to Susan lied
to no one can sit there and eat a piece
of meat without honey fruit juice and
fruit and other things for 83 years or
70 years and still be alive or talking
and walking you were lied to how does it
feel to be lied to out there does it
feel
good Stephen over there on Facebook I
can tell you firsthand the carnivore
diet doesn't work I ate just about all
meat thinking it was healthy for the
last 10 years before getting really sick
and guess what Stephen you probably had
something in between it a little bit to
keep you going and it still made you
sick that's how bad it is thank you for
for leaving your comment I really
appreciate
it I
do yeah all
right so it's hit the keto diet for a
couple of minutes too unless you guys
still want to talk about the carnivore
Madness but we can talk about um keto
for a little bit right so let's go into
that couple of key things to know about
the keto diet I just want to fill
everybody in let's just take a look at
this comment right here on IG coming
right up Debbie over there on IG high
protein high fat
caused me to need my gallbladder removed
6 years ago I'm so grateful now that I
know the truth thank you aw and let's
hit that let's hit that right now you
see this right here see that little
green thing right there see that green
thing that little green thing right
there right the
gallbladder okay high protein high
fat right kills the gallbladder it truly
does it kills the gallbladder happens to
keto people 24/7 out there they're
getting their gallbladders out left and
right I get it if you're a 24y old dude
keto guy and you're working out in the
gym and everything looks great and you
look buff and you're 23 24 years old and
you got nothing better to do than just
to work out 4 hours a day and you want
to be on your you know high fat diet and
your high protein diet sure absolutely
looks great you'll eventually hit the
wall and be doing green juices down the
road and you'll be backing down on your
meat backing down on your eggs probably
quitting your eggs eating more
vegetables eating more fruit is what's
going to happen to you because some
things going to happen to where you're
just going to get sick and you end up
sicker as the years go
by D over there on IG my mother did
carnivore this year and her kidneys
almost failed so I want to go into that
so kidneys cannot handle
carnivore it is a guaranteed kidney
death for people with weak kidneys worst
thing ever for a kidney patient to be
told is to eat a lot of meat worst thing
ever for a kidney patient to be told is
to eat any meat worst thing ever kidney
patients should never be told to eat
meat they will destroy and kill their
kidneys without even realizing it and
they'll just be like off the pasture
boom gone kidneys can't handle high
protein they can't can't handle high fat
either that is a case where I
listen I have to tell you something a
couple different things right so in a
lot of cases out out there all right a
lot of cases out there okay when someone
has a kidney disease or kidney problem
or something going on with their kidneys
they're told to eat protein and they're
told to stay away from all kinds of bad
stuff right don't don't eat the
processed food you got to but they don't
realize too that eating nothing but
chicken and meat and eggs with a kidney
problem and oh my God it is a life
shortener a life shortener really really
sad it's going to the key diet for a
little bit first of all there is no keto
diet either anymore it's gone you cannot
go into ketosis ever if you even ate a
half of avocado and avocado has sugar in
it naturally you cannot go into ketosis
if you're doing avocado it's not going
to happen if you do a nut or a seed if
you do peanut butter if you do peanut
Butter's sweet there's sugar in nuts you
can't go into ketosis if you're eating
peanut butters and nut Butters and
almond butter Butters and almond milk
and everything you can't actually go
into ketosis right so there is no
ketosis anymore the ketogenic diet has a
false name it's
fraud the ketogenic diet is fraud it's
instantaneously
fraudulent that's what it is anytime you
see keto diet it's
fraud it should be # fraud keto diet the
reason why is you can't go into ketosis
it's impossible because no one the only
way to go in ketosis if you only eat
meat and chicken itself and only do that
when you do carnivore the way carnivore
was meant to be which is terrifying
where it was just chicken and meat and
meat only or turkey and meat only or
just meat only you end up going into
ketosis in that form or shape that's the
original ketogenic diet it's carnivore
but then keto took on this whole
different life and it took on eating
some green apples and low glycemic
fruits and berries um avocados you
cannot go into ketosis if you eat even a
tablespoon of avocado because it has
sugar in it which will then stop your
ketosis it'll stop it so then if you
even have a nut you have a walnut you
just shut down ketosis if you had some
tahini you shut down ketosis you have to
understand something this is really
important to know there is no ketogenic
diet anymore it's a false name it's a
fraud name is what it is now because you
can't go into
you can't go into ketosis unless you
avoid all sugars except for the very
minute amount of sugar that's in beef
which is the blood from the animal and
that's your best bet that's the only
way J Marsh over there kidneys kidneys
handle carnivore just fine protein
doesn't hurt kidneys
lying yeah that's really kind of you to
make sure you told some kidney patient
out there that they can eat lots of
protein and carnivore for their
kidneys how about that you think I'm
lying well those words are killing how
about that those words are
killing because that's how it works out
there because you can kill your kidneys
with high protein diets if you have a
kidney problem and over time you can
weaken your adrenals with high protein
high fat diets anyway you can weaken
your adrenals anyway over time
regardless but keep in mind absolutely
without a doubt you got to be very
cautious with how much protein you eat
how much fat you eat when you got kidney
problems really important CU kidneys die
easy with kidney problems when you
proteine them to
death anyway thank you for the comment
though because we just helped more
people with kidney problems along the
way that might see this so they
learn all right so back to to a couple
different things we talked about
carnivore a little bit about how it
works we covered that a lot of details
and ins and outs about it how you you
hit the wall you you actually can't
function anymore your brain doesn't work
you don't have enough glucose to your
brain and your nutrient deficiency is
actually get out of control and
Skyrocket with carnivore here's the
other thing too you can get tested with
your blood for nutrient deficiencies
while you're on Carnivore and it might
look pretty good because your body is
scrambling to get nutrients out of every
single organ you have in your body
listen listen to this detail this is
coming straight from s so right now in
this very second you go on Carnivore
like carnivore the way they meant it to
be originally before now they're just
now they're just eating a keto diet now
they're just eating you know a keto diet
that isn't even a keto diet either now
that they're just bringing all these
fruits and berries and all this honey
and everything else but if you eat
carnivore the way they meant it to be
where you're only eating meat and meat
alone
only your blood work might show
nutrients because nutrients are pouring
out of your organs to sustain you you're
going to plead it but you don't know it
so so is telling me what's happening is
now your body's like drawing from
nutrients anywhere and anyhow they're
pouring out of Bones they're pouring out
of organs you're mineral you're getting
mineral deficient you can't go carnivore
without getting mineral deficient you're
totally screwed with minerals trace
minerals and macro minerals totally
screwed if you're carnivore so what's
happening is nutrients are pouring into
your bloodstream from all all kinds of
different organs and tissue but that's
how your deficiencies go worse and worse
and worse and worse and so when you get
your blood examined while you're on
Carnivore for a month or two you got
some nutrients in there because those
nutrients are coming out of every
orifice of your body to keep you going
because you're in a desperate mode but
then eventually once you run out of
every nutrient every Trace mineral and
every mineral and every antioxidant now
you're totally screwed you get your
blood tested two years from then oh
you're deficient like hell and then if
you switch your diet you're on a diet
that's actually helping you they'll see
your old deficiencies and be like you're
so deficient and be like what the heck
now I'm deficient that's how much
confusion it is out there it's one big
experiment on everybody it's like I'll
be an influencer be like well I'm
experimenting on myself but I'm not
really telling you I'm experimenting on
myself but this is what I'm doing for
myself hey this is working six months
later well I changed it oh I screwed you
over I [ __ ] you over oh sorry about
that oop I changed it now now I'm doing
this and this and this and this 6 months
later a whole bunch of people are
experimen ING with you they're getting
sick they're having problems they're
getting deficient and then 6 months
later you're like oh I'm doing it
different now hey guys I'm adding this
now I'm adding honey in here now yep oh
sorry about that I just screwed you over
for another six months of people out
there that won't touch honey ever
they're afraid of sugar and and those
people are like gone you don't even see
them anymore the point is it's like an
experiment where you're actually taking
people for a ride and now it's like oh
I'm doing food combining now you guys
sorry I'm a food combiner now yeah I got
into food combining okay A year later oh
what was I doing a year ago oh don't
know cuz nobody cares nobody knows now
I'm food combining oh wait a minute now
I'm on a keto diet okay now I'm
macrobiotic oh wait nobody likes okay
now I'm on this it's crazy so people
just experiment along the way now I'm
doing alkaline ionizer water which is
dangerous because of all the metal
plates they you know what they do they
leech oh wait now I'm doing colostrum
hey guys now I'm doing colostrum now now
I'm doing diet Tous Earth particles
don't ever do those that's really scary
but the point is is like unless your
doctor tells you to and that's up to you
and your doctor but the point is is now
that's what happens people are
experimenting along the way so just one
big just screw ball that's it you're
just on that ride and it's like well I'm
following this guy and a year later he's
doing something different o I just
screwed myself for the last year
following that guy that's how it
works um
yeah okay another thing too so let's get
into
it see over there on YouTube just trying
to read some of the comments you guys so
bear with me Annie over there on YouTube
two years ago I did the keto diet and
ended up in the hospital and almost died
when I got out of the hospital I heard
of medical medium you saved my
life going to get me choked up
bless you bless you I mean exactly and
that matters so you were on a keto diet
it almost killed you yeah I mean years
ago I watched the keto diet almost kill
a lot of people out there I watched it
happen it was terrible and then keto
diet changed into the paleo diet the
paleo diet was this other kind of stupid
version of the keto diet it's just it's
just here we go around and around and
around Marcel over there on YouTube my
parents were instructed by my
pediatrician to feed me a lot of protein
and calcium rich foods while I had
kidney failure my health did not improve
for years kept the kidneys sick most
likely because that's what it does but
see it's not anybody's fault in the end
but I can tell you right now what is
kind of somebody's fault right now is
the stupidity around processed foods and
and the campaigns raged and waged on
processed foods and the amount of
information that's going around about
processed Foods what what a decoy man
the darkness loves a decoy like that
loves it cuz that's not why people are
sick I'm sorry it's not good for you
you'll get a heart attack in 50 years on
processed food yes but I'm going to tell
you right now it's not why people are
sick it's not why people who go to you
know University students are sick and
can't function and need to be on adderal
it need to be on amphetamines 24/7 it
need to be on on you know um you know
all the different stimulants and every
stimulants and everything it's not
that's not why it's not because of a
burger down the street I'm sorry but
it's not because guess what in the past
it wasn't like that and the burgers were
down the street all the same kids are
getting sick everybody's getting sicker
and it's not just because people are
eating a freaking bacon double
cheeseburger once in a while yeah you'll
get a heart attack it'll clog up your
liver down the road and you'll get
obese not one carnivore and keto
person out there isn't on a ton of
caffeine not one carnivore or keto
person out there caffeine free I could
say that a h hundred times in a row
there's that one carnivore person that's
caffeine
free they can't function without it they
need their caffeine fix carnivore people
that are actually doing carnivore really
carnivore where they're eating some meat
for a little while are addicted to
caffeine they're literally circulating
caffeine all through the bloodstream
24/7 they are people out there you will
see claiming to have found the Panacea
because they get some quick results on
carnivore or keto or really just they
really just want fame and money don't be
fooled they're on caffeine and you don't
even know what they're really eating
when they go when they do their cheat
day that they're not putting on YouTube
or on IG
Neil said my emotions went crazy on keto
because you lost your glucose and you
didn't have it going to the brain so
let's talk about that a little bit keto
in the carnivore diet starves your brain
of glucose stares it starves it of
glucose right there can't function
without glucose it keeps your brain
alive it does and so what carnivore
people do now is they're bringing lemon
and honey in oh lemon was off limits
before but they're bringing lots of
lemon now because you need that lemon
juice for your brain so it can start to
function again they're bringing in honey
too limit in honey oh because they need
that honey for their brain to keep it
functioning that's what they're doing
now they've changed the game I've
watched it I've seen it out there I
predicted it that's just the way it
is let me check on that real
quick all right turn this light
on it's cooking up
nice got something cook in the oven I
can't wait to dig into it cannot
wait so what happens when you go keto is
the electricity in your brain starts to
diminish and you start to slowly die
without realizing it and you're just
walking around W on the decline and
don't realize that so that's how it
works okay you're on the decline and so
what happened was intermittent fasting
kind of took over the carnivore and keto
thing like the old carnivore thing just
recently where someone was eating just
meat or the keto thing where they were
trying to eat mostly meat so what
happened was it moved on to intermittent
fasting right that was the next place it
moved into intermittent fasting was
don't eat in the morning but make sure
you're jacked up on caffeine all day and
then eat what you want at the end of the
day and it could be
anything eat a salad with avocado in it
if you want eat a burger if you want
have some cheese if you want do whatever
you want the intermittent fasting diet
okay so it's eat until later later at
the end of the day and people were like
I feel better because they weren't
having ham and eggs first thing in the
morning burdening burdening their liver
and their digestive system improved on
the intermittent fasting diet because
their liver improved their digestion got
a little stronger they W weren't
bombarding their liver and their
gallbladder with all that fat in the
morning eggs and cheese and oils and
whatever else and peanut butter
smoothies they weren't doing doing their
peanut butter smoothies anymore and
their almond their almond butter
smoothies they weren't doing that
anymore and so they were on intermittent
fasting where they were just on caffeine
all day long and then in then later on
4:00 5:00 6 o'clock they started to eat
something and maybe it was a little
healthier than normal maybe it was just
a sloppy cheat meal but that's what
intermittent fasting
was that was the level people went to
when they tried to do keto properly
which was starve yourself of all
carbohydrates and they couldn't survive
they couldn't make it and it wouldn't
work so they had to go intermittent
fasting it's all just round and around
and here we go again that's all it is is
is round and round and round that's it
that's how it works and it's sad as hell
it's
sad because what happens is when you're
chronically sick and you got real health
problems it's not just try to lose some
weight and get your blood sugar your A1C
better if you're somebody that it's not
about the A1C and it's not about like
get a little plao r dece in your
arteries it's not about a stress test at
the doctor's office the cardiologist
office it's not about like getting your
obesity down if you're somebody and
you're sick aches and pains tingles and
numbness numbness jaw pain neck pain ear
pain riging the ears left and right
whooshing shushing in the the ears
tightness of the chest heart
palpitations aibs that are really
mysterious right all kinds of vibrations
Tremors ticks all kinds of different
back pain feet pain body pain knee pain
that's mysterious doctors are looking at
it they're doing surgeries for no reason
because they don't know what's wrong
with you insomnia restless leg syndrome
list goes on your nose is twittering
your no is twitching your eyes are
twitching you got all kinds of different
pain you got dizziness feel like you're
on a boat you got balance issues you got
vertigo and you got fatigue and brain
fog you can't think you can't get a word
out edgewise you don't know what you're
even thinking you can't think you're
suffering you're struggling you're
fatigued you're bedridden you don't feel
good you're trying to push through you
can't work you know you know you're
doubting yourself judging yourself
you're
sick that is what what
matters you don't see me talk about
processed foods day in and day out and
try to be a processed food like
knowitall um influencer on social trying
to run with the whole worry about these
foods and the processed food World worry
about these fast food restaurants these
10 fast food restaurants this is going
to kill you this and this this sorry
buddy that's not why people are sick and
suffering and it's not why the
18-year-old is sick and suffering the
20-year-old is it's not why somebody's
daughter or son leaves the
university before it's due on their
first year second year comes home and is
bed bound and can't function and quit
school it's not because of processed
food I'm
sorry and what about the three-year-old
about the 2-year-old is that processed
food too cuz I'm scratching my head here
saying okay what about the
three-year-old oh that doesn't matter
that's just some weird thing that
happened three-year-old's getting sick
5-year-old's getting sick that's really
not something to think about oh just
let's make sure we let's make sure we
protest about processed foods in every
way and make sure we we pump we plump up
Europe as if it's the Panacea to fix all
our problems with our
health got nothing against
Europe but there's a lot of sick people
there I know I've been talking to them
for 35 37
years there's a lot of sick people in
Europe yes the food's a little cleaner
yes they got regulation on some things
not everything not
everything but some things yes
true go to France go to Italy you'll get
the best bagot you ever want it the best
baggot best croissant you ever
wanted you know there won't be a food
chemical on or in your
croissant sure I'm not even saying that
right anybody French from right now is
saying he just butchered that but listen
I get it you can get the best you know
brusa you can get the best you know the
tomatoes San Marano tomatoes in Italy
grown just right and picked handpicked
by Italians right handpicked by Italian
got nothing against Italians I'm Italian
handpicked by
Italians
okay and then just sliced just right on
a beautiful
piece of
bread toasted in the oven just right
boom little bit of Parmesan regana put
on top yes it's
better but man they're sick in Italy
they are sick in Italy I'm sorry but
they are it's they're sick and it's sad
sure there might be a small village in
Italy somewhere where there are some
Cent Ian there so there's some people
there that are 100 years old and 90
years old and 80 years old true but you
talk to them about it and all their
relatives are dead they all died at 60
and 50 and 65 and 70 do you ever talk to
a person that's really old you ever talk
to somebody if you go and interview
people who are old they tell you that
their family's
dead what happened to
them sure one person made it out alive
until they 102 but why are there why are
all their family MERS dead do you know
about that do you know how it
works exactly lra said 144 you're
Italian wow I am
indeed passionate is
high true true and as an Italian I want
to go check on the dish I'm making in
the oven right
now make sure it's cooking right along
ooh
nice oh so good so good
all right so let's keep on going a
little
bit just so you know people living to
100 has reduced in every single country
around the world and when they go to a
village where the young people moved out
they ratio it the wrong way by the way
and I hate to say this you guys want to
know a little you want to you want to
know a little diddy you want to know a
little
tidbit you want one right now it's
painful okay because I know a lot of
people in Europe I know a lot of lot of
people in Italy I know a lot of people
in France I know a lot of people all
through Europe Germany and so forth and
I'm going to tell you right here okay
they take little Villages where all the
young people moved out and then they
ratio the numbers and they say this
Village is a higher amount of older
people so something must be different
here in this Village than somewhere else
it's one of the biggest
Roes yeah you know where I'm going right
but what happened is there was no way to
make money in the village anymore so all
the young people almost all of them
moved out so they couldn't do the ratio
game to Young and older people to ratio
if people are actually really older
there for a reason and they keep that
detail out what what a Roose that is
they keep the detail
out they keep the most important detail
out possible they find a remote remote
village where there hardly is a young
person working there anymore living
there because they can't sustain
themselves they have to make a life they
move their family out they start their
families out after college and so forth
they don't go home The Village just has
mostly old people and then they say whoa
there's a lot of older people in this
Village Let's test the water let's see
what they're eating oh they're eating
this beautiful grape that came off this
Vine they're eating something here
they're eating there but no one wants to
admit or tell you they don't want to
tell you the secret they're doing the
numbers and the ratio game and they're
not telling you it's because all the
young people moved out of the village
there aren't young people in that
Village there's very few you want to be
a person that's 22 years old and go to
that Village and find a mate and party
and everything else you're going to be
sitting there on the curb alone there's
nobody
there what I'm saying is we have 100y
olds all over the land around the world
but we have a decrease of it people are
dying faster and more and not living to
be older as much and we're on the last
round of the dinosaurs you guys right
now we're on the last round of the
Dinosaurs the older people that are old
now there isn't going to be a big
succession a big succession of older
people coming their way I hate to say it
but there's not and processed food is
not the answer either
way I predicted life expectancy was
dropping dramatically and it did and
science proved it and proved medical
medium right
the one thing you can actually have
confidence in is the medical medium
books because guess what it's proved
right constantly and never proved wrong
sorry but none of the medical medium
books or information have been proved
wrong yet science hasn't proved a single
thing wrong instead they keep on proving
everything right out of the books and
poaching so we got a we got a potato and
cherry tomato bake in the oven we're
having I'm having a good time are you
guys having a good time I'm having a
good time my grandfather's family all
died horrible deaths listen here's
another thing to understand if you
interview old people they're not it's
rare rare that a 101y old lady is going
to say her sister's still alive and if
she is and she's 97 it is
rare it is rare they all tell you for
the most part oh no died at 71 died at
69 o died at this person my sister my
brother my uncle but they're all
dead Marcel over there on YouTube I was
raised in a small European village where
we grew most of our food amazing
learning from your information it was
hhv6 that attacked my kidneys absolutely
that's how it
works and you weren't in that Village
eating tons and tons and tons of
McDonald's right day in and day
out they grow their own food you're
raised in a village that grows their own
food you weren't eating McDonald's day
in and day out so the processed food
propaganda is control right now but it's
a decoy it's set to do that on purpose
and darkness controls it darkness wants
it to be this big processed food thing
and that's why everybody is sick that's
what they want Uma you like the new
telegram messages you guys it check that
out when you get a chance go to my
telegram
please go to the medical medium telegram
page um I'm leaving messages really
really profound ones from Spirit of
compassion great information you know
I'm leaving them constantly now so I'm
going to be leaving a lot more please go
go there tell other people find you know
find that that telegram of mine if you
can
okay Marcel my parents were instructed
by my pediatrician to feed me a lot of
protein and calcium rich foods why I had
kidney failure my health did not improve
for
years all right so listen I'm going to
move this right here
so
um so here's what happens when you eat a
lot of processed food okay not all
processed food just some processed
food there's some processed food that
doesn't hurt someone but there's some
that causes something to happen
right over the years you get a
buildup I even know if you can even see
that you get some
plaque and then your
liver right and then your
liver over the years you get a fatty
liver dysfunctional liver
you can get that on the keto diet you
can get that on the carnivore diet you
can get that on a a high fat vegan diet
you can get that on a high fat vegan
diet your liver turn into a fatty liver
because you can have pathogens in your
liver so this is the next part and the
last part of this little talk so I I
want you guys if you get a chance to
take a few notes
okay all right
okay that's an
artery that's an
artery that's a liver right
here
okay you can be someone that that's on a
vegan diet a vegetarian diet a
Mediterranean
diet keto diet carnivore diet and your
liver go to
[ __ ] because you can have three
varieties of Epstein bar one variety of
hhb6 one variety of cegal virus two
varieties of shingles sitting inside
your liver with a whole bunch of metals
that were passed down from generation to
generation that have nothing to do with
this lifetime and your liver be a
problem and you can be drinking coffee
and tea black tea and green tea
supplements and you can be eating
chocolate and your
adrenals your adrenals
fall apart they're throwing out
adrenaline every day the adrenaline's
getting stopped up by your
liver it's not about processed foods
it's not it's other
things the same people right now telling
people don't you processed foods or
gobbling down the caffeine every single
day they're acting like they're Health
experts they're out there talking on the
lecture scene they're going on TV and
they're sitting there process foods
process foods meanwhile their caffeine
habit is off the charts they're teaching
people still drink your caffeine make
sure you still do that oh and don't
worry about alcohol either it's
processed foods the problem and what's
happening is their adrenals are blowing
out all this adrenaline it's saturating
their liver and that adrenaline makes
the liver tired and the liver goes fatty
even on a plant-based diet a vegan diet
a clean keto diet
a clean carnivore diet whatever it is
your liver can still get Mucky still
problematic your gallbladder can still
turn to crap filled with all kinds of
junk and debris and that's what could
happen right
there and so the processed food people
they're just they're just decoys trying
to become famous at this point oo I got
a buzz a lot of people are interested in
this process food processed food thing
yeah great maybe I'll make it my mission
in life life to stop the processed food
because it's killing the
planet meanwhile there's so many there's
a sea of chronically ill people all ages
suffering horribly suffering terribly
out there they're suffering for real
reasons yeah a baby boomer is going to
have a heart problem a baby boomer is
their liver going to get all stinky and
and sluggish yeah they're going to have
putrifying junk in their their arteries
that got into plaque on their walls fat
deposits on the walls of their arteries
yeah they're they're going to get
pre-diabetes they're going to get type
two diabetes Yep they're going to get
all that and then they're going to gain
weight lots of weight they're going to
get that too absolutely of course they
are and every cheeseburger they eat is
going to bring them to more weight but
guess what that person could still have
energy that person could still feel
strong that person can still be out in
the garden working they can still be
mowing the lawn and then a 19-year-old
is bedridden and no one knows wiser
nobody knows what's going on and the
19-year old is bedridden because they
got Epstein bar to the brain to the
nervous system and they've seen 20
doctors and they've had all their blood
drawn out of them and they don't have
answers they've been on steroids and
antibiotics and everything else now
they're on anti-depressants and benzos
and everything
else no one cares but it's processed
food that did it
sure sure all right let's check on
St and I just got some markers on my
hand all
right I think we're ready now I'm going
to pull the dish out I
think or I might have another minute or
two but let's see CU I turned it up hang
on you guys
yeah I mean it's looking real good but
I'm going to give it another
minute so true Anam Marta over there on
YouTube says so true Julie Tuesday 144
Julie Tuesday thanks for all the support
thanks for leaving comments like you do
I see it I read the comments you guys I
see the comments if you like this video
give me a thumbs up I never asked for
one or give me a like or whatever you
call
it you know
if you can share it with someone if you
can this information is really um
precious information from
above and it's always one step ahead of
what's happening out there mm info is
always one step ahead of what's going on
out there
always what's your answer to the ideal
diet I just saw as a question take a
look at brains saver protocols find out
what's wrong with you get the metals out
of you get the viruses killed
off you want to kill the viruses you
want to kill the bad bacteria you want
to bring your your gallbladder back to
life you want to bring your liver back
to life you want to clean up your organs
you want to get rid of a brain that's
clogged up with junk garbage poisons and
toxins you want to clean up dirty blood
syndrome sounds overwhelming just start
with one thing thing do the morning
cleanse just start with one thing do the
28 day cleanse do the heavy metal detox
cleanse but and ask your doctor what's
right for you okay take it to your
doctor the book and ask them if they say
fine go with
it but the ideal diet is customized to
you and what happens is here's what's
going on out there well keto is just
keto right is that customized to you or
is that just a one siiz fits all for a
whole bunch of people that want to keto
or what about this right you want to do
carnivore that's just a one siiz all fit
you know one
siiz that's it for
everybody that's all that is right or
you want to do something else it's one
size for just everybody right just one
thing so here's the thing what people
don't understand when you're doing
medical Medium you're customizing the
protocols you're looking at your
problems you're finding out what's wrong
with you there there are hundreds and
hundreds of different protocol calls
because you're looking for what's going
on with you and you can make it right
for yourself you can still do medical
medium and eat meat you can still do
medical medium and eat chicken if you
really wanted to you can still do
medical medium and be plant-based you
can be raw plant-based if you want and
still do medical medium but that's the
incredible part it's geared for women
and Women's Health and men too and it's
geared for customizing to what's going
on with each individual and that's what
the medical medium books have done and
you see there's a little emblem on that
book right
there see that little emblem right there
millions of copies sold in the medical
medium series millions of people around
the world had their lives changed they
live by these they're their Bibles they
sit in their kitchens with them these
books are packed with
information keep that in mind and then
stuff gets poached out of here yep it
has it's been poached out of all the
medical medium books all right so I
think my dish is just about ready I'm
going to pull it out
see here all right there we
are I am going to be careful because
this is hot and I'm using a hand towel
instead of an oven mitt
because some of the this is because it's
a bad idea but I did it anyway I did not
get burned
no I didn't so here we
go this thing is blazing hot and I don't
want to get my finger caught in there
whoa here it is you guys there it is
potato and cherry tomato
bake just showing
you woo and it's a hot one too let it
cool down a little
bit we'll give it a minute and then
we'll cut right into it see what's going
on
I love these cherry
tomatoes people are eating cherry
tomatoes again they're eating tomatoes
Again Medical medium books talked about
how The Nightshade thing was a
theory and not accurate people are
eating tomatoes
again all
right so back to
processed food
propaganda all
right there's a reason why it's becoming
like it
is Talk of the Town it's becoming
popular it's becoming the trend to hate
on processed foods there's a reason it's
to make people believe that their
chronic illness and their symptoms and
their conditions comes from those
processed
foods there's a reason why
that correlation is being forced upon
everybody and that influencers are being
stupid enough to actually run with it
and act like they're you know an expert
at this you know processed food whole
thing and that people should look out
and they should know that the rules need
to change out there and food needs to be
cleaner I get that
part but it's not responsible for your
chronic illness
you can be on a keto diet and feed your
viruses you can be on a keto diet and
feed your bacteria you can be
on an animal protein diet that's you
know the the animals are killed in your
backyard the Butter's made you churned
it yourself with your own cows and
you're churning your butter you're
milking your own cows and you're
drinking raw milk from your own cow and
you will feed your viruses and you will
be bedridden
sure if you weren't sick yet and you're
doing that everything looks great but if
you ever get sick one day or if a bug
finally gets a little strength and it
rises up it's going to feed on the foods
that you're eating even though you're
not doing processed food life you're
doing everything made at
home you're growing your all your own
food you can still get sick you're
raising your chickens you're you're
collecting your chicken eggs every
single day and you're eating them and
you're feeding them to your family and
then all of a sudden one of your
children out of your five healthy
children starts getting sick you don't
know
why because there's a virus that the
child has that's starting to take off
and grow and so now you got teenagers
and your teenagers are now some of them
are getting acne and they're getting
different problems and getting sick or
getting tired or getting some OCD and
you're like I don't get it because I've
been churning my own milk I've been
churning my own butter I've been raising
my own cows I got my like I'm raising my
own chickens they get the best organic
eggs possible I'm raising them myself
why does my daughter have OCD why does
my son have ADD what's going on and what
happened what's going on and what
happened and then you just start then
you're like what have I done wrong is it
what I'm doing what's going on it's
because there's pathogens and metals and
these Metals get into everybody they're
everywhere and we get exposure and
that's just how it works down
here there are people out there that
live by the L land right they're back to
the Landers they live off the land they
grow everything then they got sick
children like they got sick children
that got sick later after they've been
living off the land it's not because
they were living off the land that got
them sick
it's way better than processed food
diets way better than rolling up to
McDonald's every single day with your
kids definitely doesn't mean your
children are free from getting sick or
OCD when they're in college or be on
Aderall when they're you know 21 years
old or whatever it is it doesn't mean
they're not going to get exposed and
pick up bugs and pick up a new strap
from somebody else or something else and
pick up a new virus and have three
varieties of epsteam bar virus herpes
simplex one going to their brain stem
and then the 22-year-old 23-year-old is
now looking around for answers and is
mad at Mom and Dad now saying You Raised
Me on cow milk grown in our yard and You
Raised Me on chicken eggs but
something's wrong cuz I'm sick I can't
function I'm on
Aderall I've seen it because I've I've
known a lot of back to Landers over the
years and they're like how did this
happen and why is this
happening it's because it's not just
about staying away from processed foods
you should stay away but it's not just
about that there's so so much more there
the details are in the medical medium
books and yes in the medical medium
books it says stay away from processed
foods of course it
does stay away from fried greasy fast
food everywhere in
Europe here in the
states everywhere stay away from it but
if you're eating it it's not the sole
reason why you're sick sure your weight
will go up you'll feel sick your
lymphatic system will feel up with
poison and toxins
yes but there's people out there that
aren't doing anything like they're not
doing anything like that they're eating
really pure really clean and they're
suffering they can't even take a shower
they can't function they can't walk they
have brain inflammation they have
pathogens so it's important to yeah keep
them off the processed foods
but the keto
diets the other diets out there the high
fat vegan diets they can keep people
sick or or also get them sick as well
how many people went vegan and
plant-based and did the high fat vegan
plant-based diet and got themselves sick
and was like what the hell's going on
now they're back on animal protein now
they're back in carnivore carnivore with
honey and fruit but they're on they're
back to carnivore now with honey and
fruit and they were
plant-based and even being plant-based
they're doing high fat plantbased high
fat raw high fat cooked
and they still got themselves sick their
liver still got all kinds of
congested they still got gallbladder
problems eating so many nuts and Tahini
having too many oils way too much salt
off the chart and they got sick and then
they run to eggs now they're back on
eggs now they're back on dairy products
now they're back there they went from
vegan now they're eating hard cheese
AIDS just right that's not processed
from
Italy anyway you guys I'm going to cut
the soap in here or take a scoop or
however you want to call
it I might use this but I'm not
sure I might use
this bear with me for a second please
I might use
[Music]
these all
right so I'm going to cut this like a
pie or a
scoop yeah
so this is not really meant to be sliced
it's meant to be scooped just giving you
a
411 so it's meant to be
scooped but I'm going to kind of St it
in like a slice almost maybe I'll try
that and I'm going to kind
of peel it back here there we go all
right I'm going to get that on a plate
bear with
[Music]
me I'm just going to take this plate
right here if you guys don't mind and
I'm going to put
this right on here nice scoop right
here and I think I might
make another slice go another scoop go
into the other side of that plate
there there we
go all right I think I used the wrong
utensil but still it came out good I'm
going to get a fork
I think I'll use this Fork right
here that's it right there you guys over
there on Tik
Tok over there in
Rumble you guys on Rumble I really
appreciate you being there great place
Rumble and I'm having a little bit of
this that's insane I wish you guys were
with me but you know what's
amazing we're going to be all together
well oh whoever got the tickets at Cafe
Gratitude right in
October it's going to be an intimate
setting I'm going to be
there and it's going to be incredible
the pop-up
dinners all
right I went down really
hot I need a
chaser is that that slid down hot whoa
do you ever do that right you're like
you're like
Russian yeah I know you guys are hearing
things
right all right you got tickets for the
Monday one Amanda on
YouTube this is so good can you guys
make
this that's right here that's in this
life- saving book right here here it is
yum yum
yep Chelle says over there on YouTube
can you talk about opening up detox
Pathways here's how it
works when you're doing medical medium
information if you're doing the heavy
metal detox cleanse 369 cleanse you're
already opening them
up that's the whole
point you're cleansing that's what
you're doing but you can't open up
detail detox Pathways I'm going to tell
you something about detox Pathways first
of all nobody knows what the detox
pathways are out there there's no
science that actually shows something
detoxing down a pathway and so forth
right it was a term that was made up for
your
detoxing
but I mean the crap that's out there so
detox Pathways works like this
okay everybody's detox pathway is
different everybody's detox pathway is
different not all the
same because everybody is clogged up in
a different place
everybody is in a different situation
it's not one size fits all the whole
detox pathway talk falls into one siiz
fits all again medical medium
information isn't one siiz fits-all so
it doesn't adhere to the dogma of detox
Pathways because everybody's different
you may have a clogged up liver in a
different part of the liver the bottom
of the liver the center of the liver the
top of the liver you may have extremely
dehydrated dirty blood syndrome you may
have different adrenal problems than
somebody else it's releasing adrenaline
getting in the way of
detoxification everybody's detox pathway
do you want to call it that is
different one size fits all
is not a great thing when it comes down
to Healing that's why medical medium
information has the most people healed
worldwide than anything else there ever
was or ever will
be there's nothing out there there's no
influencer that got more people better
there's no you know there's no system
out there health system with some kind
of Dogma in the alternative medicine
world that got more people
better there's no place on this planet
that got more people healed and better
and recovered than medical medium
information in books ever it does not
exist so keep that in mind detox
Pathways is a one- siiz
fits-all bringing you to a place that
that's how it's going to work for you
it's like strong arming you to that's
how it's going to work for you but you
are different than this person this
person's different than this person
remember it's all about customizing
somebody May detox quicker because they
have a different pathway way than
somebody else not all or everybody's
organs sit in the same position not
every single organ is the same size not
everybody's bloodstream flows the same
way detox Pathways is kind of just a
[ __ ] term for just you know come to
me and I'll teach you how to
detox when you're doing when you're
getting the metals out you're cleaning
up the liver you are detoxing but you're
detoxing on the rate that your body
wants to detox on you're customizing it
to what your body needs and wants to do
you're different than somebody else keep
that in
mind yeah jeno over there on YouTube
word
word so keep in mind you guys that
that's how it works your lymphatic
system is a different size than somebody
else's lymphatic system and your kidneys
function and squeeze poisons out
different than somebody else's kidneys
do and your heart is smaller than
somebody else's heart and your heart is
bigger than somebody else's heart and
keep in mind with this you have
different toxins and poisons hanging up
organs your detoxification process isn't
the traditional madeup term of detox
pathway yours is going to be different
than somebody else but what so so has
done Spirit of compassion has offered is
it's not one siiz fits all offered
customizing and allowing the body to
choose its pathway the way it needs to
go for you and not just for one size
fits all and that's the difference so
when you do like the 28 day cleanse or
the 369 your body will decide how it's
going to cleanse properly the way you
need it done for customizing the way
your body works and what happened to
your body you're not somebody
else by the
way that's just a tip of the iceberg I
can cut into the detox bathway thing all
day
yeah with you know all of
it when you're healing symptoms
neurologically that you've had for 20
years and you're healing them on medical
mum
information that supersedes any any
stupid detox pathway
talk you're mending nerves and healing
them you're recovering yourself you're
fixing your brain you're losing you're
getting rid of the atrophy of the brain
you're getting brain tissue back how
about that you think I'm worried about
detox pathway when I'm worried about
getting people's brains to plump up
meaning like get brain material grain
matter to develop getting gleo cells to
reproduce getting liver cells to
reproduce and heal getting rid of you
know hunks of fat out of the liver and
getting livers to come back that's what
I'm worried about getting nervous
systems to recover getting milin nerve
sheets to repair you think I'm worried
about detox Pathways when I'm worried
about getting somebody's brain stem
fixed and their cranial nerves got holes
in them
and their cranial nerves aren't
functioning right think I'm worried
about detox pathway [ __ ] when people
got literally cranial nerve problems
where their nerves are falling apart and
they're so sick I'm worried about fixing
the real problem the Nerf the detoxing
happens naturally for each individual
just like it's supposed to when you're
healing and doing the right things and
there's nothing more cleansing and detox
detoxifying the medical medium
information nothing more cleansing and
detoxifying I'm sorry but there is it
and well what happens is I'm worried
about getting people to heal their
nerves their organs their nervous system
their cranial nerves that's what I'm
talking about that's what I care about
and guess what the detox pathway people
they didn't even know about that they
didn't even know people had neurological
problems they were all like oh you're
toxic you're
toxic I saw years of that and then they
put alcohol and the supplements they're
offering everybody be a Salesman for my
supplement company and here here's um
there's alcohol in these supplements oh
this is for your detox
Pathways all right you guys I love
you I'm going to um tank I'm going to
sit down and I'm going to have some
food I love you guys seriously