we're live right now live on facebook
live on youtube live on tick tock live
at clubhouse
celery juice kills yeah
it does celery juice
can kill it's interesting right
what does it kill it kills the pathogens
of viruses
hhv-6 hhv7
epstein-barr hpv
sedimental virus herpes simplex
8 1 2 hh v8
hhv 10 through 16. people walk around
with all these different bugs
they have them in them these bugs
different varieties of shingles viruses
different varieties of epstein-barr
that gives you the fatigue and all the
different vertigo
tingles and numbness aches and pains
celery juice
kills and it kills for you
it's killing for you let me just say
this right just
if i can just have your ear for just a
second you guys okay
what food out there
does that much killing do they all kill
for you
do all the foods kill for you
a lot of the foods kill you
so they kill you all right
and whether it's slowly whether it's
like i always say death by a thousand
cuts a lot of foods out there kill you
slowly over time a little bit at a time
a little bit of time right
but what foods out there kill for you
think about that like what foods what
foods kill for you you guys have a
clubhouse with
what foods kill for you something to
think about right there now
medical medium talks about antiviral
compounds antibacterial compounds in
fruits herbs leafy greens
wild foods right but there's only
one herb one
herb that supersedes
antiviral compounds
super seeds one herb
and it's celery it's celery
when you think about it aren't we in
this
plague pandemic plague
everybody's been locked down all this
stuff happening
right because of a pathogen
because of a bug a bug
a virus okay and
i spent decades teaching people about
bugs teaching people about epstein-barr
teaching people about books fc1 was
forgotten about it was just tucked away
it was forgotten about
two amazing virologists discovered
epstein-barr
right and they discovered it
and nobody cared nobody cared
that's right all these people getting
sick every day chronic illness getting
sick every day
all these people those people nobody
knew epstein-barr
did one thing nobody knew it
carried on it has a long lasting
lifeline in your body epstein-barr
isn't just mono because research in
science
after two brilliant virologists
discovered epstein-barr research in
science
just believed you had mono you get some
swollen glands one time only
you get a little bit of a fever you get
like listlessness malaise
right and that's it once it goes away
it never it never matters there's no
such thing as as epstein-barr
medical medium information changed the
world of medicine
right now it did by the way this is on
sale the lowest i've ever seen it's 49
off amazon.com us it's 18
and some change it's a medical textbook
it's already saved millions of lives
it's the new edition that's the one you
guys the new edition just letting you
know
an incredible book still saving lives
today
it's 18 and 72 cents it costs more to
print that book and make it
it costs more to make it so
epstein-barr was just this thing where
it was mononucleosis
so after after two great virologists
discovered epstein-barr
they discovered well that was the reason
for mononucleosis
that was the discovery right there but
then you get mono it goes away
never to worry about it ever again
that's it medical medium
changed all that epstein-barr
reactivated epstein-barr
epstein-barr causing more symptoms
neurological symptoms
neurological fatigue all this is all
this epstein-barr information is all
medical medium
doctors are using it worldwide that's
right
they talk about it on podcasts they talk
about it all over the place
and it originates from the publication
right here and also 35 years
of work so why am i even talking about
epsilon
you're wondering you don't have
epstein-barr you're thinking you're not
who cares
you don't have it everybody has it and
it awaits to come out
and the plague we're up against today
brings it out
that's medical medium information it was
published first by medical medium
and then it's being taken now okay and
they're calling it the long haul
covid now the long haul covet that's
what they call it
the long haul is epstein-barr
and i've seen bar causing that
right getting activated so i just spent
years talking about how the flu
activates epstein-barr how it lowers the
immune
immune system and activates epsom bar
and then i
published about how okay i published
about how
the plague we're up against today
instigates
right that's the textbook dr faun md
good to see you instigates
epstein barr and it comes out of
dormancy
hiding right
and all that one of the secrets to
healing
so ivan says try to taking little
let try taking a little less i was
allergic to apple
but it went away by chance by changing
the liver so by actually
helping your liver you're able to eat a
little bit more apple
anyway which is you know well if you're
cleaning up all the toxins and poisons
and all that you'd be surprised what you
can do once you start getting rid of all
those poisons and toxins and everything
else
so when it comes that dr faun good to
see you that it's an incredible textbook
really
it really is incredible medical textbook
and
it has advanced medical information good
to see you cold white spring
ashley kevin kristen says i can't
believe
i caught you live yay you make my day i
can't believe it either i'm so glad to
have you here
celery juice kills for you is what it
does
so here we are the whole world is in an
uproar
the whole world is in fear and chaos and
panic right
for a year plus right
over the plague that we've been up
against and then there's something out
there
that kills bugs kills bugs
actually destroys them kills for you
doesn't kill you it kills for you that's
what's incredible about celery juice
that's what's amazing now of course some
of you might
beg to differ and be like oh you can eat
some celery sticks and that's kind of
healthy you can have a couple of celery
sticks you could chew a few celery
sticks
that's healthy but celery can't do
anything for you
it can't do anything right
but we've seen something different
because millions of people are drinking
it getting their lives back
and they're using medical devices
that they don't need a prescription for
right do you need a prescription for
celery juice
random we'll call this says celery juice
lifted me out of
hell of insomnia so grateful that means
everything
that means everything think about that
right there
dr sherry green good to see you the
teaching information
here is priceless honored you feel that
way incredible doctor
dr sherry green so
when you really think about it okay
would you
like celery oh you want some celery
juice well i'm going to have to write a
prescription out to you
i'm going to have to write a
prescription you can't have celery juice
you know what's crazy about our world is
the medical industry
with love would love to like keep
everything
away from you everything like celery
juice
and supplementation they would love
to just keep it all under their watch
and then prescribe
a crappy version a shittier version if
they really wanted to like just
prescribe
something like that's what they would do
they're going to do it to b12
they're going to do it to vitamin c in
in the future people are not going to be
able to get vitamin c they're not going
to be able to buy i think it's going to
have to be
prescribed by a physician if the
physician believes that it's okay to do
and if the physician isn't
watched isn't watched
meaning like watched because they're
prescribing too much vitamin c
so they're going to be they're going to
be under limitations where
where doctors down the road years down
the road mark my word right here
years down the road doctors are going to
be they're going to be prescribing
vitamin c and it's small dosages
like okay 250 milligrams a day
one tablet here you go
big pharma took over the vitamin c they
own it now here you go
that's how it's going to go no one's
going to be able to get better
like that but that's how they want it
because if you're rogue if you're doing
things
your way you're rogue that's what you
are
you're rogue and because right now we're
allowed to take vitamin c
you know that's what i take is the
microc right there
but we're allowed to take vitamin c we
are
i take a whole bunch you can ask your
doctor what's right for you i'm just
telling you for me and my family
we take a lot of it we take a lot of it
so but eventually down the road it's all
going to be taken away from everybody
way down the road
and it's going to be under prescription
only and it's going to be a real crappy
kind
and they're going to be like here's
here's your prescribed dosage is all you
can take right there
that's what's going to happen down the
road just giving everybody the 4-1-1
same thing with b12
not going to have the freedom down the
road to just have b12
because science research and big pharma
and powers at b
and powers above and all the
illuminations
the illuminations are going to make sure
they have full control over our b12 too
so you get the crappy kind and it's
prescribed by only prescription
probably through shot only b12 shot
b12 shot and i told you guys about the
b12
shots you can do what you want do your
doctor tells you
but i would never let vitamin b12 go
into my arm through an ejection and
through an injection
ever ever ever vitamin b12
that's just me personally and my family
and but
down the road it's different when it
goes into the vein when b12 goes into
intravenous
vitamins the vein is different so
if you're getting intravenous iv
vitamins if you're someone like that
and you're getting vitamin b through the
veins
that's different but through an actual
injection a shot right
i would never get b12 ever
injected into the body like
from the outside the vein is different
go back to what i was saying and because
what happens is when you get when you
get
b12 shots you guys on clubhouse
guys on tick tick tick tock facebook
youtube when you get b12 shots you can
become allergic to b12
i've talked about this in the past your
body can build an
antibody against b12
making you in trouble with b12
if you had that before it's okay that
can be turned around
go to your doctor and you say hey i only
i only want to be on b12
oral b12 you can change
you can change things up and it turns
things around
michelle l said b12 shots killed her
you seem fine to me chris chris is wow
um good to see you so
me personally i would never ever
take a b12 shot vitamin b12
in a needle going into the body into the
arm into the leg into the butt
whatever that's me personally
so i have my friends and family do the
oral b12
and as far as vitamin c goes enjoy it
why it's
here because it won't be down the road
but enjoy it why it's here so why am i
talking about this a lot of people
aren't going to be
are going to have the access to vitamin
c years down the road
but we're going to have celery we're
still going to have celery access for a
while i really believe that
and eventually that's going to get weird
and they're going to halt the farming
productions down they're going to
put orders to make sure farms aren't
allowed to
grow that much celery probably gonna
spin some lies
that celery crops are damaging the
planet
because celery juice is one of our
tickets
one of our tickets to health freedom to
health freedom
ali says i can't believe people are
listening to this garbage
and getting spooked by it ali hall
well i think your psychiatrist
is calling me right now ollie because i
think i had an appointment with your
psychiatrist we were going to talk about
you
dr fizbot yeah you're the psychiatrist
for ollie
yeah what what do you think is going on
huh whoa
whoa
whoa yeah
dr feesbot is there any way you can help
ollie
you're you're a psychiatrist
straightjacket i don't i don't advise
that
dr fees but i would not put ollie in a
straitjacket that's terrible
i don't think that's right i want a
second opinion
i have dr chicken here
so i want a second opinion so i got
so uh
hold on okay so dr fees bot so ali
said don't listen to this garbage here
because it's
no one should listen to this garbage
over here um
the straight jacket for always too harsh
don't do that are you gonna section
eight ollie
don't section eight ollie no don't do
that that's terrible
oh what do you think um dr
nesbitt what do you think do i got
chicken dr nesbitt
that's his nickname do you think olly
should get into a straight jacket
you do no that's terr we have two two
professionals right here i got
the psychiatrist on the phone and i got
dr nesbit
the chicken with me and both think
ali is certifiable
that's terrible you guys that's horrible
that's not fair to anybody and no one
should
you got you guys first of all i
recommend ollie
talk to a different psychiatrist
yeah yeah i'm gonna reach out to ali and
recommend a couple different good
psychiatrists that i know out there that
would never do anything horrible
no they're really good doctors and they
help a lot of people
dr nesbitt what do you say
dr nesbitt wants to talk to you hold on
the the doctors are talking to each
other right now
just bear with me dr nesbitt the chicken
is talking to dr
fizbot always psychiatrist
okay what did you guys come conclusion
that ollie just needs celery juice
maybe that might help okay
okay wait but you think celery juice is
placebo
no it's not it's helped a lot of people
okay we're going to talk about placebo
okay guys
i'll tell you you know um health
professionals
they just say terrible things this is
awful dr sherry green you're an amazing
doctor it's an honor that you're on here
dr fond you're an amazing doctor it's an
honor that you guys are on here
um so we're talking about a few things
right here like a whole bunch of stuff
you guys i want to i want to update
everybody that just came on austin good
to see you
much light and love really good to see
you too um every now and then when i
catch your comments in the youtube
section
right good to see you guys dr chicken
marissa
and so let's go into this a little bit
more we have information to cover
they want to erwin says they want to
keep us sick they have to keep us sick
the industries have to keep you sick
that's how it works and
one way you know is that there are
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of healing stories of celery juice
helping people get out
of the woods and into the light right
but the industry they just they don't
want to know about that they don't
because because god forbid we hurt their
pockets we hurt the yachts that they
ride on
and we hear about all of it we hurt
their pockets
right massive massive mansions all that
built by people being sick right people
being sick
and so celery juice is one of these
things that's really helpful so here we
go we got a plague
circling the planet right everybody's
worried about it
right and has been worried about it
and we have a bug killer
at the grocery store so we have a bug
killer at the grocery store
because celery juice kills
it kills it's really incredible when you
think about it
i just want to look i want to cover a
couple little things you guys
first of all the mm-900 hds i don't know
if you guys
have seen this user mm-900 hds
um anyway it's 82 off just letting you
guys know
it's still on sale 25 off um
letting people know so in case someone
this is their chance or something
at this time because it's such a break
on there if you got any juice or use it
because your juicer is a medical tool
keep that in mind
people ask me all the time what juicer
do i use with juicer what do you mean
it's a medical tool what do you mean
the minute i said that everybody's like
what do you mean it's it's a medical
tool
i see it as a medical tool that's my
opinion
i i wonder what your your opinion is you
guys but my opinion is
it's a medical tool i talk to doctors
all the time and i'm like
look it's a medical tool like how is it
a medical tool
it's created to extract
herbal medicine so herbal medicine
it extracts herbal medicine so we can do
some healing
ernest says omega h um omega
mm 900 hds is the best juicer ever
it really is it really is i'm going to
do some juicing in a minute to you guys
what i like about the juicer is it pays
for itself i told you that before
sound like a broken record the other
reason i like it is because it's not
dealing with
metal always touching metal so that's a
juice there's a lot of juicers out there
there's so much metal everywhere and so
and that metal just starts to kind of
corrode that's what metal does it
corrodes
it it eventually starts to break down
that's what metal does
and so that's what i don't like you know
about the other juicers
this doesn't have that crystal clear
says
it really is a miracle i was miserable
every year with hay fever
and it made it disappear for real so if
celery juice
made something that was keeping you
miserable
every single year the worst hay fever
and it got rid of that what do you think
is going on there
one reason is hay fever
really is something else right you get
sensitive
to plants to weeds that are growing
you get sensitive to pollen you get
sensitive to dust
grass dust right it gets sensitive to
to um pine pollen okay
oak tree pollen maple pump you get
sensitive to all the pollen right
and then but one of the reasons why is
because there's something else
underlying so whenever it comes down to
allergies and stuff like that sinus
allergies where it's eye related sinus
related
hay fever in the head all that stuff in
the lungs you're dealing with
streptococcus
and then you start bringing celery in
and you start killing the strep
and when you start killing the strep you
can all of a sudden handle
that ragweed you can handle all that
white ragweed all that hay
and that's what's incredible about it
right there
um love god celery juice stopped my
colitis symptoms in a week
incredible lysi cohen good to see a good
friend of mine lissy
good to see you today so
when it comes down to it celery juice
kills and it kills for you that's what
it does
it kills and it kills for you there's
foods out there
that kill you right
the foods out there that kill you one of
the foods out there that kills us
is not buddy buddy
we we kept buddy alive we didn't let
buddy go to slaughter
so buddy's not killing us but when you
cook buddy
buddy kills you this man is saving my
life thanks mmm
and sophie thanks thanks so much for
being here
incredible truly is pork is one of those
foods that does kill us
it really does kills us over time
shortens our lives
kills our kidneys kills our kidneys and
kidney disease is crazy out there right
now but everything tastes good with
bacon
everything tastes good with bacon right
elizabeth says hey buddy and
but foods can kill so let's talk about
something too you guys before i do a
little juicing i want to cover
i want to cover something interesting
so what i got right here in front of me
you guys recognize this
is this mm glass right here a little
ammo class
so what i got tick-tock you guys
facebook youtube
clubhouse i i have some kidneys in front
of me right now
and what you're looking on top though
what you're looking at on top of these
kidneys is
what's this you guys right
that's your adrenals right there so
you're looking at your adrenals
and what i love about celery juice is
celery is used to something absolutely
amazing
it helps restore your adrenal glands
just like it helps to restore your
stomach lens remember the other day you
guys
remember the other day talking about the
stomach
right about the stomach and the stomach
glands that's your hcl
cellular juice helps to bring your
depleted stomach glands back
rebuilding your hcl so your hcl could
then kill pathogens
right yeah renata says it's the adrenals
my poor mom has adrenal cancer
i'm so sorry to hear that um
that's really difficult to to i mean she
must be struggling
so what happens is these stomach glands
um
they restore from that celery juice now
something else restores from that soy
juice
it's your adrenal glands so that's the
next thing
so the sodium cluster salts the trace
mineral salts and celery juice
go into your stomach glands and help
restore it
and then celery juice goes into
adrenal tissue as well and helps restore
it because
that's when they get depleted when they
get deleted they lose trace minerals
the cells in your adrenals need
a certain amount of trace minerals
and we lose those trace minerals we're
not getting them in good sources in good
places
we're under fight or flight we're
tanking the caffeine
we're taking the caffeine guys don't mat
you guys don't guys don't mind i'm gonna
do a little coffee break and i'm gonna
have a little chocolate too
so you guys are okay with that so let's
just take everybody
everybody i'm just gonna take a break
i'm gonna i'm gonna hold off talking and
i'm just gonna have a little bit of
coffee
gotta have my coffee
god coffee is good
guys i'm on coffee break you guys and uh
i'm about to have a piece of chocolate
too
chris chris you seem fine of me you want
a piece of chocolate with me
we're on coffee break right now all
right
just one more sip i gotta get high i got
it
it's actually really good that's really
good coffee too incredible
one thing to know about our adrenal
glands is coffee is like its number one
enemy chocolate it's it's number one
enemy too
so the reason why we lose our adrenals
over time and women lose their hair
because women are not supposed to have
hair loss they lose their hair
and their skin gets aged before it's
time
part of that is the adrenals dying the
adrenals die
so what happens is when we're aging
there's parts of us
inside of us that are actually dying our
liver starts to die
yeah and organs can die before we die do
you ever guys ever notice that
why do you think somebody can have a
heart condition and when someone has
heart
failure yeah and they're told they have
heart failure right
well it's like when you get diagnosed
with heart failure what does that mean
that means you're alive that means
you're alive
but your heart's dying right it's sick
think about that i mean isn't that crazy
how it works
we're alive we're living our lives and
organs in us
can start to die
and so what happens with adrenals
that's one of those glands that
endocrine system glands
those start to die slowly but you don't
want them
dying before we die you see how it works
i know this is intense to talk about you
don't want your adrenal glands
to putting before you
ever kaput in your life right
and so what happens with caffeine
i know i'm giving you guys a little
caffeine talk for a couple seconds you
guys love that
right caffeine destroys our adrenal
glands
i get it you know somebody who drank
coffee for 30 years they're fine i get
it
a lot of people drink coffee for two
years and they're not fine they blew out
their adrenals
yeah a lot of people eat chocolate they
burn out their adrenals
but it's the caffeine you know the
matcha tea or the chocolate
the coffee that caffeine
burns out our adrenals so you got to
think about your adrenals because
without them we
really are we're in trouble with outer
adrenals we're in big trouble
and if you're drinking your celery juice
and somebody says why are you drinking
your celery
are you drinking celery juice because of
that crazy medical medium
because uh that guy who's a medium who
talks to a spirit
why are you drinking celery you're
drinking celery juice
because you want to keep your adrenals
strong you want those restored you want
those recovered
you want your adrenals to come back
you want them strong you want them
strong
so it's so important so let's talk about
how celery juice does that i'm going to
juice a little bit of celery now
we're going to go into that for a little
bit you guys
talking about restoring the adrenals
we're talking about how celery juice
kills because it does
it does it kills the bugs
that are inside of everybody
i can't tell you how many years i've
been teaching about all the different
viruses and bacteria and what they do
and what they cause
and i've i've i've talked to a lot of
deaf ears
people just it's gone right it's just
like they're they're not even hearing it
professionals i've talked to a lot of
professionals we're like
there's no way there's no way pathogens
have anything to do with anything
there's no way
and then and then the whole world shuts
down
over a pathogen now you got all these
people
they're not being held accounted
accountable for being so ignorant about
pathogens
and now they're they're they're viral
experts now
everybody's a virus expert now
when two years ago they didn't even
think they existed
but now they're but no one's holding
anybody accountable and say hey buddy
you know what you didn't even think
pathogens existed a year and a half ago
why are you such the expert now exactly
in this world right now you don't have
to be held accountable
you can just totally screw up in the
health realm
over and over and over again be a
podcast person
be you know be be a different health
authority
and you can just make mistake after
mistake no one's saying hey
you just screwed up because two years
ago you believed
that celery juice was you know was
terrible for you
now you're thinking it might be helpful
it's like dude own up to how you were
ripping it apart all that time
it goes it goes like that for anything
though own up how
you didn't even think viruses existed
and now you've been pushed into
pushed into it the media and
and and the pandemic has made it so now
you're open to viruses but
meanwhile you've had patients in your
office
for years and you wouldn't even like
listen about the viral stuff
so uh patrice bennett says
look how much juice you get from just
one stock this is amazing
mine would never do that it is
incredible like
it's you know why the pulps the pulps
dry that's why it's incredible i know
this is the mm-900 hds you guys
i know i told you before but everybody
asks so i have to do a few days of like
hey
you guys this is it this is the model
omega juicers.com
megajuicers.com that's where the sale is
25 82
off on the model but it's the mm-900 hds
they all look the same on there
mega juicers website they got models
that look like this the model though is
is this it's a celery juicer mm-900 hds
[Music]
when i when i do celery in the morning
right
i think about what it's going to do for
me because i know it's like my bodyguard
and i know it's helping keep my adrenals
strong too
because we just burn we burn our
adrenals out that's what we do here on
planet earth
that's what we do best juicery so it's a
bit tate
haliman says best juicer ever so glad i
got it i'm so glad you got it too
i'm so glad i'm so glad
best juicer i've ever owned is paid for
itself over and over again i told you
guys about that before
best user i've ever owned really
incredible
[Music]
so i want to cover a couple of things
today
one is about restoring your adrenals how
critical it is
it's one of the things that we have to
be mindful about take care of
we have to look after if celery juice is
the only thing you can do when you can't
do anything else there's nothing you can
do
you can't do anything else that then
then you're doing celery juice it's
amazing
it's really incredible you're helping
your adrenals
your adrenals are why you can even
function talk on the phone
live your life do your house chores
work work a career talk to friends go
out your adrenals
talk about kidney stones for a little
bit
do that cover kidney stones
everybody has kidney stones by the way
everybody has kidney sediment kidney
stones
[Applause]
it's just how big do you want them to
get that's the key right how big you
want them to get
if you're somebody that it has dealt
with like the bigger
kidney stones big ones where they're
registerable
they can be seen right through testing
did you want to stay off the animal
protein
i'm not anti-animal protein okay i'm not
anti-plant-based either
i support both sides of the aisle always
have
i don't judge anybody either way
i know the animal protein people when
they get irritated they'll say the vegan
mommies are starving their kids
[Music]
i know starving of a protein i know the
plant-based
people will get mad at the animal
protein people
say they have a lack of understanding
about you know
animals having souls and stuff
but too much protein kills the kidney
and you can kill the kidneys too as a
vegan
you can kill your kidneys as a
plant-based person you can do too many
nut butters
right you can kill your kidneys with too
much fat
definitely too much protein we can kill
our kidneys but
the thing is right i'm gonna take this
kidney apart you guys
okay those kidney stones they started
really tiny and they sit in the nooks
and crannies of your kidney
right in the little nooks and crannies
that's what they do they start out
really tiny
and they start to grow kidney stones
actually grow
they become like a magnet actually and
they collect more sediment
and more sediment and more sediment
but the kidney stones are really an
indication
that you got two options you got calcium
based stones you got protein based
stones
you can have a mix you can have calcium
protein-based stones
but let me give you like a couple of
takeaways just right off the bat this
might be worth the price of admission
even though all this is free
it's always free here at medical medium
but
if you're dealing with a calcium-based
stone
the caffeine the vinegar
that will take you down that road
because the caffeine and the vinegar
will suck the life out of your bones and
teeth
it'll pull in pull pull but actually
pull out
all that good calcium okay it's one
thing that happens too
another thing that happens is if you're
eating dairy products
if you're eating eggs if you're eating
too much dairy
milk cheese butter then you can also get
a calcium stone from all of that
but you can get a calcium stone from
either calcium being removed from your
bones
and teeth and it ends up piling up in
the kidneys
so when you're doing your caffeine when
you're doing your coffee
when you're doing your chocolate
right when you're doing your coffee and
you're doing your chocolate
you're actually removing calcium from
your bones
so let me get something else for you
guys you guys are still here
don't worry still here
still mashing it we're still here
okay right here i got a jaw for you tik
tok can you guys see this clubhouse i'm
holding
a jaw that's a big tongue right here so
if you guys could see that big tongue
so that's the lower jaw
okay that's the bone the jaw bone that's
your teeth
okay guys so when you're doing your cat
when you're doing your caffeine
you're drawing calcium from inside your
teeth
and your jaw that calcium that gets
drawn out ends up piling inside your
kidneys
i'm pointing to your kidney now so it
ends up becoming little calcium stones
inside your kidney
calcium stones that can't be seen on
testing tiny
ones lots of tiny ones and you pee them
out
a lot of them don't build up they don't
get caught in there and they don't
become a big old calcium kidney stone
they get caught in there and then you
build them up build them up build them
up because they get caught in there you
guys and caught in there right
so what's happening is you keep on doing
your caffeine you keep on doing your
chocolate you keep on doing your plant
medicine chocolate you keep on doing
your matcha tea
what you do is you keep on drawing
calcium from your teeth and your jaw
and your bones right
you keep on drawing that and then
it ends up in the kidney now when it
ends up in the kidney you get these tiny
little calcium deposits crystallized
calcium
in your kidneys and you urinate them out
most of them out
you think hey i'm pretty good right now
i don't have i don't have any kidney
stones
nothing that seeable but you have the
everyday kidney stones
which nobody talks about nobody talks
about the crystallizations that form
there every single day because of the
caffeine
because of your chocolate because of
your tea and
all those little crystallizations they
all deposit inside that kidney
and here's what's sad about it you're
pissing out
your critical needed your your calcium
your own calcium the calcium that holds
your bones together you're peeing your
own calcium out
you're you're pissing out that's
how it goes so okay i don't have a
kidney stone right now everything's all
clear it looks good no kidney stones
than me
meanwhile you're peeing out lots of
kidney stones every single day lots of
kidney stones you're peeing out all your
calcium stones
calcium stones that are created because
it's just being sucked out of your jaw
being sucked out of your lower jaw
being sucked out of your bones that's
why women go to osteopenia it's why they
head there just letting you guys know so
your coffee every day
slowly draws the calcium out
and then we do too much fat and too much
protein and we
kill our kidneys it's another thing too
we kill our kidneys
then too much fat and protein can bring
some calcium out of your bones as well
but now let's go into the vinegar really
quick the apple cider vinegar or any
kind of
vinegar red wine vinegar balsamic
vinegar whatever vinegar you want
vinegar draws acetic acid draws calcium
from your bones and teeth too
and then this tires your kidneys out so
when i see somebody eating vinegar i'm
like you're tiring your kidneys out
sure you don't see it in the moment but
you're going to see it 30 years from now
20 years from now you're going to see it
somewhere down the line
and one thing spirit of compassion
taught me when i was younger is how to
have that foresight how to see
everything
how to like know and see so again you
see somebody and spirit of compassion
will tell me well yeah they have
about eight crystals in their kidneys
today they have to pee and urinate those
eight crystals out today
and then what i'd say spirit of
compassion well what's gonna happen down
the road well they're going to keep on
urinating those crystals out and keep on
losing and depleting their calcium in
the bones that person's going to get an
osteoporosis diagnosis that person's
going to go
to get osteopenia diagnosis that person
is going to need jaw work
bone graft that person's going to need
bone graft that person is going to lose
all their teeth that person
i i heard this ultimate that person's
skull is going to shrink
that one's terrible i want to cover that
real quick
too that's important we're juicing
celery we're using the mm-900 hds
incredible medical device
it's it's an amazing medical device
so you guys see this right here in
clubhouse i'm holding a brain
a head a skull
so here's what happens as you get older
you lose the calcium in your skull
your skull shrinks and when you get
older your skull is like
half the size because we have these
practices in our life
to draw calcium out of our body we do
all the caffeine we do all the vinegar
and we
are removing calcium from our skull
it's ever so mildly done it's like it's
really
minor yeah you don't see it fast
but it happens but then that day when
you're 65 years old and you slip on some
ice outside and you
land on the back your head and doctor
says well you shouldn't have cracked
your skull open
you shouldn't have fractured your skull
but you're getting older
so you got more kind of a little bit
more feeble a little bit more you're
delicate
you got older what happened is the
reason why your skull
fracture's so easy versus when you were
20 and you bend your head
you were at a pool party when you're 20
years old
right you slip on the deck and you bang
your head on the deck but your
your skull doesn't fracture
because you got enough calcium in your
skull right you're 65 years old you slip
on a deck
you bend your head you're in the you're
in the hospital you've got a fractured
skull
because the calcium's been depleting
throughout
the years nobody talks about cranial
calcium no one
it's medical medium information linda
says why don't doctors tell us all this
they're too busy writing prescriptions
and the functional medicine doctors are
too
too busy bankrolling with the highest
prices i've ever seen these days
i've seen some functional medicine
doctors people got to see them it's
twenty two hundred dollars
to see them they got a huge waiting list
but it's like twenty two hundred dollars
and here's what they get here's your gut
health product here's your fish oil
here's your other gut health probiotic
here's your
apple cider vinegar chewie's here's your
calcium supplement
here's your whatever supplement here's
this here's that here's this here's that
all junk all garbage make sure you go on
the keto diet
and we're going to draw the life out of
you we're going to suck every last
drop of blood out of you and take 14
vials of blood and make sure we do all
this
useless testing because a lot of it is
it's not the stuff people need to be
looking at like for all
all the viral panels and stuff that's
what they really need to be looking at
it's like and then we're going to take
14 to 20 vials out of you
and then 2200 what's your bill was
insurance covering it
you're lucky you got insurance your
lucky one it's twenty two hundred
dollars ma'am
mrs ferguson that's twenty four hundred
dollars
next
all right you guys i got the mm-900 hds
just lost my chocolate bar um
you got to strain the juice here's one
thing just
this is ridiculous ridiculous
this is almost stupid
look at that do you see that it's dry to
the bone
and i'm holding a little tuft of pulp
a little tough of celery pulp look at
that
do you guys see this this is a dry
container that's dry
there's there's no there's no moisture
in this container
i just juiced and there's no moisture in
this container
and i just juiced there's no juicer out
there that's done that yet i haven't
seen one yet and i've had them all
i've tried them all that's the pulp
right there
do you see this you know what that means
i just saved myself a ton of money
ton of money because i only had to use a
little bit of celery
for all this juice this is insane
you gotta strain your celery juice i've
said this a thousand times
you guys if it look i know some of you
guys are total vets
when it comes down to celery juice you
guys been doing it for a while you've
been
following the medical medium information
spirit of compassions books and stuff
and you've been
you've been like diligently doing your
celery juice you strain it all the time
and i know i sound like a broken record
probably but i can't tell you how every
day i see people they're just juicing
celery
they're not straining it and it's a
no-no you have to strain it you guys
you have to i'm just being straight up
about that
you've got to strain it i'm kind of
doing this in a weird way so i'm
spilling a few drops
but that's only because i'm being sloppy
because i'm actually doing this in front
of juicer my arm's all wrapped around
and i'm not even like looking
so i spilled a couple of tiny drops
there which really is sad
because i don't normally do that at all
okay so
look what you have right there and what
you can do is too you'll have a little
bit of pulp in the strainer
and you can squeeze that out right till
it's dry to the bone which i do
i do i love that but look at this
that's your pulp i've never seen that
anywhere
and that's my juice which is incredible
which is incredible which is incredible
it really is um
this is the mm-900 hds it's 82
off but it's the mm-900 hds i told you
guys i'm working with the company on
this because
when they told me that they had this
idea
where they can they can literally
squeeze as much juice as we can out of
celery i was like i'm on board
i'm on board how do we keep this thing
here so it doesn't go away i need people
to have an opportunity
um 32 ounces of celery juice
is what i drink every single morning
sometimes i'll drink more sometimes i'll
drink a little less
anyway it's omegajuicers.com omega omega
juicers.com omegajuicers.com
they have a sale right now it's 25 off
mm-900 hds 82. you save
but what's incredible you have to strain
it
you have to because the pulp and the
fiber
get in the way of the medicine this is
an herbal extraction
it's just like an herbal tea you have to
strain the tea
it's an herbal extraction but the
difference with celery juice you really
have to strain it
okay really important
you can you know and and here's how it
goes
pulp and fiber get in the way of the
sodium cluster salts we're doing herbal
medicine
so you're witnessing a medical tool and
what it's doing is it's extracting
herbal medicine it's extracting medicine
from celery that's how you have to look
at it that's how i look at it every
single morning that's how i see it
then it really is what it is right and
if the pulpit fiber is in the way it
interferes with the sodium cluster salts
and i know i've been showing you guys
this
what's in what's in celery salt
right the healthy form the macro
sodium right okay
but what's around there at least is the
subgroup of sodium
sodium cluster salts they float around
and suspend in a living fluid
that's the subgroup of sodium sodium
cluster salts
that's it trace mineral salts and what
happens is that
when you have fiber and pulp it gets in
the way of this
you have to extract this from the
stalks of celery in order for this to
kill for you
celery juice kills it does
so here's what happens let me just show
you guys right here okay
here's a pathogen right here so here's a
pathogen
i'm gonna do a little drawing here
that's a pathogen okay you guys see that
in tic toc you guys see that
that pathogen when it goes when it goes
near
this sodium cluster salt living fluid
living base this trace mineral living
base that that harbors like a solar
system around
the sodium in celery
when this little solar system
there's thousands of these solar systems
inside your celery juice
thousands thousands
so when that solar system runs across a
pathogen
it kills it it starts to break it down
it starts to destroy it starts to weaken
it
celery juice kills
that's what's incredible and what's
better is it kills for you
that's what it does there's a membrane
on the pathogen right there
and it's these little tiny things right
there you see these things the membrane
it's a slipcover like a pillowcase you
guys
imagine your pillowcase right over your
pillow
that pillowcase is your pillow's
protector right protects the pillow the
pillow can stay clean
[Music]
your pillowcase gets dirty you wash your
pillowcase because your pillowcase gets
dirty
well the virus and the pathogens
all have a membrane a slip cover around
it like a pillowcase cover
and it keeps it safe just like your
pillowcase keeps your pillow safe
and that membrane starts to break down
and dissolves
when it runs across that's the pathogen
right here when it runs across
the sodium cluster dissolves right there
i mean isn't that like incredible what
it does
deb says i've been drinking celery juice
daily for nine months and have healed
chronic tendinitis and vertigo is that
worth it
like does somebody want tendonitis
no right no way it's brutal somebody
want tendonitis somebody want
vertigo no it's brutal nobody wants that
and celery juice turn that around for
you
what's that worth um the juicer is 82
off when i think about i have a friend
that's sick right
a friend that's sick and my friend's
addictions
stop my friend from healing right
my friend has a lot of food addictions
can't break the fats
at all um you know i still love them
i still love them you know i'm not gonna
hate them
i'm still gonna love them and be like
man it's hard to break those food
addictions
my friends got all the food addictions
right
and the whole bit
and just gets sick he gets sick he gets
sick he gets sick he calls me up i want
help i tell him what to do
he says i can't do it my addictions are
too much
and i'm like get a juicer and he's like
get a juicer because you've got to do
celery juice
i can't spend the money i can't spend
the money i can't spend the money
i need my money for other things i'm
like look
bill says i was juicing every morning
for about a month and i started to
develop age spots
on my face not a disbeliever
want to find out why my body reacted
that way
bill it's not the juicing that does that
it's they were coming anyway
coming anyway your celery juice is
working on other things inside your body
right it's working on everything it's
working on cleaning out these kidney
stones i'm talking about it's work
it's working on restoring your adrenals
it's killing off pathogens inside your
body
so your celery juice is doing all this
work it's cleaning up a dirty liver
it's doing all this stuff but those age
spots would have been a lot worse
i've said that to people in the past
don't do celery juice and watch how bad
they get
would be a lot worse don't do celery
juice and people's other problems get a
lot worse
and would have been a lot worse people
already have
a whole bunch of stuff coming on their
way they got a track record of all this
that's in their system and all these
things that have happened and all the
bad foods
and all everything else they got a track
record of it
lots of bad meals lots of all kinds of
stuff lots of eggs
like you know what happens is
people are eating a lot of eggs all
through the years
and then they do caffeine and they're
doing caffeine too and then they're
doing chocolate yeah they might have
chocolate just once in a while
but that chocolate once in a while what
happens is that caffeine in that
chocolate is what brings about age spots
then they got chemicals they got cologne
perfume
in their life they got scented candles
they get all kinds of stuff they get
exposed to and then those age spots are
on their way because caffeine is the big
age spot cause or
it's one of the big ones they got it on
the way thank god you're doing celery
juice bill
because then main spots would have been
a lot worse and now you've got a chance
of getting those age spots cleaned up
down the road too
ernest says age spots can go away just
continue drinking your cj
it's really good advice incredible
advice
i would i would definitely
stay away from eggs if you guys can i
would stay with my caffeine i understand
everybody has a caffeine
um totally get it
angel says my age spots have failed
since
juicing celery so
oh faded so they faded since juicing
celery
typos are funny so yeah
okay so let's go back into a little bit
adrenal talk for a couple minutes but
and before i go in there i'm talking
about like why juice celery why'd you
celery
i've heard that before of the time
ernest says my age spot on my nose
disappeared
i was blown away drinking your celery
juice incredible
so i look at the celery juicer as a
medical device
that's that's different than other
juicers
all juicers are a medical device i look
at it that way okay totally on that
um but yeah
vimala says
robinson ka i'm just a very well
educated person researching healing
methods i have nothing against him
except for his tone of voice is super
nasty
and his money hungry grabber
well
i know i don't i know you give me the
lecture every time
you want me to start doing programs for
three thousand dollars a piece
i know you also want me to put out my
own line of juicers
so i could be a millionaire i know i
don't do it i know
i'm sorry i just don't
you also want me to have subscription
charges on my website because millions
of people hit my website every week
and so if i put subscription charges on
my website
i would make probably a million dollars
a day i won't do it
no i won't i know you're telling me to
do it i know i get the lecture all the
time from upr guys
the pr guys call me and wonder why when
am i going to start doing that
i know i i shouldn't put all the
information in the books to that degree
i should give them a shitty book
which is a few things and then charge
them huge programs for the rest of the
information
like 4 dollars a piece for the program
i won't do it i could be a billionaire
i get it the pr people you're just like
the rest of the pr people you keep on
telling me i could be a billionaire
tomorrow i know
i get it i can have merchandise i know i
could have t-shirts you know how many
t-shirts i would sell
i would sell crap tons t-shirts but i
don't
i know you hate the fact that you can
get my book free at the library and
everything i do is free
i know i know i i don't i can't give in
to it i can't
how come i don't have advertisers and
commercials on my youtubes and on my
podcast like everybody else does
because i don't want to do it to people
and i can't no one's going to make me do
it
how come i don't make my own line of
supplements medical medium line of
supplements
i'd be a billionaire tomorrow i'm not
going to you're not going to make me do
it
you and the rest of the pr people that
tell me every day that i'm supposed to
be doing all this i've refused to do it
because i'm not a money hungry greedy
grabber
yeah all right i love you too
was that tone any better hey can i ask
you
was that lemon mom love was that tone
for the person any better
they can't stand my tone lemon love
says money hungry question my question
mark are you kidding me everything's
free
i know i know i wish i could call that
person i just don't know that person's
number
what was that person's phone number does
anybody know
cara says aw is not a money grabber he's
still beyond generous with his
information
and time i think i know the person's
phone number it's 666 the
the i think it's 666 right is that
is that the person's phone number that
said i'm a money hungry grabber
wait they're answering hey hey
thanks for watching you don't like the
tone of my voice
what do you want me to do it's my voice
you want me to change my voice
so you're just basically discriminating
against me because you don't like the
way i sound
are you you're just are you that
judgmental where you
you just i don't go around getting mad
at people because the way they talk
and what kind of tone of voice they have
i don't say oh that person's tone is so
bad
why would you do that you must have a
lot of hate in your heart it's so sad
well i'm gonna give you a tone right now
you ready you ready
it's called a hang up dial tone
ernest says we love we love your
toenails
look i said this before and i'll say it
again you guys on clubhouse i said this
before and i'll say it again tick-tock i
said it before
said it before i'll say it again you
don't have to like me you don't have to
like my voice you don't have to like my
face you can think i'm ugly you can
think i'm
um mean you can think i'm nasty you can
think i'm a bad person
you can hate me you don't have to like
the way i look
you can do all that but i'm still going
to give you the information so you can
heal
the mala says nasty
i gotta call you back lamela 666 right
that's the son of satan right
you're the son of satan is that what you
are are you
are you the antichrist coming back are
you the antichrist coming is that the
antichrist you guys i think we have the
antichrist on here
wait you answered vanilla
are you the antichrist that the bible
says is coming
in revelations where everybody's going
to have a chip in their forehead
and and the whole world is going to be
run by one president
are you the anthony are you that are you
that anti-are you there i'm calling you
again you just hung up on me vimela
are you the antichrist where it says in
revelations
right where you're the everybody gets
the mark of the beast
and it's all because of you and
everybody's just under total nazism
like it was like literally world war ii
when they were killing all the jews
and like the seas part jesus christ
comes out of the sky and a white horse
and the angels all gather around are you
the antichrist
are you there are you there you guys
i try to make this as educational as
possible
uh jennifer says laughing so hard i'm
crying and snorting
jennifer you gotta you got a cool sense
of humor you really do
you don't you guys don't even have to
like my sense of humor
but i got to tell you this you don't
have to like me
you don't have to care about me you
don't have to think i'm a good guy it
doesn't matter
but i want to offer this i'll give you
invaluable information
critical information about healing and
your bodies
information that comes from spiritual
compassion you know what happened is
spirit of compassion said after i asked
over and over and over and over again
why me why me why me why should you give
me the
the advanced information how come me how
could be
i'm not special how can me spirit of
compassion said
because you can handle it because people
who get this gift
don't stick around long and that's the
spirit of compassion told me
when i was young and spirit of
compassion told me
that anybody who gets this gift
they don't want to stick around at all
and i talk about that the first
first part of the book you guys should
read the first part of the book origins
okay and if you guys don't have this
book
you should you should get it it's on
sale you can get it free at the library
how many hungry is that free at the
library is that sound money hungry to
you
this is the revised and expanded edition
so hungry
so money hungry you get it free at the
library
unbelievable
my st my story begins when i'm four
years old as i'm waking up one sunday
morning
i hear an elderly man speaking his voice
just outside my right ear it's very
clear
he says i am the spirit of the most high
there is no spirit above me but god
i'm confused and alarmed there's someone
else in my room
i open my eyes i look around
but i don't see anybody maybe
someone's talking or playing radio
outside i think
i get up i walk to the window there are
no people
it's too early in the morning i have no
idea what's going on
and i'm not sure i want to you know
that's just the start right there um
it costs more to print this book than to
buy it right now if you guys buy it for
on amazon.com us narashini good see
if you buy it it's literally it's like
dirt cheap
it's 49 off um
amazon makes the prices the publisher
sells the books i'm not self-published
you guys
i can be self-published tomorrow which
means
i make like a ton of money
so just so you know but i'm i'm not
self-published i could go self-published
tomorrow and i don't
publisher they're the ones that
create all that spend all the money do
all that stuff
so you can own it and get it cheap and
get it free at the library
so and also
i i have it published for a reason
is because it can't be wiped away and
scrubbed off the internet
and that's what's happening so medical
medium information
is just legendary healing information
it's already saved millions of people's
lives it's unique and original if you're
new here
and if you heard my my information from
spirit of compassion somewhere else then
it originated here
fact fact all right guys
i'm going to instagram i'm turning tick
tock back
on i'm turning clubhouse back on
you guys on clubhouse and
you guys come over to instagram go into
the main page
instagram medical meme page on ig and
listen
if you guys get kicked off the page go
to tick tock
if you get kicked off of instagram just
letting you know this is the mm 900 hds
the most incredible juicer i've ever had
um it just cuts the cost in half and
celery it's already painted itself
dozens of times for me
just letting guys know incredible the
pulp is dry to the bone
it's almost it's almost ridiculous it's
just ridiculous dr
a dry bowl heading off you guys i love
you
i'll see you guys soon