medical meaning wild blueberry drinks
challenge we're gonna be making three
drinks I'm really excited about it and
we're talking about why alcohol is
addictive and we're reading it right out
of brain saver and brain saver and brain
saver Protocols are literally like 47
off
amazon.com us but you've got to click
the little green box because that's the
coupon right there said amazon.com us so
it's like five extra dollars off which
is really incredible so check that out
okay when you get a chance
and then it makes it like 47 off which
is incredible so you'll see the little
coupon Square that's actually on the
page and you click that make sure you do
that so you guys were day two of the
wild blueberry drinks challenge we got a
lot of fun ahead of us here we're gonna
be making three drinks I want to read
about why alcohol is addictive you guys
you know I was talking about alcohol
yesterday
and it was really mind-blowing
information so I'm on page 160 right
here in brain saver so make sure you
have your book so you can read along
with me because that'll be fun so I'm
reading this part right here the
intoxication element so this is
mind-blowing information
the effect of alcohol on the brain isn't
solely from this trick sugar effect now
yesterday I was talking about how it's
the ghost of sugar it's the trick sugar
effect that the brain gets tricked with
and then you starve your brain of
glucose as you're drinking all of it you
guys know I covered it yesterday now
this is live right now this is not a
pre-recorded episode right here we're
live in the moment so the effect of
alcohol in the brain isn't solely from
this trick sugar effect where the brain
becomes starved a valuable glucose
because our brain runs on sugar glucose
alcohol is indeed a poison and as a
poison it does have an effect that can
be intoxicating and debilitating
yet the slurred speech when someone is
on their third drink is because the
brain is starting to starve from glucose
and therefore losing the ability to
function so when you're on your third
drink or your second drink depending on
the person your brain's already starting
to starve of glucose it's going into
glucose deprivation now we're going to
talk about why alcohol is so addictive
and it's important to know why that
happens because nobody knows they just
don't know that out there they just know
that people can get addicted to alcohol
and drinking and then they end up on a
park bench or their lives get destroyed
or their family's lives get destroyed or
something terrible happens or whatever
it is or they just get killed drunk
driving or kill somebody else drunk
driving whatever it is their lives can
change when they get addicted to the
alcohol right
and so but that's one aspect of it but
why are they so addicted to alcohol why
have you seen people out there so
addicted to alcohol right so that's the
whole thing too we're covering so when
inebriation becomes extreme and drastic
and someone drinks so much that they
collapse conk out and fall asleep that
drunken sleep is a game of Russian
Roulette this is mind-blowing as to why
I'm going to go into it right now
because if the brain doesn't get any
glucose at all due to the intensity of
intoxication the brain can actually
starve and that person can die in their
sleep you ever hear of those stories
right where it's like drank too much
drank too much and died in their sleep
because they literally were that
intoxicated so I'm talking about why
that happens it's because the brain
literally starved completely of glucose
and so the brain died that's it's
incredible information right here if you
guys just got on here where day two of
the wild blueberry drinks challenge I'm
reading about alcohol why alcohol is
addictive I'm breathing right out of
brain saver
on page 160 we're gonna also make some
drinks in a little while too some
non-alcoholic drinks so if you guys have
trouble viewing go to medicalmedium.com
please if you can so if you're being
kicked off of IG or you're being you're
having a problem on YouTube or
something's happening there or whatever
it is that you're seeing this
um live event right now go to
medicalmedium.com because I'm streaming
this live at medicalmedium.com right now
so
you here's another thing too or due to
alcohol poisoning one aspect of
inebriation that's not about lack of
glucose
they need they may need to vomit so I
want to go into that information too and
it's like hey well why are we talking
about this because this is the time of
year I'm seeing a lot more alcohol use
this time of year alcohol has destroyed
a lot of lives
I think a big part of why alcohol
destroys a lot of lives is the lack of
information about what it does to the
brain how it works because what happens
is when someone reads this information
and they know how alcohol poisons the
brain right and destroys the brain when
they learn why it's happening or how
it's happening it actually can stop
somebody from grabbing a drink so this
is powerful information for anybody
who's struggling and they're kind of on
the edge of drinking or not drinking
so we'll go into this a little bit more
so it's like a game of Russian Roulette
right because if the brain doesn't get
any glucose at all do you do to the
intensity of intoxication the brain can
actually starve and that person can die
in their sleep that's from being so
intoxicated that not a single like bit
of glucose gets to the brain anymore so
the person dies in their sleep
from glucose deprivation to the point
where their brain can't get glucose
anymore and then it dies
right
now you can die of alcohol poisoning too
if you're so overloaded with alcohol
because it is a poison so you can die
that way too but that essentially just
blocks out all glucose so you end up
dying of glucose deprivation no matter
what
so as the brain is dying from a lack of
glucose the nerves are not functioning
optimally the vagus nerves can become
paralyzed as the brain is losing
is the brain is is losing deeper glucose
reserves so as we lose those glucose
reserves to the brain because we're
inebriated because we're drunk because
we're drinking the vagus nerves get
affected so what you're seeing are
symptoms of the vagus nerves so if you
see somebody in there at a party
and they're Tipsy or they're partially
drunk really what you're saying is like
whoa your vagus nerves are actually
they're actually not functioning
properly that's what you're seeing which
is incredible information
you know whether anybody likes it or not
this is Advanced unique original medical
medium information it's there's no
studies out there there's nothing out
there about it it's the books are all
original info they're you know the
clinics don't know this medical research
and science doesn't know how it works
and how everything happens they just
don't know this about alcohol and that
information about the Vega service being
involved like being paralyzed that's
medical medium information and reading
right now so the vagus nerves can become
paralyzed as the brain is losing deeper
glucose reserves meaning that as someone
is vomiting in their sleep it's easier
to choke and die
so someone's vomiting in their sleep the
reason why they end up choking on their
vomit in their sleep and end up dying is
their vagus nerves
stopped working
that's how it works so if you're not at
that stage of vomiting if you're not at
that stage of being that drunk and
you're at a party or you're at at a
gathering so I'm on page 160 right now
if you're if you're somewhere
and you're drinking and someone's like
Tipsy or they're like a little bit
they're slurring their speech and
they're partially drunk
that's their vagus nerves so it's not
like hey man you're drunk dude dude man
you're drunk man it's more like choose
your Vegas nerves aren't working
because your various nerves are like
being paralyzed man because that's
really what it is it's like Yo dude
your vagus nerves you know like at a
college party it's like your vagus
nerves aren't working man they're
paralyzed
because that's what's really happening
it's not like dude you're drunk here's
your face it's more like it's like more
like yo man you're uh your vagus nerves
aren't working my Vegas nerves aren't
working anymore they're actually
stopping the work
exactly I don't know what this is I just
thought I was Tipsy you know but
but really what's happening is the vagus
nerves aren't working that's what's
happening
so as your as our brain is dying from
glucose deprivation because we're
drinking
right
the symptoms we're getting
is vagus nerve paralysis
so that's what's going on
so when you're at a party
or if you see like if you see a guy on a
park bench and they like drank all night
it's like and they're like rolling
around on the bench and they're barely
functional that's Vegas nerve paralysis
so paralysis of the vagus nerves and
that's what's going on
so when the cops pull somebody over and
they get them to walk in a straight line
and they can't walk in a straight line
right because they're intoxicated what's
happening is it's the Vegas nurse and so
really is it's not just in the future
they'll probably maybe if science
research understands that the vagus
nerves are actually a big part of this
maybe they'll have equipment meaning
like you know technology to also test
somebody's vagus nerves strength to know
if they're intoxicated too like a lot of
different things can happen down the
road
so here's what happens when you get so
inebriated so drunk
and you're it's so intoxicated the rush
of roulette occurs I saw somebody asking
about the book that's brain saver right
there just so you know there's a sale on
brainsaver at amazon.com us and there's
a coupon so if you click the Box you
even get an additional five or something
dollars more so it's really like 47 off
both books check them out right it's the
biggest sale I've ever seen yet on brain
saver and brain saver protocols I'm
letting you know but I want to give you
a forewarning
okay the books are heavy they're packed
they're like two massive Bibles the
information is really intense it's
eye-opening it's mind-blowing
information from above it's original you
won't be able to read that anywhere else
and I'm just giving you those kind of
like little disclaimers right there of
what you're up against when you get the
brain saver books
and the best part is they work the brain
shot therapies work they're life
changing they're like Miracles that's
just like and and the other information
and all the other stuff and the heavy
metal detox lenses of it it works
okay ready guys eating enough glucose
rich foods and keeping your fats low is
important before a shrinking night so
you have ample storage bins of glucose
freshly available
so eating ample amounts of glucose
before your drinking night and I know
like a lot of you guys aren't going to
be revved up for a drinking night
but yeah and you know what's funny
medical people say how medical medium is
common sense medical medium information
is not common sense because Common Sense
doesn't know this information because
it's not common
medical medium information just makes
sense that's really what is it actually
just makes sense because the information
is is far from common if nobody's ever
seen it before so it's incredible and
the truth hits you it speaks to you and
it just stands out
eating enough glucose rich foods because
that glucose deprivation that happens
when we drink eating enough glucose rich
foods is really helpful before a
drinking night so if you're gonna be
partying man if you're going to be out
there partying like yeah no I'm going to
drink a lot of wine I'm going to my
friend's house and drink a lot of wine
or whatever's going on make sure you're
eating enough glucose rich foods a lot
of people they don't even do that of
course they don't know
so and keeping your fats low is
important too before drinking night so
you have ample storage bins of glucose
freshly available for your Noggin for
your brain this is why when someone says
I'm drinking on an empty stomach
I haven't eaten today you'll see them
get buzzed faster
now medical research and science has no
idea why someone gets buzzed faster
they don't know
it's just
we all know
that we get buzzed faster on an empty
stomach look naturally we know that
didn't eat all day and then you just go
into some hard liquor you're gonna give
us real real fast okay so I'm drinking
on an empty stomach I haven't eaten
today you'll see them get buzzed faster
showing those first effects of drinking
early we think this Buzz
this tipsiness check this out you guys
it's because the brain becomes
intoxicated with alcohol
that's why we think we're getting a buzz
quicker really an alcohol Buzz is a
brain starving of glucose so here's
what's happening you're not eating all
day your brain is already low on glucose
or you're not eating hardly anything the
day before you drink the day the day
you're drinking
your brain is already in glucose
deprivation it's starving from glucose
it actually leaves glucose desperately
so we think this Buzz this tipsiness is
because the brain becomes intoxicated
with alcohol yeah well no I'm drinking
my brain's getting intoxicated really an
alcohol Buzz is a brain starving glucose
the liver is starting to mop up the
alcohol so as that party night starts to
happen our liver is actually starting to
mop up the alcohol so it's not releasing
glucose anymore that means even your own
liver loses all its ability to release
the glucose reserves you see how it
works you guys so here you don't eat all
day then you start drinking you get
buzzed faster that's because the liver
shuts down and starts to mop up all that
alcohol really fast and in an instant it
stops releasing glucose so now your
brain is really not getting glucose
there's no glucose in your bloodstream
your liver is not releasing anymore and
you start drinking and boom you get hit
with that buzz faster
and that's what science research does it
know they don't know how that works
it's incredible information
so really an alcohol Buzz is a brain
starving glucose the liver starting to
mop all the alcohol up so it's not
releasing glucose anymore and because
someone didn't eat they also don't have
freshly available glucose in the
bloodstream for someone who did eat that
day to someone who actually ate that day
it takes longer for the alcohol to
affect them as they start drinking
because they at least have that fresh
glucose for the brain so someone if you
take two people one person didn't eat
that day and they and the other person
ate that day and they went to the same
party and their livers were fairly in
the same amount of condition and they're
roughly around the same ages
one dude is going to get drunk way
faster than the other dude the other
dude that actually ate that day is gonna
get drunk not as fast right
it takes a larger volume of alcohol for
intoxication to come into it that is for
the poison aspect of alcohol to play a
role in someone's symptoms even then
drunkenness is part of intoxication
by alcohol and part brain starving of
glucose so I'm going to read this next
part it's pretty cool
a drunkenness we're only about
intoxication of alcohol
the symptoms would be limited someone
would be nauseous vomiting feel sick in
the head feel dizzy yet while greatly
sick they would still be coherent
see the difference
you would still be coherent
and that's something science research
missed
you can still get alcohol poisoning
but be completely coherent
that's an incredible piece of
information if drunkenness were only
about intoxication of alcohol
if it was only just about alcohol being
poisonous
if being drunk was only just about the
alcohol itself
the symptoms would be limited
someone would be nauseous because they
were poisoned from alcohol
vomiting because they were poisoned from
alcohol feel sick in the head because
they were poisoned from alcohol feel
dizzy yet while greatly sick they would
still be coherent
you see the difference
that's just incredible when I heard that
from SOC when I got that information was
writing it down this book because you
can't find that anywhere it doesn't
exist when I was getting that
information and putting I was just mind
blown I didn't know that I did not know
that if it was just the alcohol aspect
of alcohol you'd be completely coherent
you would just feel sick
that's an incredible piece of
information I mean maybe look maybe
someone doesn't think that's like
interesting but I find that really
interesting it's really unbelievable
okay so check this out it's the
starvation of the brain happening at the
same time that leads to the loss of
motor skill function slurred speech and
other difficulty speaking not
understanding what someone is saying
like when you're drunk say what what is
that what
I know
you know I've been like your best friend
forever
like we're like the greatest friends
ever like right like you know like we
just met an hour ago but I feel like
you're like the best friend I've ever
had I know we just met like an hour ago
in this bar
but honestly like I feel like knowing
you my whole lifetime
if it was
if it was just alcohol that would not
happen if you were just alcohol poisoned
you would be completely coherent like
this you would just be like hold on you
guys I have to vomit
hold on you guys I'm feeling really
nauseous
you guys I got alcohol poisoning but
yeah I could drive home I could drive
home with alcohol poisoning because I'm
totally coherent it's just that I might
have to puke so just hang on for a
minute in the car but you would be
completely coherent
but because it's not just about alcohol
intoxication it's not just about
being intoxicated with alcohol it's more
than that it's the starvation of the
brain getting glucose and that's
something nobody knows either that it's
a starvation factor of not getting
glucose to the brain that makes you get
into the place of symptoms showing
symptoms that are slurred speech
showing symptoms of not being coherent
not hearing and receiving information
properly
by having outbursts of anger or whatever
it is it's all involved right there
those are symptoms of the brain starving
to death and that's the symptoms of
glucose not getting to the brain
it's just incredible
so
you lose motor skill function without
the glucose you get the slurred speech
and other difficulty speaking and not
understanding what someone is saying and
at the same time saying things you don't
know you're saying as the brain is
getting very little glucose on the edge
of staying alive certain parts of the
brain start to shut down so here's what
you're witnessing because the brain is
starving to death of glucose which is
sugar
and you're drinking what you what you're
witnessing with symptoms is somebody's
brain dying and actually shutting down
different parts of their brain is
actually shutting down if you guys just
got on here we're on page 161
which is really cool we're in brain
saver right now we're talking about the
brain we're talking about alcohol
alcohol addiction how it's even possible
to be addicted to alcohol all of it like
we're cutting into it this is really
cool we're also making three drinks
we've got lots of bottles of vodka no we
don't that's a joke kidding but we're
making non-alcohol drinks right which is
really cool we got the Wild blueber and
today is day two of the wild blueberry
drinks challenge so we're gonna have
some fun I got the blender out I got the
juicer out I got the well even warmer
out right here there's a lot of cool
stuff going on I got the wild blueberry
juice I don't know if you guys seen it's
10 off at Wyman's check out the link in
the description
and the link in the profile right that's
the wild blueberry juice the wild
blueberry juice you guys know I work
with these guys because I want to keep
this stuff around forever because it is
incredible I call this stuff medicine it
is unbelievable how they they get this
wild food out of the field and they
press it so we could actually have this
in our lives even a little bit of this a
day even just like a small amount every
day those anthocyanins going in is
critical because you're looking at
anthocyanins right there it's charged
man anyway
it's just so cool
so let's get into this part now
misguided hangover cures I like this
part this is fun
a hangover
like drunkenness itself is part from
starvation of glucose that hangover you
get
the next day
that's part of being starved of glucose
to the brain
apart from intoxication of alcohol too
meaning
your your alcohol sick right
the worst approach for Recovery is to
drink again the next day how many times
have you guys heard that before I just
want to ask you guys this question have
you heard that before where if you got a
hangover you party the night before that
drink the next morning it'll help have
you heard that one I'm just curious so
I'm hoping you guys get that I hope you
can respond to that one
have you like heard that one before like
just drink the next morning just drink
the next day like when you wake up just
crack open a beer you know by like noon
time if you still got that hangover just
get the Vodka out and just get something
out right have you guys heard that whole
little bit of information out there
so the worst but listen to this okay
coming from SLC because it's in the
books right here
the worst approach for Recovery is to
drink again the next day
so here's what's really cool about
getting the information above it's not
man-made so it's free of like all the
guessing games okay because some poor
sap is just gonna keep on drinking the
next day and that's not gonna be good
so when Spirit was giving me the
information right here about this I was
like this is so incredible
the worst approach for Recovery is to
drink again the next day even though
that's the advice given to many people
who drink that is the advice I've seen
professionals advise
their clients and their patients to
drink the next morning to try to avoid a
hangover
well I got news it doesn't shake a
hangover because once again you're
starving the brain of glucose so now
you're going into the next day and
you're now starving the brain of glucose
again so instead of helping you out of a
hangover you're actually killing your
brain the next morning and I've seen
professionals recommend drinking some a
little bit the next morning when really
those professionals have no idea and
this is how the guessing game World
works and you can take this in any
aspect of alternative medicine health or
whatever about guessing games in general
right you guys know the history of
guessing games out there so
that alone is starting now to Now kill
the brain because it's lacking glucose
the brain starts to die again
the reason people tend to gorge on food
the day after drinking is because their
brain is asking for what it's asking for
glucose
that's why people Gorge it's another
reason why people Gorge at two three
o'clock in the morning at a diner
their brain is desperate for glucose
it was so deprived they were drunk a
little too long which is drunk at all
and they were depriving the brain of
glucose so it was starving so that
moment comes
so the reason people tend to gorge on
all that diner food were their pancakes
and everything else and eggs and hash
browns with oil and sausage and desserts
and everything else in chocolate cake
whatever they could find right inside
diners is because their brain is dying
and it's asking for glucose depending on
how much alcohol someone consumed the
brain narrowly missed starving to death
from a lack of glucose keep that in mind
people who are actually drunk
their brain almost completely starves to
death
so now the organ sends messaging
throughout the body that it needs large
amounts of glucose desperately and
immediately and that's why a lot of
people scoff down a lot of diner food in
the middle of the night two three in the
morning it's not because they're really
hungry
they may be hungry too but it's because
the brain is begging for glucose
this is really cool at the same time
someone could still be nauseous from the
alcohol feeling sick to the stomach and
they can't really hold down food yet
they'll still scoff down food I've seen
a lot of people where they're on that
they're not even past the drunken stage
and they're in a diner and they're just
scoffing it down sending it down that
queasy part of a hangover is from toxic
the toxic nature of alcohol
many people don't drink to the point of
nausea and vomiting they are still
looking to scarf down food to sober up
I've seen people just do a couple of
drinks at a party at dinner party where
they had a couple glasses of wine and
then when the party was over and they're
clean say they hosted the party and
they're cleaning up everything they're
now like scoffing at three o'clock in
the morning they're eating whatever
they're eating their leftover hors
d'oeuvres they're eating the appetizers
they're they're scoffing it down
the same night they drank they're
looking for a diner and there's people
that look for diners or drive-throughs
at two or five o'clock in the morning
ordering a whole stack of pancakes with
maple syrup toast eggs bacon waffles
hash browns burgers fries tacos or
burritos
a friend of mine's always like going for
the tacos and burritos you know always
tells me well yeah I know I got drunk
and yeah you know I'm like what are you
gonna get when are you gonna get free
from that stuff a lot of people they
just don't want to let it go
say this doctor friend some people yeah
doctors drink just so you know a lot of
doctors drink out there some people get
confused glucose is not the problem it's
what the brain needs so let's make sure
that's straight
glucose isn't causing any of the
problems it's the brain dying and having
a lack of glucose it needs glucose
and here's another thing or they're
turning to ample food the next day so if
they don't do it that night they got
drunk they went to sleep
the next day it's scoff City it's like
tank the Food City
you know and people are all on the high
fat diet so they have glucose issues
already they have glucose deficiencies
already so let's get into it a little
bit more
the common phrase is sopping up the
alcohol have you guys heard that before
like let's sop up the alcohol
let's sop it up
you know that's that's what happens out
there you better eat something man you
got to stop up the alcohol you gotta you
know you got to stop up that whiskey
it even happens when someone is actively
drinking out at a party or a bar when a
companion says you've got to eat
something to stop up that alcohol have
you heard that before
what no one realizes is that eating food
after drinking alcohol is actually about
getting glucose to the brain so it can
come out of its starving State and start
to function again
the brain wants to start to function
again and it has to get out of that
starvation stage
because we misunderstand what's going on
in the brain and body we're still not
getting what our brain really needs and
here's another incredible part of this
information right here because we're
adding fat
mistakenly we reach for a combination of
carbohydrates plus fat
pancakes and sausage
pancakes with butter
we're mixing fats with carbohydrates
that's how it works cheeseburger fats
with carbohydrates the bun on the
cheeseburger the cheese itself fats and
carbohydrates
macaroni and cheese see people eat that
in diners fats and carbohydrates you got
the pasta and then you've got the cheese
and the oil
everybody's going for the wrong
combination
here our brain is starving to death
because we were drinking and then when
we do reach for food because our brain
is desperate and asking us to get food
as fast as possible we end up picking a
food that doesn't help the brain
and that's where we go wrong too
see Mystic mango said this is truly
amazing information
um arto says this is so interesting
incredible
Michelle says this chapter is amazing is
it this chapter is really mind-blowing
every time I read this chapter it's like
I get the same reaction I'm like I can't
believe this information
so because we misunderstand what's going
on in the brain and body we're still not
getting what our brain really needs
because we're adding fat mistakenly we
reach for a combination of carbohydrates
plus fat like I was saying and that fat
inhibits
the glucose
from getting to the brain
so we don't recover ourselves properly
we don't know how to bring glucose back
to the brain
we drink
we party
right that's what people do and then we
eat because our brain is crying for
glucose to save it because we did the
Russian Roulette we gave it glucose
deprivation
and now we end up eating foods that are
not really giving the brain enough
glucose again
so the brain's still struggling
here's something that's interesting for
example frying hash browns in oil hash
browns are not bad
if they're hash browns with no oil and
no fat
so if we fry hash browns in oil butter
and grease it inhibits the potatoes
glucose from easily getting to the brain
and by the way that's medical medium
information
for years
it's inhibiting no one knew that part
they didn't know that part
that the fat thrown on the potato is
what's stopping
the carbohydrate from the potato
from helping the person
it's mm info
from above
now we're getting insulin resistance
which is more medical meme information
nobody knew it was the fat causing
insulin resistance
that is medical medium info published
info
lectured info podcasted info
it's not sugar that creates insulin
resistance it's fat that creates insulin
resistance and you'll see more of that
out there as people poach that that's
actually being poached right now out
there for medical medium books
and this is going back more than you
know decades now this information he
said check this out and her body has to
fight to divide the sugar and fat so the
sugar can get get too much needed places
so here's how it works when you dump the
wrong combination of food inside your
body after drinking alcohol
your brain has to fight
to get the glucose because the
combinations are always fat plus sugar
Cookies Cakes Donuts macaroni and cheese
pasta pizza pasta with oil and fat and
cheese
sauce with oil fat eggs and bacon eggs
with butter
like it's it's all this different
combinations so as we're trying to
recover our brain is trying to actually
find glucose and it's fighting its way
through all those different combinations
it's not like we're trying to recover
from a drunken stupor by consuming fruit
such as banana you guys know anybody who
got totally
crab-faced totally drunk and they just
knew better like
they knew better to just use bananas as
their recovery or a papayas
or mineral salts from leafy greens and
celery juice
papayas and bananas like you know like
all of it instead we go for a plate of
eggs which is fat or we go for toast
with avocado that might be something
right there
so
someone will just do avocado toast on
the next morning right but they're still
mixing a fat with the carbohydrate
therefore the brain still has to
struggle getting that glucose to the
brain right
or oatmeal with nut butter or nut milk
or almond milk and avocado and nut
butter are both fats getting in the way
of glucose from the carbohydrates from
the toaster oatmeal now I'm not ripping
apart avocado that's not what I'm doing
I'm not saying you can't eat oatmeal I'm
saying that the combinations aren't the
correct ways to recover after drinking
this is Page 162 right now of brain
saver
reading it as we speak
insane deal the biggest sale on these
two books I've ever seen yet I'm just
letting you know I have not seen a sale
on these two books at amazon.com us as
low as it is right now it's like 47 off
or something you have to click the
little box where it's a coupon
but it's an insane sale right here on
these books at amazon.com
it's really incredible
so you guys
this information is just mind-blowing
across the board Pizza people do that's
sugar and fat it's often the most
popular go-to after drinking is pizza
and that's your fat and your
carbohydrate but yet it's not recovering
the brain fast enough babe if you're
young and indestructible and you haven't
experienced chronic illness yet or
anything else
and you don't have like mental health
conditions you're not suffering with
high anxiety and all these other things
in depression depersonalization and OCD
and you get drunk
and you just go for pizza every time
sure
feels like it works it's another day you
recover and that's it but it breaks you
down slowly and if you do have problems
like mental health issues or anything
else like all the different things that
are in the brain books then yeah this is
really bad and I see people do that out
there they got OCD and depression and
anxiety and they're still drinking
so we gotta make some drinks you guys
let's get going on that
so that's the brain saver information a
little bit on alcohol let's get started
I got three drinks to make I'm excited
so uh we got a lot of stuff out here
which is really cool
first thing is the wild the blueberry
and lime juice so it's the sparkling
wild blueberry and lime juice so I want
to get started with that
so to start with
I'm going to drop a little bit of
sparkling water in here I'm going to do
a quarter cup of sparkling water
so I'm going to kind of gauge right
there there we go that's quarter cup
nice these are options for holidays and
Gatherings without the alcohol
it's a good way to do it all right now
I'm going to do a cup of wild blueberry
juice
so Wyman's wild blueberry juice
incredible product
amazing actually really incredible in so
many ways so I'm going to drop a cup in
here
there we go
then I'm going to put a half a
tablespoon
of lime juice now I got a really ripe
lime so I want to show you this lime
now ripe limes are a whole nother world
you can use
well this one's actually partially ripe
which is really great so that's got the
green but it's also got the lighter
color on there the yellow so these are
partially ripe anyway so these are
amazing too but the real real green
limes they're they're not as good as
when they're ripe this is a really ripe
lime which is great so you take a look
and you'll see the difference right
really juicy it's got a color inside and
then the less ripe they are like the
green one right there let me just cut
that
seemed less ripe it's still juicy
because these are partially ripe if you
look see the yellow on them but man like
when they're really green it's hard to
even squeeze energies out of them plus
they're not really ripe they're more
bitey they got like a bite to them
they're not as sweet because there is
such thing as a sweet lime and so that's
what these are right here these are just
great ones do a half a tablespoon of
lime juice
so grab a little tablespoon really quick
out of here
pretty easy
so
got that in there you guys
awesome
all right so that's the that's the
recipe right there I'm just going to
kind of mix it and then I'm gonna pour
it now I'm gonna pour it into a
champagne glass
right here
okay so I'm gonna get some in here like
this
[Music]
nice
perfect and then I'm going to cut a
piece of
lime right here
or
maybe I'll use a green
one right here
it's got a better look to it
that is
the wild sparkling wild blueberry lime
juice right there take a look give you a
little close-up on that maybe it'll
show up there
okay there we are you guys see that I'll
pull it back here I'll put it up closer
there we go whoa nice
that's it right there
I will sip it in a little while but I
got two more drinks to bake so I'm gonna
move this over
I'll bring you back in there
all right
next one you guys
brain shot therapy have you been doing
the brain shot therapies this is the
adrenal fight or flight stabilizer so
that's what I'm making next
foreign
everything out for that I got a juicer
right here so I'm going to use this real
quick
now
let's go find this one
here's what we're making
does anybody need an adrenal fight or
flight stabilizer during the holidays
or are they extra stressed during the
holidays you know I was debating with
this one I was like look
I was like
is anybody gonna want one during this
time it's not doesn't sound that fun
does it but I think a lot of people
their stress is really cranked up it's
really amped up and because your stress
is so amped up because of the holidays
and everything going on that is actually
a pretty good thing for them to have in
their life
so I'm going to make one
right here so a little piece of Ginger
is first let me do that
I love this one I mean I do all the
brain shots I love them all but um
but I'm always under stress for so many
reasons so it's actually really helpful
to do this one so I'm gonna do a
get my Ginger ready right here
so I'm gonna pop this in here so one
inch piece of fresh ginger right there
that's first
so
I said my sister said
on IG those brain shots make a huge
difference in my chemical sensitivities
yeah I just I'm honestly what these
brain shots do for people I mean I'm not
today's the why blueberry drinks
challenge day you know but all I can say
is you guys know if you've done these
the brain shot therapies I mean insane
what they do they're miracles from above
I can't wait to do more about them
it's just I don't know it actually
there's a loss for words for it of what
I've seen it's just miraculous that's
the bottom line I don't even know how to
size it up okay so one inch piece of
fresh ginger right there I'm gonna just
turn this on
I'm gonna pop that in boom so you put
that in your juicer
don't even need this
you don't need it let's go with a clove
of garlic now I got a cool garlic
sitting around somewhere already done
pop that in there
you can use a small clove of garlic
you could have a big clove of garlic
right but you don't want to use like a
really large clove of garlic you don't
want to use like the biggest clove you
can find
it's not a medium to small is good that
works
and we're doing the wild blueberry juice
in this adrenal
fight or flight stabilizer that's what
we're using instead of the wild
blueberry you know the Frozen wall
blueberry so I'm going to go with the
lemon half peel
it's a tickle lemon I peeled it
all right there's there's the other half
I'm gonna drop this in there right now
okay and then I'm gonna use some parsley
now it's a cup of tightly packed parsley
so I'm going to gauge that
parsley that I grew
I'm using the garden parsley that I have
I love the adrenal fighter plate
stabilizer
I love how it feels the minute you drink
it how it feels when it goes down
just it's incredible
foreign
you guys do you have experience with
this adrenal fight or flight stabilizer
because it's really something to
experience if you haven't
okay now I'm gonna do a half cup of kale
and engage it so I need a little bit
more than that
a little more
now the option you'll see there's an
option for a watermelon rind
I actually have a watermelon on me right
now
so being that I have one I am going to
I'm going to cut a piece of the Rind off
right now
you guys can see that and I'm gonna
throw down some
okay
foreign
fight or fight stabilizer
I get happy knowing I'm about to drink
it
because I know the effects I know what
it does I know how it feels and now I'm
going to mix two teaspoons of wild
two teaspoons of wild blueberry juice in
there too so that's next
foreign
drop two teaspoons in here that's a half
a teaspoon it looks like just do that
here we go
amazing have you guys tried this I mean
seriously
foreign
I'm going to move the juicer out of the
way you guys don't mind
by the way if you guys know about the
mm1500
I won't go into it
but that's dry
that's like dry like I'm sorry but the
other juicers aren't doing that I'm just
showing you you know what that means you
save money
that just blows my mind all right
I'm mixing in those two teaspoons right
there of the wild blueberry juice
[Music]
the adrenal fight-or-flight stabilizer
it hits me
right on the first or second sip right
now it's the first sip
and you feel it
[Music]
it's so good you guys
this one really resonates with me you
know you'll find the brain shot
Therapies
which ones you need in the moment you
know because that's what it is and right
now
stress is high
and this lowers it for me brings it down
it's so good
and you could feel it
bartender give me another and I have a
little bit more for another
um
I feel so good you guys this is
incredible so these are the three drinks
no I got one more
one more drink to make
I'm making the wild blueberry latte
that's next
so
there's a different feel you get
when you're giving your brain what it
needs
and you're feeding your body and giving
it what it needs right information too
like it comes from above like the
adrenal fight-or-flight stabilizer
that's information that no one would
know to make a combination
of specific things working together
ingredients like they are in the amounts
to do something inside the body to feed
the adrenals in the brain
and that's what's incredible about these
books by the way
if you don't know about the brain shot
therapies I'm just letting you know take
advantage of Amazon sale which is the
best sale I've ever seen on these two
books yet it's incredible so there's a
coupon like I said and everything
amazing you guys are having problem
watching this right now go to
medicalmedium.com I'm streaming it live
right now this is not a pre-recorded
this is live in the moment I'm letting
you know all right so let's work on the
next drink
okay
yep and we're always live
all right I'm gonna move this over to
you guys so let's get going
yep and I'm gonna bring the blender why
not
get the blender going we're gonna pop
some stuff in here let's see what we're
gonna put in here
this is gonna be fun okay
so we're gonna grab some measuring cups
here
we need three quarters of a cup of water
it goes in here
we need half a cup of milk wait a minute
what kind of milk
huh coconut milk interesting unsweetened
okay we need one to two one did you
teaspoons of honey
I drop a little bit of that in there too
right one to two tablespoons of honey
credible
foreign
okay we need a quarter cup of wild
blueberry juice
I really love this latte I'm gonna be
honest
quarter cup of wild blueberry juice yes
we do
sorry guys I Disappeared for a second
so sorry
yep
and this is the wild blueberry juice I
use right here which is incredible
that's the Wyman's is 10 off so make
sure you check that out when you get a
chance you guys know I work with these
guys
because that stuff is the bomb it is
incredible
I mean I'm not gonna I don't have time
to go into like the whole thing with the
anthocyanins and the blue color and and
the the ability to survive thousands of
years like all of it I mean while
blueberry juice is a wild food and what
that does and how incredible that is
like seriously like this is another
level if you're somebody that believes
in food or you believe in food helping
you heal if you're somebody that just
got here and you're like what is he
doing but I do believe in food know the
difference of a wild food know the
difference of like wild blueberries what
this means and then if the food actually
is pressed in the nutrients that are
pressed out of it that literally fall
into what you're looking at right here
it's a whole different game whole
different part of the healing world so
just know that if you're somebody that
likes food you like watermelons you like
greens you like whatever it is ginger
you like lemon
if you're somebody interested in food
for healing I mean
learn about the wild blueberry whoa I
mean I'm just giving you that little
you know piece of inflammation there how
incredible that is all right we need
some cinnamon
we need a little cardamon
drop a little bit of that in there
okay quarter teaspoon and a half
teaspoon
yep
I think I'm gonna blend this up
that's what I think I'm gonna do
all right
we're taking off
we are Blended you guys
then what I'm going to do is I'm going
to take this and I'm going to pour it
into this pot which is getting hot
we're going to strain it
we're straining all the little bits of
coconut pieces right all those little
bits of coconut we're straining that
that's what we're doing
okay
let that kind of drain a little bit in
there
and I'm gonna move the blender
it is heating up right now the pot is on
kind of just finish this little
straining process
so what you're looking right there is
the latte is in the process of being
made
that's what I'm talking about
okay one here I'm gonna put a new lemon
on here a new lime piece really
gonna drink a little bit of this if you
guys don't mind
nice
here but that's heating up I think
aw Bar and Grill is actually opening up
oh dear
all right
being used with AWS Bar and Grill it
keeps me really busy and then I get in
trouble you guys know how it works
right
all right you guys
I got a busy uh Bar and Grill going you
guys know I I run a business
CW's Bar and Grill and it gets it
interferes with like the work we're
doing right the medical medium
information everything it interferes and
everything because I have
I have to attend everybody
and I'm not even allowed to have a sip
right now I gotta just get busy right do
you guys want shots sorry about this
let's get
what
the dogs are barking now
for DW bars and grills
nope
you guys keep me really busy hang on
who wants this
um
okay would you like a little sip
okay here we go was that good
uh baby grogu
okay I know I need another shot hang on
you guys just bear with me
uh
the W Bar and Grill
yeah yeah it's a busy day we just opened
up people are pouring in
yeah checking these here everybody here
is grogu's here groco baby grogu's here
yeah
um Ralphie the dog is here who else
yep
um yep and jump Baby Joey yeah
everybody's here
okay um what do you want I'm sorry I
didn't hear you it's getting loud
um french fries
we have the french fries we have the
french fries which are made in um animal
fat
yeah animal fat they're dipped in animal
yeah
you don't want those
yeah either do I I don't want to eat
those right now either oh hold on
no we have we have uh fries that aren't
yeah
yeah we don't use canola oil no we don't
use canola oil for our fries we don't
nope nope not at all and we don't use
animal fat either I was a mistake I
didn't know what I was even saying
we don't use canola oil with our french
fries or animal fat all right just
yep
I just sorry I'm hearing Mrs Ferguson
come down the steps yeah we're a hotel
upstairs too we have rooms upstairs
yep Mrs Ferguson injured herself on the
way down the step she slipped
okay Mr Ferguson don't worry Mr Ferguson
is he okay he's on the toilet still
I told him
I told him what he needs to do he's not
doing it he's stuck in his ways how long
he's been on the toilet a couple hours
this morning
you want me to call 9-1-1
um
all right let's go let's go The Latte is
heating up you guys you just have to
hang on I'm trying to run a whole bunch
of things at once it's actually getting
out of control let's get the latte oh
it's heating up nice
oh good good we're ready
let me bring this down here a little bit
okay
I'm gonna mix this a little bit too nice
you're not touching your shots you guys
yeah
right I'm gonna pour
this into a little mug
hey guys this is what I'm gonna do
this is going to go straight into here
okay
I would say this is one of my favorites
of all time
foreign
I got a new little pan here it's going
right on top
now I got some coconut
milk right here
nice
okay
let's get that nice and warm here
and I'm about to do some other stuff too
you guys
all right let me just heat this up and
we're almost there are you guys doing
okay
all right if you guys just got here
watch this from the whole beginning
because we talked about alcohol
addiction I'm not hurting anybody's
feelings am I
you know being addicted to alcohol and
the effects on the brain how it works
like information you've never heard
before so I hope you watch this from the
beginning this is day two of the wild
blueberry drinks challenge
I'm just heating this up for the moment
and we're just about to finish the latte
which is incredible
this is the sparkling wild blueberry
lime right here which is really amazing
all on its own
all right this is ready
ready
let's turn that off
so I'm going to strain this
we're going to pour it into a
measuring cup is what I'm going to do
or in here
oh nice and hot
all right
got this little thing here you guys
at AWS Bar and Grill we make a lot of
messes
and then I got a lot of cleaning to do
too so lots of cleaning to do
what I'm doing is just frothing this
you guys hanging in there
all right
I just want to give it a really good go
just you know a few more seconds in here
right you see that you guys
got a close-up on the camera
amazing
this thing's incredible
here we go
if you have guests you want to give it a
good you know whisk right
I'm gently going to pour this on top
here we go
I'm going to sprinkle some cinnamon on
top too
so when I get all the foam on here
have you guys made this recipe
just sprinkle a tiny bit of cinnamon on
here as well
she won't don't want to overdo it you
don't want to do an Overkill
you want to just lightly
I'm gonna put it in my hand
and I'm gonna just
do it this way so that you don't just
overdo it there you go
that's it amazing
that's an incredible latte
I think so because I really like it
and it tastes incredible too so
it's from brain saver
um
oh my God so good
you guys you have to make this for the
holidays I'm serious like you have to
please do because you will not believe
what it tastes like
it's so good
I mean it's so good
like I just want to just like
take it over here and
amazing Jenna says you have smooth hands
of a 20 year old
you can be a hand model
thank you
be hand model
how much to model my hands hmm
let me get where models get
um one million dollars to model my hands
for a shoot no problem
okay I'm just gonna
guys
make sure you check out the sale that I
can't even believe a sale on amazon.com
us unbelievable in these books
that's actually amazing
we just made the adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer right there one of the brain
shot Therapies
Dr fun good to see you
we read out a brain saver
we made the latte
not a brain saver as well
so and I'll show you the latte in here
check this out you guys
we just made this the wild blueberry
latte
so good can't get enough of it actually
that's right here out of protocols
I don't know which one I like best
foreign
I am a 20 year old
I am 20 years old
I'm not even 21 yet
you know my my hands
um
anyway 10 off by the way the wild
blueberry juice check out Wyman's
incredible stuff
like I mean I could talk about the wild
blueberry juice and the wild blueberry
forever
at such an amazing food we have on this
planet right now and we need foods that
are Above the Rest
this we just need foods that are Above
the Rest it's critical in our lives
for people especially when they're
dealing with things they're dealing with
are you guys okay
do you like to try some
you would like to try some huh
um
what else would you like
Dr Nesbitt just came out of surgery
um Dr Nesbitt would you like something
would you like to try this
Dr Nesmith said it's not good at all
he thinks it tastes terrible he would
rather have a glass of wine personally
he said
what about this
no says he wouldn't want that either he
wants a shot of hard whiskey
he wants uh vodka
can I have some
Dr Nesbitt just removed somebody's brain
the other day
he said it was an accident he thought
they were a cadaver he thought that the
nurse brought a cadaver into the
operation room so he removed the brain
without thinking about it
and then he realized the person was
alive and they were only there to get
their appendix out
it was a mistake
um insurance cover it
Dr Nesbitt said that insurance covered
it
so he removed the brain
okay but I think he needed quit surgery
he says no never he's going to work he's
never going to retire
you guys this is day two of the medical
medium wild blueberry day challenge
remember
two watches from the beginning if you
want to learn about alcohol addiction
alcohol poisoning alcohol everything
um I'm gonna turn this over here
okay
here we go
all right you guys
more mm food and drink Monica says I
will gladly
be at your service and offer as much as
I can free information and we do it the
way we do it you guys I love you guys
this has been an incredible challenge
I'm honored you're here thank you for
coming seriously
hmm
and I really appreciate it truly do
I hope you guys are taking care of
yourselves doing all the good stuff
and have you checked out brain saver
we're giving it a moment to scroll
through it there's a lot of information
there Dr Nesbitt you are a foul surgeon
I just saw somebody said Dr Fawn
holidays can be a tough time for a lot
of people and
you know like keep a sense of humor keep
a light heart to remember that try to
keep a light heart with everything
holidays wise and all that so
try to remember that
you're a good person you didn't do
anything wrong it's not your fault
because that's what people are blamed on
all the time what their illnesses and
everything have compassion for yourself
pat yourself on the back Dr Nesbitt what
do you have to say
he says pat yourself on the head
why
should be thankful you still have a
brain because you remove the brain in
the operation room this morning when he
shouldn't have so you're still hung up
on that says yeah he's hung up on that
his OCD is acting up
um
after Nesbitt has OCD
but you don't have depression right just
OCD he says
he's depressed if he doesn't drink
but he's not depressed when he drinks
what does that mean
all right you guys
pat yourself on the back have compassion
for yourself truly and know that I care
and I can't wait to see you next time
we'll do other cool topics look out for
the medical meeting podcast at Apple
podcast I did a swelling episode it's
really packed with information
information nobody knows
and you know what I know people want to
shame me all the time for saying that
that nobody knows but what am I supposed
to do like lie and say oh I researched
somewhere and found it uh no
it's medical medium information it's
Unique and original and from above and
I'm kind of tired of being shamed
at this point for saying it
um kind of tired of being shamed for you
know first for saying where the
information comes from above it's like
I've been discriminated against for so
many years that it gets really old after
a while am I supposed to lie and say
that all the information that's in eight
the eight volumes of books here
is from some other source when there's
when it's not when research designs
didn't know any of it and it's all
original from these books am I supposed
to lie and pretend it came from
somewhere else
it came from above you don't have to
believe it believe I'm a genius then
okay
believe I'm a genius
um
right
and that's fine too whatever you want to
believe but it comes from above
and um
so anyway
it's incredible information we have a
fun event coming up in January so be on
the lookout get the medical medium
newsletter get on the medical medium
newsletter please so you can learn about
the fun event coming in January and we
have a couple of things going on but the
event in January is going to be
incredible go to medicalme.com sign up
to the newsletter when you can
Dr Nesbitt what are you doing
medicalmedium.com sign up to the
newsletter please so you can actually be
alerted as to what we got going on what
we're doing the event that's coming up
so keep that in mind too right
it's just so good I just can't get
enough of that it's just so yummy
I'm leaving telegram audio messages
exclusively
and it's a public platform
The Message is I'm leaving on telegram
are public telegram is a public platform
it's not a private platform anybody
could be on there subscribe to my
telegram I'm leaving messages on there
to the public they're not private
um messages that messages that don't
post anywhere else I post it on the
telegram public platform so and they're
exclusive messages there so keep that in
mind too right
I love you guys
take care
and I will talk to you soon I'm going to
be leaving a telegram sometime this week
so look out for it I can't wait