today I'm answering health questions but
I have an update for you now you know
there's something happening September
7th at
aan right it's going to be a meet and
greet and I'm going to be there but like
medical medium fashion goes it is
turning into to be something into a
bigger thing and a more crazier thing so
now it's not just a meat and greet like
originally I was keeping it lowkey and I
was like hey that's okay we'll do a meet
and greet some people will come but a
lot of requests a lot of people want to
come and now I'm pulling my hair out and
I'm just like what is going on so now
it's going to be a little bit different
like an
Afterparty an Afterparty so September
7th airan the commemorative customized
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie bottle which I want to talk
about for a second before we answer
questions that smoothie bottle is why
I'm going to be there because it's going
to be this like one time only customized
smoothie bottle medical medium glass
bottle that's a collector's item in the
whole bit which is really incredible
because the heavy metal detox smoothie
did so well there they want to put it
there every day fresh made every morning
in the refrigerator section made fresh
in that glass bottle but here's the
here's the problem here
that customized glass bottle they're
only making so many of them until they
move it into the like a normal medical
medium bottle right the customized
collector's bottle you might you might
want to look out for the email that
we'll be sending out if you're coming
because you need to pre-order it you
should pre-order it so you get one is
what I'm saying cuz this is going to be
a really cool legendary bottle and you
might want to actually be there to
pre-order you want to pre-order it so
I'm going to have an email go at some
point showing you like what to do to
pre-order that so you get the smoothie
in that commemorative customized glass
bottle it's going to sell out that day
there's only 1,500 bottles that will be
available so you're going to want to
pre-order it so that's the other thing I
wanted to say but let's go back to this
a little
bit let's go back to this okay all right
before I answer some Q&A on health
because that's why I'm here going to
talk about health and everything before
we go there though I just want to give
you another little you know moment with
this
it's a medical medium Afterparty yeah
it's a medical medium
Afterparty
gulp
including yeah possible light blast yep
and what happened was it was going to be
just a meet and greet I was going to
meet you I was going to say hi and I'm
still doing that but so many people are
coming we realize it's bigger than we
thought so we're going to be actually
doing a medical medium after party
somewhere else afterwards so I'm letting
you know this is the
information the way this happens is just
unbelievable yeah life BLS definitely
and we have some fun things planned I
just want to tell you like this
Afterparty there is some fun things
planned I'm not going to open the my big
mouth right now I'm not going to just
you know blabber it all out but I'm just
going to tell you right now yeah there's
going to be some fun stuff so I'm
excited about that so let me just give
you if you just got on here I saw
somebody saying what is this what is
this what are you talking about before I
do the questions about answering
questions about
health yeah um it's going to be it's
going to be pretty amazing we're trying
to keep it lowkey at first just the meet
and greet are one because of the
customized commemorative incredible
glass bottle airan incredible glass
bottle heavy metal detox smoothie right
just 1,500 are being made I think
something around there so you're going
to want to pre-order it and I'll send
that email out so you guys know how to
pre-order that when it comes it's not
coming like I don't think it's going to
be in the next couple days but we'll
have that email as soon as we can but
this turned out to be something bigger
so many people request so many requests
and so forth that we're doing a medical
media after party got help me because
we're going to do a light blast and yeah
and and some other things are going to
be happening so just letting you know if
you're signed up now remember register
so I know you're coming register okay
sign up and register up for the Awan
event so the Awan meet and greets sign
up and register for that for the meet
and greet okay link is in the profile
link is in the description so sign up so
I know that you're coming and bringing
what you're bringing you know two people
three people what are you doing bringing
four people I think I saw somebody they
say we're bringing 10 people so yeah 10
people so anyway so it turned out to be
more than what I was thinking it would
be originally lowkey meet and greet say
hi to me I'm there right love to meet
you and then now there's a medical meme
after party
afterwards medical M after party you
will receive a paper invite with the
direction
and or your ticket in
aan just letting you know that's how
it's going to
go and who knows what
else like Pure medical medium fashion it
gets more intense and more things happen
that are
unexpected letting you know all right so
I just wanted to run that by you guys
you will have to be at aan though to get
your invite to do an Afterparty so it's
not something that like oh well hey I'm
not going to go to aan and which is fine
don't go if you don't want to but but
you're not going to be able to go to the
Afterparty because that's when I'm
handing out the invite it's at aan so
I'm there meet and greet hand out the
invite Aran will have celery juice by
the way and steamed potatoes just
411 they're going to have steamed
potatoes cuz that's what they did last
time time they did the whole steamed
potato thing for everybody if you
remember that's what they did so yeah so
they're going to have that again the
steamed potatoes and they're going to
have plenty of celery juice so that's
going to be cool too so if you can't
make yours that morning and you can't
get rid you can't find it that morning
or whatever it is Boom they're going to
have it there now this is all happening
starting around 7
a.m. yep I'm an early bird I go to bed
at 3:00 in the morning I wake up at 5:
I'm an early bird
I go to bed at 3:00 every night 3: in
the morning and I wake up at
4:45 anyway either way 7 in the
morning on September
7th that's when it starts I'm going to
be there for a few
hours and with the meet and greet okay
get you that invite to the
Afterparty I'm going
to yep hopefully everything goes nice
and smooth and I'm going to do a light
blast so we'll see anyway you guys all
right I want to get into a Q&A but I
just wanted to tell you what's happening
oh yeah don't forget listen out or look
out for that email from me okay where
you can pre-order that incredible
commemorative customized airwan and
medical medium collaboration heavy metal
detox
bottle and because there's only going to
be like 1,500 of those made and so you
want to pre-order that early Sol look
out for that email when you get a chance
you can end up with one of those I am so
excited I have not seen one hasn't been
it's not in my hand or anything I'm
going to see that that bottle myself and
be drinking out of it September 7th at
airan so that's what I'm going to see I
don't it's not like I'm going to get a
bottle beforehand or anything else I
wish I could but it's going to be when
you guys get it too so I'm excited all
right you guys do a little bit by the
way also
taada yeah heavy metal detox smoothie
got my oranges right here that's right
got my wild blueberries Frozen wild
blueberries right there the Wyman's ones
right got some slunch right there got
the viy stuff too boom boom boom
incredible spirulina the whole bit if
you see in here right check this
out okay that's the bmer GW blueberry
powder you guys know I work with these
guys I endorse them them but you got to
kind of do this right here and realize
the reason why you're doing that okay
you're breaking it up a little bit the
reason why you got to break it up a
little bit is because there's no
anti-caking
agents to stop it from sticking together
foreign agents so that's how incredible
this stuff is so I have this stuff right
here vimergy stuff I got Wyman's wild
blueberry juice right
here I know they got a sale coming up at
some point I don't know when it is but
they do I got a delicious mango right
here I had in the fridge I've been
holding on to this one hopefully it
looks pretty good inside I hope so I
really hope so hope it looks good in
there okay so I got the mango right
there too heavy metal detox smoothie and
I want to answer some questions to you I
got the medical medium books some of
them right here in with me right brains
saer
protocols this book right here
unbelievable the amount of information
in and brainsaver protocols by the way
and of course medical medium new edition
book one cleanse to heal legendary book
right there books that have saved lives
books that are saving lives every day
Liver Rescue over here on I you probably
can't see that but I got Liver Rescue
right there how many people have had
their lives saved by Liver Rescue
information and protocols including 369
right and then of course brain saver wow
the information just about like
supplements that are actually dangerous
or not good for you you wouldn't believe
what people are taking every day I hear
it all the time when they get this book
and they actually go to that section and
they find out they've been taking
something that's hurting them hurting
their liver hurting their brain hurting
their pancreas hurting their stomach and
so forth intestinal track the
information is there in there so
valuable it's beyond valuable right
and you guys so you guys keeping like
your eyes open these days on on a whole
bunch of stuff that's happening out
there in the health world right um a lot
of people getting sick right now so keep
your immune system strong that's always
important you know the hmds is what I'm
making right here which I'm excited
about um so
anyway so I'm just looking so you guys
just give me a chance to look through
comments too to see if I can catch one
here one doing other stuff so I bought
the medical medium books in audio
version best choice ever amazing thank
you John incredible encyclopedias for
life that's that's how I feel too
they're they're encyclopedias for almost
turned on the uh burner right there
encyclopedias for life they are Apon
right best books to ever exist my kids
will read them amazing and that's really
special to me I'm honored that's
incredible so very special to S so as
well it really is um people you know a
lot of people what they'll say is
they'll say oh that medical medium in
his stupid celerate juice what does he
know what does he know and they never
read the books they didn't know that
these Bibles got out there in the world
they didn't know that these Bibles got
out there and they're saving people's
lives and the millions that have had
their health change because of it they
don't know the incredible information
from above that's in here and they don't
realize that information they may be
talking about out there originated from
the books right but they be like that
medical medium who is that guy what has
he done who is he meanwhile I mean they
don't realize it's these right here from
s so clearly nature says where do you
start with MCAS and you're reacting to
almost all
foods including most of the healing
foods I was doing great with medical
medium and then um C rocked my world
with chronic shingles and MC s you know
with
okay you know what happens is that if C
rocked your world if you guys know what
I mean by C because even though
everybody's saying the word they're all
saying the word you know vovid vovid
vovid you know the word vovid vovid
they're always saying vovid vovid vovid
everybody's on the internet saying v v v
they're all saying that word right okay
do you see I'm not really saying that
word because they have nothing to worry
about but I do
I do have something to worry about even
though it's everywhere it's on all the
platforms and everybody V it V it it's
old news old news I still have to like
be careful and not see that word it's
crazy so back to the
Sea what happens with the sea is when
that sea finally dies off it can linger
in people too by the way and when it
finally dies off it produces a
tremendous amount of toxin if you're
somebody that's already chemical
sensitive and you're food sensitive and
this is important you guys if you're
food sensitive chemical sensitive
supplement sensitive you know with
anything you're just sensitive with
anything and everything and you don't
even know what why you're reacting or
where you're reacting and how it
works if you're somebody doing that and
you get C
bid and you get C what happens is though
c not only lowers the immune system cuz
it it it's in the body the immune
system's trying to get rid of it it's
trying to destroy it and the SE is
creating all this trouble right just
like the flu the flu does the same thing
it really creates a lot of problems it
breaks down the immune system but what
the flu and vit do and rs you know V and
all this what it
does is it produces poison and if you're
already chemical sensitive and you're
you've been recovering so you're
chemical sensitive person and you've
been recovering and you're doing good
and you're moving up the ladder and then
boom vit kicks you back knocks you back
a little bit Boom the flu knocks you
back a little bit boom RSV knocks you
back a little bit and lowers your your
immune system it's also going to produce
all this toxin tons of toxin it's going
to produce produce produce while it's
being killed too so as your immune
system's killing it it's going to
produce poison and toxin and when it
does that you're going to be more
chemical sensitive more supplement
sensitive more food sensitive more
sensitive more you know chemical
sensitive in the air sensitive for all
these other
reasons then because the sea the volid
knocked your immune system down because
RSV flu whatever knocked your immune
system down then the shingles Rises up
and now the shingles is moving up now
the herpes simplex one the cold sores
are popping out everywhere and then you
know herp Simplex two genital sores
popping out everywhere down here then
you know it's not just that and you know
next thing you know an epscene bar
starts to come up creeping up giving you
the chronic fatigue again next thing you
know the shingles you get a swash of
shingles here a swash of shingles here a
swash of shingles here or you get
shingles pain and nerve pain without
having the actual rash right all this
comes up because the flu and RSV and the
vulet all knocked down all knocked down
the immune system but produced a lot of
poison too and when it produced a lot of
poison you're now chemical sensitive
again you're now you're now supplement
sensitive you're now food sensitive you
don't know what to eat to do or what and
then on top of it if shingles started
rising up and shingles started coming up
and you know um cyto virus started
coming up your herpes simplex one
started coming up started rising up cuz
your immune system was down kicked down
by vet kick down by flu whatever you
kick down by the sea what happens is
that you're as things are go getting
stronger like the the shingles and
everything and Epstein bars and all
that's getting
stronger then that's producing more
neurotoxin and more neurotoxin and more
neurotoxin now once again now you're
like crap not only am I chemical
sensitive supplement sensitive food
sensitive but now I'm really feeling
like wow out of whack and I don't know
what's going on I feel like I'm out of
whack so what happens is when that
shingles and those herpe viruses those
the herpetic family starts to rise up
and you got low grade infections and
they're rising up now they're producing
all this neurotoxin and now you're back
in the saddle again with this whole
thing and you're just like oh my God
what is this I'm back to being sensitive
again that's how it works but but but
but but have no
fear with time and caring learning
protocols right learning
protocols so many of them suppl
mentation protocols and so forth and all
of that you start fixing things as I
throw these books all around everywhere
when you're learning what to do you're
learning how to rebuild the immune
system that's total immune right there
every day every day it's like who's
reaching out okay it's a cousin okay
yeah what's going on what's going on are
you are you doing something for your
immune system are you doing total immune
every day it's like someone's calling me
you know family and so forth or an old
friend is like what aw what do I do you
know I caught this I caught that my
immune system's really low and that's
the total immune by the way do you guys
know I'll just show you this really
quick no big deal it's total immune
that's by viy V is and Victor i m is and
Mary E RG y okay you guys know I work
with those guys because they're
incredible and um I endorse them because
the stuff's amazing I'm not the owner I
don't own a percentage of the company I
don't have stocks I don't have share in
the company I don't own a percentage of
the company that I'm just going to lay
that down now because there's a lot of
stupid talk out there and conspiracy out
there on AW constantly and it's just out
of control anyway but I endorse these
guys I work with them because they're
that incredible I stand behind these
guys with them anyway that's the total
immune and we're going into the fall
we're going into the fall that's total
immune right from bgy right there so
check that
out but have no fear there's ways to
build up your immune system there's ways
to lower the
neurotoxic rate there's ways of
recovering the SI the body system
lymphatic system the nervous system
right cardiovascular system whatever it
is there's ways of recovering your body
systems and then you're less sensitive
less chemical sensitive less food
sensitive less supplement sensitive out
there in a whole bit a lot of people are
supplement sensitive because they did
the swallowing all the charcoal years
ago they did crazy liver flushes with
all the olive oil can't even tell you
how stupid that is it's unbelievable
what people have done out there okay
okay and that's the thing with a lot of
people they've tried they've done all
the fish oil gobbling down the fish oil
every day for so long they've done
garbage bulk
multivitamins with all kinds of
magnesium sterate and everything else
Under the Sun in it they've done a lot
of stuff that hindered their system
weakened their system made them
sensitive and that's a whole thing that
people don't realize when it comes down
to supplement
sensitivities cor over there on YouTube
says I used to do ACV shots now I know
it it pains me pains me if I look online
for a minute and I'm looking on YouTube
for a second and then you see like an ad
come up with some like nutritionist
that's like here's the best way to help
your stomach problem or the best way for
your health it's doing this and they
take a apple cider vinegar put two
tablespoons of Apple Cedar vinegar put
lemon in there of course medical medium
stuff Le put lemon in there and put a
little bit of cayenne pepper in there
too and mix it up and you take this
every day and then the media comes along
it's like we'll do an article on you
because you're such a smart nutritionist
it's like meanwhile that apple centa
vinegar will rot your teeth out they
will fall apart down the road and you'll
be getting the whole veneers and
everything else and all that stuff it's
crazy what happens and the apple cided
vinegar destroys gut balance everybody's
like microbiome microbiome it's like
another microbiome doctor another
microbiome microbiome microbiome you
want to destroy your microbiome do the
ACV destroys it anyway so very important
to know vinegars are so bad on your
system but when people do all those
kinds of things they get sensitive later
they can get more chemical sensitive
they can get more food sensitive and
supplement sensitive yes it's it's so
true blooding soil Shield Maiden that is
a really cool handle where can I buy
your books audio books go to Amazon go
to Amazon you can go right there the
books are on sale today at Amazon
right there you go you can totally find
them there medical medium books most
bookstores too you can walk in
bookstores they're out there which is
incredible thanks to my publisher
they're in bookstores around the world
and um and that that's been a blessing
to get them out there best way to get
rid of chronic sinus in my head and eyes
learning what understanding what chronic
sinus means like what is it you know if
you weren't diagnosed with a pup in your
in your sinus cavity or something else
or maybe you're dealing with scar tissue
in your sinus cavity you know how did it
get there what happened what's going on
with sinuses why are you having a
post-nasal drip why are you having
sinusitis right so learning key pieces
to all of that and you know when I tell
doctor friends that come to me and
doctors that try to reach out to me I
talked to one recently by the way just
recing about all kinds of different
things I didn't talk about sinusitis but
we talked about UTI and stuff and it's
important to know what sinusitis is that
right there when the doctor doesn't know
what it is when the doctor doesn't know
why you have sinus sinusitis right they
just don't know a lot of people will
have bacteria that is Strep so the whole
strep family right strep bacteria
creates a sinusitis it creates UTI
conjunctive vitis it creates acne it
creates sore throats it creates ear
infections it creates otitis media it
creates all kinds of different stuff
conjunctivitis sty I know I said that
sty it creates all these things right
strep is behind so it's getting to the
underlying part of why you have the
sinusitis it's getting to the underlying
aspect and that's the key right there
and then what happens is the strep sits
inside the sinuses has a field day
because the immune systems low and when
your immune system is low the strep is
doing a dance inside the person's sinus
cavities and lymphatic system what I've
seen over the years is a lot of people
and not everybody not everybody but a
lot of people will have the acne along
with some sinusitis along with
mucus mucus forming spittle you know
just a mucus
congestion you know they'll have that
they'll have some acne they'll get some
ear stuff they'll get some eye stuff
they'll get all kinds of dry eyes their
eyes are so dry because their ducks are
clogged with strap and they don't know
it they got strep on their anus they got
strep in their mouth they don't know it
they got strep in their Ducks of their
eyes they got SHP in their ears they get
the sostis they their immune system's
low it may be battling one or two or
three different varieties of SHP and
people don't realize this so you know so
what do we do what do we do medical
medium books what do we have in here
we've got strep information in these
books strep protocols in these books
critical and in those protocols you'll
see something like zinc like use the
viery zinc just letting you know but you
know there's like you see things like
zinc in there and you see other things
too you see other stuff golden seal but
you see there's protocols right and then
Foods to avoid foods to avoid now listen
out of all this all the different
so-called modalities out there medical
medium information is probably one of
the more lenient when it comes down to
food okay probably one of the more
lenient but people heal because it's not
about taking away everybody's food quite
the contrary with medical Med
information there's people that quote
can only eat four blueberries before
they found medical medium
information they can only eat four
blueberries a day before they found
medical medium information they realize
they can eat way more blueberries and do
their healing and heal there's people
out there that couldn't touch a piece of
fruit were told stay away from banana
stay away from anything stay away from
oranges stay away from leafy greens
people being told that vegetables are
toxic and I still see that out there
there's ads running out there all the
time like your vegetables are toxic
don't eat any vegetables that's the
problem right there so how do people
heal but staying away from certain foods
can help with the sinusitis it can help
with the strap and that's really
important right there Sapphire Rose on
YouTube can toxic heavy metals block you
spiritually and only allow you to
progress to a certain level of
Consciousness and manifestations okay so
okay toxic heavy metals can definitely
rain on somebody's parade on a lot of
levels it doesn't mean you never
spiritually grow but toxic heavy metals
can talk for you they can speak for you
that's why we're sitting here making
little detox
movie because I never want I would like
I would like this right now because I
never want metals to speak for me ever I
don't because if they were speaking for
me they'd probably be doing this yeah
fish oil is great okay you know 20 15
fish oil is amazing take lots of fish
oil 2016 ooh do a liver flush with tons
of olive oil 2017 make sure you do lots
of ionized alkaline water 2018 make sure
you cold plunge cold plunge that's the
answer 2019 make sure you do you do like
grounding Barefoot always be barefoot
2020 meanwhile you stay sick you stay
sick you stay sick I don't let metal
speak for me if they spoke for me people
would not be getting better out there I
can promise promise you that because I'd
probably hear so
wrong and I'd probably be listening to S
so and be like what did you say um what
um swimming's healthy for you is that
what you said or did you just say cold
plunging is healthy for you freeze your
butt off the point is is that yeah I
don't want Metals ever speaking for me
down the road as I get older and older
and older I don't want Metals talking
for me and that's what happens so with a
lot of people metals are talking for
them keep that in mind
they are and they get and what happens
is metals are speaking for them they can
contradict themselves Seven Ways to
Sunday they can make people miserable
emotionally they can make people say
things they never wanted to
say metals can create tourettes
OCD yeah metals can create depression
anxiety uh-huh medals can create
depersonalization metals can make memory
go see you
later bye memory what was that can't
remember gone boom well you know I'm a
short I'm a short kind of what is it
called the I can remember things from
the past long long ago but shortterm
memory I just don't have so my
short-term memory is gone like where did
I just put my keys or what did I just do
a minute ago did I just go to the
bathroom was I just outside oh I forgot
got to do this I just got off the phone
somebody but I don't even know what they
said cuz it short-term memory and I
forgot but I can remember riding a
bicycle when I was a kid I remember when
we went to that lake with my family and
I remember this but I can't remember a
single thing right now yeah shortterm
memory
medals right those are like you so okay
can you grow spiritually while while
dealing with toxic heavy metals sure you
can you can it could be a fight could be
a fight but the fact that you have toxic
heavy metals and it's impeding your life
that's the growth right there and I
don't know what kind of spiritually
growth growth you might be thinking
spiritual growth are you talking about
just you know yoga and and meditation
and and you're you know you're you're
going to Retreats and you're talking
about spiritual Concepts talking about
that kind of spiritual growth are you
talking about like the guts are you
talking about spiritual growth you know
where you've been through hell and back
and you're seasoned you're no full
you've been down the road before you
know what's up you know there's Darkness
you know there's good you know there's
evil you know yeah you know there's
genocide on this planet there always has
been you know that there's crazy stuff
happening all the time and you know
everybody's out for something it seems
like and everybody's a bullshitter and
all these things and you're aware of
this and you're wise to to this yeah
that spiritual growth it's a different
kind of spiritual growth right spiritual
growth of Hard Knocks and then there's
the suffering if you've suffered you've
been down on your hands and knees and
you're praying to God like God am I
going to die now what the heck is going
on I need to heal I can't function like
that kind of thing and you're fighting
you know you're fighting for it man
you're fighting and you're struggling
you're trying to get better and you're
just like oh my God oh my God tell about
that spiritual growth because that's
spiritual growth right there too because
I've seen people they're down on their
knees man they've risen out of the ashes
and they're Spiritual Beings after they
rise out of the ashes like that and I've
talked to a lot of them and I've seen a
lot of them at the medical medium event
June 15th right and I was in the
presence of people you know I mean
people are like they're like aw you know
I I can't believe I'm I'm here and I get
to say hi and you're signing my book but
what they don't realize is I can't
believe that that I'm in the presence of
these Masters these people you guys who
rose out of the ashes fought for it you
guys are Spiritual Beings you guys have
Supernatural Powers you haven't even
tapped into because of what you went
through and I can't believe that I'm so
blessed that I'm you know in front of
you you know that I'm in front of you
that's a big deal for me keep that in
mind I know people are like I can't
believe I'm talking aw right now and and
I'm like actually I can't believe that
I'm meeting you right now and I'm saying
hi right now so he said I am on heavy
metal detox smoothie since seven years
thanks to you and I have begun studying
again at 61 years
old yeah the heavy metal
detox it clears someone it clears
them it's like a clearing over time is
what it is
and yes toxic heavy metals speak for
people they make people break up in
relationships they make people say
things they shouldn't have said in a
relationship and regret it later they
make people like get really really
emotional and triggered so easy because
they got Metals getting in the way of
their neurons so they're receiving
messages messages are leaving them in
ways that aren't as healthy as it could
be the heavy the heavy metals can
saturate into people's brains and
confuse use neurons and neurotransmitter
chemicals and and um and all of it
electrical impulses allowing somebody to
shift gears in a way that may not be
fruitful and helpful and then the metals
speak for people and it's really
difficult and that's okay that's okay
because we work on cleaning them up and
getting them out and getting them to go
away that's important right there so
keep that in mind anyway making a little
bit of a smoothie right here heav metal
detox movie you guys just got on here
okay um I'm going to be at Awan
September 7th for a meet and greet and
then it kind of turned into
something more in like Pure medical me
fashion we have to do something about it
and that means there's an Afterparty and
I'm going to be most likely doing a
light blast on that day September
7th and in order to even go to the
Afterparty you do have to be a airan so
I can at least hand you an invite a
ticket to get to there so that's
something that's important also keep in
mind pre-ordering your customized bottle
the heavy metal detox smoothie medical
medium glass bottle commemorative bottle
they're only making like 1,00 of them or
something like that don't quote me on
the exact amount but it's something like
that you you're going to want to listen
out for the
email that we're that we're sending out
at some point because you're going to
want to pre-order that one so when you
get there you can get a hold of one of
those bottles meaning with a smoothie in
it so you can drink it and have some fun
be sure to register link is in the
description and on YouTube and on Rumble
and on Facebook and on Telegram and the
link is in the profile and on Instagram
and it's on Tik Tok too make sure that
you register so I know if you're coming
if you're not coming I mean sure
surprise me I guess and don't register
but then you know it's not it doesn't
make things easier for me so anyway
important to know the medical medium
Afterparty that's that's in what
happening just letting you know
September 7th you got to go to aan to
even know where to go and how to do it
and hey you want to come and i' love to
meet
you yep that's where you'll get the
invite to the Afterparty medical mum
Afterparty all right let's get going on
this all right I'm just looking for
utensils I'm going to use this one right
here you guys don't mind
let me get some wild blueberries in here
is what we're going to do so look look
if you want to do more than two cups be
my guest if you want to do less than two
cups be my guest okay it's okay I've
always said the heavy metal detox isn't
just smoothie it could be a smoothie
Bowl it can be a meal throughout the day
as long as you have the five key
ingredients to do the job that needs to
be done
the five key ingredients the spirulina
you got to have that the barley grass
juice powder you got to have that the
right the wild blueberries you got to
have that and the dols that's the liquid
dols right there um all right let me
just get some blueberries in here ooh
don't call them blueberries do not call
them blueberries these are wild
blueberries huge difference I just
insulted these wild blueberries by
calling them a blueberry
because there's a vast difference from
cultivated clamshell meaning like you
get the little pint-sized clam shell the
plastic clam shells at the store and
it's a cultivated blueberry it's not a
wild blueberry people use them all the
time they don't do a scratch compared to
the wild blueberry very important when
it comes down to doing the job Kelly
over there on YouTube that makes me tear
up your info has saved my life after
cancer thank you for being here Kelly
amazing and thank you for um just being
in the community oh my God over there on
YouTube Om I have so many doctors in my
family and they all have friends Etc but
none could help your truth Shines My
question is how effective is the vimergy
wbb powder wild blueberry powder versus
the frozen fruit love from Ireland so
here's what I do okay now all right so
keep this in mind right you got the
blueberries you got the wild blueberries
like the Wyman's company that I endorse
they're the ones that I use right for
the Frozen wild blueberry okay all right
and this is another wild blueberry that
comes from a different area on the
planet okay very important to know here
right I like
using like different wild blueberri so I
got this one here from viy which I'm
excited about and I showed you the no
anti-caking agents right how incredible
that is
and I like the Wyman's too and I'm going
to put a little bit of the Wyman's while
blueberry juice in there too
because every strain of wild
blueberry right is a little different
still holds power but it's a little
different that's how incredible it is
right the low Bush so this is the low
Bush wild blueberry it's really
incredible that we even have access to
this and I dream about that when I was
young I remember I was laying in a wild
Blueberry field low Bush wild Blueberry
field and I was doing that thing where
you ever you know where you go into the
snow and you do the angel thing in the
snow where you wave your arms and your
legs go out like this and your Fanning
right in the snow and you're laying on
your back and you're just doing right
you're just doing this while you're
laying on your back right you know and
you try to make your wings as big as you
want whatever and you're doing that
there okay well I
as a child would love laying in a wild
Blueberry field and S so would tell me
the power of the wild blueberry how
incredible it was and what it does for
the body and the antioxidant power it
has for the brain and nervous system and
for the everything for the immune system
right and then I would lay in the wild
blueberry fields and I would do the
whole Angel Fanning thing where I'd kind
of have my legs spreading and my arms
spreading and I would do like like that
in the field and then when I would get
up there'd be like an imprint of an
angel in the wild Blueberry Patch right
just like if you were doing that in the
snow it's just incredible God I just
love thinking about that all right so
let's get some cilantro in here if you
guys are okay with that so I'm going to
pop a cup in here maybe a little bit
more surprise surprise a little bit
more but do you realize what I just did
you guys know this right right um are
you making dinner tonight would you like
some cilantro on your f
would you like some cilantro on your
chicken if you're a chicken eater right
avocado if you're an avocado eater right
I'm having some cilantro for dinner
tonight I eat cilantro I can have just a
little bit of that right on my avocado
little bit of that on my right my fish I
could just do that okay but that's
nothing compared to when you eat
cilantro and you use it and the hmds is
incredible because of the amount of
cilantro that goes in there you're using
this herb as a leafy green and man when
you supersede greens by using a leafy
green herb to this capacity that's
another thing all on its own never mind
the metal enhancement stuff that that
cilantro does with removing Metals
incredible so here we go all right so
let's move on a little bit I'm going to
add just a little bit more I'm going to
do the wild blueberry powder I love this
I love love seeing clumps love seeing
big clumps in
here if I don't see big clumps in here I
will not be happy I want big fat clumps
in this there's a reason for that okay
no anti-caking agents you guys have to
understand there people out there
they're chemical sensitive and they're
everything sensitive and they could be
doing caking they could doing
anti-caking agents and they don't even
know it they're in every patter out
there no company does this
this is different entirely different
companies may say that they they don't
do it they don't do it because it takes
too much energy too much time too much
money no one would do it anyway it's the
five main ingredients that makes the
difference that's what it is now if you
got three out of five you got three out
of five and I'll talk about that okay we
got Boom the wild blueberry we knocked
that out of the park wild blueberry
juice frozen wild blueberry from londs
right we got the viy wild blueberry
powder we're killing it with wild
blueberry killing it it's just amazing
right so let's move on let's go with
some dols here it is liquid douls
phenomenal product right there all on
its own and what I do is I'll just take
a droper full if I can't get the heavy
metal detox smoothie in but I want to
get at least three of the five
ingredients to the heavy metal detox in
my body so I can make a difference right
with Metals if I want to do that I will
do a straight dropper full of the ads
right in my mouth just like that okay
I'm going to pop that in
there
boom remember you don't have to have the
Smoothie you can have it in a smoothie
Bowl you can have it on a salad but get
your five key ingredients in through the
course of the day that is what it's all
about right here that's the medical
medium heavy metal detox okay keep that
in mind all right to move on a little
bit barley grass juice
powder
uh-huh that's right amazing stuff by the
way amazing barley grass juice
powder very
important right it's juice that's the
difference because what happens with a
lot of people and I love when this
clumps up if you get a clump in here
no anti-caking agents as well incredible
so that's the vimergy Bley grass cheese
powder that's a supplement all on its
own right I get I give a little bit to
my animals so I take a little bit of the
barrass juice powder and it goes in my
animal my
animals right my
dogs and other animals I have right it
goes into their food every single day I
put that in their food okay all right so
we got that in there now we got the
spirulina can't say enough about
spirulina but when it's the best kind
out there I can't say enough it's the
vmer spirulina and I'm going to pop some
of that in
there
man incredible really incredible
incredible for the immune system all of
this incredible for nutrients dense
nutrients that actually go in the right
places into the cells of our body into
healthy cells keeping them strong into
toxic cells and pulling stuff out right
this stuff is going into toxic cells and
pulling stuff out that shouldn't be in
there but feeding cells with things that
the cells need nutrients serious
nutrients all
right Susan see over there on YouTube aw
I heal lung cancer following your
information can get me emotional um
thank you so much you're a lifesaver I'm
forever grateful to you and S so thank
you for being here Susan truly okay all
right I'm going to kind of crack into an
orange right I'm going to squeeze some
of that in
here love oranges love love love oranges
okay you love the barley grass cheese
powder too amazing all right
just reading some comments you
guys
okay someone said why do I always feel
left
out a lot of people have the feel left
out syndrome they do they do it it's not
just feeling left out a lot of people
have the feeling like they're missing
out okay and
not everything is physical not
everything is physical but I've seen
people have those experiences where they
feel that way and once they rid metals
and other poisons and toxins they're
feeling different feeling different you
know and also I mean if someone had a
childhood injury okay some bullying that
happened in their life growing up or
their family was abusive or they were
they suffered mental abuse when they
were a child or a teenager
We're Young Adult and they suffered this
okay it can hang on it can be wired into
those neurons and it it needs some
healing and when it's wired into those
neurons we have allergies like allergies
to different people and different
experiences and different words and all
kinds of
stuff somebody can have emotional
injuries to the brain that caused a
little bit of scar tissue in the brain
creating something like the feeling of
always feeling left
out there's there's a lot of stuff that
that can go on Fon says over there on
YouTube feel so weird I've been watching
your videos for 3 years and I thought
you didn't do anything in person anymore
fast forward 3 years and you've done two
events in less than two months amazing
At Your Service I am I am at your
service okay okay all right
let's see what this mango looks like
that's kind of what I want to do what
does this mango look like ah this mango
looks good it does setad of banana I'm
doing mango CU I got some mangoes in my
refrigerator so instead of bananas I'm
doing some
mango it's right knock this in here
let's go I love
bananas I just don't have any right now
now okay Sapphire says why do some
people end up on this healing path and
some
don't you mean the healing path of
medical medum information
learning these incredible tools from
above and some don't end
up it's a lot of Darkness out
there trying to derail a lot of people
all the time
it's in the
media a lot of people are brainwashed
and
conditioned a lot of people are
brainwashed in
institutions that they've graduated from
a lot of people there's a lot of reasons
why people and it sometimes it takes a
Jesus come to Jesus moment sometimes it
takes to it takes a person a moment of
you know I'm praying to God because I
need answers sometimes it takes like a
non-religious person who just you know
hates God and hates even the thought of
God and doesn't believe in anything like
that doesn't believe there's this one
God sitting on a throne with a big gray
beard that's going to punish everybody
if they do something wrong whatever it
is and they have they're so allergic to
religion and they don't believe in
anything not even say something
Supernatural some kind of spiritual
anything and then they have this moment
where it hits them and just
like
boom and it hits
them going to peel this back a little
bit
here all
right
nice get a little bit more of this mango
in here if you guys don't
mind sad part about it all so what do
what do our bodies think we our
Consciousness can think all kinds of
crap and things and different stuff what
does our body think how about that right
there what about
that Laray over there on IG do you need
a
binder I was told if you don't take one
it can make you feel sick from the
toxins as they leave your body okay
let's let's go into this really
quick I'm going to like bullet point
this right now for you
medical medium
information on heavy
metals and the heavy metal
detox was the
Forefront still is but when it hit it
was groundbreaking nobody even knew
about any of the stuff like this or
Metals what they do or anything like
that but what happened was my
competitors my
competitors very important to
know were like how did this guy do this
how does he have millions of people all
around the world how were millions of
books sold on the planet all around the
world teaching people about detoxing
medals and I want a piece of that my
competitors decided to start attacking
medical medium information by saying out
there you need binders you need binders
oh you're they were so sick of hearing
everybody doing the medical medium heavy
metal detox that they came up with this
other alternative opposition weapon
a verbal
weapon they were so sick of hearing it
everywhere from nutritionists to health
coaches to regular influencers they
hated hearing I'm on the heavy metal
detox I'm on the medical medium heavy
metal detox I'm on the heavy metal heavy
metal heavy metal heavy metal medical
medium medical medium medical medium
medical and they just totally just
popped and they said yeah but you know
what he doesn't have any binders in
there what there's no binders in medical
medium there's there's no bonders in his
in in his smoothie or in his heavy metal
detox program thingy even though there's
no program but protocol it is a protocol
and what happened was yeah the
competitors were like yeah we're getting
a rise out of people we're scaring them
we're telling him there's no binders in
his stuff you need a binder his heavy
metal detox doesn't work because you
need a binder you need the proper binder
so what happened was about four years
ago maybe 5 years ago somewhere around
that time period the opposite
the jealous jealous greedy
greedy people competitors were like
binder binder binder people wanted to
make money some people in the medical
medium Community were like you know
Screw Anthony let me go and push a
binder let me go and push Zite or some
other thing and call it a binder Anthony
doesn't know anything he doesn't know
how to do anything even meanwhile people
are healing around the world including
them it wasn't it was a way for people
to bank over the last so many years to
try to sell a binder here you're not on
charcoal charcoal will help do it you're
not on this this will help do it you're
not on Zite that will help do it right
it was all about like you you need to be
in a binder you're on heavy metal detox
you don't have a binder what what what
and they spread this
cancellation tactic technique all
around and then people were also selling
binders all kinds of what they called
were binders like you need to be on this
binder and were selling it and then
they'll do this oh yeah you're taking
the medical meme heavy metal detox
smoothie you should also add this in
there this will help you add shilene in
there add xelate in there add folic
minerals and fulid acid fulvic acid in
there do that and just so they can sell
stuff and sell stuff because they were
training people the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie or heavy metal
detox doesn't have a
binder okay and that's where the binder
thing came out that's where it all kind
of like developed just in the health
scene right now but guess what guess
what it is all binder baby it is all
binder that's how stupid the whole thing
was but they made some Headway a little
bit because they convinced enough people
that they were doing something wrong
because they needed a binder yeah they
hurt those people because they use
zeolites that actually weren't edible
varieties of zeolite they were doing
that they were doing charcoal and
damaging their Linings of their
intestinal tract they were doing all
kinds of things and they're con
convincing people they needed these
binders when they didn't because guess
what the binder is built into the heavy
metal detox that's right the binder is
built in
here the ultimate binders are in here
that is the whole point it's there to
grab on to junk and garbage and metals
and stuff and poisons and pesticides and
anything else it's there to bind onto it
and take it out and if you read the
medical medium books you'll see the
process in how it
works and it has Street Credibility man
it has street cred of saving people's
lives of removing crap out of them so
they could think clear and get their
life back and rid their depression and
everything else it is a
binder it is a
binder but my
competitors wanted to bank and they
wanted to try to take me down so they
pulled the binder game and they
convinced a few people to be concerned
about binders but those people were
screwed over by them and that's what
happened just line you're actually going
to be there no way YouTube looking
forward to seeing you in Calabasas
Anthony guess what you know what a wild
blueberry is it's a
binder it's a binder did you ever see a
gel up did you ever see it turned into a
pecon pecon you know did you ever see
that where it's like all
pectin it's PE
it is a binder it's moving through to
bind onto anything that was detoxed out
of you it is a binder it's rolling out
of
you and when I heard that when I heard
people do that and try to set me up and
try to frame me on no binder crap and
try to like do everything that could to
take down the heavy metal detox that
saved lives the the one that has the
street cred when I heard people do that
and say it doesn't have a binder it
doesn't have a binder it's like Joker
man it is a binder what do you think the
wild blueberry is what do you think that
gelatinous gel that builds up and
becomes this gelatinous Clump what do
you think that ptin is it is the binder
and not only that what do you think
sparina is it's a binder what do you
think dols is it's a binder but not just
a binder it's a binder that works
pulling out what it needs to pull out
metals and so forth and everything else
it is a
binder and that makes you wake up in the
morning and go there's a lot of people
out there that are either just greedy
jealous or they're just idiots they you
know they're they're out there and
they're out there trying to stare people
away so they don't heal they're trying
to mess people's heads up so they don't
heal it's a dogat dog world out there is
what it is that's what it is it's a wolf
that eats a coyote it's a coyote that
eats a
fox and that's what's going on out there
are you a fox or you you a wolf or you a
coyote whatever you are it's dog eat dog
and that's what it is out
there because nobody cares about The
Chronic Leo really they just care about
making money nobody cares about somebody
being sick really they don't care they
just care about the new like shock and
awe and the new shiny thing and you know
hey heal this in 10 seconds um do this
in 10 seconds you know top five things
whatever Debbie says I love what you
share fairly new to it all what you
share makes so much sense I know I need
to change diet detox very Unsure how or
where to start have some of your books
going to order both brain saver books
and cleanse to heel incredible start
with a morning cleanse ask your doctor
what's right for you ask your doctor and
say is it okay if I can do the morning
cleanse from medical medium book right
here Anthony William but yeah morning
cleanse is what I would start with I'm
going to I'm going to blend this up
because I'm getting hungry and I'm
getting thirsty
thirsty I'm getting
Thursday all right let's go let's turn
this
on and let's hit
it
uhoh oh there we go
[Music]
got some music in my head right
now
done
done all right
someone said the other day that I'm not
charismatic I have no Charisma right you
can think that that's fine I'm not a big
believer that I have Charisma or I'm
charismatic but when they were saying it
they were like this they were on some
video they're going you know they're
like Anthony's not charismatic he's not
he has no Charisma whatsoever and I'm
like dude I'm sure a lot of people would
say that about you you shouldn't be
saying that I'm not saying the most
charismatic person person but when I saw
that I was just like oh my God okay
whatever all right you guys
look I'm so psyched about this this is
the binder that's the whole
point I don't know what else to say
about it that's what this
is It's the whole
point duh but any any kind of like
reason to stop try to stop something and
Bank you know off of like stopping it
Michelle B over there on
YouTube I didn't eat bananas for 28
years until I found medical
medium they caused me so much stomach
pain now I eat them every day with no
pain it's incredible it really is that
may not be a big deal to some people but
can I tell you something that's huge
that's huge couldn't eat bananas for 28
years now you you can eat them that's a
big deal it means something it means
something to me so thank you for telling
me about it because I know a bunch of
people where that that's everything to
them and so important crispy perspective
over there on YouTube what's up Krispy
what do you got cooking there you
are okay making the hmds advanced
oo nice
you're brave man you're
brave making the heavy metal detox
Advan nice from the heavy metal detox
cleanse and
protocols nice nice this wasn't even the
advanced this is the classic right
here this is the
classic you guys don't mind
right oh so good I just don't want a
blue face right now in front of you guys
although I'll just down this thing on
you know what who cares Hannah over
there [__] what is the recipe for this
smoothie little bit of
orange wild blueberries little bit of
wild blueberries two cups of wild
blueberries you could do one cup you can
do less it's okay some wild blueberry
juice the Wyman's wild blueberry juice
do you have it look out for their sale
coming up right
cilantro beautiful cilantro right there
you can find the recipe at medical.com
you can go right to Medical me.com and
find the recipe and all the books too
it's in the
books okay in Orange did I say an
orange okay did I say that DOL that's
the vmer liquid douls right there it's
incredible product right there vmer g v
is in Victor i m RG y i support these
guys I endorse these guys and I'm going
to make this clear because of the rumors
or the conspiracy cuz just like a new
conspiracy on me every day I do not own
this company I don't own a percentage of
this company I'm not an owner on any
level I don't have shares in this
company I don't have stock in this
company critical to
know all
right
period period and then of course the um
v g spirina EMG barleygrass cheese
powder um yeah okay that's what's in
there
Mimi theity aw tell us more about
meaning of life
please
well I think we all put our pants on the
same way every single morning
and that tells you
something very
important if you wear
pants tells you a lot it's an old saying
that's been around for many many years
that person puts their pants on the same
way you do every single
morning but it really tells you
something really important so no matter
who you are on this planet or what
you're doing or anything else in
that anything else no matter what you do
looking up to somebody on this planet or
looking down to somebody else on this
[Music]
planet when they get out of bed and
maybe isn't right away you know they
have to put their pants on pretty much
the same way as everybody else puts
their pants pants
on
and and the next part I'm not going to
tell you because it's kind of sad but I
think what I'll do is a telegram about
it instead at some point cuz spirit's
giving me a lot of information of why
that's important to know it'll give you
some meaning about
life and it just hits you like
this and you're just like
whoa even has to be emotional What
Spirit just told me that has to be that
has to be
delivered with all the extra
information you guys heavy metal detox
smoothie
is what I just made are you going to be
there September
7th you do the cilantro nerve gut
stabilizer for my hmds is that okay yeah
I think it's fine ask your doctor what's
right for you but I think it's
great I tell you know friends that have
done that have done that before it's
fine make sure you are on the medical
medium newsletter I have some special
things coming out on there very
important I'm sending out an email so
you guys know how to pre-order your
commemorative custom smoothie in the
glass bottle at aan on the day of the
7th so that you get it and they don't
run out on you and you actually can get
one so just look out for that email
that's number one number
two turns out it's not going to just be
a meet and
greet where I meet and greet you there
like planned it's still a meet and greet
but now it's even more which I don't
even know I mean that's that's crazy
right it's even more and the meet and
greet is now turned into also meet and
greet and then an Afterparty but you got
to be at
aan to get an invite to get to that
after party and I'm going to do
everything I can in my power with my
free
will to give everybody a light blast and
a really potent one
too keep you in keep that in mind going
to be a Calabasas in California
Calabasas in California
hey
Awan aan is going to be awesome they're
looking out for our people they're
looking out for the medical medium
Community they are excited they are
excited about you guys coming and
they're looking out for you guys they
want you guys to have a good experience
a happy experience there and so they
care and they care about the medical
medium community and that's another
reason why I'm even there because they
actually care and when I find people in
the world that actually care about the
medical M community and the chronically
ill right in the medical mem community
that takes me to another level of how I
feel with all of it and them and the
whole bsiness I support them Iran is
going to be awesome like I said it's
special when everyone gets to see each
other so it's the medical M Community
seeing each other talking to each other
all of that and that's incredible all on
its own so is there somebody in the
medical medum community you always
wanted to say hi to you and you happen
to go there all of a sudden you meet
somebody you never thought you'd meet or
you meet somebody that you knew online
in the community but you're there and
everybody's seeing each other it is like
another level and the energy there and
the Angelic nature on all of it and
around all of it is just incredible by
the
way
yep yeah Tamara Jones says YouTube Holy
Cow bunch of explanation points it takes
so much
Charisma to
get the aw wait what is that Charisma to
get
AI okay let me see Tamara you said holy
cow it takes so much Charisma to get all
of us interested in healing explanation
points I love your charisma it's a
healing it it's a healing variety of
Charisma I got charisma
okay thank you I'm
honored aw's got no Charisma that guy's
got no
Charisma thank you you guys I'm excited
all
right we talked about a bunch of stuff
we talked about custis we talked about
strep we talked about what happens when
you get C which is noid you get noid I
got it you know what I mean right
novit when you get novit the flu RSV
knocks down the immune system we talked
about that how all these other things we
talked about chemical sensitivity
supplement sensitivities we talked about
certain supplements that are actually
dangerous for you out there we made the
hmds we talked about how Metals how they
speak for us which is not good too and a
bunch of other stuff we talked about
Lucy says coming to see you with my kids
whoa so who is coming September
7th make sure you
register
yep got medical medium.com register link
is in the description link is in the
profile if you're
coming
yep Shen
777 aw you're the only one I can listen
to all day every day God bless
you God bless you I am honored beyond
all
honored I don't don't think I even like
my voice I don't think I like my voice
so I'm honored Nancy Newman says I love
the oral care with celery juice whoa
okay medical medium tools are so
powerful there's so many people that
reverse their their cavities because of
celery juice right Dental healing tools
I love the oral care with celery juice
and propolis and dental Healing Foods
please share more it works here's the
propolis pure right here there are
people out there suffering from so many
different conditions and oral conditions
and they have no idea no idea about what
I'm holding in my hand this is the
vimergy
propolis this has the active cortin
inside of it the polyphenols it has the
active cortin that's the propolis right
there I have everybody I know on
propolis everybody I know like family
close friends childhood friends I have
them on propolis every day are you
taking your propolis oh no I forgot
haven't taken it the last two days take
your propolis take your
prop this is one of the most incredible
products right there that's the vimergy
one these in Victor i m e RG y right
there okay topically on
sores how many people get Source in
their mouth I tell family and friends
put it topically on on sores in your
mouth yeah how many people have all
kinds of different sores in their mouth
put it topically in sores ask your
doctor what's right for you tell your
doctor what do what does he or she think
about the propolis for sores and stuff
like that mouth sores and all that other
stuff oral health Oral Care oh my God
drove me nuts the oil pulling the oil
pulling you
know whoa
Tik Tok just restricted
me um they punish and punish and punish
for no reason they just punish hey check
this out okay oil pulling heard that for
years right medical medium even put
medical medium information s so put
information about oil pulling in the
books
right okay everybody's like oil pulling
oil pulling that's what you use for oral
health that's what it is and medical Med
information was like no that's not the
answer there's a lot of reasons why
that's not the answer
right and it's like oil boing if
everybody knew that what propolis did
and how good it was for oral health if
they only knew like how do we how do we
teach out there like you know I got
people that learn the information from s
so some a messenger and then they go and
teach it and they're they're out there
teaching they're like propis is critical
for that I like oil that's the best one
they're like no propolis they're like no
oil pulling how do you actually help
people heal and get the information they
need how anyway you
guys it's incredible
stuff thanks time and energy that's for
sure you guys it's been
amazing thank you for um your questions
thank you for being on here thanks for
hanging out while we made the smoothie
I'm going to guzzle it soon as we hang
up here soon as we sign off I'm going to
guzzle it and are you coming September
7th the Calabasas in
California and for a meet and greet I'd
be honored to meet you once again like I
said I'm honored to be in your presence
and that's how I felt June 15th I still
feel that way I always have felt that
way I love you guys too and
so if I see you guys there I see you
guys there if you can't make it can't
make it it's just the way it is
Christine says what company to get the
propolis and tell others too tell others
too this is vimergy that's the company V
I'll spell it out real slow V is
invictor i m and Mary
ergy.com I love you guys tell other
people about it so they have a shot to
move themselves forward love you guys
I'll see you September 7th if you're
coming guys are amazing God bless you
okay right