friends challenge you guys this is the
pre-cleanse right here this is it
pre-cleanse because tomorrow
we're doing it i am so pumped up you're
looking around in here do you guys see
anything in here
you see like winter squash
you see lemon water right there i see
oranges i see lemons i see everything
we're gonna juice a little bit of celery
right lost that one they got it we're
gonna do we're gonna have some fun it's
gonna be awesome so we're doing the
medical medium morning plans challenge
but really we're getting ready for it
okay
i'm doing it anyway today but it starts
tomorrow and it's free
it's free
good to see you guys coming on here i'm
excited about this i'm gonna talk about
why
you have to cleanse why it's important
if you hear someone say the body
cleanses itself
they're wrong
i mean
the body does not cleanse itself
we
get
sick
and we die
that's how it works on planet earth
that's how it works okay
do you want to get sick early
and die early
or do you want to get
sick
way at the end
and die later that's a better option
right because everybody dies and
everybody dies and they get sick right
everybody gets sick sometime and
whatever that's the way the world works
right now okay because the world is too
polluted
it's too problematic
there's too many traps there's too much
junk in the way
and it's rigged like that so we die
early that's how the world is rigged
right
the
evil doers
on the planet
want people
gone
that's what they want right
so there's all these ways they do it
there's all these traps set for
everybody so if you hear some dietitian
some nutritionist some functional
medicine doctors some health some health
food advocate somebody whatever some
health coach whatever some nutritionists
whatever it is if you hear them say in
an article or you hear them saying
social media somewhere else the body
cleanses itself you don't need to drink
celery juice medical medium's wrong you
just eat the stick oh you just have
fruits and vegetables and that's the
good thing to do
if they're saying that
they're oblivious to how the world works
they're oblivious to what's really
happening
they're oblivious to any of it they're
ignorant to all of it
they don't know what's happening they
don't know what's being dumped on us
don't know what's in our water they
don't know what's in our food they don't
know anything
and then what's worse they don't know
anything about the human body because
your liver is this filter and it
contains all that junk and it holds on
to it and then it gets sick
and then it gets sick and our body gets
sick so if you guys just came on here
watch this from the beginning this is an
important talk of why you need to
cleanse and i just want to give a
reminder right now
okay
right there
i i'm gonna mention it it's only two
days left in the in in the sale on this
is the mm900 hds i hope you guys get
your juicers ready and if you have any
juicer fine if you got a blender we'll
just blend the celery and strain it if
we have to but this right here
is on sale it's the mm 900 hds food
costs are going up this machine saves
you money it squeezes the juice out of
it i'll show you later anyways i got to
juice celery
and megajuicers.com that's where the
sales at it's the celery juicer the mm
900 hcs there's only a couple days left
so i'm just reminding you guys okay
reminding you because it's coming up
tomorrow starts the medical medium
morning cleanse challenge
that's when it starts do you guys have
your books where the morning cleanse is
on tic tac you guys do you have the
cleanse the heel book you're not gonna
be disappointed you'll be mind blown if
you know anything about health or if you
don't know anything about health your
mind will still be blown
even the most what people feel is the
most advanced people in health when they
read cleanse the heal they get an
awakening and they can't believe how
much they didn't know and this is a book
to have over 200 symptoms conditions
supplements and dosages protocols
cleanses
you got the heavy metal detox cleansing
here
mono cleanses and the morning cleanse
and the 369 cleanses right but
have your book ready get it free at the
library get it free at the library
perfectly fine if you want to do that
you get it amazon.com right 51 off but
have your book ready you guys
i can literally
shut
the world out
disappear
and then surface
with a paid for cleanse
where you got to pay five thousand
dollars
in order to do a cleanse with medical
media
okay
thousands upon thousands of people will
sign up to that cleanse
at five thousand dollars a piece around
the world
right i don't wanna do that i don't like
that
what we're doing here free
free
free it's me my time i hope you guys
want to join in medical medium morning
cleanse challenge it starts tomorrow
it's free
it's so free you can go to the library
and pick up cleanse the heel and not
even buy it if you don't want to if
that's the route you want to go or on
amazon so
why do we need to cleanse good to see
you guys
glad you guys are coming on we're live
on tick tock live and telegram thank you
guys on telegram for being here guys are
awesome
and rumble we got youtube we got
facebook right we're all here live
so
our body builds up toxins
yes
it really does
and we fall apart
as the gears go on our skin
falls apart
okay we get the eczema psoriasis we get
the vitiligo we get dermatitis we get
all kinds of different skin conditions
okay
we get viral
we get the fever blisters the cold sores
the herpes simplex one right we get all
that so we get the fever blisters oh i
got a fever blister right now we got to
do something about that we have to
cleanse out those poisons and toxins and
get the bugs out of the body too so
cleansing is critical right
and then
our liver
that's your filter in the body right
there you guys
so everything you're breathing in you
guys don't breathe in anything you guys
are breathing in pure air
you guys live in a bubble
is that
you know what i mean you know
you don't need to cleanse
you don't have to cleanse ever your body
cleanses itself
it's like okay is someone living in a
bubble
is that that's what everybody's doing on
the planet we're living in a bubble
because
the last i heard or remember
is
crap is spewing out of smokestacks
in all in all the industries around the
world every country around the world
right okay car exhausts is spewing right
all around the world okay
they're dropping mosquito spray on
everybody in every village and town all
around the world the chemical companies
make trillions of gallons of mosquito
spray
when whether there's mosquitoes or not
and they just dump it on everybody they
dump it on houses at night they drop it
out of helicopters all around the
country all around the u.s in every
state while you're sleeping you wake up
in the morning and you breathe in all
that mosquito spray and you have no idea
it all goes in the liver
right there okay
pesticides that are sprayed on crops all
around the world and all the ag land
blows with the wind and you just breathe
it in
and then hey
maybe you ordered some scented candles
that stuff is so toxic it goes into your
liver this stuff is unbelievably toxic
scented candles loaded with an
abomination of chemicals why do we need
to cleanse perfumes colognes you guys
have no idea how toxic perfumes clones
you know perfumes clones are just filled
with basically all pesticides
now i'm not talking about like a partial
pesticide
i'm talking about they use the same
stuff did you know chemicals they drop
on agricultural land like pesticides
insecticides rodenticides fungicides all
that stuff they put on the crops did you
know it smells like cologne and perfume
did you guys know that
all this stuff's important how much how
much like foil do we touch every single
day it absorbs into our hand how many
heavy metals do we have in our system
all of it gasoline fumes you breathe in
in the pump you're breathing in all
those gas fumes you're breathing in
somebody vaping around the corner you're
you're just walking down a city street
wherever you are you're breathing and
people vaping in their cars you got the
car windows cracked and all that
vaping's coming out the window like this
and it's getting sucked into your car
yeah you're breathing in little bits of
it everywhere so basically you're just
this filter bringing in all the toxins
and the poisons every single day it's
coming out of the walls in our houses
it's coming out of the sofas it's coming
out of the bed there's fire retardant
it's on all the beds and
bedding and everything else fungicides
on people's bedding they don't know they
buy it sits in there for 10 years we are
saturated and inundated with toxins on a
level people have no idea and let's wait
i'm not even talking about the sea trail
not even talking about the sea trail
not even talking about how much is
dumped on us on a daily basis but guess
what
you can read an article that comes out
probably every month somewhere whether
it's a slam on medical medium or slam on
something else and that article says you
don't need a cleanse
you know your body takes care of itself
it cleanses itself i mean
i don't know if that's even ignorance i
don't know what that is i don't know if
it's stupidity i don't know if it's just
a newbie that doesn't know anything
i love when there's all these health
professionals i mean i've been in this
for 35 plus years going over 35 years
now and i live when health professionals
are born yesterday they have an
awakening like i'm going to eat fruits
and vegetables and i'm going to eat
organic and then i'm going to get a
little degree somewhere and get my
masters and then i'm gonna get an
interview in somebody's article someday
and i'm gonna act like i've been in this
forever and it's really sad
and what do they do they'll say
something like you don't need to cleanse
it's not what we were taught in our
nutrition school
you know what's really sad
so here's what here's what our options
are on planet earth here's what they are
right if you guys just came on here
before we run into the options on planet
earth these guys just came on here this
is the pre-cleanse
we're getting rigged up we're getting
ready for the medical medium warning
cleanse
do you have the book
if you don't have the bulk go to the
library get it out today get it out for
free okay
maybe you can get it from amazon really
fast too
regardless amazon right the medical
medium morning clench challenge is what
we're doing this is the morning cleanses
inclines the heel
this is the book to have
okay bella princess says i get migraines
from all the perfume
oh yeah
that stuff is brutal you see one i think
is
way back i opened up the i think i was
doing a tick tock video
back last year and i popped open the top
of that baby i mean this thing is
reeking just holding in my hand right
and i popped off the top and i sprayed
it in my face
it was really it was really a stupid
thing to do
and trust me my my crew that was with me
my production crew was with me they were
so upset at me when i did that when i
was doing the tick tock video and i was
like
and
my crew they were angry at me for
probably weeks or more
that just just hung around that smell
hung around you can't get rid of it i
know
so you guys
make sure you have the medical medium
cleanse the heel book amazon.com 51 off
right now okay
which is 16.99 or get it free at the
library because we're doing a free
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
we're starting tomorrow make sure you
have your juicers too if you have a
juicer fantastic if you don't have a
juicer
right
the mm-900 72 dollars off right now
megajuicers.com
check it out right it's the mm-900 hds
it's almost 72 off the sale is going to
end on the 31st
you got a couple more days
but have your juicer ready if you don't
have a juicer and you have a blender use
a blender i don't care what you got
there i don't you know what whatever you
can do if you have a blender and you
want to grind up some celery sticks and
squeeze it out with the cheesecloth the
nut milk bag i'm on board
i don't care if you got the worst juicer
in the world i don't care
let's get it out and let's shove celery
through there let's do this whole
cleanse thing because we're going to
have fun that's the mm-900
just letting everybody know that sale is
going to end pretty soon
right
we got some options on planet earth
we could cleanse
try to control it detox
right
keep the real true balance going
where we're getting more out of us
than what toxic crap is coming in us
more toxic stuff coming out of us
than what's coming in it's like the boat
man it's like the boat you're sitting in
that little boat
and the water's coming in because
there's a hole in that boat and you got
a bucket and that water's coming in
quick and you're scooping the water out
as the water is coming in right that's
what you're doing
okay you gotta scoop the water out
faster than the water coming into the
boat that's going to sink your ass
that's the whole point so you don't get
sunk and go down
and drown
and so what we got to do is when we're
cleansing is we're getting the toxins
out faster than they are coming in
because when you're doing like the
medical meeting morning cleanse
challenge which is so easy to do you
guys it's so easy to do it's insane i'm
going to run by everything about it and
what we got to do but when you're doing
this okay you're getting more out of you
every day
than what's coming into you
so important to know
ns ask me where are you doing the
cleanse here on facebook in a facebook
group
if i took this privately to a facebook
group or something like that an
individual facebook group or anything
like that and i was charging for it and
all these other things that wouldn't be
the right thing to do no we're doing it
here
right here we're doing on a rumble we're
doing it on youtube we're doing it on
tik tok we're doing it on telegram we're
doing it on instagram sign up for my
newsletter so you know what's going on
so it is
sign up to the newsletter so
medicalmedium.com go to
medicalmedium.com when you get a chance
sign up to the medical medium newsletter
so you know what where and how because
it's a free cleanse
and it's about taking control over your
health it's about empowerment
for real real empowerment because you're
being the man
you're beating the man down
right you know like the evil doers that
literally don't really care about your
children and your family and don't care
about anything they don't care if you're
breathing in everything bad under the
sun you're breathing in chemicals none
of that stuff is regulated properly all
the chemicals coming from the
the air fresheners to the hair chemicals
to the body lotion chemicals to the
fragrances to the perfumes to the clones
to the insecticides pesticides
herbicides fungicides they douse
everything on to everything you breathe
in 24 7 out there those are just some of
the toxins we're up against that
saturate the body right this is about
empowerment making sure that they don't
kill you faster
here's the options on planet earth they
can kill you faster
because haven't you guys noticed
everybody just gets sick and dies
you guys haven't noticed that yet
maybe if you're young and you don't know
how it works and you feel indestructible
and you've never been taught that you
don't know anybody that died yet
and you're in that zone where hey your
parents are still alive everything's
good you don't even think everything's
like great and you don't know how the
world works but here's how it works you
get older and everybody around you gets
sick and they die that's how it works on
planet earth i'm only saying this
because it's legit it's what happens now
what goes on is we all get sick
we all get the cancers we all get the
autoimmune it starts to break us down we
all get diseases we all get the gout we
all get the heart problems we all get
the brain problems we all get the brain
tumors we all get all these things
that's how it works on planet earth
maybe you guys know because you're
chronically ill for a long time and you
use medical medium to get you out of
that chronic illness and get your life
back so you use them to pull you out of
that
to get your life back dino good to see
you right there
dino rubio you always leave comments on
youtube
you said we are born chemically polluted
spot on
and here's the thing
the options even got more
insane on planet earth recently
we're heading into a really serious
place where people are going to be
dropping off a lot more and dropping off
a lot more dropping off a lot more if
you don't know how to get that stuff out
of you
that they're tricking you that's going
in you see so that's how it works right
all this stuff going inside of you a
whole bit claudia says talk about how
the lymphatic system is the backup for
the liver thanks good question awesome
everybody's worried about the lymphatic
system right in health and in it's
usually newbies you're not newbie
claudia i know that but there's usually
newbies right they get in health and
they're like i'm getting a lymphatic
massage
i'm like i need i need my lymph my
lymphatic stuff that's what it is i talk
to my nutritionist and they're all about
lymphatic
that's what it is right it's all about
that and i went to my acupuncturist
they're all about my lymphatic and my
functional medicine doctor said you know
my lymphatic system is where the
troubles at
wrong
it's not how it works
your lymphatic system
only becomes a problem because of your
liver has already gotten there first
your liver has already gotten sick first
for the lymphatic system to get sick
later
if you're working on the lymphatic
system but not working on the liver then
you're not working on the root cause of
the root problem that's what's happening
your liver gets stagnant and sluggish
first
and
your lymphatic system is the dump ground
it's like the dumping ground for a liver
that's already pushed over the edge it's
already so polluted it's already sick
and so the lymphatic system if we got
the we got our eyes on the lymphatic
system all the time but we don't have
our eyes on everything else we don't
have our eyes on all the bugs that are
inside our liver we don't have the our
eyes on the epstein bar that's inside
our liver we don't have our eyes on any
of that we don't have our eyes on all
the toxic heavy metals and the
pollutants and the chemicals if we don't
have our eyes on all that you know
aluminum and everything else and mercury
and copper if we don't have our eyes on
everything that's saturating inside your
liver and making it sick and stagnant
and sluggish and instead we're just
doing topical stuff
like oh my lymphatic system that's
that's where the problem is really okay
oh i took this lymphatic system tonic
here to help me that somebody
recommended it's like oh my god you're
so far off and guess what 20 30 years
from now you're gonna be so sick
and so lost
and like i said on here on planet earth
that's how it rolls everybody has a
symptom i don't know if you guys know
this yet kids included all have symptoms
all have problems it's only getting
worse out there because the world's
getting more polluted and more shady
than ever in all kind of sinister ways
and if we don't do something about it
and empower ourselves and stay strong
then how are we going to battle it and
how we're going to recover and heal
how are we going to do it
so if you hear right
do you hear you don't need to cleanse
somebody that just doesn't understand
health
now i know that there's some bad
cleanses throughout the years that have
given people about the given people a
bad ride and have given
cleansing a bad name
i've never supported any of those
cleanses ever
i've never supported just shoving water
and cayenne pepper and oil in a drink
and then sent it down all day and all
night i've never never supported any
ridiculous
problematic cleanse that was ever
offered out there the medical medium
information's different it's about the
chronically ill and recovering it's
about recovering sensitive people you
guys it's about
people who are sensitive because they've
been injured with their health along the
way they've been chronically sick for
many many years the cleansing that we're
talking about is an entirely different
ballpark and it gets people better and
it's so important jennifer said i've
been doing the morning cleanse and or
doing mono cleanses awesomes right from
this book here and pretty much cured my
fibromyalgia in six months
incredible i'm amazed anthony you've
definitely got the right information and
fibromyalgia if you read and cleanse the
heal and jennifer you probably know this
right is the epstein bar so that's
that's the epstein bar causing that
nerve inflammation causing all that
fibromyalgia and what you did was you
did these cleanses you did the mono
cleanse and you starved out the epstein
bar so what you did is you starved out
and killed off the epstein-barr that's
amazing and
that's actually really incredible i'm
really proud of you seriously
i got my little viruses here too
kelly z said i healed my interstitial
cystitis and so many other conditions
with medical medium information i don't
know where i'd be if i hadn't found him
i'm so thankful love you with all my
heart mm and spirit
that's on youtube right there kelly
you're on youtube i'm honored to hear
truly thank you for being here
and i'm proud of you seriously am so i'm
excited you guys look this is the pre
talk right this is the plan we're going
to do some stuff we'll run some celery
and we'll talk about some squash too
maybe i'll crack one open right here
which is fun i know this isn't the
amazon live cooking show but we'll still
crack some stuff open and have some fun
but we're just doing the pre-talk
because this is important we're going
we're going to where we need to go which
is getting into that morning cleanse
challenge tomorrow right katie says i've
been doing the morning cleanse and heavy
metal detox yeah
smoothie for almost three years i healed
from hashimoto's you destroyed your
epstein-barr that causes hashimoto's
thyroiditis which is
medical meme information now that
science is trying to steal all the mm
info about epstein-barr from me years
later that's on facebook katie fantastic
but you killed off your epstein bar you
knocked it back you restored your
thyroid mm info i'm really really proud
of you i can't even tell you're
so proud of you
big time big time
you guys i'm a little more pumped up
today if you notice
um
one reason is because we're going into a
cleanse tomorrow okay we're going to do
a cleanse i've been excited about this
because i've been wanting to get to this
point with everything to get you know to
get to where we need to and i think
right now it's winter in a lot of places
right we're in the united states it's
winter
in the us right now okay
you know on the other side of the world
it's not winter but it's winter right
now in the u.s and
um
and also in other places too around the
world too it's winter so it's kind of a
great place to get some of these toxins
and poison so they don't incubate
they don't incubate
and that's what happens when we go into
this like kind of like hibernation we
end up not eating so good either and we
end up really compacting the poisons and
toxins into our
liver we end up compacting it into our
cells right and those toxins and poisons
get they just get stuck in there is what
they do they get stuck in the cells of
the organs that's what happens right
there and so
cleansing
right
gets those poisons out so we're not
stagnant
so if you're looking at that snow
blowing if you're looking at that wind
of blowing outside and you're inside and
you're trying to stay warm at least you
know you're cleaning out all the junk
and all the garbage outside of you like
you're getting it out of you right the
inside stuff you're getting it out of
you so it's so important okay
so i'm excited let's talk about the
pre-cleanse
information
you will not be eating
avocados
tomorrow morning
on the medical media morning cleanse
challenge
so you won't be eating avocados tomorrow
morning okay
i know you guys love your avocado i love
avocado too who doesn't love avocado
right
i never said avocado was bad for you
either i actually have this incredible
avocado recipe that i love
guacamole medical medium guacamole the
point is is that we're not gonna be
having avocados we're not okay we have
to let them go they can't be we can't
have avocado toast
till noon or after
you have to save your avocado toast if
that's what you're gonna have till noon
and after
okay very important to know right so
that's
that's important lorraine l good to see
you lorraine i do a lot of soups in the
cold weather winter here in the uk
winter in the uk
it's cold out there
i agree you guys won't be doing any
cashews in the morning or nut butters
you guys aren't gonna be doing any
tahini
right got some tahini here not gonna do
any almond butter got some almond butter
right here right
i know you guys throw peanut butter
in your smoothies and on your acai bowls
and on everything else you eat nope not
gonna be doing that
not gonna be doing your chocolate that's
cacao powder right there that stuff is
just basically a drug i don't i this
isn't here because i use it
i don't use it
it's a friends
yeah sure right you know it's a friends
it's not mine you guys i don't use cacao
powder
it's it's for a friend
actually it's a prop
that's that is cacao powder but it's a
prop and i don't i don't do cacao powder
i just don't want to destroy my brain
so another thing you don't do is you
don't do coconut oil
that's different than cacao powder you
know cacao powder is another story but
you don't want to do any fats tomorrow
morning during the medical medium
morning cleanse challenge you don't want
to do oils you don't want to do coconut
oil i know so many of you guys do
coconut oil in the morning don't do that
don't throw cashews in a smoothie don't
throw nut butter peanut butter and
smoothies don't have any nuts before
noon don't throw any tahini in there
before noon keep the fats away really
important right there
no almonds make sure you're not doing
any almonds or anything like that so
you got to keep the fats out now i know
some of you guys don't know about
like
you don't know about medical medium
information
but it's not that almonds or
tahini or
avocado
is not a healthy fat i'm not saying that
they're better than grease and lard
they're better than fried grease lard
oil chicken fat
they're better than fried chicken skin
they're better than you know
hydrogenated oils they're better than
all that
it's just that you won't be able to
cleanse if you're doing all the fats you
won't be there's fat and cacao there
won't be any cleansing if you put cacao
powder in your smoothie in the morning
and never cleanse
you'll never cleanse if you put almond
butter in your smoothie in the morning
you never cleansed you guys just came on
here get ready for the medical meeting
morning cleanse challenge starts
tomorrow make sure you have a cleanse
the heel book make sure you have your
juicer the juicer is on sale right now
megajuicers.com 72 off it's incredible
it's a celery juicer it saves you money
food costs going up
that one saves money i'll show you later
anyway how that works get ready for the
cleanse challenge you're not going to be
doing fats no eggs in the morning that's
another thing you won't do
so we're not gonna do any eggs we're not
gonna do any butter so we're not gonna
have some eggs right
okay for those babies
you're not gonna have eggs
not tomorrow morning
by the way eggs aren't a healthy fat
they are not a healthy fat
almond butter's a healthy fat
right
cacao is not a healthy fat because it
destroys your adrenals and it ages you
quick and then boom you get aged much
quicker than you should because the
stuff just destroys your adrenals but
that's another story don't get mad about
the cacao if you guys like chocolate
fine i'm you can have chocolate if
that's what you like whatever what i'm
just saying
this is not a healthy fat eggs aren't a
healthy fat but almond butter is a
healthy fat tahini is a healthy fat
right almonds cashews are a healthy fat
coconut oil is a healthy fat olive oil
is a healthy fat right
so hemp seeds are a healthy fat pumpkin
seeds are a healthy fat even sunflower
seeds are a healthy fat because i know
people are like no
he doesn't know anything all the vegan
doctors say too much the omega-6s in the
sunflower oil
sunflower seeds are a healthy fat
compared to pork fat
egg fat
right bacon fat which is pork fat
compared to a lot of bad fats right
because of so many reads anyway
that's really important to know so
you guys won't be doing pork in the
morning
no bacon
no ham
the medical medium cleanse
you're not going to be doing pork
bacon
ham
in the am
now i prefer
you don't
i prefer you don't have any lamb
in the morning too not that you guys are
having lamb in the morning but don't
have any lamb
in the morning that's a sheep
well you know what
don't have any lamb
don't have any pork
don't have any pigs
in the morning
so that's important to know so keep that
out of the diet
this is really an important cleanse
so i'm going to put
a guy there i'm going to put this guy
here right
don't have any dairy products
don't have any moo
that's a bad move right
well the cleanse challenge goes for two
days we're starting it tomorrow
we're going to do it tomorrow we're
going to do it the next day that's what
we're doing i'm really pumped up about
this okay
yeah marissa spiritual yeah asking for a
friend
hey listen you guys no dairy products no
cheese no milk no butter
keep that in mind please right no cheese
no milk no butter i can say this all i
want i guarantee you there's going to be
a boatload of people having some cheese
and some eggs tomorrow morning an egg
and cheese sandwich i can sit here and
scream
from the mountain tops and be like no
and you guys some of you guys will still
have some bacon and eggs tomorrow
morning right
let's talk about a couple more things
guys this is the free
cleanse
make sure you have your book amazon.com
us
51 off
we're doing the medical media morning
cleanse out of this book right here so
please have it ready go to the library
get it for free too if you really want
to do that perfectly fine
have it ready do you own a juicer if you
don't own a juicer i need you there at
the cleanse anyway because i want you to
get healthy so use your blender if you
don't own a juicer use your blender this
is the mm 900 hds you guys know i
endorse this model
this is the one that saves people money
everybody's saying how much money it's
saving they're using less celery it's
real it's true
it's an incredible juicer juicer sales
on for a couple more days
i'm just trying to get you prepared do
you have your celery
if you guys are prepared you're not
going to be able to do it tomorrow with
me maybe you can do it another day on
your own get the book and do it on your
own like next week
do it in a few days
have your celery ready
have the celery ready do you guys have
your lemons ready okay
do you have your lemons ready right here
we're doing the lemon water have your
lemons ready
do something good for your body
because this
morning cleanse challenge is that
opportunity
to do something good for your body it's
an opportunity is what it is
right
and i want to help
i want you to have a better life
is what i want
i want to help so let's go
let's go into it a little bit
i'm just going gonna move this perfume
here okay
and
i'm gonna spray perfume in my
in my drink
no i'm not all right let's go you guys
let's talk about this
[Music]
we're just a snapshot in time
take note of this one
okay
you see someone
they look healthy
they're young
but it's a snapshot in time
do you ever see those old photos of like
people in black and white
in the 1930s they all look like they're
all standing together and they all look
miserable and it's kind of spooky and
it's just a bunch of people like
like you know it's a husband and a wife
a couple of kids and aunt and uncle
couple nephews whatever and they're all
grouped together and it's 1932 or it's
1928 or it's 1919
and you see that photo
it's a snapshot in time
but what you don't see is what happened
to them all along the way
you don't see
what tumor grew in one of them
okay would chronic illness are
neurological disorder overcame one of
them you don't see what stroke happened
in them
as the years went by you don't see the
struggle and the suffering
okay as
they battled whatever it was that came
their way
or a snapshot in time when a dietitian
functional medicine doctor nutritionist
or anybody else sits there and says you
don't need to cleanse and they're
sitting there they're just a snapshot in
time because what's going to happen is
10 years from now i'd like to see that
dietitian that nutritionist that whoever
it is that functional medicine doctor i
want to see what happened along their
journey did they get fibro really bad
did they get hoshis did they get eczema
did they have a stroke did they have a
heart attack did they get cancer did
they get als did they get multiple
sclerosis what happened to them i want
to know because guess what as the years
go by it happens and people all get sick
and it's a snapshot in time
it's what it is
charlenski says for the lemon water do
you just cut lemons and put it in the
water you could do that
that's okay
i'll show you how i do it too but you
can definitely do that so i'm going to
take this cup right here
and i'll give you a quick run down this
is just so you're ready for tomorrow so
i'm going to cut this lemon in half and
the details are in the cleanse the heel
book so you're going to want i want to
get the cleanse the heel book one way of
doing it is just squeezing that half
right in here like that
and adding water that's one way to do it
take a half squeeze it in and add water
you want 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water
on an empty stomach first thing in the
morning because you want to flush
you want to flush
that liver
you flush the liver and the lymphatic
system starts to clean up
you want to go after the lymphatic
system with different things then you're
going to miss out on the liver you want
to get the liver that's where it's at
right
so you want to flush that liver in the
morning so that's the lemon water right
there
so that's so i just want you prepared i
want you ready for this
someone says you don't need to cleanse
they're a snapshot in time you don't
know what's going to happen to them 10
years from now you don't know what's
going to happen to them 20 years from
now
and guess what they won't be held
accountable for what they said 10 years
or 20 years before and deterred a bunch
of people into healing
so
they won't be held accountable doesn't
matter if they stroke out 15 years from
now does it matter if they take a
medical treatment that finishes their
life it doesn't matter if something else
happens to them doesn't matter if
whatever that does it
they won't be held accountable for what
they said 15 years before when they told
5000 people or 100 000 people you don't
need a cleanse
michaela says my teeth became sensitive
to lemons and acid fruit in them
in the month why can be
so it's not the lemons it's not the acid
fruit those are just letting you know
something else is happening so so that's
what that is
so lemons and things like that that make
you feel sensitive one thing is is it
cold anything cold another thing too is
nothing else makes you sensitive be your
own detective so kind of like chart
everything like what else kind of sets
you off a little bit too right but what
that means is it's not the lemon that
causes the problem it's the lemon
showcasing that you already have a
sensitive nerve developing from
something else from some other situation
and so sensitive nerves trigeminal
nerves facial nerves all these nerves
that are actually all intertwined to our
mouth or draw everything right cranial
nerves that go through our mouth and jaw
something's already happening there
and lemon water is helpful for that
situation even though it's setting off
an alarm bell so that's how that works
did you if you want to know
what's going on with your health i mean
just take a look at the book learn about
all these things that causes all the
problems right and that's important to
know sandra says lemon tastes like eggs
to me
i hope you like the taste of eggs
because lemon's so good for you
tomorrow morning
we're going to be doing lemon water
we're going to be doing the celery juice
okay
we're going to talk about what foods you
can eat
right
i'm going to juice some celery right now
so i'm going to do that
and
you're going to do the celery juice
16 to 32 ounces try to get 32 ounces in
if you can if you can't get 32 ounces in
you can't get 32 ounces in
try to get 16 ounces in if you can't get
32 ounces in so that's important to know
if you guys just came on here this is
the mm-900 hds it's on sale right now
for two more days
it's not just the juicer
the reason why i endorse this model is
because it saves you money
and it doesn't have the metal gears
grinding against each other
so you get metal particles with all the
other juicers
so that's important
the pulp comes out dry
it comes out drier than other machines
so you save that much more money when
you're buying your celery
okay
that's important to know right there
if you have a chronic condition
this is one of the powerful tools to
reversing it over time
juicing celery is one of the powerful
tools this is a medical device
hold on guys
i just shut everything down for a second
you guys want to be on these medical
devices
blood work all the time because you're
sick
right
all kinds of medical tools and devices
you got to be on i got a pacemaker over
here let me look i think i might have a
pacemaker over here you guys want to be
on these medical devices see what else
they got
got
see what else i have here
because this is a medical device right
here
this is a medical device right here
herbal extractor right hold on
because
i don't want to be on
all these medical devices and medical
things i don't want to be on these i
don't want to be on this i don't want to
be hooked up to things and hooked up to
monitors and hooked up to stuff i
thought i had a pacemaker in here
i don't want to be hooked up to all this
stuff
right
i don't want to be getting my urine
samples checked every minute i don't
want to be getting my blood drawn every
five seconds i don't want any of that
personally
you know and
i don't know about you guys but i don't
want that stuff you know
it's just it
i i don't want to be in the hospital
down the road
i don't want to be having to go to my
doctor every 10 minutes and making
doctor appointments
i don't want any of that you know what i
mean so what i when i here's what i do
so what i use is i do different medical
devices
it's what i do so i do different medical
that's what i do right
this is the medical device right here
that i do you're looking at it right
here so let's go back to juicing
this is the medical device
it's an herbal extractor herbal medicine
machine
it's a medicine maker
right you're looking at an herb
if
i hear one more time
that celery's a vegetable
then i'm i might lose hope and humanity
and i might believe that our health
professionals
and nutritionists and dietitians
and medical doctors
are missing a lot of brain cells
if i hear that this is a vegetable one
more time
this is an herb
and this is herbal medicine
and that's why it moves the needles
that's why it's one of the reasons why
it moves the needle because it's herbal
medicine it's one reason right there
it's what's in this herbal medicine
tara appleman good to see you i know
right
it's incredible really and
you guys this is the mmm 900 hds
it's on sale it's 20 off you'll see it
at the checkout
right almost 72
off
this is the last couple of days for this
sale for this machine
i hope you have a juicer or some way to
get your celery juice going for tomorrow
we're doing the medical medium morning
friends now listen if you don't have a
juicer if you can't do celery juice that
you want to be there
for free at the medical media morning
cleanse challenge so you can learn how
to do it so you can do it another day
then be there tomorrow it's a two-day
challenge okay this is a mega this is an
omega juicer model it's the mm 900
hps link is in the description
okay
link is in profile tik tok link is in
the description
you guys
on facebook youtube right link is in
description
people are asking me all the time what
juicer is the best this one's the best
because it's squeezing out all the juice
and it's saving you money and right now
food costs going up
because the world is definitely a dark
place so they're gonna make sure they
jack up the food costs and the food
costs are going to go up people have a
hard time getting healthy
they're going to try to buy cheaper food
that makes them unhealthy
that's just how the system is rigged
it's rigged like that purposely
and so
that means you need to kind of supersede
that so what i like about this juicer is
it helps me supersede that because it's
battling that saving you money and
that's what i love right
so yeah
so
celery juice is
a critical part of cleansing
tomorrow morning
medical medium cleanse challenge starts
we're going to do lemon water we're
going to do our celery juice right here
now listen if you if you can only do
that that's fine
if you're somebody that's so toxic where
celery just goes into you and it starts
to kill all the pathogens starts to kill
the bacteria in your gut it starts to
kill everything in you and you have
diarrhea then go slow then do two ounces
of celery juice tomorrow right
let's use two ounces of celery juice
tomorrow
here's what's going to happen during
your medical meeting morning cleanse
right here's what's going to happen
you're going to start restoring the hcl
in your stomach
you guys see that on tick-tock you're
going to start restoring the hcl in your
stomach
you're going to start cleaning
your intestinal tract environment
poisons toxins ransom fats rancid
proteins petrified proteins
you're going to start killing off little
bugs that shouldn't be
in your gut the bad bugs that shouldn't
be in your gut you're going to start
this is what's going to happen during
your medical medium morning cleanse
challenge you're going to start killing
off
little bad bugs
all in your intestinal tract right
so that's just some of the things that
are that are going to happen make sure
you have the cleanse to heal book it's
critical
make sure you have the cleanse of your
book really important
critical piece of it right there
so we're juicing some celery right now
what i'm doing is i'm trying to get 32
ounces
that's what i like to do in the morning
is 32 ounces
starbucks 22 says can angels help
dissolve
the sea trails
that'll be a talk for another day
that's a good question
question i'm gonna ask
spirit of compassion
so i like to do that i like to ask
questions
the passion lots of questions
that
are mind-blowing like answers and
questions it's incredible all right so
we're just we're just coming up to like
what i love about this juicer you guys
it's quiet you don't wake up the
household
i can talk to you guys why it's while
it's on it's a cold pressed juicer
doesn't have the metal gear so you're
not getting metal particles over time
and you're in your juice which is
incredible right
so what you'll notice here
is that is the pulp right there
juicers on sale for two more days i'm
just letting you know almost 72 dollars
off of megajuicers.com you have to get
the mm 900 hds or you're not going to
have this juicer
it's that specific model right and what
you're looking at right here is pulp in
my fingertips
and it's dry it's just slightly damp
right
in here
there you go
and it dries out quick too because it's
just damp so what happens it just dries
up and it starts to fall apart quick
that's where you're saving your money
with the mm-900 hds right there
that's where you're saving it so when
you run green i like to run greens
through what i do is i take
i take greens and i run that through
sometimes too
right
but there you go
that's the pulp it's dry that's the
mm-900 so let's strain the cylinder
juice you always want to strain it keep
that in mind that's important
because it's herbal medicine you're
doing an extraction you don't want
anything in there
but the extraction itself so that's
important to know right there so i'm
going to move this over
so let's get some celery juice going
i got a friend saves all his cardboard
boxes
right
because at home why don't you recycle
them that's what i said i said why don't
you recycle your cardboard boxes
and my friend said
no i save every last one of them okay
so i save every last one of those
cardboard boxes
and go why
you never know when you're gonna need
one
right
you never know
because i like to save things
it's kind of like you aw you like to
save lives
because i like to save cardboard boxes
you like to save lives that's what you
do you know and
so what i think about that when i even
think about what he said
it blows me away because it's not just
about wanting to save lives and
obviously that's why we're in this
i mean right that's why we're in it but
it's about saving organs
it's about
saving
time with loved ones too you know so
when you stick around longer on this
planet because you cleanse and you
restore and you bank minerals
back into your organs and you bring
yourself back
you get more precious moments
with maybe someone you meet that you
would have never met because you lived
long enough to meet them or precious
moments with family members you actually
get those precious moments saved because
guess what you get more of them and you
get more memories because your brain
comes back and you get rid of all that
alzheimer's that's starting up from your
celery juice and you're cleansing and
you're getting the poisons and toxins
out right and so what happens is you get
these precious moments
and that's what you end up
getting in the end is all those extra
precious critical moments that your soul
holds on to you so when you do die and
leave this place your soul leaves and it
leaves with all of these precious
moments more precious moments and
memories are in that soul of yours as
it's floating out and leaving and
propelling out of the solar system
more time here on earth and more
precious moments and if you're going
through a struggle and a hardship right
now what you're doing is you're working
on healing yourself so that you stay
here longer and so you can then meet
somebody and because that's what happens
our life changes all the time we end up
seeing we meet new people in our life
the journey changes to a whole different
place and what happens is we've been
able to kind of be a part of that
transition making that happen by taking
care of ourselves by cleansing and
everything else
staying here longer because of it
and that's what matters right there so
you guys just giving you a rundown real
recap real quick right
we're doing the medical media morning
cleanse challenge tomorrow make sure you
have a book so you understand the
details right there so you understand
the details
link is in the profile link is in the
description
make sure you have a juicer if you don't
have a juicer this one's on sale for a
couple more days and this is the one
that i use and there's a reason why
because it saves money blah blah blah i
told you but if you have a blender and
it's all you have get your blender out
and get ready because you're gonna check
out medicalmedium.com sign up to the
newsletter too and you can also look and
you can see ways we do things like using
a blender grinding up celery and then
using a cheesecloth if that's all you
have but be there on that cleanse last
but not least
if you don't even want to cleanse and
you don't want to do the morning clench
challenge with me be there anyway
why not learn about it so you can do it
next week or next month or next year
and why not
i'm going to instagram
i'm putting tick tock back on i'm
putting telegram back on
and we're getting ready
for the medical medium cleanse challenge
that's what this is this is like the pre
challenge we're doing it man get your
lemons ready
get your celery ready
right and guess what
i got some oatmeal here i got some
millet here
right
i'm going to talk about that on ig in a
couple of minutes in a little bit we're
going to go to ig i'm going to talk
about oatmeal i'm going to talk about
millet i'm going to talk about how you
can do that into the medical medium
morning cleanse i'm going to talk about
winter squash i might crack one open
we're going to do some different stuff
coming right up so you guys come on with
me to
ig and i'm turning tick tock back on so
you guys hang in there and i'm turning
telegram back on i love you guys greatly
i'll