announcement making an announcement did
you get the email you guys okay
September 7th I'm going to be in person
at
airan yep believe it or
not okay September 7th I'm going to be
in person at airan calabases right so
California Calabasas Los Angeles
California area so just letting you know
I'm going to be there in person for a
meet and greet exactly so to meet and
greet now it's not going to
be a huge event in the park like the
last one was and I want to make that
clear it's not going to be a huge event
in the park right there's not going to
be the park at all this is going to be
I'm going to be at the Calabasas airan
that store there September 7th 7 in the
morning I'm going to be there at 700 in
the morning and I'm going to be there
for a meet and greet a lot of people
didn't get a chance actually to get to
the other one down Culver City back uh
June 15th a lot of people missed that
opportunity I wanted to make sure we had
another opportunity but let me talk
about why I'm going to be there like
this is incredible so the heavy metal
detox smoothie did so phenomenal it did
so amazing at
aan that they created a custom bottle
limited edition collector's custom
bottle medical medium bottle that's
going to be made fresh every day and put
in the refrigerator section so people
can grab and go so I'm like really
excited about this this is incredible
news a lot of people they want to go
right in there and they want to just
grab it and go it's made fresh every day
but it's going to be a collector's
bottle a customized bottle they're doing
because it was such a phenomenal success
in so many ways it was so incredible
that whole day was incredible by the way
you guys know that it was just amazing
so what I'm to do to celebrate this is
I'm going to be there for a meet and
greet so if you guys want to be there
that would be incredible once the custom
medical medium bottle sells out it'll
still be in the refrigerator section as
the heavy metal detox smoothie in a
glass bottle made fresh every single day
at airwan in the refrigerator there but
there's going to be a limited customized
bottle which is really cool that is
going to be why I'm there I'm also there
for anybody who maybe missed out on the
last chance to see me so I'm excited
about this I just I mean I'm actually
I'm beaming about this I'm trying to
contain myself I'm trying to contain
myself so I wanted to make this
announcement today did you get the email
so you have the details and stuff like
that and it's good to register it's good
to register and sign up so make sure you
go to medicalmedium.com and you actually
register and sign up so we just know
who's kind of coming in the whole bid
are you bringing people are you bringing
your family are you bringing your
friends so it's September 7th
that's when it is it's going to be 7:00
in the morning it starts I'm going to be
there real early and I'm going to be in
the store the calabasa store at aan and
I'm going to be there for meet and greet
so I'm excited about that so if you guys
come by I'd love to meet you this is
different than the um different than the
big book signing event at arowana the
whole thing it's different this is going
to be a meet and greet so that's going
to be exciting so I'm really pumped up
about that okay would love to say hi to
you in the whole bit so that's coming
September 7th and it's coming up pretty
soon but as I said before this is an
exciting Moment In Time the heavy metal
detox smoothie did so great there that
they're actually putting it in a
customized bottle made fresh every day
in refrigerator section it's in all of
their stores it's incredible so I'm
really pumped up totally pumped up about
this so I wanted to let everybody know
I'm also making the heavy metal detox
smoothie right here right now so I got
my blender and everything so I'm going
to make that cuz I am hungry I'm excited
about having some right now so you know
you can make it at home too of course I
got all my stuff here to make it good to
see you guys we're a lot of you guys
because last time we talked about a lot
of you guys were at the last one June
15th it was an unbelievable moment in
time and and aan was so blown away by
the amount of people that came and how
everybody was it was incredible this
will not be streamed live I'm just
letting everybody know so September 7th
coming up will not be streamed live I
want people to know that I know we
streamed the June
15th event live is what we did and you
can see that on YouTube you can see the
June 15th um event on YouTube if you
want to go and see but this isn't going
to be streamed live but I'm going to be
in the calabases store September 7th um
for a meet and greet
so I'm hoping you guys come if you get a
chance that would be incredible I'm
going to be there at 700 in the morning
when the store opens just letting you
know and so I'm going to be standing
right
there and love to meet you guys
seriously so I'm excited about that so
anyway and just the Smoothie did so
phenomenal the heavy metal detox did so
amazing that they're like we're putting
this in the store in the refrigerator
section in a custom I you know glass
bottle we're putting it on the Shelf
made fresh every day just like it was at
the event June 15th remember when you
came in if you were there if you guys
were there you came in and it was they
were on the Shelf like that in
refrigerator section all bottled up made
fresh right that night that was crazy
how amazing that was and just go in
there and it's great for grab and go so
you don't just you know if you're
somebody that's in a rush and you go
into any of the aan stores you can just
grab grab it and boom Cash Out grab and
go and that's that's a great way of
doing it too so this is going to be so
exciting so exciting if look if you
can't get out here because you're on the
East Coast or something or somewhere
else I understand um but hey if you're
around or you manage to get out there
would love to meet you could could be at
the Calabasas store at aan so I'm
excited September 7th 700 in the morning
I'll be there and check out the details
there's any information you need to know
did you get the email we sent it out
earlier so really exciting so you guys
and I'm making the heavy metal detox
cloie right now isn't that incredible so
you guys were at the last one so I saw a
couple people saying they were at the
last one and this is different this
isn't like the event in the park I want
everybody to know there isn't going to
be like other speakers there so that's
not going to be happening it's just
going to be little all me in the store
to meet you okay the link to register in
the IG profile check it out or in the
description of this video check that out
too um if you're watching the video that
way or this way or whatever way so
you'll see the link there about it to
register and everything else you go to
Medical medium.com as well you can do
that as well too so you guys I'm going
to make a heavy metal detox smoothie
right now I got a bunch of stuff in
front of me I got this fresh cilantro
people don't get enough cilantro in them
they just don't they just don't get
enough cilantro in them fact fact a lot
of people just get a little bit of
cilantro in them here and there
different ways maybe it's on top of a
salad if you're lucky maybe you had a
guacamole and it had a a few sprigs of
leaves of cilantro in the guacamole and
that's how you had it a lot of people
don't eat a lot of cilantro but that is
a leafy herb green and in medical medium
information going all the way back that
is powerful that alone is a healing tool
people do not understand can't be
measured people don't get it really out
there in the health movement they don't
know what that is right there cilantro
oh okay cilantro it's got its health
benefits or whatever it's got you know
or whatever people talk about but the
difference is right there when you use
it like in the hmds and you use like a
cup of it the something else happens the
nutrient profile the phytochemical
compounds all of it that's involved in
cilantro alone is powerful so when you
actually have it as a leafy green herb
boom that is powerful right there for
your health leafy green herb and it's
powerful okay and so that's the cilantro
that's going to go in here too then you
got the Wyman's wild blueberries right
you guys know I work with Wyman's that's
an incredible wild blueberry it's a
trusted Source it's my favorite of all
in the wild blueberry world so there it
is right there got the Frozen wild
blueberries that's in there I happen to
have a mango here I don't have any
bananas on hand but a lot of people they
don't use bananas in their hmds they'll
use something like some papaya I talked
about Alternatives in the medical medium
books they'll use some papaya they'll
use some mango they'll do that and
they'll put mango in there which is fine
and that's what I have right here I have
mango because remember the five
ingredients are the key the cilantro the
barleygrass juice powder barleygrass
juice powder right the wild blueberries
that's the other one right there the
sparina that's the other one and the DOL
so that's the key so whether you put it
into like a smoothie bowl like a lot of
people in the medical meme Community
have done you know and I've talked about
in the books unless you put it in like a
smoothie bowl or you make a smoothie out
of it or you eat them throughout the day
you're having your do like I got a
friend that takes the the vimer do
liquid and they take the vimer Dos
liquid they take it like that it's like
a supplement they take it it's not even
in their smoothie and then they're
having cilantro and something else
you're eating they'll have a whole bunch
of cilantro then they'll do like
spirulina and they'll mix it with
coconut water and then they'll do this
throughout the day but they'll get their
five key ingredients key ingredients
that are critical that's the whole point
with the hmds
and so however you dress it up like you
put banana in here you put you know
something else mango you have mango you
have it a smoothie bowl or you spread it
out through the day it's the five
ingredients that's the medical medium
heavy metal detox that's listed out in
the medical medium first book right here
that's what that is so it's important to
know this stuff I don't talk about it
enough I should I mean heck it's an
incredible
credible tool that's gone around the
planet has changed lives around the
planets helped helped move people
forward you guys know this I should be
shouting the crap out of the heavy metal
detox every day I mean you see people
out there it's like you'll see somebody
in the health movement or somebody in
their like a health professional and
they get one person better out of like
500 people and they get them just better
a little bit better and they're
screaming screaming I got someone
feeling better they're screaming the
hmds around the world has literally
gotten people in in moved forward in
their healing process in such
unbelievable Ways by the thousands and
hundreds and hundreds of thousands of
people it's that incredible and
meanwhile I go kind of like blank and I
go kind of quiet about it like you know
I just you I'm doing things and whatever
and meanwhile I should be screaming the
heck out of it because of what it's done
and what it does for people yeah yeah
exactly it's the best smoothie ever it's
the best heavy metal detox right
approach ever so incredible let's see so
whoa I literally have two or three heavy
metal detoxes a day sometimes double
doses that's amazing so anyway right
here I'm making this hmds now so I got
the mangoes right here so let's just you
know we'll talk and stuff let's see if
these mangoes are looking good I've had
these in the fridge for a while shame on
me shame on me to have them in the
fridge for a while okay things got busy
they were kind of on the side of the
fridge there I kind of didn't catch them
for a while they were there they should
have been already eaten should already
ate them so here we go I'm going to pop
some mango in here this is great you
guys can see this okay it's beautiful
mangoes too beautiful so I'm going with
mango instead of banana I don't have any
bananas on hand and that's okay cuz this
is uh an incredible alternative to make
the Smoothie really really good so I'm
going to put the pretty much most of
this mango in here if you're okay with
that are you signing books I was at the
launch but line got cut off look if you
bring a book okay yeah you put it in
front of me I'll sign it but but I'm
only going to sign one one book one book
I can't sign um I can't sign six seven
books and I was doing that a lot of
people were putting six books somebody
put nine
books in front of me nine books they
even put a story seat in front of me so
I just want to talk about that they put
an aan story seat in front of me for me
to sign so it was like for this it was
for the heavy metal detox smoothie right
and so I signed nine books right
this one person and signed a story
receipt and then signed their their um
their shirt that they were
wearing so I did that
too
anyway and guess what I'm honored to do
so more than honored to do so mango
juice going everywhere just going to cut
some of this mango back I'll I'll I'll
actually suck on this pit
later so anybody who's a mango fan
fishot the whole bit I'm not tossing
this mango bit in the trash even though
I'm doing this demo right now it's a
little demonstration but what I'm going
to do is just I'm just going to cut some
of this in here there we go amazing and
I'm going to keep that mango around cuz
that one I am definitely going to be
using thousands upon
thousands of signatures I did at that
event you guys
thousands now there were well over
10,000 people there I think from what we
from what a couple of people that were
working for us there that were that were
working on everything and and and doing
a account and everything there were
we're getting an official count pretty
soon I think it was over 20,000 people
so I'm just letting you guys know from
what the official count looks like it's
turning into it was over 20,000 people
at that event um just just letting you
guys know I signed as many books as I
could um and I think um but at at here
at this meet and greet I mean if you
bring a book and you throw it in front
of me I'm going to try to sign it people
had
also people um a lot of people saw the
lines and they left was another thing
too the lines went around the city
Culver City entire fire department was
was out there entire police Police
Department was out there they've never
seen anything like that in Culver City
it was the biggest event that Culver has
ever seen so it was it was unbelievable
I mean there were
helicopters it was it was just it was
just nuts and everybody was so amazing
everybody in the medical me Community
were literally Saints I mean they were
just so incredible the best community
the best people the best crowd I mean it
all of it was just unbelievable boots
McGee says
I wimped out on I you wimped out on
cilantro and when I started using a full
Bunch within a few months my driving
anxiety went away who driving anxiety
that's a tough one for a lot of people
driving anxiety W that's
incredible all right so we got some
mango in here I'm happy about that I am
let's pop in some other stuff in here
let's put in some blueberries let me get
a nice spoon right
here and let me put two cups roughly two
cups of wild blueberries in here if you
guys don't mind I'm excited about
this there we
go I'll put some more in here um yeah
and I'm I'm hungry right
now so that's going to work really good
okay let's put a little cilantro in here
next about a cup okay
and I'm going to put a little bit more
cuz I
do I usually do I'm going to put a
little bit more like I said this is a
leafy green
herb this isn't just plain lettuce or
iceberg lettuce or just plain Roma
lettuce this is a leafy green herb
powerful live healthy Vita says I didn't
even notice it was so crowded because of
how Cal calm and peaceful the large
crowd was laugh out loud the best
community everybody was so cool
everybody was so calm everybody was just
in in such such a positive positive
energy positive light it was just the
vibration everything was just incredible
really really most amazing people on the
planet I'm sorry to say am I just bias
or something the most amazing people in
the plan is medical meme community
Chrissy said I was in Culver City but
joined the line too late to get my book
signed wish I could go to the next event
but we'll have to skip out oh my
god
oh yeah I mean it was like I said I
think the official count is is is over
20,000 I don't think that's going to
happen look I don't think that's going
to happen here this is not this
September 7th is not an event I'm going
to do a meet and greet I'm going to be
there you throw a book and St front of
me I'm going to sign it I'm going to you
know definitely meet you right that's
what's going to happen there um but I
don't think it's going to be anything
like we're looking like 15 20,000 people
or more Amanda doesn't surprise me I
went to a concert at a stadium that
holds 25k and I looked and I thought
that looks like about the same amount of
people as were at the mm event well it's
really funny because there was one guy
there that's like he he does security
for concerts and stuff like that and he
said there were 30,000 people there I
said it can't be 30,000 he said there's
30,000 people here I do security for
concerts and the whole bed he said this
is this is close to 30,000 so that's
what that's what um it is professional
the security professional who is there
who does concerts pretty much only and
that's what he was saying from what he
can see and tell so he was saying no
there's he said aw there's 30,000 people
here I'm just going to tell you my
professional opinion from what I see I
said well we still don't know the
official number and that was happening
that day like that and then we're
hearing that it it it was definitely
most likely over 20 so
yeah okay all right what else where am
I I'm in orang land right
here I don't know why I have to throw
throw it in the air like I do but I do
so I'm going to pop some orange in here
this is so
great okay
all right it was so well organized it
felt like a spiritual event it was it
was
Supernatural nothing can explain it
otherwise I'm just going to be straight
with you guys like I always am and I'm
just going to tell you one thing right
now it was it was Supernatural is what
it was I was able to knock out a bunch
of light blasts right and and that that
alone was was incredible at the moment
but it was Supernatural
there was an energy and a light over the
entire
event separate from the light blast of
the light coming down hitting everybody
in the crown of their head and we
separate from that there was a light
that was
just over the entire entire V like a
like a bubble like a light bubble it's
just crazy how incredible all of it was
and you felt it
too so yeah
so I'm getting some orange in here I put
a little bit more orange in here this is
the longest making
smoothie what I love about the hmds it
is hydrating by the way too which is
incredible people are not they're not
hydrated enough and I'm going to do a
whole thing about water if you guys are
okay with that sometime I might leave a
little message on telegram about water
too you don't want to over drink water
you don't want to be drinking too much
water I love how you know there's so
many people there's amateurs in the
health movement that are um they get
into the health movement and they're
they're amateurs whether they're even
they're they're Physicians too and
doctors of different kinds and they go
into the social media world and they
start getting into health for the first
time and in all their their career and
they get interested and they'll do or
trainers or health coaches and they'll
say water drink a lot of water that's
number one that will do you know how
many people with chronic illness did the
water thing I remember going back back
30 years and people actually coming to
me for help 30 years ago 35 years ago
and they're coming to me for help and
they're like I'm drinking lots of water
you know my doctor told me to drink a
lot of water my health person told me to
drink a lot of water this trainer of
mine told me to drink a lot of water
that'll fix my problem did it fix it no
I'm sick with fatigue and chronic
illness and pain everywhere and I can't
do this and I can't do that high anxiety
and that water trick that like you know
that water circus trick
has been around forever it's like you
know and they make they make it sound
like they got their cop together so much
too like on socials you'll see like a
new brand new trainer just getting into
it for a year they have some following
and they're like you know they're doing
their training and they're like the
first thing you want to do if you got
anything wrong like chronic illness is
you want to drink lots of water lots of
water and it's
like 35 years of hearing
that thousands and thousands of people
with all kinds of chronic illness drank
a lot of water
it's not removing their problem I'm
sorry it's not getting rid of their
severe severe clinical depression their
severe eczema their severe whatever it
is that they're dealing with they
neurological problems their multiple
sclerosis symptoms whatever it is
neurological lime drinking a ton of
water is not going to get rid of it it's
not going to do it but they'll sure as
heck make it look good and it's like you
know are you dehydrated that could be
your whole problem make sure you're
drinking lots of water every single day
and then everybody's like oh my God oh
my God oh my God it's like yeah okay but
when you're sick you know better when
you're seasoned you know better that
that's that's just not what it is and I
want to talk about water more I think
it's important in
hydration now I obviously I talk about
it in the liver book boom it's right
over there I don't know if you see that
I'm not grabbing it right here for IG or
anything but the liver book Liver Rescue
hydration is important people get thick
dirty blood syndrome is what they do
their blood's thick it's dirty it's
gnarly it's filled with a lot of poisons
and toxins
and can even gel up and get into the
heart valves and everything like that it
can get into all the different n valves
it can gel up and so what happens is
that their their blood gets so thick and
toxic okay I've talked about hydration
for years it's amazing how it's like oh
it's supposed to be this quick fix for
everybody with chronic illness everybody
looks like an expert every newbie that
comes in on the scene that is trying to
teach people or whatever and they're
they're doing it and they're hitting the
water thing and I'm just like uh don't
even go now what are you going to do are
you going to head to the ionizer water
machine stuff are you going to head
there now because that is an epic
disaster for People's Health people have
no idea how bad that is for their health
they're doing these good things for them
and then they're drinking that ionizer
water machine stuff and they don't
realize that anything they're doing good
for them is just saving them from what
that is doing to hurt them it's crazy
how that works works like my God any
every time I run across anybody and
they're saying well I'm doing this like
alkaline ionizer water stuff water
machine water and and I'm just like dear
God you have no idea I won't go into the
details on it right here but you have no
idea what you're doing that's going to
impede your health up here in so many
ways down the road whoa
anyway
yep yeah so Healing For Life 14 4 listen
I honor honor what you're saying right
now you're on YouTube healing Life For
Life 144 you said this late notices
blasphemy totally
understand not in my control totally
understand I really do this late notice
is blasphemy and I totally respect what
you're saying and I respect every word
as I lose that down every word I respect
it I understand but honestly I actually
I actually had no
control W all right let's go we got some
orange juice in here I put some fresh
squeezed orange I got my mango to
replace my banana and you can do other
stuff too just get the five ingredients
in and then cilantro I got a nice
heaping amount of cilantro right there I
do nice heaping amount Tick Tock you
guys see that IG you guys see that okay
all right so let's move into some viy
stuff right so that's the DOL right
there and I know people are screaming
out there seos seos remember the whole
like everybody was screaming the heck
out of seos just like five years ago
it's like seos seos seos is going to
save your life seos is going to save
your life and it's just like dear Lord
I'm not saying seos is bad I'm not
saying it's like a terrible thing that's
not what I'm saying he like seos seos
just like 5G 5G 5G is going to kill you
remember that do you guys remember that
like do you remember when the internet
was like everybody like comments
everywhere in everybody's feed from here
to high heaven is 5G 5G 5G 5G 5G 5G 5G
is going to kill you 5G 5G it was nuts
it was nuts you guys remember the 5G
thing how Inc how like insane that whole
5G thing was and you didn't hear me
freaking out about 5G right you didn't
now everybody still alive is everybody
still alive after 5G I just want to know
is everybody still alive because you
didn't see me go on this massive tie
raid against 5G did you was can you can
you find something on me publicly where
I'm like 5G is going to kill you 5G is
going to rot your brain 5G is going to
do this to you 5G is going to do that do
can you can you find anything on there
about me doing that no you can't okay I
talk about like EMF and all kinds of
other stuff obviously but yeah I'm just
going to say that like the 5G hysteria
that happened I know some of you might
get mad at me yeah we're all still here
just like I thought we were and we still
need to protect ourselves exactly from
all that we got to protect ourselves
right from all the smart stuff we do
smart stuff and EMF and everything else
radiation right I've talked about that
and and my books are filled with that
information but the point is is that
like there's so many things oh wait I
says oh I can't go this short notice
totally understand it is a short notice
September 7th
in Calabasas right if you guys just got
on here I just made an announcement that
I'm going to be doing a meet and greet
I'm going to be there in person to meet
and greet you guys um so anyway
so yeah I know isn't that crazy okay so
here is the dols right here so this is
the vimergy dols you guys know I work
with vimergy the best stuff out there
let me just say this really quick I just
want to say this I had to get a tinure
I had to purchase a
tincture
for a family member something that viy
didn't have so something that them did
not have Port this this is really
interesting so I had to go and
purchase that tincture that
herb and I got
non-alcohol non-alcohol alcohol free
first thing that happened was I opened
the bottle and I smelt it and it had
alcohol in it first thing right
there very important to know so I had to
purchase this herb for a family member
because I needed this herb because
Spirit of compassion said that's the
herb I need so I said well vmer doesn't
carry that herb right now so I can't go
to that high quality let me search for
the highest quality herb I can find out
there because I this herb so I purchased
what I thought could be possibly the
best out there that's out there because
what am I going to do I purchase it it
says alcohol free I open it up smell
alcohol instantly smell alcohol first
things first so I said well that's not
going to work I ordered another version
from a different company then another
version of the herb from another company
then four more from four other companies
and it opened up a couple of them
alcohol they said alcohol free you ready
for this I opened up another
one and it was just straight garbage no
alcohol in it but it had the worst kind
of Glycerin in it the worst of the worst
of the worst I opened up another one
worst kind of Glycerin in it now I know
how like I know that that's not going to
do it's not going to
do it was just terrible junk and garbage
and that's why I work with vimergy
that's why I endorse that them like I do
because it's a it's a world away from
that it's a world away from the tricks
and the games and the crap and the
garbage out there this is important it's
a world away from all the tricks and the
games and the garbage out there I can't
say it enough you guys it's not a
joke it's unbelievable on what's out
there here I am I need an herb vimer
doesn't stock that herb right now I go
and have to find it somewhere I'm buying
what I think is the best options you can
find out there
I'm looking everywhere I'm ordering each
one alcohol in that one Al who knows
what kind of alcohol in there alcohol in
this one alcohol in that one oh this one
doesn't have alcohol but it's just
straight garbage it's got something else
in there or it's just junk all on its
own or it's got a bad glycerin it's like
here's one that's alcohol-free maybe
they did the herb right in this one and
then the glycerin was just terrible
terrible glycerin so I'm thinking oh my
God like what kind of or it is that what
are they even using and they're like oh
I know what it is and see the whole
point is that that's the difference
right there so when I when I get vimergy
that that's what I mean that's what
you're getting with vimergy you're
getting away from that it's a world
apart from that this is important I'm
making the heavy metal detox smoothie I
saw somebody said what are we talking
about I'm making the hmds right here I
got all my stuff out here but I'm
talking about like something that's
really important because I just had to
seek out another herb that vimergy does
not stock and they do not they do not
stock at all and I had to go get it and
it was terrifying in my opinion it had
some form of Al couple of them had some
forms of alcohol in it who knows what
and nobody knows and it was alcohol-free
what was it even doing in there and then
the other stuff too I was just talking
about as well which was the glycerin
terrible glycerin just it's I just want
to say that I I like I
appreciate vimergy for what they've done
I don't care what anybody thinks of me
oh he just works with them or something
I don't care what anybody says and
remember I don't own vimergy I don't own
stocks shares I don't own any percentage
of the company I'm not an owner of the
company on any
level very important to know because I
know there's lies out there left and
right about that but the point is is
that I back these
guys I I support them and back them
endorse them because of what they have
done and still do and it can't be
matched and you kind of forget about it
because I haven't been taking anything
personally or having a family member
take anything personally that that
they're taking that's outside of the viy
supplements and this is the first time
in a long time and it was like wakeup
call man it was like wakeup call
unfreaking believable it was a wakeup
call so when I had to go outside of the
BG's protective bubble outside of their
unbelievable incredible Angelic products
when I had to go outside of that and
then get an herb I was up against the
wild west of crap alcohol nobody knows
what kind of alcohol it says alcohol
free but it was loaded in there no one
would ever know and there are brands
that you would you probably somebody
probably uses that are just watching
this right now and then other other
brands have the terrifying bad glycerin
in there it's like why West out there
and it's like I just wanted to just be
like okay I I I just wish I didn't need
that herb for somebody I just wish I
could push that away and go back into
the vimergy bubble of safety of how
incredible the stuff is but minute
you're pushed out of it a little bit and
it got pushed out of it to go it's just
it's just
unbelievable anyway so important to know
so that's the DOL right there and adul
liquid just yeah mind blowing all on its
own
but I'm still seeing every day out there
just all the different Malarkey that's
happening in so many different
ways um seriously all the different
things that are happening out there like
I still see people using the alkine
ionizer water machines I still see them
doing that if they only knew what is
happening with that they just wouldn't
even believe it it's just it's just
awful this is barley grass juice powder
by the way going in the each MDS that's
barley grass juice powder that's the
vimer G1 V is in Victor i m e RG y right
there okay not barly grass a big mistake
with the hmds and I see it out there all
the time is when they do the mm hmds
that what they do is they put barley
grass in that scratchy stuff right
basically it's like horse grass right
it's like it's like coming off of a farm
field sitting there rolled up in a ball
like a baale of hay you know you know
they're using that and then it's all
pulverized down and crushed down and
it's putting canisters and you'll see
there's canisters out there there's
green caners out there with different
Greens in it and it's like barley grass
not barley grass juice powder yeah and
that that's that's a problem especially
if you have intestinal track issues and
stuff but that's the juice powder right
there I'm going to put the vimergy wild
blueberry now what you'll notice right
here this this is mind-blowing right
here I got to show you this okay all
right so I'm going to put this in front
of you right there take a look okay let
me just get a utensil so I want you guys
to see this okay
right see what I have to do in here with
this see
this do you know why I have to do that
because it's the first of its kind that
doesn't have the anti- binder agents in
it all your powders out there all your
stuff out there has the antibinding
agents in it you you like the taste of
that binder that they use the anti-
binder agents exactly anti-caking agents
there's none in here so what I'm doing
is I'm breaking up the wild blueberry
powder the reason why it's in that it's
doing that people don't know is because
of the quality it doesn't have the
anti-caking agents because that's what
people are actually eating every day
what are they
corn things like that starch of some
bizarre type of starch
all kinds of different
stuff who knows what if there's talc in
there in people's stuff what if there's
talc in there how about that to keep it
from like caking Anyway here goes the
spirina right
here okay spirulin there are differences
with with qualities of Spirulina when
you see spirulina and all these
different products out there plan on it
being the junk just just to so people
can make money and save save wherever
they can remember uses the top tier
stuff so that's the spirina no
anti-caking agent so anyway that's going
in the
hmds which is incredible I got that I'm
putting a little bit of Wyman's W
blueberry juice right there in
here little shot of that in there too
I'm ready to blend this up I'm
hungry all right let's pop it on here
let's do it so the
hmds is is
legendary on its own for what it has
done for people people who have suffered
greatly people who lost hope and they
used the hmds and it changed their life
they used the heavy metal detox and it
changed their
life what you want to do is you want to
put that lid
on all
right let's go here let's get this
blending up
[Music]
here we
go list
for boom there we
go let's move this out of the way you
guys
put that
[Music]
here and there we are
amazing there we
are there's the hmds right there and I'm
excited about this someone asked if they
can if I can uh list a link of the
product somewhere like where is it um if
you comment
once
um one live you know here's what I could
do right here
is check out the link in the profile in
the link in the description if you could
see it if there is to this live you know
all
right
yeah all
right so someone asked to link the
products is what happened so I'm going
to figure that out for you guys all
right so I just made this it's in here
um all right I want to about a couple
other cool things too about everything
so listen to this right here so the back
to the water thing I was talking about
earlier about hydration and stuff I
think anybody who seasoned and been
there and done that they know that just
drinking a ton of water isn't going to
fix their neurological problems you
don't want to be dehydrated you want to
drink a little bit of water I'm going to
go into a whole talk about that as we go
along as
well um as we go along in the future
because I want to do some water talks I
think that's going to be a good thing
for a lot of people a lot of people
don't know how much water should they
drain
how much water they shouldn't drink what
are you doing are youing coconut water
are you drinking other things are you
drinking celery juice are you drinking
the hmds every single day all those
things add into the equation so I want
to do an in-depth talk about water and
water drinking because I've seen people
out there drink too much water while
they're doing all this other stuff and
I've seen people not drink enough water
too at the same time out there but the
bottom line is is the water trick all in
its own to to heal people is a mirage
all on its own yeah of course if you're
severely dehydrated and you're not
drinking anything then you better get
some water but but the bottom line is
and yeah it's going to help but what I'm
talking about is everyday chronic
illness people who are suffering with so
many symptoms and conditions water
doesn't fix it it just doesn't fix it
but get out there you'll hear every day
from professionals on social media
they'll be like drink water it's the
first thing you need to do and it makes
you feel like well confident like whoa I
think I have a way to get better now
just drink a lot of water then they end
up drinking too much water and they
dilute their electrolytes they're
diluting
everything and that's another whole
problem all on its own so I want to talk
about that to you guys anyway I just
made the hmds I like having it with a
spoon sometimes not just drinking it
like this but with a spoon if you guys
just got here I was making an
announcement today it's going to be a
meet and greet September 7th in
Calabasas California okay and I'm going
to be there at
Aran um you know if you're in the area
in California come on down drive out
would love to meet you okay and say hi
this is different than the event that
was June 15th in the park it's very
different um and I don't do in-person
events often so I want to say that this
is important to know when have I done
inperson event so it's not like this is
something where you know this is
something that's normal it's it's still
not normal unless I start doing more
stuff but it's still not normal
definitely not anyway I wanted to let
everybody know about that so it's a
celebration to the
customized bottle they're doing the hmds
in aan h like on the refrigerator shelf
in a custom bottle they're limitate the
custom bottles and then after that
they're going to use the regular airwan
bottle with the hmds in it but it's
going to be limited addition certain
amount of bottles I'm excited to be
there for this cuz they're launching
this it's going to be in the
refrigerator it's going to be
amazing and it's there for grab and go
it's made fresh every single day this is
a huge thing because it just shows like
everything like they were so they it did
so good they're like the hmds did so
good at aan that we want to put it in a
in a bottle and put it on the Shelf it's
just mindblowing the whole thing so but
I'll be there for a meet and greet
September 7th I'll be there at 7:00 in
the morning so and it'll be there for a
few hours so just let everybody know if
you want to head there and so forth
anyway listen sign up for my newsletter
so you can be informed on things too and
register still put your name in a
register if you're coming if you're
coming if you're not coming don't
register if you're not I just want to
say that if you're not coming don't
register don't don't like put your name
in it for fun please don't do that so if
you don't think you're coming at all you
think it's possible you're coming
register but if you don't think you're
coming at all don't register and put
your name
in it's important right so medical m.com
you can register there you'll see it
also you'll see the link where you can
register a link in the description in
the profile
and you can um you know you can also go
like I said to the website and anybody
if you're interested in vimergy products
or anything like that go to vimergy.com
V is inv Victor i m is in Mary E RG
y.com to check these out and like I said
there's no anti-caking agents in here
that's unheard of that doesn't exist out
there I'm just going to tell you right
now in all those powders no one realizes
and same thing with the tinctures like I
was talking about I was trying to get
another Urban look what happened aan
also carries
Wyman's they carry Wyman's while
blueberry juice I live by this right
here that is a gift from God the fact
that they can even do that and put that
press that and put that in there so
there's that and vimergy is also at aan
too so yeah really
amazing so when and where is the next
event please east coast don't know I
don't know I'm just know that I'm going
to be here September 7th right in
Calabasas you guys I'm really excited
about it all right anyway thanks for
hanging out I'm going to enjoy this I am
hungry I'm going to have my hmds right
here looking forward to it I might even
use this fancy little spoon right there
ceramic spoon is what I'm going to do
and I am pumped up you guys love you
guys