issues gut problems intestinal tract
problems
fermentation in the gut acids in the gut
we're talking about celery juice the
power of celery juice for cleaning up
the gut right all of that
and
where's your trash can
that's what i want to know
you guys got a trash can i could borrow
well hey
i don't need to borrow your trash can
because i got my own trash can it's
right here
i got my own trash can let me just let
me just show you my trash can right here
you guys
oh i'm gonna show you my trash can right
here
this is a really good trash can too i
got this at
what store did i get this trash can at
really works
i just showing you guys my trash can
here now wait oh yep oh trash cans
falling apart
well let me tell you something because
what happens is people don't realize it
but they're dumping all kinds of stuff
in their trash can every single day
right and it's like nah nah nah i'll eat
better tomorrow i'll eat better later
i'll eat better another day
maybe i'll eat better i'll eat better
i'll start january 1st
guys when's january 1st
when is it like 11 months from now i'll
start then i'll start january 1st i
missed this january 1st
so i don't want to start now i think
i'll just go for the rest of the year
and then maybe i'll start working on my
diet
january 1st 2023
but anyway
talking about the gut we're talking
about what's going on with the gut
everybody's got why there's problems why
there's not problems and everything talk
about autoimmune
because autoimmune
isn't related to your gut so much
but yet autoimmune tends to get worse
right
as we're dumping all kinds of stuff and
garbage in our guts but there's the
relations are not what people think
we're going to cover that for a little
bit too you guys
the mm-900 hds is on sale not for much
longer
and you'll see okay at omegajuicers.com
right you'll see the link in the profile
link in the description okay when you
put the juice when you when you put the
juicer in your cart
and then you check out you'll see it
automatically come up 71
98 cents savings
and food food is going up food prices
i'm hearing every day people i know
they're like oh my god you know what the
food cost me the other day
you know what all that you know what all
that meat cost me the other day you know
you know what everything cost me the
other day food's going up up up
but
when food goes up prices go right food
food prices go up food shortages happen
food prices go up whatever is happening
right now inflation's happening right
all of that
and so what i like about the mm-900 you
squeeze more juice out people swear by
it i swear by it you squeeze more juice
out you save a lot of money as the year
goes on you save more money you save
more money i'm gonna juice some celery
because celery juice is critical for the
trash can
because what that's what's happening
with everybody we're dumping crap in our
trash can all the time
how many of these have you had maybe it
doesn't look like this maybe it was
different maybe it was homemade maybe it
was some other kind of way you did it
but we we really filled that can
how many diners have you how many people
were shit-faced during college and maybe
maybe even after college whatever and
they're in the diner and they're tanking
a whole bunch of bacon a whole bunch of
stuff and everything else how many
people are doing that right all this
time
and so and it's not even just that it's
pizza every day it's everything else
kelly beeton says love my juicer
it's incredible really the mm-900 hds
we're gonna juice some celery juice
celery juice is a powerhouse it's not a
joke
hey you know what's really screwed up
[Music]
you know what's really screwed up
right
everybody who who is who's who
everybody who's so called something out
there right now right
everybody who thinks there's something
or they're considered something out
there like relevant right anybody who's
who's who and relevant or whatever and
they're all drinking celery juice
but they don't show it
but you catch them all the time
you see their celery juice in their
kitchen counter during a pick
maybe a selfie whatever that they they
post
and you see the celery juice
and you see it in different like you
know they'll do the like whatever the
collage of photos and stuff like that
and you see the celery juice in there
but they won't say celery juice
they won't say
if it wasn't for that freaking damn
celery juice my skin would look like
they don't say if it wasn't for that
celery juice i'd be constipated off my
ass right now
they're not they're not saying if it
wasn't for that celery juice i'd have
flatulence and embarrass myself in front
of a whole crowd of people that i'm
around every day they're not saying that
either they're not saying if i didn't
have celery juice
these hemorrhoids wouldn't have gone
away
you know they don't see any of that they
don't see any of that and that's what's
incredible and
but it's like everybody who's who's who
right on social media whether it's tick
tock instagram youtube whatever it is
you see the celery juice in the back you
see the celery juice in the corner you
see the celery is just hidden somewhere
else and you know what
self they're being selfish because
you're not saying you know what i get it
i'm not selling celery juice i'm selling
you know a designer shirt today i'm
selling some skin cream i'm selling
something else because hey you know i'm
selling this fine everybody do what you
want
but they're not saying
by the way i get it
here's the celery juice guess i drink it
every morning
it has gotten rid of my ibs it's gotten
my skin better it's helped me get rid of
my eczema it's moved the needle it's
changed my life it's turned my life
around i can't live without it every
time i stop drinking it my life starts
to go downhill again with my health
my functional medicine doctor said i'm
doing better than ever and it's because
of my celery juice everybody i know
knows i drink celery juice but yeah i
won't talk about it i hide it because
i'm not gonna
allow someone else to learn about it you
know so they can save their butts
because it's all about me me me me me
it's all about me and my selfies it's
all about me and my thing here i am now
i'm on the beach everybody here we go
this is my lifestyle this is what i'm
doing you think anybody really gives a
about anybody's chronically ill
that could be like wait a minute celery
juice i heard about it does it really
work
yeah it really works right
but hey that's how it works out there
the sales on a couple more days on the
mm-900
71.98 i told you guys i would never talk
about that juicer unless it was on sale
because
that's the bottom line i want you to be
able to afford it i want you to be able
to be able to get it if you need to get
if you're using some other juicer use it
if you've got a juicer that you're using
keep it and use it i'm going to talk
about how that saves us money
what that does what celery juice does
and how critical that is i'm talking
about the trash can right now too
because what we do is we dump all kinds
of stuff inside this trash can
and
this trash can is important to us right
here this is not the normal trash can
this one's important to us
we beat down and kill our livers is what
we do
we blow up our stomachs and destroy our
stomachs and stomach glands is what we
do okay
we injure and and annihilate our colons
too is what we do boom right we kill our
small intestinal tracts we don't even
know it boom right
and we become a mess is what happens
everything ferments in here everything
starts to fall apart in here we got
resilience your body's got resilience
right we can
our bodies are tough our bodies want to
recover they want to do the right thing
but we tend to
through just the course of life because
life is hard life is not easy we tend to
do things that we're not supposed to hey
we're not taught
no one's being taught to do things that
can be really helpful instead they're
being taught to do something that's
actually harmful that happens all the
time you guys know i talk about that all
the time out there
so let's go into it a little bit right
your stomach
critical
organ
right there your stomach is critical so
let's go into that a little bit so when
it comes down to your stomach right
one thing that's really important to
know
is we can destroy the stump the stomach
glands inside your stomach these little
glands that produce your gastric acid
your gastric acid is your defense
mechanism
to stop the bugs
if your hydrochloric acid is really
strong
really strong
it will kill
a case of mono
before the mono can even start
so if you kiss somebody with
mononucleosis which is epstein-barr
fresh infection
and you kiss them
and they pass that epstein-barr virus
into your mouth
as you're kissing them
you're making out with them that
epstein-barr virus goes into your mouth
say you're just drinking off of
somebody's glass yeah i'll share that
glass with you
sure
right and boom now you got mononucleosis
if your hcl is strong really strong
it will kill and destroy that
epstein-barr virus before it can take
hold or take root
so as that epstein-barr virus
goes into the mouth into your spit
and then you swallow that epstein-barr
virus with your spit down your esophagus
down your throat down your esophagus and
that spit ends up inside your stomach
with an epstein-barr virus
your hcl will kill the epstein-barr
virus so you don't catch mono
but no one's stomach acid is that strong
no one's gastric glands are that strong
it's rare really rare the world beats us
down the bad food beats us down
life beats us down
all kinds of things beat us down vinegar
can kill that uh that opportunity for
anybody if you're tank and vinegar
apple cider vinegar is so good for you
meanwhile boom you destroy your stomach
lands and then the toxic fragrances beat
our own
body systems down the chemical warfare
the sea trails beat us down not allowed
to say that word you know there's
so much that breaks us down the mosquito
spray they spray on every state in the
united states every town every village
in the united states they dump mosquito
spray on it all year long out of
helicopters on your children on your
babies on you
purposely
it's nothing to do with mosquitoes
because mosquitoes never die
mosquitoes are there for eternity
the point is we're up against so much
and it beats down our systems this is
not our fault
it's not our fault celery juice is
critical to bringing us back you have to
get the hcl strong you guys
it's not a joke it's not you know what's
sad
it's a lot of people partaking in celery
juice
selfishly
right
because
and there's a lot of people that are
partaking in sellers who are saying it's
saving my life it's turning my life
around it's and you guys you guys are
doing that by the way you're the ones
that are saying that you're like seller
jesus saving my life celery juice has
saved my life
celery juice is moving the needle celery
juice is doing this it's one of the most
powerful tools
it's one of them but it's one of one of
the important ones right out of all the
powerful tools it's at celery juice
don't ever let anybody turn your mind
around brainwash you different and be
like oh that's just
whatever green juice that's just
whatever or celery juice isn't good for
you blah blah blah science says this or
whatever article they read celery juice
isn't good because my naturopathic
doctor told me oh it's got too much salt
whatever it is don't get fooled
don't get fooled
because
it's a massive trick because all the
who's who is drinking it
all the influencers
are drinking it
all the youtube stars influencer stars
whatever they're tick-tock people
whatever it is that's going on we're on
tick-tock right now instagram people
whatever facebook people they're all
drinking it
and they're doing it they're doing it
athletes drinking it everybody's
drinking it think you got to keep it
quiet they got to keep it quiet but they
drink it they're they're taking
advantage of its power all the time and
then
word gets out like oh you're not
supposed to drink it because this doctor
on a podcast says so you're not supposed
to drink it because of this and then all
these people get cheated everybody
should be shouting out to the ruth
rooftops everybody should be shouting
out to the rooftops is what they should
be doing big time i want to show you the
mm-900
hds okay
now
a juicer is a juicer
there's a ton of juicers out there
there's a difference here a big
difference that's why an indoor that's
why i endorsed it huge difference
the metal gears aren't there
metal
okay
any metal
is toxic to the body the metal gears and
juicers
intoxicate you
over time if you're drinking your green
juice
you've got your metal gears grinding
against each other you're getting little
specks of metal
thank god you're drinking your green
juice if you're doing it getting all
those little specks of metal but at the
same time you're getting all these
little specks of metal because you're
drinking your green juice
what i love about the mm-900 it doesn't
do that you don't have the metal gears
grinding against each other that's
critical to know right there
one
important reason to drink celery juice
i'm going to tell you right now is
when's your last blood test when was it
on tick tock when was your last blood
test just so you know telegram when was
your last blood test
facebook youtube right rumble
rumble when's the last blood test you
had
when they draw your blood
they take critical
nutrients out
we get deficiencies from our blood draws
that's why the medical mean podcast at
apple podcast the blood draw vampire
blood draw right bloodletting episode i
talk about how you have to ask for half
files how you have to ask for quarter
vials you have to have the phlebotomist
for half aisles you gotta be very
careful because they will bleed you to
death that's why so many people with
lyme disease have died over the years
because they were bled to death so many
people with cancer died early because
they were bled to death so many people
with diseases and autoimmune get sick
they're bedridden because they're bled
and blood and blood people now are bled
every minute when's your last blood test
if you're getting routine blood work and
you're not doing it right and even if
you were kind of doing it right if
you're getting routine blood work for
mystery issues
because that's what people do they get
routine blood work over and over again
for mystery issues you're losing all
these critical electrolytes trace
minerals you're losing things that keep
your brain healthy your body healthy
you're losing critical things
celery juice
helps to bring that back if you're
somebody that had two blood tests two
blood tests this year celery juice helps
to bring you back you don't ever recover
from blood leading
they take the blood from you it can take
six months to recover your white blood
cells just so you know we're where the
white blood cells right there
takes six months to recover your white
blood cells that's why celery juice is
critical all on its own
green juice isn't gonna do that
celery juice does that the trace mineral
salts the sodium cluster salts it's one
aspect of celery juice really important
to know most people already have a
weakened broken down immune system and
they're getting blood work over and over
again and it's weakening more weakening
them more and they're not getting any
celery juice in you the one way to
escape that torturous situation of being
in a vicious cycle of getting your life
robbed from you from blood taken from
you is making sure you're putting
something back in to save your life and
that's why celery juice is critical you
had a blood test once every year
you still need the celery juice
georgiana says you had it in september
right sarah says yes six months to a
year you get your blood work
they pull the blood out of you you get
weakened from it and we don't put
anything back to try to curve that
balance to try to shape that balance is
what happens it's very important to know
that's one reason celery juice is
critical but one really important reason
it really is
you know so we're talking about the
celery juice right now this is the
mm-900 hcs i'm going to show you how the
celery juicer works a little bit i'm
just moving some of these foods away
right here
okay
you guys
71.98 off on this right now on
megajuicers.com this is the mm-900 hds
you got to check it out when you get a
chance if you don't have this model it's
something to look forward to down the
road might be something you you can do
so let's go into this a little bit too
and when you order this what you do is
you go to you know you check out right
you put it in your cart you check out
and then you'll see the sale people are
always asking me when is the sale for
the mm 900 when is the sale i missed the
last sale when is it it's right now
letting you guys know
let you know
rajini said i felt so bad for weeks
after my last blood test last last
august what happens is
celery is just critical to help with all
of that and that's what happens i tell
my friends my family if you're getting
blood work
you got to put back in the tank you got
to put back in the tank that's critical
well the well the doctor said at the
doctor's office the nurse practitioner
said to just eat a lot when i got home
just eat whatever just make sure i eat a
lot of food when i get home i said so
basically the doctor told you to go fill
your trash can
your intestinal tract trash can
instead of doing something that was
critically needed your doctor and your
practitioner and the nurse practitioner
didn't tell you to go start celery juice
right away because they just took 25
vials of blood 14 vials of blood 10
vials of blood they didn't say
go home and make sure you get some
celery juice in make sure you get some
fruit in you make sure you do the right
thing make sure you get some magnesium
in you no they don't say any of that
they just say go home and make sure you
eat build your blood back up
it's really sad
machines 20 off
right so when you get to megajuicers.com
or you see the lincoln profile and you
see the link in the description
right you
put this put put it in your card and
you'll see when you check out you'll see
the discount which is incredible right
there people are always asking me what
juicer do i use people are always asking
me how do i do it you know what's going
on how do i either the whole thing so
the mm-900 saves us a lot of money
my family a lot of money that's what i
love right that's why i endorse the
machine
so
let's see if we got it plugged in right
here we do what i love about it it's
quiet
it's quiet it's not going
[Music]
it's not doing something like that
it's not making these crazy noises so
what what happens is i'm up usually
really late at night right i'm working
working working or i get up really early
in the morning or i never went to bed
because i was working all night and i
want to get the juicer going and i want
to get the celery going so i'll start
juicing at five in the morning six in
the morning and i don't want to wake up
the house this machine doesn't wake up
the house and that's what's really
important too it doesn't leak up
everybody and that's that's a big deal
so
slow masticating juicer it's a cold
pressed juicer that's what it is
71.98 off
it's this is a medical device
it's a medical device is what it is
medical devices
don't have to be
a pacemaker
they can be
an herbal extractor
because before you get to that pacemaker
in your life
before you end up
having to get a pacemaker
if you use an herbal extractor medical
device
earlier in your life
taking care of your heart with celery
juice
so that you don't have to end up with a
pacemaker i mean that's the last thing
you want to do i'll have to get a
pacemaker prop
you don't want to end up with a
pacemaker jennifer king says i can't
believe
to tell you how celery juice has helped
me and it's been two weeks jennifer
incredible two weeks are doing it
amazing you can't begin to tell me oh
that's incredible that's really amazing
so
i'm so proud of you so what i like about
medical devices herbal extractors
it's a device you want to use before you
get real sick you know what i mean oh
man i'm getting sick i got an autoimmune
diagnosis i got a bunch of mystery
symptoms i got tingles and numbness
aches and pains i got eye floaters my
skin's getting really bad and chewed up
i got acne i think it's acne the doctor
doesn't know what it is that's bumping
up on my face i got all these different
problems
maybe it's time to get
a medical device
in
maybe i can get a medical device before
someday i have to get a medical device
the bummer kind of medical devices right
something like that
so
one of the things i love about celery
juice
trace mineral salts
get absorbed into your heart muscle
muscles
i know everybody's worried about muscles
they're trying to build up their muscles
dudes are always trying to build up
their muscles right dudes are in the gym
like if they can if they got the luxury
and they don't have to work like a
billion hours a week
if
if there are some dudes that got the
luxury and they can work out in the gym
every single day and they can go and do
an hour or two in the gym they want to
build up their muscles right
well
what happens is that trace mineral salts
are critical for muscles to sustain
themselves and build up your heart is a
muscle so trace mineral salts from
celery juice goes into the heart
what i love about
what i love about celery juice right
it's the cleaner
that goes into the heart valves and
cleans the edges of the valves it cleans
the edges
so what it does is it cleans the edges
of the valves
the edges of the valves get gunked up
like your drain you know what i mean so
i got the sink right here okay
i'm running it right now okay
that water is going down the drain right
now so on my in my sink right now the
water's going down the drain okay
what happens our bloodstream is our
water right that's our bloodstream
that's our water and it gets gunked up
with toxins and garbage
and as it gets gunked up with toxins and
garbage it ends up in here ends up into
the ventricles it ends up into the heart
valves
all that gunk ends up in there
celery juice
is that cleaner
to the heart valves
yeah you know if you're not that bad
often you just get a better diet
your blood pressure will go down you get
rid of your processed food you should do
all right but if you got bigger problems
than that
celery juice is critical for it or if
you want to prevent bigger
problems celery juice
is there for you so that's something
right there so i was going into
going into the heart a little bit too so
let's head into
adrenals
but you know what if we're going to go
into the heart we're going to talk about
veins and we're going to talk about
arteries varicose veins
all those veins
right that nobody likes to get nobody
likes to get those varicose veins nobody
likes to get spider veins that's from
the liver not being cleaned up
for years and years everybody's on the
high fat diets
and the liver gets stagnant sluggish the
liver gets toxic it's filled with
pathogens and garbage and metals and
what happens is your veins just start
blowing up
everybody's veins start blowing up they
get the varicose veins they grow veins
the veins start to expand the veins
start to weaken the veins start to
collapse as well that happens to people
too
elias says how much celery juice a day
do you recommend 16 ounces on an empty
stomach every single morning if you can
i would go up to 32 ounces
if you got some other stuff going on if
you got some things happening in your
life you want to push it up to 32 ounces
now for years and years and years i said
16 ounces i've also told people they go
to 32 to get 64 ounces you can do you do
64 ounces right
and i told people to do that for years
but i'm going to tell you right now the
world is changing this world is becoming
a very
disturbing place for a lot of reasons
right
i won't go into a lot of those reasons
because you can't you actually can't
i'll lose all contact with your boss but
what happens is the world is a really
disturbing place
and so our bodies are taking that heat
for taking the stress they're taking the
garbage and clothing around and taking
the fragrances they're taking you know
the chemicals are taking the
insecticides right they're taking all
this bad stuff all the time and that's
what's happening they're taking
everything out of the sun and so we also
it's not even just about eating bad
foods or eating good foods it eats more
than that right truly disturbing i know
the ring it's truly disturbing really
what you'll notice about the mm-900
it's quiet i can talk to you guys while
juicing which is incredible so it's not
like i'm screaming over you guys either
right so we're live right now on tick
tock live on rumble facebook youtube
telegram
debbie gale says no you want just celery
juice with nothing at it don't add
anything to your celery just do a
separate juice
do a separate juice now what i do with
the mm-900 is i like to run greens
through the mm-9002 so what i'll do is
i'll do my celery juice now right i'll
have my celery juice with nothing mixed
into it no apples no greens no nothing
mixed into it you want it to have the
power it's an herb that has to be alone
by itself to turn your life around to
turn your life around you guys but what
happens is
i'll make another juice later with the
mm 900
i'll throw a couple of kale leaves in
there and then throw some celery in
there i'll throw some spinach in here
some celery
i'll throw i'll throw i'll throw some
parsley in here and some celery
it's incredible the machine is
incredible so i like doing some leafy
greens mixed with stuff but that is
different medicine
this is
the medicine that changes lives and
moves the needle when celery juice it's
by itself
nothing else compares
and that's what's incredible about it
that's why people are getting their
lives back which is so nice
so i just did some juicing right there
i got a nice thing of juice
it's not the most fibrous celery which
is really great because you know you get
less the fiber is not like filling up
but the irony is
that's my pulp
do you guys see that
that wasn't a camera trick
it's not always like this there's just
sometimes there's more pulp than this i
mean you guys know with the mm-900 you
get more pulp because the celery might
have more fiber
right but the point is is that's how
insane that is
i think about this
right germ theory i know you always i
know you're always talking smack about
a medical medium all the time so it's
still great to have you on here by the
way but i know on youtube you always
leave messages like
the medical medium doesn't know what
he's talking about
medical medium has no idea how anything
works the medical term theory it's good
to have you here but your gym theory
just so you know i'm holding
pulp that's dry
that's dry pulp okay it's not soaking
wet like where you're squeezing
constantly squeezing out juice or you're
trying to run the pulp back in the
machine right
but that's dry pulp
that's how you're saving money right
there
that's how you're saving money because
you're you're buying less celery you're
buying less greens if you want to do
greens but you're buying less celery
right but this is the celery juicer it's
amazing for celery saves you money on
celery and celery is your herbal
medicine so what happens with this
juicer right you have this juicer
and you say well that's my herbal
extractor like that's my herbal medicine
extractor that's for my ailments that's
for my autoimmune that's for my acid
reflux that's for my all my
disorders that i have that's what all my
different symptoms i'm suffering from
that's what my endometriosis my
reproductive systems my hpv whatever it
is that's going on in your life
my constipation my hemorrhoids my polyps
whatever i got in my intestinal tract
right link is in the description you
guys
the link is in the bio up there tick
tock you guys link is in the description
check them out right
okay
so
what i'm going to do is strain this
right now so let's get a glass
i have one right here let's just use
this
and
with the food short prices going up and
food shortages and everything else i
keep on hearing happening out there and
stuff stuff by four and warm people up
for a long time it's good to have
something that saves me some money
and also helping you heal
strain
your celery juice
get those little tiny
bits of fiber out of there
your stomach
just needs the herbal extraction it
doesn't need the fiber because you throw
it the fiber
should not be mixed with the sodium
cluster salts naturally in the celery
juice that are turning your life
around look at that is that gorgeous or
what it's incredible really it's a
beautiful glass of celery juice you guys
see that in tic-tac
incredible the mm-900 the sales on now
save
71.98
right
and
look you guys always ask me
right when the sale ends
i get a flurry of dms a flurry of
messages i get a flurry of everything
saying once the next sale is it's still
on sale i want to get the juicer i'm
like
and then what i do
is i
will stick my head out of the window
open the window to the house
and then i'll scream
because
because i feel bad for everybody it's
like
you missed it dude you missed it i don't
know what to tell you let's talk about
the liver
your liver is your fish filter did you
ever see the fish filter in the tank do
you ever see the filter in the tank
you guys ever see that you guys ever go
to the grocery store and you see
lobsters in the tank
did you guys ever see that you ever go
to the grocery store you see all those
poor lobsters
this poor lobsters
sitting there
they're all in there they were ripped
out of the ocean
they were pulled up by a lobster trap
ripped out of the ocean and now they're
in a store tank they're all sitting down
there like this and they're all just
depressed they got rubber bands on their
claws right okay
those lobsters are non-stop
so they just go in a bathroom
and that everything and all their all
the stuff the excrement that's coming
out of those lobsters
right
you know that you know that but you know
that trail that's in the tail if
you've ever had lobster right so all
that's coming out of the lobster and it
has to go somewhere so it goes into a
filter
so those big tanks in the supermarkets
have this filter the filter's sucking
all that up
that's your liver
your liver sitting there
inside your body right now sucking all
that garbage up so what is it sucking up
it's sucking up the gas fumes at the gas
station
you like the smell of that gasoline
smells good
okay i got the pump in
yeah smells like gasoline
hey man
this gasoline is knocking me out
hey
give me a couch
i think you'll roll a doobie now right
like that's what it is it's like
literally can knock you out it can get
you stuck so that's what gasoline fumes
can do you smell gasoline too long it
can really hurt you it can set you in a
bad direction
that goes into your liver all the gas
fumes you've ever breathed in sit inside
the liver for a lifetime and then become
a cancer because they end up feeding
a virus eventually inside your body now
you've got liver cancer now you've got
another cancer now you got whatever so
it's important to know that whatever
we're actually getting so many toxins
inside of us all the time but what do we
do to clear them out what are we doing
to get that stuff out of us how are we
blowing that out of us
celery juice is one of the ways it's one
of the tools
so
what i love about the medicine maker and
i call this thing the medicine maker
i call this thing the medicine machine i
call this the herbal extractor i call
this the medical device i call this a
lot of things
because that's what it is
so someone asked where can i buy one on
tick tock so you go to
omegajuicers.com or look at the link in
the bio omega juicers.com right
and you find the mm-900 hds
that's the one that's the celery juicer
so just so you know
so jenna says i hope this helps my
daughter it's helped a lot of people
around the world it really has he says i
love the juicer right
so it's important it juices more than
celery it does
i'll throw greens in here so i'll throw
greens in here which i really like juice
i'm a big
juicer of greens the reason why celery
juice is so important why i'm always
like celery juice or juice because
because it's so easy on the system for
everybody's
messed up dilapidated injured
damaged
intestinal tracts damaged guts got
diverticulitis diverticulosis they got
ibs they got celiac they got crohn's
they got colitis they got h pylori they
got acid reflux they got low
hydrochloric acid they got inflammation
they did everything wrong with their
guts
they got e coli c diff
they got old salmonella just floating
around in there they got everything
under the sun in there and it's time to
kind of get that cleaned up start to
restore that garbage jump that we have
inside of us right
it's incredible how it works
people are worried about food costs
they're worried about it okay and and so
that's one thing right there and that's
the thing about especially with the
tough times people are worried about
tough times worried about food costs
i'd like to save money
basically with another juicer that
probably would have been that much juice
some juicers that much juice
there's a lot of juicers with the
centrifuge
that centrifuge right the metal
i probably would say it would get this
much juice out of what i just ran
through there you see what i'm showing
you guys right now so i'm showing you
like one inch here of juice right one
inch here of juice is two inches of
juice right here how many ounces that is
okay
so and then there's some juicers you'd
probably get that much out of
there's some juicers you might get that
much out of look i'm not saying every
juicer out there you're gonna get this
much juice where you're only getting
like two inches juice which is only
getting like three four ounces of juice
to how much celery i just ran through
here i'm not saying that
but
someone else could have run that much
celery through in a juicer and maybe got
that much right maybe they got that much
but they're not going to get this much
some juicers this much some juicers this
much some juicers this much some juicers
may be here
but every bit counts because it's a
whole other half a head of salt a
quarter head of celery or three more
sticks and then three more sticks adds
up three more six adds up three more
sticks adds up and since we're on evil
planet earth
eventually
they're probably getting you know down
the road 20 years from now they're going
to be messing with celery give it like
they're gonna be like you know it's
always going to be like
i don't know
cars would be driving down the street
with a little thing on top somebody be
in there like you're only allowed two
sticks of celery per day
two six to celery
per day or we're going to come and get
you
that's how the world's going
but not right up
the liver works unconditionally for you
unconditionally for you
it loves you you can't feel the love
you can't see the love
i get it we need to see it man
show me the love
that's what people are like out there
it's like show me the love my feelings
are hurt show me the love or i'm sad man
right
but but our liver can't show us the love
he's not like a dog right it's not like
a dog a dog
a dog
right
a dog will you know we'll show you it's
love right but like yeah yeah i don't
want to treat and i do love you right
you know and but
can a chicken show you i don't know if a
chicken can show you
i don't know if a chicken can show you
up i'm not sure about a chicken
the point is is your liver can't show
you you can't see it but it's there the
love is there your liver loves you
unconditionally like nothing else your
liver wants to live it wants to stay
alive it doesn't want to be transplanted
your liver doesn't want to be removed it
doesn't want to be taken out of the body
it doesn't want to die it doesn't want
to be transplanted it wants wants to
stay alive and it loves you and so what
it does is it just needs a little help
and a little love back that's what
celery juice does for it
i'm going to talk about the adrenals for
a couple of seconds too you guys
one thing
in this world
you will get that's a guarantee
let's talk into a doctor friend of mine
who likes to he's like a philosopher
he's like
i've heard this a billion times out
there but he but he said it anyway
right
he said
there's only one certainty in life and
i'm like what is it like i didn't know
what he's gonna say
what is it
he's an old surgeon and he's like
death
that's the only certainty in life
i said well
i'll tell you one certainty in life he's
like what is it
what is it
that this world is gonna
f up your adrenals really bad
that's a certainty in life here
whether we're taught to play excessively
whether we're taught to do a whole bunch
of drugs and destroy ourselves whether
we have no choice but to go on a whole
bunch of medicational drugs because we
get too sick
whether we're up against a whole bunch
of emotional stress whether we're up
against a whole another problem in our
life whatever it is one thing's certain
in life there's one thing certain on
this planet is your adrenals are going
to take a hit throughout the life
yeah planet stress exactly
whether it's broken relationships broken
trust whether it's
whether it's a boyfriend breaking up
whether it's a girlfriend breaking up
whether it's a divorce whether it's
something else whether it's a tragic
loss whether it's something that we've
gone through that's unimaginable whether
it's something that you think no one
understands whether it's being
misunderstood whether it's being hard
hurt whether it's our heartache whether
our heart is hurting emotionally whether
we take an emotional hit whether we feel
the personalization because we've had it
beaten out of us or our soul feels like
it's been beaten out of us whatever it
is our adrenals are going to take a hit
the reason why people start to bounce
back
they start to get what feels like some
soul back
celery juice restores those adrenal
glands it's one of those things that
feeds them they're thirsty buggers these
are thirsty critters these are thirsty
critters
and that reminds me since we're talking
about critters so are these these are
really thirsty critters too but they
don't like celery juice
these critters
hate celery juice these critters like to
drink and eat other things
they do
they like to drink all kinds of stuff
and eat all kinds of stuff inside the
body and they like to they like to
thrive and colonize and then make you
sick and then you get your lupus and
your neurological lime and then you get
everything else in the sun your
hashimoto's your eczema your psoriasis
you get all your other problems right
here and so what celery juice does is
celery juice likes to
break down
and destroy these little buggers
shingles epstein bars hhv-6s hhv-7s
hhv-8
10 through 16 that's undiscovered
all of them herpes simplex one two
you know a friend of mine reached out i
haven't talked to in a long time the
practitioner
you know i've been doing a lot of
medical medium stuff for all my patients
and i see all the time aw
i see all the time people coming in with
cold sores
everybody's got a cold sore everybody's
got herpes everybody's got herpes
simplex one
everybody's got a fever blister and
they're all coming in it's like kids
have fever blisters adults have fever
blisters everybody's got these fever
blisters and i say yeah and there's so
many different varieties of fever
blisters it's like what do you think
i'm like well medical medium protocols
about how to break down fever blisters
how to break down the virus and all that
so medical medium protocols are critical
it's like no i know because i'm just
starting to get into those now because
nothing else i'm doing is working so i'm
starting to use the medical medium
protocols and celery juice i noticed aw
celery juice is one of the top pro on
the top of the protocols it's always
like 32 ounces of celery juice
16 ounces of celery juice
children's dosages of celery juice like
all these things it's about dosages it's
about all that stuff right here and so
that's important all its own to break
down the different viruses that people
have cold sores fever blisters and all
that it's like aw tell me what the cold
sore virus even does i'm like trigeminal
neuralgia shingles does that too but
trigeminal neuralgia pain in the gums
burning tongue
burning mouth back of the neck pain ear
pain all kinds of problems like that you
know and and that was just some of the
things and
it's critical celery juice is one of
those critical things just so you know
check out the cleansing hill book and i
just want to tell you guys
we're doing the medical medium morning
cleanse
this weekend
get prepared if you don't have a book
make sure you get one go to the library
get it for free
if you need to it's a challenge we're
doing the morning cleanse challenge it's
gonna be fun we might have some fun
we might do something crazy i don't know
we might have some fun and so we do the
medical medium morning cleanse challenge
it's coming on this weekend
get a copy of cleanse the heal it's
critical it's a free cleanse
you know it's not a 5 000 cleanse it's a
free lens that i'm actually doing
with you guys medical medium morning
cleanse challenge coming up coming up
this weekend make sure you have a
cleanse to heal book celery juice is
gonna be in the morning cleanse
challenge do you have a juicer
71 off 98 cents if you have a juicer use
it i don't care what it is if you have a
blender use it
i'll get a blender out someday i'll get
a blender out
and i'll show you how to do celery just
through a blender it's not ideal it's
not the greatest but you throw your
celery in there you blend it up you
don't add water
and then you squeeze the crap out of it
with a cheesecloth or a nut milk bag and
you you squeeze it out
and then you got yourself some celery
juice so if all you have is a blender be
there the medical medium morning cleanse
challenge this weekend coming up you
guys
so make sure you have a copy of the book
cleanse the heal get it free to leverage
if you don't want to get it on sale at
amazon
one last little note on this mm 900 hds
megajuicers.com 71 off
make sure you check it out link is in
description link is in the profile
doesn't have the metal gears thank god
okay it's a cold pressed juicer it's
incredible and it saves people money
there's just some things there's other
stuff about it i don't even talk about
it it's great
so
it's important so carlita says why am i
still having some acne breakouts even if
i removed eggs and dairy from my diet
how long did you remove eggs and dairy
from your diet number one because if you
remove eggs and dairy from your diet you
still have eggs and dairy inside your
liver for quite a little bit of a while
could could be in there for a good few
months or more
and then whatever's feeding on it will
keep on feeding on it that's one thing
the other thing is that's one level
there's different varieties of bacteria
i mean strengths of bacteria that cause
acne so if you read cleanse the heal and
you check into it and check with your
doctor if you want but if you if you
re-cleanse the heal you read about
streptococcus causing acne right
some people streptococcus is strong some
of it is even antibiotic resistance
right resistant so
there's an acne protocol so removing
eggs doesn't mean it's going to fix your
acne but it's going to help so the acne
doesn't get worse and worse and worse
removing eggs stops it from getting
worse and worse and worse but that's
just one aspect of the protocol is
removing eggs right that's one aspect
removing dairy then
the other aspect is did you remove
gluten because that's another thing that
feeds streptococcus bacteria that causes
acne then are you using something to
kill the acne
are you juicing something to kill the
acne herbal medicine how much celery
juice are you doing to kill off the
streptococcus that's causing the acne
that's another edge of the protocol see
medical meaning protocols aren't just
this one little thing where it's like
hey i'll take get rid of some eggs and i
did the medical medium protocol you
there's a thousand protocols you can
customize and go as far as you need to
go to get better and heal and that's
what people do
julia says i needed to remove all fats
before my acne went away that means the
streptococcus that you had julie was
hiding behind all that fat that was in
the foods right so that was critical to
do too so it was really smart and then
when you apply celery juice or any
protocols you annihilate that strep
bacteria because you don't have so much
fat in the blood and that's another
thing right there see there's so much
information to use so you can heal and
get better so yeah
yeah medical medium information knocks
out
strep like nobody does umakali golden
seal has helped me with acne
awesome
awesome your videos are amazing by the
way they make me laugh and they're
spreading knowledge and educating people
around the world
you guys
i love you much
um
i'm heading to ig pretty soon just gonna
clean up a little bit we're gonna go to
ig we're turning tick tock back on we're
turning telegram back on hope you guys
learned some stuff from all this
information about the gut and how how
the body works a little bit and
everything else and why celery juice is
so important
and know that i love you guys
and i'll see you soon let's go to
ig let's turn tick tock back on let's
turn telegram back on let's have some
fun
and i'll see you guys soon