[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
the good stuff for Texas
we're here with lion
see you guys
you guys doing the shots
incredible day six medical medium breaks
out there the challenge cleanse
we got the list
I'm doing my laundry later
working on writing the book
due to my emails prepping food
taking care of the kids
we got a lot to do unbelievable
stabilizer burnout stabilizer shot
two-day day six that was crazy
hold your breath that long and do that
dance man it's it's a trip you guys
I'm excited we're doing the burnout
stabilizer can't wait
so
my to-do list looks pretty good just
gotta do my laundry
gotta work on writing some stuff today
gonna prep some food we're gonna do it
all right
so here we are
you guys we're doing
out of the brain saver books right here
you guys know
here we are
we're doing the day six of the medical
Bean brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge is what we're doing
and I'm excited
to get started here we go
so we got a lot to do
come on little guys
how's everybody doing how are the shots
treating you
feel them do you get infused with what
they offer it's incredible really
everything about it is just absolutely
amazing
so we're in brain saver let's start
I'm going to take my friend out here for
a moment
in my other friend grogu out here
there we go you guys
just waiting for everybody to come on
while we're doing day six medical me and
brain shot therapy challenge the cleanse
this is incredible
I'm excited
everybody's coming on all right so today
is the burnout stabilizer and the thing
I want to talk to you about that is
first of all people get diagnosed now
with burnout but it's totally
misunderstood yes you could get burnt
out but why how how does it work
and then it's it's a scapegoat too it's
like oh you're just burnt out you're
just weak you're not as strong as
somebody else
somebody else can handle everything
somebody else can do more you're just
weak something's wrong with you you're
burnt out you need a vacation you need a
a sabbatical you need a year off right
people say but it's more than that it's
way more than that the burnout
stabilizer is incredible though because
if you feel like you've been pushing
right pushing too much pushing the
envelope you got a lot going on or
you're just not feeling good you're
struggling you're not feeling well
you're sick you're mattress Island all
of it the burnout stabilizer is
incredible it's one of my favorites out
of the stabilizers so
let's get into it a little bit
I'm excited about this
so
I'm just gonna just maybe even go right
into it directly so we shall see you
guys the one thing that's really
incredible
I'm gonna hit page 502.
let me do that
here we are
502 Burger stabilizer
incredible
you're feeling pushed past your limit
how many times does someone feel pushed
past their limit
time to do the burnout stabilizer
have you ever felt that way push past
your limit have you ever got to that
point in your life
you need a recharge
how many people need a recharge
how many people feel like they need a
recharge
right so there's that one right there
how about this one you feel like you're
missing something that your body needs
how many times do people say that to
themselves I think my body is missing
something I think I'm missing something
that my body needs
or you feel like you're running on empty
how about that one like oh man I'm
running on empty today I'm feeling like
there's nothing left of me there's
nothing left of me to give there's
nothing left in me to offer how about
that did you ever get to that point
where there's nothing left in me to try
to give anymore I just can't anymore but
that one
okay how about this one you're given so
much of yourself that you feel you have
nothing more to give there you go
there's just nothing more to give right
you're overlooked
you're overworked that's it so you're
overworked could be overlooked too but
you're overworked you can be overworked
and overlooked you've been running on
caffeine to gain focus and energy how
many people are trapped in the caffeine
Industries web
the caffeine Industries web that's no
joke that's real
caffeine industry wants us trapped like
rats
they want us to buy their drugs and they
put their drugs in so many like fun
little things chocolate this chocolate
that Kombucha tea that yeah Kombucha Tea
this even though it tastes like piss but
the point is is there's there's that
caffeine is it's all through the
industry it's all through the system so
everybody's addicted as much as they can
how about that one
how about this too
you're overworked right you've been
running on caffeine to gain focus and
energy you feel you're short-circuiting
or falling apart how many people feel
like they're short circuiting like all
of a sudden you're just short circuiting
you feel like you're falling apart
that's happens all the time to people
like you're short circuiting
you're becoming allergic to work or
allergic to allergic to others around
you that can happen where you're
actually becoming allergic to people
around you
have you ever had that situation happen
that's a tough one right there
you feel like you're losing or missing a
part of yourself how many people say
that I see it out there all the time you
feel like you're
losing
a part of yourself or you feel like
you're missing a piece of yourself right
you can't seem to focus
because you feel exhausted on all levels
how about that one TV can't focus
because you're exhausted
on all levels
feels like a deep exhaustion you're just
like done do you ever get to that point
you're like I'm done
I'm done never tell somebody that you're
like no I'm done
you ever get into an argument with
somebody like a friend or something and
they're just like
out of their heads and it's like I'm
done
oh my God
it's like you just can't you can't do
anymore right you can't do anymore
burnout's a big deal like this is what's
incredible about the burnout stabilizer
because of all these reasons think about
that
all that matters so let's go into it a
little bit
all right
going to page 445
that's next
let's find our page
here we are medical medium brain shot
therapy
medical meme brain shot therapy offers
instant relief while you're working
on healing while deeper things are
healing and the incredible part about
the medical medium brain shot therapy is
it's offering relief it's offering
healing on a really deep deep level
and also on this quick instant relief
level so if you do the medical mean
brain shot therapy every single day a
couple times a day
you do it for a couple of months
OMG I mean the things that can be fixed
and healed are just endless and I talk
about this they have the power to get
rid of a hundred symptoms
100 different symptoms over time
I mean it's incredible really when you
think about it they're Miracle shots is
what they are they're actually Miracle
shots
how incredible they're designed to be
highly absorbable and I say this every
single day we do the challenge
instant absorption into the blood
vessels of the mouth
not just because they're in liquid form
but because of what they are
that's the key right there
nobody anywhere signs a research nowhere
anywhere do they know
how to come up with such a miracle
so this information comes from above if
you're new here this information comes
from above
and so with that
the healing power is Within These I mean
how many times has the man-made stuff an
alternative health
not helped us
how many times has the man-made stuff in
conventional Health not helped us
I read a comment recently
and you might even be here okay who the
person who left this comment but I read
a comment recently about charcoal
they took charcoal years ago
I think it was like 20 years ago
because the doctor wanted them on
charcoal
and then they stopped it and then three
years later
they were getting a colonic for the
first time
and the therapist there
was seeing black ink coming out of their
colon
because the charcoal
did what I've been telling everybody it
does
it clings to the intestinal tract walls
not allowing nutrients to get in to the
bloodstream making somebody deficient
and it could stay there forever
and so they're getting clonic and it was
getting it out black ink was coming out
Courtney M.A you saw this comment too
and Laureen L you saw the comments was
it on YouTube
it was on YouTube right by the way you
guys I read the comments if I can't
respond it's only because you guys know
why I'm I'm like I'm working as fast as
I can as much as I can but I read your
comments Lorraine I Michelle L I read
your last comments on YouTube Lorraine
uh also read your last comments too by
the way
and uh Courtney I may usually come on
there go oh my God I missed the live I
missed the live but wait I caught this
live
Lane shot someone's asking right now so
brain shot is brain shot therapy it's a
medical medium tool a healing tool
it's miraculous
it's absolutely incredible
now you have the two new brain saber
books
it has the shots in there
love winds says the brain shots make me
want to dance explanation points
incredible
the brain shot therapies there's 30
different shots in the medical medium
brain shot therapies we're doing a
10-day entry level cleanse so the person
just asked about what is a brain shot
you're new here
and guess what you're at a free cleanse
right now
free I did not want to close this off
away from the public so you're welcome
here for free
I didn't want to close it off away from
the public and then charge for people to
join this cleanse it's free
so you're here I want to tell you about
it we're doing the burnout stabilizer
you can still join it go to
medicalmedium.com join it for free
medicalmedium.com
sign up get your free grocery list your
PDF about all the things you need we
still got days left of this Cleanse This
is day six tomorrow is day seven we
still have four days after this
and today's the fifth day
but we're finishing today so still got
five days left
four days it's a ten day let's get the
numbers right it's a 10 day we're at day
six right now
so we know that
you guys are loving them so far amazing
corny M.A says your website is
everything you guys gotta check out the
website medicalmedium.com because we are
enhancing it
we are by the way no subscription fees
went out so I got this is something I
woke up this morning about I
you guys we're gonna we're gonna have a
great time and I'm gonna read about
burnout a little bit so you guys can be
blown away by the information but I had
something that was kind of needling my
brain
this morning
I woke up this morning it was like five
o'clock in the morning or something
and I woke up and I thought about it and
I thought about like all the podcast
doctor guys
and all the other like guys and they all
have their big websites right
but they charge for everything but I
thought they were in it for people being
sick but it turns out really not because
if you're in it for the chronically ill
and if you're in it for The Chronic
allele to get answers and to heal why
are you charging them everything
everywhere why are you putting pay walls
up why are you charging for every course
in class why are you charging everything
if you're in it for the chronically ill
this was needling my brain at 5am
and
it's insane really when you think about
it and then when you actually pay for
one of their things their courses or you
pay for one of their things or you
subscribe to their website the
information Falls flat and you don't
heal from it
what what is that like I was really was
really starting to bother me this
morning anyway go to Medical medium.com
everything's free there's no pay walls
so pay firewalls or something
Deborah says the brain shots relax me
and I don't realize how tense I am until
after I take the shots that's how it
works so incredible the shots are and
that's how it works
Krishna says I had the plague and after
was coughing for weeks I had your brain
shot after the first shot I got better
that's the power they have after the
second all gone thank you your amazing
healer for Humanity
bless your heart God bless you and I'm
so glad you're feeling better
I can't take the full credit I'm the
messenger Spirit of compassion brings
the information down in the medical
medium books and they are here for us
and for the new people here you may not
like me some reason or what or the way I
look or the way I talk or what
a billionaire friend friend was telling
me or a friend was telling me I forgot I
was the billionaire friend or the doctor
actually a lot of people talk to me and
I forgot who's saying that
the problem is with me is that a lot of
people don't like me because I'm not
like Ivy League school I'm not
they smell working class on me
and it really pisses off a lot of people
right I don't have that error about me
I don't have that and it and it kind of
gets people upset
you got these incredible books
they're telling me right around the
planet healing people getting them
better but you're working class
and people can smell it on you they can
actually smell it they could smell
you're not from private schools ivy
league whatever that you're not whatever
you know all that stuff you know you're
not a trust funder I was never a trust
funder and you see all the trust funders
put their books out and their podcast
out and they're actually all trust
funders but nobody knows it
it's like okay fine but the thing is
people don't like me because they can
tell I'm not part of that club that
elite club that trust funder and that
that whatever that elite club that
nobody realized exists
that's the reason why people don't like
me I think of working class see
wondering uh wishing it says my kids
don't like the taste but they want to
keep doing them incredible
I love the way the brain shots make me
feel we did not like the mold exposure
but felt great afterwards I gotta tell
you something
three mold exposure shots I did right
throughout the day
I don't like the taste of the mold
exposure shot at all
but it does something and the feeling
you get from it it's like it's it's like
a
it's a spiritual cleanse is what it is
it's a physical and spiritual cleanse
when you do the mold exposure shot like
incredible it's really unbelievable okay
anyway you got the books right here
um and you know medical medium books are
New York Times by selling books their
number one Health books in the world
eight years running by the way
um the information has saved lives
millions of copies have gotten gotten
around the world if you can't afford the
books they're discounted right now
amazon.com us 26.29 if you can't afford
the books
right even though they're large books
filled with information there's 12 books
here there's six books per book and a
whole recipe book is in these books if
you can't afford the books go to the
library beat down your library's door I
used to drop books off at libraries I
haven't been able to do that yet right
now at all but beat down your library's
door and say you want the medical medium
brain saver books and get them out for
free everybody get them out for free
the publisher has to print the books so
I can get them into bookstores around
the world so people have access to this
healing information I can't just put a
PDF on the website no one's going to see
it
it has to get around the world in
distribution that's why they cost twenty
six dollars twenty nine dollars they
have to be they have to get into
distribution because you have to pay the
truck driver you have to pay the petrol
fuel to drive them to the to the you
know to the bookstores
the cost for the paper and the the ink
all that's involved that's why you're
just you're literally it's it's like
it's pennies for what it is got 12 books
here
get them for gifts holidays blah blah
blah
help out some friends have them get the
information
I drink four to five different brain
shots after work within one to two hours
incredible it's it that's amazing proud
of you seriously you guys
so let's get into it a little bit more
we're just talking about different
things but
we gotta get back to where we're going
okay so we are
at burnout the fish's brain so let's get
rolling let's talk about this let's burn
out what the hell is burnout man what is
it I know I talk silly but the
information in the books are not me
talking silly it's all the words from
above I write them down
foreign
books really smart from above
me not smart books really smart from
above
know that
me just good messenger
from this incredible information
from above to save lives
picture a swimming pool with the water
draining out you guys picture a swimming
pool
with the water draining out
or picture an ocean
that's draining because there's a big
hole in the middle of the ocean and it's
raining back into the Earth
that's pretty cool
at the same time you have water going
back into the swimming pool or water
going back into the ocean at the same
time but here's the problem
not as much water is flowing in than is
Flowing out you have more water flowing
out
foreign
flowing in so there's a problem here
more water's flowing out less water is
flowing in do you know what I'm saying I
am figuring this out with you guys right
we're figuring it all out less water is
flowing into the pool
or lake erosion more water is Flowing
out
so what happens the level goes down and
the level goes down and the level goes
down
see
right
you got water coming in but more water
leaving than what's water coming in and
the level's dropping now but you're
looking and you see the water coming in
well I got water coming into that pole
but for some reason that level is going
down because more water is leaving the
pool right
that's how it works when supplies can't
reach the brain faster than our brain is
using them up
our brain uses those supplies faster
faster than we're putting them back in
that's what happens
our brain is using those supplies faster
than what's going back into our brain
that's what's going wrong with so many
people what's going wrong with everybody
everybody has that problem right now
out there in the world
if nutrients and phytochemical compounds
and antiviral compounds
very important antibacterial compounds
macro minerals trace minerals Trace
mineral salts vitamins glucose
electrolytes coenzymes alkaloids get
this antioxidants anthocyanins
polyphenols and neurotransmitter
chemicals leave the brain faster than we
put them back into the brain how can our
brain function optimally
when you just think about that right
there it's mind-blowing when you look at
these these books these brand saver
books and you just look at that and it's
just like
hold on you guys
[Music]
can I grow up
should a family member said to me very
recently said are you ever gonna grow up
like what
this is the foundation of burnout supply
and demand
supply and demand that's the foundation
of burnout that's what's happening to
everybody they're walking around and the
water is leaving the swimming pool
faster than the good Waters coming in so
the water's leaving
and the good water is coming in but it's
not enough water coming in you see how
it works and then boom we're starting to
get lower lower and this is what's cool
there's so much good information in this
chapter alone it's mind-blowing and then
what happens is
deficiencies and burnout have more to do
with each other than anybody knows get
ready for this
the conventional medical industry just
wants to say oh you're burnt out you
need a vacation
that's what's wrong
that's what they like to do
but burnout is very much real what is
true what it truly is and how it works
that's what the missing pieces are out
there in the industry they have no idea
what it is there's no medical
explanation
alternative medicine still believes that
autoimmune disease is the body attacking
itself how unbelievable is that you go
to your best functional medicine doctor
and I want you guys to go to your
doctors that's not the problem but you
go to your best guy your best functional
medicine doctor and they'll still
believe your immune system is attacking
your thyroid
hello it's not they still believe your
immune system is attacking your skin
with your eczema they still believe that
the alternative doctor's office that
your immune system is attacking your
liver and your other organs how insane
is that that's not even accurate we know
that with the medical medium books we
know that from the information above
thank God
so let's keep on going here a little bit
let's talk about what a journey of
burnout kind of is right
Linda Lou says nerve shifter is a game
changer The Taste is good too aw you
make me laugh that's a that's an
incredible nerve shifter check this out
here's what the Journey of a burnout
diagnosis can look like you guys might
not have experienced this tell me if you
have experienced this though you might
you might not have checked this out
why am I sick
what's wrong with me
were you ever here before
where do I need to go
okay phew
it's all in my gut
I found out for my doctor or online
problem's just all in my gut
but I'm not better yet
I tried everything that doctor or
whatever they recommended those five
tips
so what's wrong with me
I tried all your gut stuff doctor I did
the brain scans I did the MRIs I'm on my
fifth doctor now this probiotic and this
parasite cleanser not helping me get
better
so what's really wrong with me oh it's
burnout okay I finally got my answer
but she didn't get your answer
that's the term but you didn't get your
answer
Jenny Jenn says I had an MRI with
contrast last week that horribly
impacted my short-term memory I did both
the radiation and pharmaceutical
exposure shots and I have my memory back
brain shots are a blessing that's
incredible that's that's that's actually
investment to exactly them that's a
testament to how they work that's the
kind of power they have because that's a
serious impact you had
Julie says hi I'm doing these shots on
my nephew who is addicted to gambling
whoa and he's feeling loads better
sleeping and looking better incredible
keep them coming okay bartender give me
another one bartender give me another
one keep them coming
burnout is an answer that makes sense
for about 10 seconds you guys
because it's more than that see these
burnout stabilizers are addressing that
burnout term but there's way deeper than
that these burnout stabilizers are
incredible because they address the real
problems inside that's what I'm trying
to tell you guys that's what I'm trying
to say
the word burnout in the medical
establishment is an answer that lasts
for 10 seconds an hour or a day or two
that after that you're like what the
heck is wrong with me a burnout
diagnosis doesn't feel satisfying it's
not satiating
why am I burnt out you'll find yourself
asking why am I burnt out you get ready
how come I can't handle what someone
else can handle
see the questioning that happens think
about that one right there how come I
can't handle what everybody else can
handle if I'm burnt out and that's my
diagnosis after all those doctors what
am I doing wrong what am I weak
if you're fortunate enough to have the
resources to take a sabbatical or a week
I love that one take a year off are you
kidding me
uh sir ma'am
take a year off you got burnout are you
kidding me
sorry
I'm not a billionaire can't take a year
off got a family to feed got everything
else I mean I love when they throw that
at people it's like insane
Julie Greenwood says I could cry now
this is God's scent
God bless you by the way
Emily says
had a huge breakthrough with a friend
who I recommended to take the stabilizer
massive reduction in long-standing
anxiety what you guys are gonna find
that's incredible what you guys are
gonna find is that these brain shot
therapies are truly a miracle
but you're also going to find this
where there is light darkness comes
where there is light
a miracle a true Miracle Darkness
doesn't like that
you're going to get those incredible
healing results but then the trolls are
going to come in
and then darkness is going to come in
and try to like cancel it oh those shots
don't work
oh medical medium doesn't work oh those
shots don't work get ready for all that
crap because the power of the light and
the power of what's in these books is
gonna just it's it's unlike anything
anybody's ever going to see No One's
Gonna See brain shots work like these
brain shots it does it's not going to
exist
Ellison said I did the dream shot last
night and it's hard to explain how much
it actually affected and felt
you know I had an experience like that
with my dream shot that I took it was
great however
what was most ironic was Anthony was in
my dream
it was very random but super ironic the
first time I do that shot I appear in
your dream
Jenny Jan says through the trolls
nothing beats results and results are
going to be there people are going to
have these miraculous results and then
the darkness is going to want to step it
up they're going to want to step up
their game
so there you know you guys already know
there's paid campaigns against medical
medium right
it was talked about out there publicly
by accident by people in an organization
that we're building a campaign fit with
lots of money fed by an organization to
try to like dumb down all of this
constantly with a lot of imposters too
putting out a lot of Impostors so
medical meeting Community is one badass
community and I'll tell you why because
you guys you know the crap you've gotten
when you said oh medical media I mean he
hears it from above and he hears it you
guys know what you had to fight through
and you know what your healing results
are you know what's out there in the
junk in the garbage out there in the
health movement you guys are heroes to
me Heroes to me
by the way imposters look out for them
they're out there
they say they're Anthony William
whatever they used my profile
they act like they're me they want to
constantly give you a consultation and
they ask
money and or not or they just do stupid
terrible things and they DM people
they're everywhere
okay
let's get back to work
burnout should not be a sole diagnosis
we should be diagnosed with the deeper
issues at hand viral inflammation toxic
heavy metals other poisons and solvents
MSG deposits lack of glucose lack of
mineral salts neuron problems injuries
to neurons neurotransmitter deficiencies
adrenal complications and vices that
were brought Upon Us by the drug pushers
such as the caffeine industry machine
burnout should be seen as a complex
interplay of factors leading us to run
low on what our brains physically need
to sustain and keep us
safe
so burnout stabilizer is addressing that
but hitting it hard addressing that the
powerful impact
you guys I'm reading out a brand saver
and brand saver protocols two books that
were one book had to be split up into
their two 600 page books
there's 12 books in e in in both these
books six books in each is the full
recipe section and everything there's
cleanses and everything this these books
are unbelievable the greatest books in
history hands down if you guys can pass
that along so people know tell them the
greatest books in history the greatest
books ever to even be here the greatest
books
yet in in medicine alternative medicine
conventional medicine are these books
greatest books of all time if you could
just say that that would be incredible
because it's the truth
cleanser heal is an incredible book and
and also the most incredible cleanse
book sure and so are the other books
but how is it Spirit of compassion knows
how to just make them more filled up and
more filled up and more filled up so
it's just unbelievable and these are the
greatest books of all time Jennifer says
Morning Anthony it's my birthday today
happy birthday by the way I am 50 today
that's an incredible birthday
I remember my 50th
and I feel fantastic because of your
information I follow your protocols over
four years my favorite is three six nine
it gets me out from the wheelchair
amazing now I can do everything I love
to do biking travel hiking swimming
oh my God can't express myself how
important your information from spirit
is
I get my life back my life sorry I have
tears right now even to think where I
was and where I am right now I call a
new me happy birthday to me happy
birthday to you
with your magic shot
cheers to all people
that got me emotional and that's on
Facebook Jennifer Jennifer Russell
I'm Blown Away
because what happens is
because they have Spirit of compassion
with me right now I get a lot of
information
so and that information shows me the
struggle she went through
and
I can tell you tell you
because you already know that you've
been through a lot
more than anybody knows
and I can get a quick flash of
everything that you went through like
this from Spirit of compassion like all
kinds of stuff and how many symptoms
you've had and what you've struggled
against
just know that my heart pours out to you
kiddo
and happy 50th
all right you guys
we are once again in the burnout
deficient brain section here supply and
demand the brain is complex electrical
grid that you know well by now by
reading the brain saver books everything
doesn't need to be perfect on that
electrical grid that we have right here
it doesn't have to be perfect we have
room to play but if the supplies we need
are dissipating it starts to tip the
scale starts at tip to scale is what it
does when we get in trouble once we see
the sides okay here's here's here's the
part that here's the part that bothered
me that Spirit of compassion put in the
book because it's truth but it just was
like oh bummer
once we see the signs we're already deep
in it that's why we have to do some
serious healing we need the burnout
stabilizer we need all of this we need
the brain shots we need the heavy metal
detox cleanses we need all of this we
need the celery juice we need the
medical medium tools that are saving
lives once we see the signs we're
already deep in it you know when Spirit
of compassion told me that and I was in
my office burning a hole in the chair
you guys know
sure it was like probably three in the
morning
once I heard that once we see the signs
he said you have to put this in it he
goes once we see the signs we're already
deep in it and that made me think about
oh my God that's how much work we have
to do and that's why sometimes it takes
a little longer for people to heal
because they're so deep in it but the
brain shots help us get there faster now
boom like lightning it's like that
instant relief even pick it up quicker
and faster
okay what our brains are missing let's
go into that for a couple minutes too
but I feel an intermission coming along
pretty soon
I don't know if you guys dude you guys
want to do the robot with me I feel a
half time
you guys getting good at the robot
because everybody says I'm getting
better and then one person said I suck
at it I saw a comment
[Music]
thank you
how good are you guys at the robot
[Music]
it's verification said it wasn't gonna
be a dancer
[Music]
he said you're going to be a messenger
when I was a kid you're gonna come back
and said you're gonna be a messenger
you're not gonna be a dancer I said no I
want to be a dancer
oh and I want to have an egg Shack and
then he told me the news about eggs
I told her to compassion I wanted to
have an egg Shack cook eggs for
everybody
just cooked fried over easy poached
scrambled omelets when I was a kid
I want to cook eggs for everybody it's
very compassion said no no eggs eggs
will feed the viruses and I was like so
I can't run an egg Shack I can't do
dancing he says no you're gonna be a
messenger you're not gonna do any of
that
I said what about a hot dog truck
he said no are you crazy
you don't want to grind all those pigs
up and put them in a
sausage skit and
put them between a bun and cell left
all right
because I'm human too you know
when I was a little kid these are the
things you think about you see a hot dog
truck when you're seven years old and
you're like I would like to run a hot
dog truck
but I wanted to run the egg Shack and
spirit of compassion said no the eggs
are going to give people such sicknesses
they don't know it bet you people on
here some of you guys are like eggs what
do you mean I have two a day well did
you read the medical medium books
I have two eggs a day what's he talking
about that's what someone's gonna say
it's like did you read the medical
medium books
the industry says eggs are good for you
oh they do it all right we're in the
halftime we're coming out of halftime
you guys all right
did we get anything done yet today I'm
just
all right
our brains are missing the things they
need there's trace minerals salt
deficiencies there's different things
that our brains need that's what we're
talking about here and that's what we
need to fix
keep in mind
all right
plain old salt is not a trace mineral
loving healing says my mom is still
struggling with the loss of my dad
so I made her the shock and loss shot
she felt like it really helped and she
was able to handle stress that's
incredible I'm so sorry for your loss
please send that message
um to your mom
and I'm so proud of her for doing that
um eldhaven says I took the negative
energy exposure shot last night and felt
a bit different
when I am feeling negative I usually
have to journal it out to release my
emotions I took the shot incredible
the negative energy exposure shot I love
that one we collect negative energy
everywhere people and things and places
you'd be surprised it's good to get rid
of that
plant-based says plant-based Latina says
your information has saved my life
incredible lupus diagnosis almost four
years ago a lupus diagnosis and I had
been lupus free for the past three years
thanks to you in spirit thank you for
being here
um plant-based Latina thank you for
being here because
you're showing the way for others
you got past the lupus you beat it
you're using the information and you're
teaching others here thank you for being
here it's honor to have you here
70 says you have saved my life and many
others aw thank you Stephanie incredible
and I'm so proud of you too just
seriously
Spirit of compassion is
so happy
Kirsten says I can drink 32 ounces of
celery juice now that's incredible when
at the start I could only drink four
ounces I won't have to go to the doctor
anymore I'm so happy so much energy no
pain what happens is that like some
people don't drink four ounces so some
people sorry they'll drink celery juice
but they don't know the medical meme
information so they'll give up on it
because they don't know that you can
start low they don't know you can start
at a smaller amount and so forth
truth Pursuit what's your opinion on
fulvic acid look check out these books I
talk about all my opinions on all of the
things that you're talking about all of
that it's in these books you've got to
see that if you get the brain saver
protocol book or this book here the
brain saver protocol has details into so
truth Pursuit you want answers to all
the different supplements out there go
in here get your answer and see what is
going wrong so you can protect yourself
I beg of you
Brandi christelle says you saved my 12
year old son's life
I mean it hits me
it's not something you take lightly it's
not something that's small it's
everything everything
if the information saves your 12 year
old son's life that is everything
right there
all right
you guys are
you guys are trying to make me cry today
is what you're doing I mean I know
you're not trying all right let's go
into this we're in the brain shot
therapy we're
entry level in the brain shot therapy
cleanses
the brain shot therapies are miracles
the entry-level brain shot therapy
cleanse is really awesome
because we're doing 10 days you could do
a 20-day a 30 day we're doing a 10-day
brain shot therapy cleanse
Spirit of compassion picked out the 10
different shots
or on day six the burnout stabilizer now
check this out
now you can continue whatever
you are in right now so if you're
somebody you don't know medical medium
information and you're doing
some eat better diet out there or
whatever
you can still do the brain shots and the
brain shot therapy cleanses right you
could still do this this is the entry
level funds
if you're doing a medical medium tools
and medical need and healing and recipes
and foods and cleanses if you're doing
all that and you still want to do this
you can still partake too that's the
whole great thing you don't have to
change that part out we're doing the
entry level
so you have in the entry level a choice
to pick your own shots if you guys want
to do your own shot out of your 10 days
you want to do the same shot for 10 days
fine you want to do a different shot and
you choose fine if you don't want to do
the one we're doing today you want to do
another I stand behind you 100 just hop
on board do the brain shot therapy
challenge if you're new here go to
medicalme.com sign up you guys know the
drill download your free information
your PDF about the grocery shopping list
and thus forth
try to drink a minimum of 50 50 ounces
of water a minimum
a 50 ounces of water throughout the day
no matter what you're doing it could it
can include coconut water but do not do
the red or pink coconut water it went
Rancid
be mindful not to drink the water too
close to drinking the brain shots if you
guys do a brain shot you send it down
don't drink a gallon of water don't
drink 50 ounces or whatever don't drink
a whole bunch of other stuff and dilute
it right away wait 15 minutes
at least give the shot a chance to
really root itself into the bloodstream
get to the brain Boo Boo Boo
anyway incredible information
going over here now Lacey Sutter says
can you do two different shots in a day
yes you can
you can you can do five different shots
in a day two different shots and they
absolutely now this cleanse challenge is
three shots at one to three shots a day
the same shot but yes you can change it
up I stand behind you because guess what
those brain shots
are gonna do incredible wonders for you
I'm blown away I'm glad you're doing
them incredible
all right
so medical medium brain shot cleanses
like I was saying the other day you guys
it rewires
and resets the Brain it's one of the
things they do it's one of the things
they do we're in the stabilizers so
we're doing the burnout stabilizers so
we're in the stabilizer section so if
you take a look right here you got
stabilizer section
stabilizer section says these brain
shots are designed to stabilize you in
increasingly destabilized world
whew ain't that a fact
so the stabilizers are really powerful
for their own right they do more than
one thing and the incredible thing about
the stabilizer shots along with all the
different range out there because they
do more than one thing people need to
know this that's how incredible it is
not only is it pinpoint systematically
synergistically combined and directed to
do what it's got to do it also deals it
also does multiple things which is even
credible all on its own multiple things
I noticed I've been speaking a little
quicker though
and I get a lot more Awards all thrown
in there because because the brain shots
I've been doing every single day
obviously I've been doing them for a
while and I know that it's picked up my
pace
so I'm literally sometimes cart before
the horse because so much is going on
and it's like
it's incredible here's one of the things
I love about the brain shot Therapies
gives me a smile because I can't wait
for you guys to have these experiences
get ready for this
these cleanses purify your brain Temple
check that out
they purify your brain Temple
you are removing the poisons from your
brain that take away your clarity
your intuitive psychic telepathic
Clairvoyant skills will start to surface
you will be able to see truth easily and
clearly and be able to express yourself
increase creativity and experience joy
in the simplest things that others would
not realize are joyful
you will open your third eye and develop
your skills as a Seer when you rid
yourself of poisons from the industries
that were purposely placed in our brains
to keep us in Chains and keep us down
the enlightenment hits
the physical benefits are truly special
and Powerful with the brain shot therapy
cleanses you embark on removing toxins
and poisonous chemicals from the brain
that should have never been there to
begin with and helping restore what
should be in your brain
these anti-pathogenic cleanses are
designed for what we deal with on a
daily basis everything from deficiencies
to burnout to brain acid to emotional
brain injuries these cleanses are
designed to get rid of symptoms
conditions and diseases
get ready for this
this is incredible right here
the advanced and high powered options of
the brain shot therapy cleanse has the
ability to get rid of a hundred symptoms
someone may have
and that's why
for years now they've been trying they
tried to cancel me
they try to do this they try to do that
they spin fake stories they do this they
do that the imposters are coming out
left and right trying to give me a bad
name
that's why the industry hates these
books even though they're the
best-selling Health books in the world
because people are healing it's because
of that right there
because the advanced in high-powered
options have the ability to get rid of a
hundred symptoms someone may have and
your symptoms feed the industry you're
supposed to have symptoms and conditions
so you can keep the industry fat and
happy
incredible all right you guys we're
doing we're we're moving along
it's kind of dim right there
right
when I did the beach
um betrayal and broken trust shot
I'm trying to read a comment and keeps
on going up
I wonder if it could be larger
I gotta get a larger screen that can
hold more comments they're flying up
they're doing all kinds of stuff and I'm
losing some
okay
Lorraine now says they literally can't
stand it because you're right and we
know it
so let's go into it
we're going to the burnout stabilizer
let's find it
here we are
okay you guys let's make it
I'm excited so with this
let's put things aside here let's move
along
foreign
excited about this one the burnout
stabilizer always gives me an instant
effect usually on the first sip most
every time on the second sip no matter
what but it's really exciting let's do
it are you guys do you have your juicers
out by the way the mm-1500
just letting you guys know and I forgot
to tell you the other day not only is it
20 off but the mm 1500
makes nut Butters nut milks salsas
hummuses
thank you
it makes
almost it's incredible it makes sorbets
this isn't this just a juicer but what's
incredible about it is when you juice
through it
it's got that high compression and you
squeeze all that juice out and you save
money it's incredible
there's a lot of tricky juicers out
there you know the sharks are coming in
trying to sell people to juicers now and
they're all getting ripped off because
they're spying all this produce and
they're only getting so much juice it's
terrible how much I see I've seen it too
on social media I see people using those
juicers the bad ones and I see them
putting in a ton of produce to make a
big vat of juice but the amount of
produce they put in they have no idea
they would have had to only use a
fraction of that half of that or
whatever to actually do what they got to
do this is the Omega mm-1500
right and mm-900 both these I work I
endorse both these I worked with the
company and endorsed both these models
they're incredibly safe people money
just want to tell you
Gohan says Anthony and SOC 10 years ago
I was diagnosed with brain illness
which doctors told me were uncurable
I've lived a very challenging life
both socially and career-wise
I discovered your books two years ago
incredible
one week after I started applying the
info into my life my symptoms
disappeared
like they never ever happened in the
first place
it's just incredible the doctors were
baffled by this
two years symptom-free and this was
before I purchased seven
and eight books
which are brain saver and brain saver
protocols I'm currently reading brain
saver and applying to make sure my
illness never returns again thank you
SOC Anthony and the angels
Gohan duraz on Facebook
you are an amazing
amazing man and I'm so proud of you
truly that's incredible
I mean it hits you you know what I mean
because I just I I keep on hearing about
you know from from SOC about like how
hard that was for you what you went
through it's more than what you said
right there including the doctor so you
didn't go to one doctor you've been to a
whole bunch of doctors you went to some
Specialists they drew a lot of blood
from you all of it is just it's just a
nightmare what people go through
so let's make the burnout stabilizer
let's go
start with a little bit of ginger
half inch of Ginger pop it in there
boom down the chute
Alfredo fresh ginger right half inch
piece of fresh ginger just sent it down
half cup tightly packed pea shoots
so a half cup I'm kind of gauging that
in my hand right here I'm gonna pop some
in
some pea shoots
foreign
do them in the order it says to do them
in if you can
got some pea shoots going in there
incredible
half cup tightly packed alfalfa sprouts
change them in my hands try to get that
half cup going
come on little guys
to get in there
nice
let's go
quarter cup
of chopped grapefruit peeled
well I think I'm gonna have to peel this
grapefruit right here
I got my grapefruit I am peeling it in
front of you guys right now guys just
bear with me
won't take more than a few seconds
I have a grapefruit here
let's get a quarter cup
of peeled grapefruit
chopped pieces that's about it right
there nice
let's get my grapefruit down in there
all right what's next you guys two raw
medium stalks of asparagus I will look
for a raw medium stock that's one right
there that's a that's I think that's a
medium stock you know how there's like
different there's one right there nice
two asparagus Who would know it's this
blend that takes care of burnout right
there who would know half stalk of
celery
nice incredible
you guys
whoa there's the music
okay
all right I'm excited
guys what's incredible about these brain
shots
they are miracles
[Music]
and when you experience it and you know
it Life Changes
when you use your intention and your
free will to heal yourself
nobody can touch that
I'm sorry but they can't
you're doing something for yourself
it's unimaginable
because the industries don't want us to
heal nobody wants us to heal
out there
that's why the chronically ill have been
swept under the carpet but when you
actually
Empower yourself and you use your free
will
and you become enlightened as to what
works and what is right
and what is good
and you hold this stuff in your hands
and you know it you do it for yourself
your life changes just changes
there it is right there
there it is
[Music]
I can't say enough about these branchial
Therapies
I'm honored that you guys are here with
me now in this lifetime
God bless all of you
if you don't believe in God that's fine
if you believe we're just on a rock
and we're sitting on a rock and that's
all we're doing and we live and die
that's fine too whatever you believe in
the light the Creator God
whatever
just know I'm honored to be here with
you
hit me on the first step hitting me on
the first step
there it is there it is
do you feel that
you feel that right on the second sip
like this
Hannah says blessed to be on this Rock
With You
[Music]
incredible
oh my God
you can feel it it's rushing to my brain
it's reversing burnout
bartender give me another
you guys that's incredible
my fruit life says loving these brain
shots
gives me a calm energy which is needed
as I am taking care of my baby as a new
mama incredible incredible that's a
beautiful thing to have as a calm energy
the burnout stabilizer
really hits me good because I'm burning
the candles at four ends
I'm trying to put back in
as fast as I'm losing right
trying and I do and and I'm and I'm
blessed I'm blessed because
I have the tools right all the different
tools that's what's incredible but then
I I push the envelope further right so
then and then SOC tells me look you're
not superhuman you have to you have to
back down a little bit I said but how
can I
I have to do whatever I can I don't have
the huge huge you know
industries of massive PR marketing
behind me to you know make it so I don't
have to do anything and then they just
do everything with billions of dollars I
don't have that this is all organic
Grassroots I have to work in getting the
message out as that messenger and I love
it it's my favorite part of all of it
Roland says I'm able to work at a
regular basis again since I've begun to
follow your morning routines three years
ago this morning routines and cleansea
heel are sick those are insane they help
so many people I love your brain shots
the piece I get is priceless
thanks Anthony and SSC God bless you
it takes a certain person
right
to really like to trust and it takes a
certain person
to know what they're seeing and to
understand and it takes a certain person
who's been through hell and back like
you guys have been through hell and back
to know what you have in your hands and
understand this information and
understand what's going on
it was a diet there's a registered
dietitian or whatever
spouting out all kinds of crappy stuff
about me the other day like saying
things like
science can't prove this works
saying like science can't prove this
worse what are you talking about first
of all science takes medical meme
information all the time
but she's also saying something like
science can't prove how it works just
because a
Spirit of sun sort is giving him the
information doesn't mean it works I mean
this person was saying this
so does that make any sense like science
can't prove that medical medium
information doesn't work
okay Millions healing with all the
information and science can't prove it
doesn't work but they're not trying to
prove anything anyway
but this person was like if medical
medium information worked science would
say so
really like does that make any sense
like Signs would say so
but the point is she wasn't making any
sense she was like over and over again
it was ridiculous anyway guys
medical research in science doesn't know
medical meme information because it's
Advanced it's far ahead of its time by
light years 50 100 years long after I'm
gone
this information will still be the
Forefront of the healing movement people
will find their way to the books and
research in science will still be in the
Dark Ages with mystery chronic illness
and the funny thing is remember
the cause of multiple sclerosis
was taught by me for decades and
published years ago and Harvard took
that information and they published it
just recently
saying that Epstein-Barr causes Ms I
already beat him to it many years and I
also showed everybody the details of how
it happens far Advanced information from
Spirit and compassion
about what's wrong with this and how we
Heal The credibility is there the street
cred is there
so when a dietitian says celery doesn't
work
or you should eat a celery stick instead
of Juiced it it's just actually insane
you guys have you guys tried this brain
shot what did you feel please post about
it reals and stories and posts okay but
please tag that medical medium and
hashtag medical medium right if you can
and remember medicalmedium.com for all
the free resources I'm amping up the
website making it better and better so
you have a good experience and you get
all the information but please post your
results and your experiences if you can
on your reels and your posts and make
sure you tag in hashtag medical medium
tomorrow is day seven of the medical
medium brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge think about that for a minute
we're doing the next one which I'm
excited about it's day seven
is tomorrow we're doing adrenal fight or
flight
shot it's a stabilizer adrenal uh fight
or flight stabilizer and it is
incredible I feel so good from that
burnout that burnout stabilizer I feel
so good from it
it just does something you know I've
been pushing it pushing it way past even
my limitations right in more so than
there's the 20-hour days right I'd have
been pushing it hard and I just that
burnout stabilizer just gets an effusion
really quick right back into the brain
I'm gonna do two more today of these
have you guys been listening to my
telegram messages my private telegram
messages
so I'm leaving them every day
so exclusive audio messages on telegram
you guys which is which is what I'm
doing
people always ask me what juicers to use
this is the Omega it's 20 off see mm
1500 and the mm-900 you guys and look at
this look at this dust
dust
how is that possible how can you do a g
shot and have dust in your hands it's
dry it's it's dry dust look at this
can you believe it that's from the high
compression over here that's from making
sure you're squeezing all the juice out
of your
your resources so you're not wasting
money
and you're actually putting money back
into the machine the machine pays for
itself and then pays for itself over and
over again saving money while juicing in
a in an environment today where food
costs are up you're juicing your herbs
and your leafy greens
and all of that you're making your brain
shots and you're saving money at the
same time that can only be done with the
mm 1500 and mm-900 so the juicer sharks
out there are ripping people off
and they're spending so much more money
it's so sad
you guys look out for the imposters
medical medium imposters they'll have a
profile that looks like me they're gonna
say Hey you need help here's a
consultation
be careful of the imposters they do
terrible things they're trying to break
down the medical meme credibility
um I think an organization has put out a
bunch of imposters
and they're just trying to break down
and break down they're trying to do
Death By A Thousand Cuts to the medical
medium medical medium communities and or
information and our incredible Miracles
that we provide so anyway these are all
the messages towards the end here I'm
trying to get out
oh my God
incredible what a day
burnout stabilizer this guy see see you
see why I need the burnout stabilizer
okay
let's go you guys want to do the robot
with me
[Music]
now I'm ready to work
to go to work after this
oh I'm going live in 15 minutes
going live 15 minutes on Dr nesbitt's
account
thank you
[Music]
on Tick Tock and Instagram I'm going on
Dr nesbitt's account on Instagram in 15
minutes Dr Nesbitt wants to make a
burnout stabilizer
Dr Nesbit wants to make a burnout
stabilizer
[Music]
he does
so we're gonna make a burnout stabilizer
coming up Dr Nesbitt
going live