nerve gut stabilizer that's why you see
all this parsley in front of me right
here an incredible medical medium tool
mind-blowing actually because it
actually heals the body and moves people
forward I want to read about that a
little bit also doing the vitamin C
shock therapy that is a powerful tool
we're going into a time period right now
a lot of bugs going around the whole bit
people come down the flu and all kinds
of different stuff and the C and all
kinds of stuff and RSV everything people
are actually getting stuff so so guess
what vitamin C shock therapy should be
doing it every single day if you need to
I'm going to do that too so I have the
vitamin C in front of me which I'm
really pumped up about right there and I
am going to make it I have the different
things that I need as well I got oranges
right here in front of me too now I got
to make an announcement Cafe Gratitude
in
LA Cafe Gratitude in La the
collaboration between them and me
medical medium Cafe Gratitude medical
medium meals are on the menu at Cafe
Gratitude in LA right now so hey if you
get a chance check it out you can order
them to go you can order them to be
delivered you can go in there sit down
and eat them I'm excited about it so I
don't know if you guys know about the
collaboration that's happened but it is
really phenomenal incredible restaurant
incredible restaurant and they have the
medical medium meals in there so I'm
excited about that and you might have a
ticket for for October 21st 22nd 23rd
24th because guess what I'm going to be
there in person for the meet and greet
and we're all eating and that's next
week so look out for that four sold out
nights popup dinners four popup dinners
sold out sold out in seconds 12 seconds
sold out 12 seconds and the first time
the link got out somehow and it was
already selling out before we could even
announce it so it's actually really
exciting once again Cafe Gratitude and
medical medium collaboration meals are
on the menu there in LA I'm going to be
there soon and it's what six days is
that what I said six days from now
October 21st that's the first popup
dinner night that's been sold out it's
going to be really cool intimate setting
because guess what it's just going to be
me in the restaurant with you guys if
you got a ticket it's going to be
incredible that I'm excited about so
okay talking about scared to death
scared to death that's what's happening
now if you don't see it out there then I
don't know you're in a bubble but right
now out there in the world of Health
everybody screaming bloody murder that's
what they're doing this will kill you
that will kill you this is bad for you
this is bad for you pesticides this is
that oceans this that everything
pesticide your food this Stu like it is
going nuts right now air fresheners
fragrances it's people are freaking out
everybody's looking for something right
now to BL blame something on of course
but it's
irresponsible in nature so it's
irresponsible in the way they're doing
it so I want to cover that as well
scared to death you see it everywhere
okay what I'm trying to say is that news
articles people's articles
podcasts
influencers everybody's doing shock and
awe and trying to scare everybody to
death to get a click a like and so forth
that's how it's going right now there's
going to be overtime an allergic
response to it so I'm giving you the
prediction right now so it's going to
happen there's going to be a huge flip
might take a year or two maybe a little
longer but a huge flip where people are
going to be sick to death of it they are
they're going to be sick of it but right
now people are getting a high off of it
and they're just like saying it every
minute like you got to worry about
Metals you got to worry about this you
got to sound
familiar but when medical medium broke
all this stuff out there and put this
information out there many many years
ago and for years I've been fighting for
it I was called crazy I was called no
way this is lunacy I was called this
can't be true how can you be talking
about this how is this even possible
clones aren't bad for you perfumes
aren't bad for you what's he talking
about perfume what is that what's
natural flavors he's crazy about natural
flavors what's going on with this in
citric acid now everybody's freaking the
out is what they're doing
and they're taking medical medium
information of course yes they are it's
true they are they're taking it they're
running with it but they're leaving out
how to protect yourself and how to heal
that's what's happening now they leave
out how to protect yourself for the most
part outside of things they poached but
they leave out how to protect yourself
and how to heal if you just got on here
you guys we're going into the parsley
shot the partially shot nerve nerve gut
acid stable
izer and we're going into the vitamin C
shock therapy which if you don't know
about the vitamin C shock therapy you
should know about it it is a powerful
powerful medical medium healing tool
that it should never be
underestimated ever it's that powerful
it's that incredible so that's what
we're talking about today I got some
books in front of me too I got some
oranges like I said I got the parsley
that's what I need I got the honey right
here I got the vitamin C letting you
know and I got I'm finishing right now
my cup of lemon balm tea right
here so
good so right now the big thing is Scare
Tactics scare people into what what what
oh my God I'm GNA die what the sky's
falling where where's the fire that is
the scare tactic now it's on every
Health podcast it's in every article
it's every influencer that's the new
tactic with
no ways of helping people get through it
no good answers on how to heal no
answers on how to defend yourself
protect your family protect your
children none of that is there it's just
caffeine's bad caffeine's going to kill
you medical mem information but you so
so many Trends and traps out there
instead they throw you in
it's like caffeine's bad do this and
what they give you sucks this is bad do
salt and water that sucks this is this
is bad do my do my carnivore packet of
protein it's got junk and [ __ ] in it do
this is bad then do this it's so that's
what's happening right now it's all a
method methodology on scaring the [ __ ]
out of people scaring them to death then
getting them to buy whatever it is
they're selling that's the tactic and
guess what it's going to get old pretty
quick it's already starting to get old
but that's the tactic by my program
because guess what this is going to
happen to you that's going to happen to
you so buy my program that's the game
the name of the game so I'm letting you
guys know that's what's going on out
there there's no responsibility to
helping a person to actually telling a
person here's how you get this out of
your body here's how you can protect
your child here's how you can help
yourself here's what you do to avoid
this problem that's not there it's just
screaming so right now it's all about
screaming as if they all woke up and
that's what happened so bottom line is
influencers podcast people people in
health just woke up the other day that's
what happened they woke up they realize
the air fresheners that they were just
using a year ago just using a year ago
is bad so you got these podcast doctors
now you got these podcast influencers
now in the health movement they were
lighting all the scented candles during
covid yes during the pandemic they were
lighting all the scented candles they
were that's what they were doing now
they're screaming how bad they are but
they were using them they were lighting
them they had their air fresheners and
all their apartments and all their
houses they were cranking the caffeine
and the espressos up to here they were
they were doing all of this and guess
what they were newbies in the health
movement just starting just in on with
their training wheels brand new they
were just basically learning just the
other day you don't have those air
fresheners they were learning just the
other day like last year perfumes might
not be good but they were using perfum
per fumes 3 years ago 2 years ago 4
years ago in
fact and in truth if you enter a home of
one of these podcast doctors or one of
these podcast influencers in the health
movement and you smelt their home or
their apartment even if they threw out
their air freshener I can guarantee you
all you smell is air freshener and
perfume all in their clothing in their
closets everywhere cologne whatever from
their boyfriends or husbands or whoever
and their Partners just living with
stink but now they're experts all of a
sudden now they're experts all of a
sudden right there's something you can
do to really help move people forward
it's called you make them aware and then
you give them options to heal and
recover and protect themselves options
that actually work not buy my program
now the same [ __ ] program I've been
selling for a few years oo I just
discovered air fresheners are bad for
you buy my program now and people go
what huh what's in our food what's on
our stuff natural flavors MSG what do
you mean oh fragrances are bad whoa I'm
scared now oh my God I got to do
something what are you offering you're
offering a uh some kind of a program
there you go that's what's happening
today and then the ads so another thing
too there's a game the game is
run hundreds of thousands of dollars of
ads ad a month get a whole bunch of
people in they're buying all your crap
you bring them in through Scare Tactics
you're bringing them in through scaring
them to death you don't give them any
answers to move them forward after they
wasted their two three5
$110,000 and you move them on you do the
shuffle and you move them on and you get
the new people in so there's a revolving
door happening right now with all of the
the health influencers not all of them
but most of them it's
scare them to death bring them in they
buy something right tell them how
they're killing themselves and then
after they buy it they don't get answers
shuffle them along it's a shuffle and
move them along and get the new cycle of
people in so it's
like out boop b boop bop out scare them
Boop new person in buy their [ __ ] oop
out get the new person that's it run
more ads then go through the whole
system the Google ads and the Facebook
ads and the IG ads and all that and have
people standing there going I was really
sick a long time ago and I I didn't know
what it was and then I discovered it was
toxic heavy metals really sounds like
you're reading the medical me books I
discovered it's toxic heavy metals and
Corella does not stabilize and hold the
medals really published First Medical
medium glad you're using the book and
it's not it's actually doesn't even work
but you should follow my cell detox and
recovery program and learn about it
because y I'm a doctor and boop boop
doctor that lost his license but I'm a
doctor and you should check it out
there's this is happening every minute
out there right so the game is you scare
the crap out of people you move them in
you sell them [ __ ] you push them out
they don't they're not any wiser they're
not going to heal they're not going to
recover and they're not going to get
better and then you get the new crowd in
with the ads that's how it's done you
guys you suck them in boom right you
take them for take them for what they
got shuffle them out shuffle in Shuffle
out and that's the game and that's the
name of the game right now all at the
same time your feed is growing all at
the same time you're building up right
you're building up your numbers you're
building up your emails that's the name
of the game I'm not saying that's the
worst thing what I'm saying is the
answers aren't there you just got
totally screwed over and you're never
going to have the answers and off you go
with some kind of bull crap recycled
stuff that was all put together and HH
Posh and that's what's happening to
everybody
today
and it's Fierce I always say dog eat dog
but man it's bear eat bear is what it is
it's a bear eat bear that's the kind of
world we're in now in the health realm
why should I care why am I even talking
about it who gives a [ __ ] it's because
the chronically ill get tangled up and
eaten up in in the process that's why
the chronically ill and the chronically
sick people who don't have much people
who have given it all way people have
done what they could to try to survive
they've been to 20 doctors they've tried
to heal and they just need to be taught
real things that move them forward like
a vitamin C shock therapy which is
critical or a nerve gut acid stabilizer
which The Parsley sitting here in front
of us so I want to go over a couple of
powerful tools and then I want to bring
us back really quick Cafe Gratitude if
you guys just got on here the
collaboration between Cafe Gratitude
medical medium they are all set right
now the restaurant is rigged with
medical medium recipes in Cafe Gratitude
in LA and if you got a ticket for the
popup dinners they've been sold out they
sold out 12 seconds but if you got a
ticket it's going to be really amazing
October 21st 22nd 23rd 4th and look if
you didn't get a chance maybe we'll do
it again with Cafe Gratitude and we'll
do another like four nights at sometime
and maybe you can get in because it's
going to be a meet and greet a personal
it's in the restaurant I'm there eating
with everybody and some cool things are
going to happen you know like true
medical medium
fashion Jenny Mack over there in IG sold
out in less then seconds couldn't get a
ticket to any and I had two computers
and a phone oh my God and and my
apologies truly my
apologies the restaurants you know they
only hold so many people right so Amanda
over there in IG says yay my husband and
I are going what there this weekend to
try the medical medium dishes thank you
for going there and trying the medical
medium dishes because this is a
legendary moment in
time they're a profound legendary
restaurant Cafe Gratitude in LA
okay and they've taken the medical mean
recipes and Chef Drew just said you know
what we're going to do this we're going
to do a little this we collaborated and
it is going to be insane over there what
you can get them right now the dishes
right now over there Linda over there in
IG yes I was at the Venice location last
night for dinner what fabulous
scrumptious excellent Service Such
wonderful experience highly recommend
whoa you were at the Venice
location what the heck you are eating
the medical medium
dishes I am honored first of all because
I think they're that good too and to
hear that you think they're that good
too that's incredible it's wonderful
wonderful
wonderful and I'll add one more word
amazing amazing
onig want to read one more comment if
you guys are okay with that over there
Yono says already tried the veggie rolls
and papaya salad so
good oh my God I'm freaking out
I'm I'm I'm going into I'm going into
shock right now
because I can't wait for the 21st 22nd
23rd 24th okay he with henna wow three
hours with you a dream come true my
whole family is coming how did you get
tickets to that your whole family's
coming okay that's exciting all right
yeah it's three hours with me exactly
it's a meet and greet with 3 hours with
the medical medium I'm going to be there
it's going to be
like unhinged it's going to be unhinged
I got a smile on my face right now
because I know it's actually going to be
really really really awesome and I know
it
is all right so um you guys hang in
there cuz I'm going to make make the
nerve gut acid stabilizer I am have you
actually tried the nerve gut acid
stabilizer
because it's a needle mover I mean it's
a needle mover man it moves a needle
it's like the gas moves man it does it's
like stepping on the gas in your car and
that thing moves h
and gas that's stuck in people and and
people are constipated and problematic
and their gut is so off the amount of
microbiome [ __ ] that's for sale out
there the amount of people selling their
own microbiome crap stuff just thrown
together with crap you don't even know
how it's made unbelievable and all you
need is the nerve gut stabilizer A's
having major issues right now A lot of
people are reporting getting kicked off
the live streams they won't let people
on the screen and it's
freezing and that's what they've done to
Medical medium we have reached out to ig
for that and they turn off sound as well
so if you're even hearing me on IG
because they've really just I can see
they kicked at
least they kicked at least a th000
people off for sure so they're keeping
the number somewhere around 400 and
everybody's reporting how they're
getting kicked off if you're
experiencing this please report it to us
in the D Ms okay so we can use that data
we can use that data um to help defend
ourselves from the IG kickoff today
because that's what they're doing
they're kicking people off and you know
it makes sense because somebody you know
working there probably is really jealous
as hell about the Cafe Gratitude and
medical Med medium collaboration and you
better believe it's happening you know
or actually um you know leave the
information if you got any if you if you
screenshoot it and so forth leave it at
Medical mem safes
space.com go to Medical m.com all right
all right well listen you can go to
rumble I'm on YouTube live right now
okay and Rumble all right also
telegram's happening right now and I got
Tik Tock up as we speak
so the amount of
might might of the amount of microbiome
stuff is crazy you got like fulvic
minerals which never fixed anybody I'm
just going to be honest you got
sh never fixed anybody it doesn't people
are chronically ill and they go on that
they don't get better their skin doesn't
get better their exan orasis doesn't get
better when you're on shil it doesn't
your neurological symptoms tix and
spasms don't get better your migraines
don't get better your trigeminal
neuralgia don't get better your rashes
and different things and pains on knees
and ankles and swelling and doesn't get
better okay your tingles and numbness
and you're ringing in the ears and your
vertigo doesn't get better your
depression and anxiety don't get better
you can buy a $50 bottle of chillogy and
your depression is not going away it's
not going anywhere and that's how it
always was
right and same thing with a
probiotic your tingles and numbness your
nerve pain your fatigue your neur
ological fatigue your dizziness all this
different stuff doesn't go away doesn't
go away with a probiotic either I'm
sorry but it doesn't but what happens is
in the microbiome world all this stuff
is thrown together all this different
stuff you know including like ACV
gummies and things like that it's all
just slapped together with a bunch of
crap in it and there's so many things
out there for the microbiome world and
people are still stuck they're stuck so
stuck so bad that all these dudes tried
all that and then they went to carnivore
and I'll talk about that another day and
then they go to carnivore because it's
called process elimination where they're
totally screwed and they don't know what
to eat anymore they're afraid of this
afraid of that and they start narrowing
it down to just meat and meat only they
tried all the microbiome products they
tried all the different protein patterns
they tried everything to do to help
their gut in some way some fashion some
shape some form goes nowhere and now
they're just stuck with a piece of meat
they realize they're bumping against the
wall they got nowhere to go with this
process elimination so now they're
adding fruit and they're adding honey
and adding lemon and stuff like that to
try to crawl out of it so they're just
going back to a keto diet basically with
with fruit and
meat so what I'm trying to say overall
that's just one example so many other
examples of people losing their ability
to eat the things that they want to eat
and they're stuck they don't know where
to go they can't eat this lettuce they
can't eat that they can't eat this herb
they can't and they're just getting
knocked down to just basically
oatmeal all of a sudden they're on
oatmeal and oatmeal only I'm saying this
because there are people out there and I
see that there young influencers out
there that people bring to my attention
and say look at this person this
person's really suffering they're just
on oatmeal like that's the saddest thing
I've ever seen only on oatmeal because
they don't know what to eat know what to
do know how to heal know how to recover
and it just gets all taken away from
them and they don't know what they're
reacting to and it just goes Boop Bo
Boop and now they're just on oatmeal and
that's it plus a microbiome product and
so forth and everything there's a ton of
this kind of stuff going on out there
meanwhile if they only knew medical
medium information and they knew about
the nerve gut acid stabilizer okay then
things can change so what I have in
front of me right here is nerve gut acid
stabilizer so I'm going to show you
right here if they only knew about these
things life could be so different when
you use the nerve good acid stabilizer
on a on a regular basis Miracles
actually happen for so many people it's
really a very special special thing and
that's a medical medium brain shot
therapy which is the brainsaver protocol
book and
then people are sick because of
something people are struggling because
of something they're struggling because
they're immune system is struggling I
talked about this in some of the immune
system shows right that we've done
if you're sick your immune system is
sick it is so simplified so simplified
you're sick your immune system's down
it's sick you got something wrong with
you your immune system's struggling you
got aches and pains immune system you
got ringing in your ears immune system
you got whooing popping in your ears
ticks and spasms Tremors your immune
system you got trigeminal neuralgia
teeth pain a jaw pain your immune system
you got migraines your immune
system you got restless leg syndrome
insomnia your immune
system need I say
more you got Mass cell problems immune
system you got like you can just keep on
one thing at a time whatever you got
going your immune system is struggling
struggling what does your immune system
need what what does it need right
vitamin C vitamin C is critical for the
immune system it just is so critical
that if you were on a ship out in the
ocean for a long time
eating beef
jerky you will fall apart fall apart
it's why carnivore people can't eat meat
there's no vitamin C no vitamin C it's
why if you're actually eating meat for
two years your Skin's going to look like
crap in five
years that's why the carnivore diet
isn't the carnivore diet anymore they
just try to use the name carnivore diet
is just a keto diet with fruit it's meat
and fruit now I'm saying this because if
you don't put the fruit in there and get
any vitamin C you're screwed you're
screwed you will fall apart your body
your connective tissue you can't just be
on meat and this isn't coming from a
plant-based situation I'm not saying
that you got to be all plant-based you
can't eat meat that's not it at all I'm
saying you will be so totally
screwed your body will fall apart your
collagen will fall apart yes doesn't
matter how much protein you think you're
getting everything's going to fall
apart you have to have vitamin C
vitamin
C gotta contain
myself because the amount of stupidity
in the health realm is so bad and it's
never ending I've been watching it for
decades it's never ending Lauren moch
over there yes I was in the hospital
from gastritis they sent me home with
medicine took one pill and then
discovered the nerve gut stabilizer shot
worked better didn't have to take my any
more medicine after that's incredible
Lauren it is and I think what happens
with people okay is there's a lot of
people in the health movement they they
they lack the experience because they
haven't been truly that sick yet so
their influencers built on health
because they have an interest in it but
they haven't been that sick yet they
will down the road I know one who's a
podcast person right now
it's a pretty well-known podcast to a
degree and they're just eating meat
right now they're in the process or
she's just eating meat yeah because
she's getting sick getting desperate had
to do the elimination process and get
down to just meat because she heard
about you she carnivore people on there
and then she's going to have to go from
there and eventually add fruit something
she was afraid of all these years the
point is is no matter what if you're a
health person influencer health
podcaster or whoever it is and you
haven't been sick enough you lack a
tremendous amount of experience you
might say you were sick but you might
not have been that sick you really
weren't that
sick and so what happens is people
with less
experience about what's going on with
the chronic Leo and being sick are out
there running the scene I call them the
health slum Lords they run the scene
they dominate the scene they take take
over they got a lot of money they can
throw the money around they can throw it
into teams of people doing a ton of work
and then they haven't been sick enough
they don't know the experience with
chronic illness they don't understand
and then they sit there just throwing
out stuff like feal matter implant
disastrous yeah disastrous like other
things
too like running your blood through the
machines and running it back into your
body
disastrous so many different you know
things out there ACV
disastrous all kinds of stuff right
these are just the name of few I mean
there's tons and tons of stuff but they
don't know because they haven't been
truly that sick yet and if they get sick
and when they really really get sick ah
man they're going to be swimming in that
what do I do now what do I what kind of
water do I drink let me try this let me
try that they're going to be in that
place where they're drowning
ing drowning in
misinformation and they may have an
Awakening one day and realize that
medical medium people have
healed dasty chronic illness just real
real serious chronic illness and have
come out of that risen out of the ashes
and come out of that you know medical
mean people know they know the
communities know that what it's like to
be on couch Island and Mattress Island
for years and then to come out of it and
rise out of that
okay just like what Lauren said about
her stomach and use the nerve gut acid
stabilizer all this is important and
once again why do I care why do I care
you know I care because I see The
Chronic Ill get affected and get stomped
on constantly out there it's pain
staking I see them get tricked I see
them swimming in all kinds of trends
that don't work
it's every day out there and they're
getting lured in by microbiome talk
they're getting lured in by
flash shiny things and shiny
objects and they don't
realize about like something like the
vitamin C shock
therapy if you're somebody who's got any
kind of symptom any kind of problem
whatever it is your immune system needs
help bottom line
your immune system needs assistance now
we have like assistance to destroy our
immune systems it's everywhere we're up
against all kinds of stuff that's what
we do on planet Earth and there's plenty
of assistance to that like we can just
annihilate our immune system in so many
different ways very simply just caffeine
alone is an immune system Destroyer
caffeine alone okay that's an immune
system Destroyer just like when a mom is
on caffeine while pregnant and the
baby's immune system gets compromised
from that
caffeine but there's an answer to that
moms have to look out and become aware
and not do caffeine on any level moms
should not be eating
chocolate chocolate is harmful for the
baby extremely harmful for the baby I
talked about this for years you guys
might remember maybe some of you don't
but chocolate is really bad during a
pregnancy and I look if somebody just
asked a book on in I just saw right
there brain saver protocols there it is
okay all
right immune system problems are rampant
immune cells are actually struggling in
human kind right now it's it's actually
the biggest thing happening you don't
hear it as the biggest thing happening
you don't you hear other things like
processed foods are the biggest problem
on planet Earth processed foods aren't
the biggest problem on planet Earth and
like I said before you take processed
foods away from people they will find it
one way or another just like moonshine
just like prohibition just like when
they removed alcohol out of people's
hands back in the 20s and 30s just like
when they did that people were just
brewing their own moonshine in the woods
and that's what they did they consumed
it that way because they're going to
find it no matter what if they want it
lra 144 Anthony I did the nerve gut ask
stabilizer today to strength me
strengthen me for my flight to LA
tomorrow lar 144 where are you flying LA
tomorrow where you
going are you going to Cafe
Gratitude October 21st 22nd 23rd 24th
which night do you have it's going to be
really
fun so I want to make the vitamin C
shock therapy
critical for so many people I want to
read about it a little bit too
okay over there
[ __ ] um still freezing up over
there keeps on freezing up the screen
okay all right so we're talking about
medical medium vitamin C shock
therapy why does medical medium vitamin
C shock therapy bring healing to a new
level because it takes a a specific type
of glucose attached to that vitamin C so
here's another thing that's important
right here nutrients
antioxidants they need a
sugar to travel far they need a sugar to
travel far that's part of the healing
that is part of the healing they need
glucose to enter cells so when you're
using something to beat something and to
heal and recover and move past illness
and you need something like that making
that work is is even part of how you
heal how do you make that even work when
you need something and you can get a
hold of it you can take it to another
level to make it work so the vitamin C
shock therapy and I have the vimergy
micro C powder right here by the way
this in combination of the MSM I don't
know if you guys
remember does the skin good does the
skin really good okay I do not have a
face lift I don't get facials I don't go
to Spas I want people to know all right
I don't get facials never had a facial
in my life never ever and I can't say
that I can't say that that's something
dangerous to say if it wasn't true
because guess what wherever I got that
facial somebody's probably going to come
out become a hater and be like he had 10
facials a week over here I haven't I've
never had had a
facial point is never had a facial do
not never had any kind of exfoliation
process ever no exfoliation process on
my face I'm telling you right now by the
way okay that's the micro C powder what
do I do for my skin vitamin C vitamin C
you guys know I endorse viy that's the
most incredible vitamin C there is on on
the market on the
market there's nothing that touches it
okay a lot of you do the medical medium
Skin Potion which you take the micro C
and you actually do that and the MSM
right I love this stuff love this stuff
I just love
it it is so good for people people out
there have no idea I know you guys know
a lot of you do the medium Skin Potion
get the recipe at Medical medium.com
please the Skin Potion one of the things
with me is I I don't talk about myself I
talk about Spirit of compassion I talk
about Spirit of compassion trying to
help the chronically ill I talk about me
trying to work with Spirit of compassion
getting the information two be that
Messenger right getting that information
out there putting the prophecies out
there in the books all of that right
I've talked about all that okay and and
little
tidbits you know this and this but what
people don't realize right is I don't
get facials I don't get
exfoliations I don't even use like thick
lotions and lotions and whatnot all over
my face it's very important to know that
like I've kept my skin in a good place
because of high amounts of vitamin C of
course there's other things too other
things like celery juice and so forth
and other stuff but high amounts of
vitamin
C huge for the skin when everybody was
doing the collagen thing which because
now they're they they've taken the
medical Med information remember medical
medium information I put it in the books
published at first about you can't do
you can't get collagen from eating
collagen you can't just eat collagen and
you grow collagen and develop collagen
produce collagen doesn't work you can't
eat a sheep's eyeball to fix your
eyeball you can't eat a human's eyeball
to fix your eyeball you can't eat
somebody's liver you can't eat a cow's
liver to fix your liver you can't you
got liver problems that cow's liver is
going to make your liver worse keep that
in mind it just is and you can't consume
collagen thinking that that's going to
produce collagen somehow in you but
guess what the health industry made that
massive mistake I mean I was laughing at
that for years it's painful because the
amount of collagen people purchased and
thought they were doing something for
themselves and the amount of like super
models out there talking about how their
collagen all that collagen is helping
them and everything you know meanwhile
they're getting you know they're getting
exfoliations and facials day in and day
out and day in and day out the point is
is collagen doesn't build collagen and
no disrespect to supermodels of course
but but collagen doesn't build collagen
it doesn't you need building blocks so
medical beam information was about the
building blocks to collagen that was the
whole point there about putting that
information out first and one of those
building blocks is Vitamin C you care
about your skin than vitamin C now you
may not care about your skin and that's
fine so care about your immune system
though especially when there's all kinds
of stuff going around especially when
you got symptoms and conditions you got
symptoms you're struggling you got a
condition your immune system struggling
that's how it works immune system
struggles when you don't feel good and
that's What vitamin C really is for you
can be on a ship with beef beef jerky if
you're on that ship too long out in Sea
you will get scurvy your bones will fall
apart you will get rickets rickets will
eat your bones they will drill through
your bones like rickets
will will burrow through your skin it's
critical to know if you're on a ship
okay I I mean look now that carnivore
dudes on social know that you need to
eat some fruit at least to keep yourself
alive now they know you need a little
lemon and you need some fruit to keep
the themselves can you imagine a whole
bunch of carnivore dudes before they
knew that and they were just packing
beef jerky on their little trip on a
boat and if they were on that boat for a
year can you imagine what they would
look like when they came back riddled in
rickets riddled and scurvy they would be
a mess they wouldn't have a muscle on
them they would just be literally
skeletons of themselves they would be
shadows of themselves that's how
ridiculous that is because there's a
reason why you take a lime tree on a
ship that's going to be out in Sea for a
long time because the lime will save
your life it will save your life the
orange will save your
life it just will vitamin C and then you
take like a pure vitamin C like this
like a pure form of vitamin C right here
like the vimergy one which isn't all
ascorbic acid it's not ascorbic acid I'm
saying this cuz this is important to
know because people burn holes in their
guts with ascorbic acid they get all the
vitamin C packets straight ascorbic acid
they think they're doing their body good
they're pouring that in stuff here let
me just open up another one of these
packets and pour it in here it's
straight ascorbic
acid it's too harsh on the stomach
lining too harsh to the gastric glands
too harsh to the dadum to the intestinal
lining too harsh and people just eat up
their lining with that ascorbic acid and
that's what people do right and then the
viy right here so if you don't know the
stuff V is in viictor i m is a Mary E RG
y.com you can go to vimergy.com
vimergy that micro C right there is
buffered truly buffered it's not a scorc
acid and it's buffered so that's a whole
game danger right there I can't talk
about it enough and I don't talk about
it enough I should be talking about this
stuff every hour every day because it's
that important for chronic illness it's
that important for the immune system
because hey that's what everybody's
dealing with they're dealing with maxed
out immune systems burnt out immune
systems okay low immune systems damaged
immune systems and the scare and the
fear tactics out there to get people
interested in stuff so they buy their
stuff that scare and fear tactic doesn't
come with help and answers and options
doesn't come with stuff if they say
vitamin C it's ascorbic acid great got a
new problem now you're just you're
ripping up your
lining it's just it's just like this
anyway all right so I'm going to make
this right now okay I'm going to warm up
this water really quick a little bit so
you can warm up your water I got a tea
kettle right there warming up the the
water a little bit okay doing the
medical medium vitamin C shock therapy
right here I have it in the book so I'm
in protocols brain saver protocols do
you have this book
okay vitamin C shock therapy really
important all right so you're going to
mix water I'm going to get the water and
some of the powder if you have the
capsules if you have the the viy
capsules open up the capsules drop them
in take two
capsules open them up drop it into the
water and mix it so you guys doing this
with me do you have your stuff already
and we're going to do it together right
here this is pretty cool
okay grab a little spoon right here if
you guys are okay with that all right
water's
ready so I'm going to drop some water in
here first
there we go I mean you only need a cup
you can do more if you want that's
fine
okay got my
water I am going to drop some vitamin C
in
here all
right just like
that I'm going to put a little bit of
honey in here too remember the glucose
Honey's got its own
powers a little bit of honey in
there okay that's the
glucose vitamin C shock therapy is
really incredible because you're you're
actually bonding that antioxidant into
the glucose of Honey which already has
phytochemical compounds which is a
wonderful thing all on its own let's get
an orange here okay the Orange is
dropping everywhere
you can put a whole Orange in there you
can put a half an orange in there that's
okay so I'm squeezing right
now half an orange I'm going to squeeze
a little bit more this orange here so if
you guys just came on here this is the
medical medium vitamin C shock therapy
man the bugs going around and everything
else out there and everybody's immune
system is always under attack fight or
flight and that's the problem too a lot
of people's immune system immune systems
are under adrenaline attack from all the
fight or flight they got stress they got
all these things going on and that
stress really affects the immune system
but people don't know why or how well
it's affecting it because adrenaline
shocks immune cells adrenaline from
stress so it hits the immune system so
I'm going to stir this
up okay repeat this every two hours
every two waking
hours ask your doctor what's right for
you ask your doctor if you can do the
vitamin C shock
therapy that's what I would do go to
your doctor go to your doctor today call
them up give them a call call the office
hello Dr job's office how can I help you
yeah can you ask him if I can do the
medical medium vitamin C shock therapy
uh hold
on okay okay you know what happens is
the vitamin C shock therapies you can do
it in different ways
look when any anything that's immune
system related okay I tell family and
friends
UTI kidney infections bladder infections
okay boom sore throats you don't feel
good earaches different things happening
you think you're getting some congestion
maybe starting a cough maybe you're
starting a flu maybe you're starting SE
maybe you got something else going on
right maybe you just feel like you're
run down maybe you've been doing a lot
not sleeping as much not taking care of
yourself because you can't because
you're working really hard something I
am guilty of very very
guilty I'm guilty of the crime of
working a lot of hours trying to get
these books done and everything else and
not getting enough
sleep so this is something that that is
is just really powerful that for that
how is hot water is it hot water it's
warm water you can do it in hot I like
warm water for this okay so how hot is
the water is the question mark on IG I
just saw it's not that hot watch you
don't even need to blow on
it little edgy but it's not hot you can
definitely do that it's like the perfect
temperature right
there so that is the medical me and vit
vitamin C shock
therapy so sh so I'm going to read a
little bit of this too you don't want to
Scorch it you don't want it boiling you
don't want to put boiling water in there
you
don't
so um I'm almost out of this one I've
really knocked it I've knocked it down
I'm just saying pretty much there isn't
much left at the bottom of there Janine
says does the powder have stronger
powers than the micro C tablets you can
do the micro tablets they're also really
powerful too it's okay this one right
here has a little bit added things for
skin keep that in mind right but it's
more convenient that's the key it's more
convenient I love the the capsules I
take them all the time I'll take eight
capsules so when I do the vitamin C
capsules the micro C I'll do like eight
capsules boom I want to get vitamin C in
me I do I want my skin looking good I
don't want my skin to fall apart I don't
want my skin to start getting all like
nasty and stuff I don't and I I want it
to look good I want it to Glow so yeah I
take a lot of vitamin C but I don't take
ascorbic acid I don't take somebody
else's vitamin C I take the vimergy
vitamin C for the Vitamin C shock
therapy powder it's not nice because you
don't have to open up the capsules it's
easy you scoop it you put it in you mix
it up I like it for that reason right
there but of course you can open up the
capsules vitam medical me and vitamin C
shock therapy is set up where you can
just open up the capsules and put it in
there it says that but I use both I do I
do I'll do it this way and pop some
capsules of
course so why does the medical me
vitamin C shock therapy bring healing to
a new
level because it takes specific kind of
glucose you'll find mainly in raw
honey so it's not even just you got one
thing you got the power of the micro se
but when you put it with honey something
happens and that was something Spirit of
compassion taught me all these years so
it's like well I I need to make sure
this gets out there and message this
information when you add that raw honey
or a raw honey to that
antioxidant and that buffer antioxidant
what could happen is another
level so and what you do is you freshly
squeeze the vitamin C from an orange in
here too which is another type of
vitamin C from an orange so what you're
doing is you're doing two kinds of
vitamin C right there vitamin C from
Citrus from the orange coupled with the
micro C from vimergy and you're doing
that with the glucose from the Raw honey
and you have
yourself something that's
incredible I'm reading right here if you
guys don't mind
right you need the right kind of non
ascorbic acid vitamin C non ascorbic
acid vitamin C please know
that so important if you guys know all
this already just hang in there I'm
going to be going to be doing some other
stuff today so hang in there if you're
an expert at this the medical me
information but non ascorbic
acid and to this day you see it every
day out there you see an influence out
there like I'm taking my vitamin C and
it's just straight of Scorpi acid I'm
like you're you're lighting your guts on
fire during the medical medium broadcast
channel I will share the recipes there
after this live on
IG all
right so it drives the vitamin C into
the cell so I want to go into that you
need a sugar to drive a nutrient into a
cell there are billions of dollars of
nutraceutical that were sold through the
last 25 30 years and because people had
a fear of
fruit none of that stuff got driven into
cells even if those neutraceuticals
worked I take vitamin E I take vitamin A
I take a probiotic well that's still I
take well all these nutrients they put
in probiotic now none of them go into
anything I take you know I take this I
take that I take vitamin B I take a b
complex I take methola right it doesn't
go into the cells it doesn't enter it if
you're afraid of something that you need
a special glucose one that's really
bioidentical to our bodies which is like
a glucose from
honey so when you do this vitamin C
shock therapy what you're doing is
you're bringing the vitamin C deeper
into the cells so when you do this every
two hours because you think something's
coming on you think something's wrong
and you're doing this every two hours
you're infusing your cells you're
entering into those cells non ascorbic
acid vitamin C directly into the cells
like that you're mainlining it into the
liver and into the liver cells the liver
has its own immune system
and so that vitamin C is being driven to
those immune cells now immune cells feed
off of vitamin C it is a food for immune
cells immune cells need the vitamin C
they utilize they consume and they need
the vitamin C and so when you put it in
here mix them just like this with the
raw honey and then you're adding in the
orange you're mainlining those nutrients
that vitamin C and in this case a non-
ascorbic acid one directly into your C
that's one of those keys it's a
key to the
engine Fox over there [ __ ] what books
what book is this please the 1w is
reading from
protocols brains saer
protocols bugs don't like vitamin C
toxins don't like vitamin C
free radicals don't like vitamin C
people get filled up with free radicals
free radicals help you oxidize our body
is
oxidizing vitamin C slows down the
oxidizing process it is an antioxidant
that slows down the oxidation process of
our cells dying then if everybody has
all these different toxins in them and
poison poisons those free radicals
oxidize cells faster vitamin C is doing
a job by stopping those cells from
oxidizing faster hence saving your
skin helping to protect your skin
because your skin is a sign that there's
serious oxidation process going on
there's all kinds of things going on too
and you lose that collagen in your skin
by eating collagen and that's what
people do they're eating all this
collagen
it's really sad out there and I see
influencers out there too talking like
you know they're doing raw dairy they're
they're doing raw milk they're doing
like the raw cheese they're doing
they're doing their raw dairy products
and I'm like and they're just like
talking about collagen and I'm
like no no you're not going to get any
collagen from that but you better be
taking a vitamin C and if you take an
ascorbic acid vitamin C over time you're
just going to start giving your
intestine and your lining to your
stomach and dadum with lash when you
give it Whiplash it starts to get
sensitive so what happens with the
scorpicol acid it can up that game for
those sensitivities because that scorc
acid is so acidic it's like battery
acid on the intestinal track it's
battery acid on the Linings it's battery
acid on the dadum the stomach lining the
esophagus escorp acid becomes like
battery acid on the
esophagus and so they're doing all this
ascorbic acid every day and they think
they're doing their body good when
they're putting practically what feels
like battery acid on their Linings and
then their nerves are on those Linings
inside those Linings their vagus nerves
are
inside those Linings and once those
Vegas nerves the bell rings too much the
bell rings once once the bell rings too
much with those Vegas
nerves then boom I don't know what I'm
sensitive to I don't know what food I'm
sensitive to nothing's digesting I don't
feel good everything kind of
hurts and people are like lost let me go
to the next food allergy doctor let me
get you know let me get an all cat let
me get this let me get that and they're
all just going to these you know these
food allergy Specialists it's like oh
you're allergic to this you're allergic
to fennel you're like
you know you ever look at those lists
did you guys ever did you ever go
through that any of you ever gone
through that you get this list this long
from from an allergist doctor right of
some kind alternative allergist doctor
whatever and you get this list this long
and it's crap on there right you're
allergic to fenel bulb fenel fenel Leaf
you're allergic to
Yaro you're allergic to chamomile you're
allergic to every
fruit you're not allergic to eggs you're
allergic did you see that how many
people have those where you're like
allergic to cantro you're allergic to
parsley you're allergic to dragon fruit
some some weird you know you're allergic
to and you'll see it you're allergic to
peanut butter fruit you're
allergic yeah you're allergic to honey
you're allergic to maple
syrup my God it's a brain screw yes
you've been through that yes you been
through that too yes when I did an
allergy test yes
exactly and so you got nowhere to go
what do I eat you can eat raw cheese
okay great thank you Doctor that's so
great I'm scared to death of every
single fruit and vegetable in the fruit
and vegetable Kingdom but but I can eat
meat great and raw dairy
wonderful and meanwhile they're
suffering they're struggling they don't
feel well they got all these symptoms
and conditions great maybe I can eat ve
you know and this what happens people
are like eating ve now the only thing
they're eating is
VE you're allergic to this fish but you
can have this fish it's the stupidest
thing I've ever seen and it always has
been the stupidest thing I've ever seen
and it's another musical cheer game
right musical chair game yeah the
allergy test right Tara
terat over there in IG I think so it's
crazy how it works and that's what
people go through and the same thing
back to scorc acid it lights the nerves
on fire over time people get hypers
sensitive it becomes an acidy burning
mechanism that makes nerve sensitive so
when you're doing ascorbic acid this is
not ascorbic acid it's non ascorbic when
you're doing ascorbic acid your Vegas
nerves get hypers
sensitive they can because the Linings
of your intestine the lining of your
dadum your
stomach gets lit up from what feels like
that battery acid
so different because I can say that 20
times and somebody will still just go
and like get a vitamin C out there and
they don't know it it's like
huh and you know what's a trick out
there now too there's some ascorbic acid
vitamin C's that say buffer it's a
Scorpi acid but it's buffered so they
try to throw something in there to mix
with these Scorpi acid to buffer it it's
still the same it's a Scorpi acid it's
still going to be a fire pit in the gut
and that is not a scor Bic so medical
medium vitamin C shock
therapy right here there's a couple of
little pieces of orange in
there that's so good put the raw honey
in there now remember every two hours
every two waking hours if you think
something's going on you think
something's wrong and if you don't have
anything going
on what you do is you do one of these a
day or two of these a day
but ask your doctor what's right for you
that's what I would do take the book to
the doctor ask your doctor can I do the
medical Bei and vitamin C shock therapy
see what your doctor says that's
all and do what your doctor tells you
all right if you
want all right so that's that let's go
into um let's do the nerve gut acid
stabilizer I'm going to move the micro
over and if you guys want to know vimer
V is inv Victor i m is the Mary E RG y
them.com okay you guys know I endorse
these guys and you know why cuz where
can you get that you can't sorry you
can't get micro anywhere it just doesn't
exist and people got broken broken
immune systems nobody gets it vimergy is
now available in the EU
vi.
vi. and that can help a lot of people
because vimergy is now out there in the
EU
amazing game changer for the people in
the
EU
EU all
right
let's let's look for that
asset stabilizer right
there see where it is looking looking
looking whoa burnout stabilizer that's a
good one to so I'm in the book right
now cuz I want to read about
[Music]
it you know I love these you guys do the
brain shot
therapies you ever get a chance to do
these
[Music]
I just love looking at these the craving
shifter anger shifter guilt and shame
shifter so many people are riddled in
guilt and shouldn't be riddled in guilt
they think everything is their fault
they think every problem that happens is
because they they you know created it a
lot of people believe they created their
problems all their problems it's all
because they're a bad person and that's
sad all on its
own so the nerve gut asset stabilizer is
really easy to make you just need a
juice
I got the parsley right here okay if
you're looking to strengthen your Vagas
nerves how about that how many people
need to strengthen their Vagas nerves
yeah exactly you're dealing with gastric
spasms flatulence chronic gastritis
remember remember I think Lauren you
actually said it fixed your gastritis
mild acid reflux or digestive
disturbances for acute acid reflux
relief you can see the aloe vera shock
therapy which is really cool if you feel
like your food is not digesting breaking
down or assimilating so if you're
somebody that feels like it's just not
breaking down it's not assimilating if
you're struggling like
that if you feel like you have poor
nutrient absorption that's another one
too nutrient absorption like Poe
malabsorption right people are all
screaming that these days it's amazing
go on a carnivore diet just eat meat but
yeah you'll be malabsorption if you do
something else out
there you've been told you have a
microbiome or gut microf Flora condition
or problem have you been told about that
like you got a microbiome issue oh it's
your microbiome the problem is now with
alternative doctors too and a lot of
people out there is they'll just be like
all like microbiome right that's their
whole thing you go there you can have
like Epstein bar it could be eating your
thyroid to [ __ ] burrowing holes in your
thyroid you can
be you can be sitting there with
strep in your urethra you can have shrep
in your kidneys you can go to like these
alternative doctors sometimes or
whatever conventional doctor alternative
doctor you can go to a doctor and you
can have like shingles breaking out
everywhere and they'll just be like if
they're a microbiome doctor it's just
everything's microbiome it's like boom
microb you can go there with vertigo
where you're you can't you like you're
having this bed spins and you're
vomiting every day and you you walk into
a doctor that just specializes in
microbiome because that's what they do
it's all going to be like your
microbiome doctor I got I'm dizzy I got
balance issues I've been dealing with
vertigo for two years now and I don't
know why I vomit every now and then
because I can't drive and I get sick
it's your
microbiome here a microbiome Specialists
but if that's Doctor you have listen you
know listen to your doctor of course the
point is though and ask your doctor if
this is okay if you're somebody that's
told you got a microbiome problem or
microf Flora
condition nerve gut acid stabilizer ask
your
doctor if you feel like your blood is
toxic and your blood right it feels
toxic or you feel toxic this is the
nerve gut acid stabilizer if you feel
that your liver and lymph are toxic I
know everybody told that their lymphatic
system is toxic everybody's told that
right but the sad part is they're not
fixing the liver if the liver's not
fixed then all that [ __ ] gets dumped
into the lymphatic right so here you are
you got a dirty liver but everybody's
like working on your lymphatic system
it's like dirty liver but they're all
trying to like you know squeeze your
lymphatic system you're getting all the
lymphatic work done right the drainage
you're you're taking things thinking
it's helping your lymphatic system
everybody's like take this take that
and you're doing it and the meanwhile
you got a liver problem no one realizes
nobody knows that we have to clean up
that underlying fatty liver because if
we don't clean up that underlying fatty
liver your lymphatic system is going to
be dirty from here to Kingdom Come it's
going to be dirty it just is so yeah you
can spend the next $100,000 in the next
10 years doing lymphatic work or you can
fix your
liver all right over on IG
good um thought Garden says good
question how do you know if you
need to strengthen your vagus nerve how
do you know Tremors ticks
spasms digestion you feel like your
digestion is is shot or you're not
digesting food whatsoever so you feel
funny there different weird experiences
with you know tightness of the chest
tightness of the throat anxiety
depression these are just some some some
things I mean the list can go on and on
and on and
on and you can
strengthen the list goes on and you
can't strengthen the Vegas nerves with
exercises that is I want you exercising
but you're not strengthening the Vagas
nerves with exercises that I just blow
the roof off of that one there are no
such thing as a Vegas nerve exercise I'm
very sorry but there isn't if a Vegas
nerve is
inflamed and you want to exercise your
Vegas nerves they will get
worse it's why people can't exercise
they get chronically sick because your
Vegas nerves are inflamed and if you try
to exercise a Vegas nerve you're screwed
you're going to be in bed
longer you don't want to jab at your
Vegas nerves in any way shape or form
form or try to pull any crazy man-made
thought up exercises to Vegas nerves
that people don't even know where
they're even situated
perfectly in fact people called it Vegas
nerve but there's
two so it's like let me go get my Vegas
nerves exercised let me pull all these
exercises on my Vegas nerve oh the Vegas
nerve expert didn't even know there's
two Vegas
nerves I mean I can't can't even I can't
even I can't even I can't I can't read
brain saver I have a whole section on
the Vegas nerves so read the Brain saer
book to learn about the Vegas nerves
strengthen the Vegas nerves with
cleaning out and killing what's
inflaming the Vegas nerves that's how
you strengthen them you have to kill the
pathogens that are hurting your Vegas
nerves and then you got to know what to
take to rebuild your Vegas nerves that's
how you k your Vegas nerves Vegas nerve
exercises do not work if you're getting
improvements then you never had a Vegas
nerve problem you had some other problem
where exercise is helping you if you're
if you're improving from somebody's
Vagas nerve exercise that means whatever
exercise you're
doing is good for you in other ways
improving other problems that aren't
Vegas nerve related because when you
have true Vegas nerve problems you can't
play with them you can't toy with them
you can't mess with them they will get
worse aggravated they will light on fire
and your butt is going to be in trouble
and that's what happens every day out
there it's why somebody with chronic
fatigue syndrome and neurological
fatigue who's got all kinds of different
body symptoms starts doing something
like Vegas nerve exercises they end up
seizuring practically they end up
shutting down totally tired and have to
lay down there's a reason and another
thing too there's a reason why they
can't exercise do you you don't think
that the chronic leil wouldn't go go
into a gym and exercise 4 hours a
day like people who haven't experienced
a health problem yet and they're 22
years old you don't think a 40-year-old
who's suffering from chronic illness
every day neurological problems you
don't think the
40-year-old doesn't want to get into the
gym and work
out and not be sick in bed you don't
think that you you don't think they want
to get into a gym and work out they
can't get into a gym and work out
because they're struggling with all
kinds of neurological problems cranial
problems Vegas there of issues they're
struggling where you can't exercise it
all starts falling apart it's not you
have to go slow you have to you have to
do you know you have to do a little bit
at a little bit while you're healing the
nervous system and healing Kim Miller
says exercise would put me in a panic
when my Vegas nerves were at their worst
exactly can you imagine your Vegas
nerves at the worst and you're doing
Vegas nerve
exercises o I can imagine I've seen a
lot of people do it I've seen a lot of
people try it and
woo
exactly I get it you see 22y olds 22y 24
year olds exercising in the gym they're
doing two hours they never experienced
anything yet they may down the road when
they contract 10 more bugs and then when
they do then they'll be sick and then
yeah all right let's get some let's get
some of this going
here all right
somebody shut me
up all right Details Matter put it that
way the details matter they
do I'm not going to strain this you can
strain it and you don't have to strain
it I'm going to make this real thick
real real real thick okay that's what
I'm going to do make this stuff
thick so let's get some parsley in here
nerve gut acid stabilizer one of my
favorite Bulletin news flash Cafe
Gratitude in
La collaboration with medical
medium recipes are on their menu you can
get them right now order order them
online pick them up go into the
restaurant beautiful restaurants
beautiful restaurants Cafe Gratitude
gorgeous
restaurants Tammy yes I've noticed a
trend in the last year of ways to
stimulate the Vegas herbs as if they
want to be stimulated when they are
already fired up when they are already
effed up in a lot of people
man every last bit of juice gets
extracted out of this with these juicers
the mm900 I'm using right now for this I
mean this stuff is coming out
powder I see people throwing away so
much money with those those different
juicers out there now oh my God they're
throwing away so much produce they have
to use twice as much produce I guess you
know if you're rich
you can do that but oh my
God all right so I'm making a parsley
shot this juicer is on sale right now
for
$219 at a mega
juicers me come
on it's
insane all
right how are you going to fix your
Vegas neres if exactly you're
aggravating them because they're
inflamed oh my God that whole Vegas and
by the way that Vegas nerve thing took
off because of the medical medium
information in
books and so people just ran with it
they became Vegas nerve experts this
juicer is on sale for $290 right now
link is in the bio I endorse this juicer
cuz it saves you money how
insane running some beautiful parsley
through
here
yep people always ask me and I never
barely ever even talk
about talk about
it I mean I got lot going on there's a
lot of stuff
happening haven't had a
chance I'm making two shots purposely
because I want two shots for
myself so if you guys don't mind I might
even might even be making three shots or
four
shots Amy over there on YouTube no sound
coming from on Instagram yeah know I
know
they yeah I
know they suppress the uh live
today it's glitched please DM us so we
can report it to Instagram and have them
fix it
okay
amazing I'm just I'm just really excited
you know really really
excited first of all that is like air
dry never seen anything like that from
another juicer out
there the amount of money you save it's
ridiculous
unbelievable all right I'm so excited
about this Cafe Gratitude thing Cafe
Gratitude collaboration medical medium I
can't even tell
you all right this is one one strong
shot right there whoa okay nerve gut
acid stabilizer right there there's one
shot whoa I made a lot of shots now um
I'm really psyched look at that no wait
three I think it's three shots I me
whoa look at
that nice you guys don't worry I'm still
here and I think I got room for almost
one more right there that might be four
shots
there they are
there does a nerve G asset stabilizer
right here out of
protocols mock
it mock it evil
doers Lifesaver Game
Changer Game
Changer I think what's happening to is
you know you have all these tools
they're all here from s so but people in
the medical Community they they haven't
tried them yet they've only tried like
one thing or two things right they may
be a dabbler so what so what just glad
they're here but they don't know how far
they can go how far they can go they
don't they
don't so we're talking about today I'm
going to take a shot pretty
soon nice talking about scared to death
just a little recap on that back to that
the trend is scare the crap out of
people scare them into following you so
you can buy their [ __ ] not scare them to
fix their
problems not scare them to fix their
problem scare them to get more listens
and more views and more likes scare the
hell out of them then sell them your
same old crap like colostrum and junk
and gar and collagen and whatever else
they're going to do or a
program but
use the old the Earth's coming to an
end pesticides all over the
planet this and this is happening I mean
I can talk about it all day right for
air fresheners now like you know what I
mean oh my God I got ostracized I got
totally totally mocked and ridiculed for
talking about air fresheners just four
and a half years ago just four and a
half years ago I was talking about him
way before then I put him in the books
but I mean I I remember doing a live and
talking about it and people were
freaking there were these people that
just woke up one day and got into the
health movement started their health
feeds and they're just like why is he
talking about air
fresheners but the point is you guys if
you're going to if you're going to scare
people to death if you're going to scare
the crap out of them and tell them that
their children are in danger they're in
danger D look out for this this is
happening then you better offer
solutions that
work that's what this is about okay and
medical medium information already told
everybody about all this stuff that's
out there and what we got to worry about
but it's the tools Bray Wilkerson over
there nerve gut acid stabilizer stopped
my anxiety attacks they were so
miserable felt like I was
dying unbelievable
for
warning just want to let everybody
know that ain't no
joke you got to hold your breath you got
to hold your nose sometimes with that
parle so strong over there in IG the
voice says exactly these brain shots
take healing to the next level I've
never experienced
healing my healing move forward as fast
as the brain
shots yeah I you know what I can't take
this shot all one shot but I guess I'll
Just
sh
bartender give
me a mother new one
man give me a new
one give me another Arena Park says I
love this brain shot it is so simple and
so healing I make I make several shots
and drink them at once my gut is doing
extremely well on
it what it does for the body in so many
ways I'm telling you right here this is
an
herb this isn't a leafy green this is a
leafy green herb medical medium
information lra 144 Anthony I did nerve
gut acid stabilizer strengthen me for my
light in LA
tomorrow Jess elain just made it Jess oh
your flight your flight T LA
tomorrow Jess I know I said this before
I'll say it again it was an honor
meeting you at the meet and greet atan
all right I'm send another one
down
bartender give me another
you you you guys you guys these are that
potent
right like they're that potent right
like are you that like you get hit with
it like I get hit with
it oh my
God I got a third one and I'm going to
take the
leftover oh my God I might I pretty much
got a fourth
one dang
nand over there on YouTube says Anthony
the messages at telegram make me get out
of bed forever thank you love love okay
listen go to my telegram if you can
subscribe to my telegram I'm leaving
messages I'm leaving them late at night
but I'm leaving them every single
day from above information
yes I burp too I'm a I'm a human being
I'm
leave nerve gut assd stabilizer I'm
sitting down I'm leaving
information from above s so's with me
especially in that moment because I'm
not doing 20 other things but so's you
know seeing that I'm making things get
in the way because I'm doing 20 things
CU I want to do 20 things but s so's is
with me when I leave those
telegrams okay oh my god do a
third bartender give me another
one bargender
fourth one going down
why did that shot feel like bigger than
the other shot I think it's still just a
O but that one was
huge I don't know why anyway you guys
just did four shots of the nerve gut
acid
stabilizer use it if you have body odor
and you're confused by it more
noticeably than other situations where
you actually notice it body odor
if you're dealing with chronic nausea or
chronic bloating use the nerve gut acid
stabilizer if you're trying to repair
acidic body systems and you want to make
your body systems more alkaline uh-huh
uh-huh
uh-huh what's the difference between
I'll give you a quiz what's the
difference between am I getting drunk on
these what's the difference
between this right here here the nerve
gut acid stabilizer for getting you
alkaline or alkaline ionizer water
machines the difference is the alkaline
ionizer water machines I don't care what
brand it is leeches
Metals uh-huh uh-huh that's right
because the plates that have electricity
to them end up corroding over time you
don't see it at first but it's corroding
but it happens all the time when you're
using those machines so you think you're
getting alkaline with alkaline water and
you're filling yourself with free
radicals filling yourself up with free
radicals that's the difference between
that getting you alkaline and that
poisoning
you all right you guys
amazing great live good to see you guys
one last time on Cafe Gratitude medical
medium collaboration it is a very
special
special time in history Cafe Gratitude
is a legendary restaurant beautiful
restaurant too just gorgeous beautiful
restaurant so amazing and their food is
balls to the wall now they have medical
medium
dishes I can't wait to see you guys on
21st 22nd 23rd 24th popup sold out popup
dinners if you go to Cafe Gratitude and
experience the medical medium dishes on
the menu please share your experience
and tag at medal medium in the stories
or post so we can see them
hashtag and so forth
guys
amazing and uh I'll see you
soon I'm going to wash that
down with the medical medium vitamin C
shock
therapy and of course the best vitaminc
there is hands down that's out there I
don't care what anybody says I know it's
the best I'll post these recipes in the
medical medium inside scoop on
Instagram and listen out for my telegram
messages
mhm and know that I care you guys are
amazing