we're talking about adrenaline we're
talking about adrenalized emotions do
you ever get adrenaline rush
you're here you got the adrenaline
moving you're shaking you feel it you
feel it adrenaline right
maybe it's just like something could be
anything that happens anything that
happens and it's like your adrenaline's
gone
it's going
you get a phone call as soon as you feel
your adrenaline going something's
happening and you feel your adrenaline
going right the whole bit you got to
talk about adrenalized emotions is what
we're going to talk about which is
actually kind of really a good topic
good cool topic
gonna talk about it right here in brain
saver the brain saver boss oh my God
where have they been the brain saver
books
anyway okay recipe
boom right there
got a recipe right there it's Asian
inspired potato skillet
by the way have you made this one yet
because I have I'm gonna going to
attempt to make it again I got all my
stuff right there what do I have I got
the
uh I got the sugar snaps I got the
shiitake mushroom I got the yellow onion
I got the ginger I got the limes I got
the cilantro out of the garden it's a
bunch of things here that are out of the
garden right the
onions are out of the garden
the Cilantro's out of the garden these
killer peppers are out of the garden
which is cool awesome
all right you guys are talking about
adrenalized emotions we're making some
food let me get this on so I'm gonna
have this like medium Heat
right
Yeah medium heat because that's going to
get hot
let's chop up some onions really quick
if you guys don't mind good to see you
guys glad you're coming on
but I I don't think I've done a cooking
show in a really long time I just wanna
I don't know why I feel like I need to
say that
but
I really haven't done a cooking show I
feel the adrenaline now from doing a
cooking show I could feel it now
adrenalized emotions over doing a
cooking show
seriously though a lot of people they
get jacked up they're like really do
right
there
going through something some kind of
hardship some kind of loss anything like
that they're going through a tough time
they're going through something where
and nobody understands unless they've
gone through it
nobody gets it unless they've gone
through it right
did you ever tell a friend like hey man
I'm going through a lot of right
now a lot
a lot
and they're just like what are you going
through I'm like yeah I'm going through
all kinds of stuff and they're like they
don't really get it did you ever notice
that something that you're going through
something that's happening in your life
and they don't get it somebody doesn't
get it
because they haven't experienced it
themselves you see that's a big deal
right there a lot of people work on
referencing
you can see somebody run out of a built
burning building right they run onto
they run out of burning building and
they run across the street they get hit
by a truck at the same time
and
it'd be like hey hey whoa whoa that guy
ran a burning building whoa he just got
run over
but yet you talk to the guy later on in
the hospital and you're like hey you
okay they're like you wouldn't believe
it that was them I can't even tell you
and you can't really you can't reference
it unless it happened to you A lot of
people do that
they just don't know what you're going
through with all your chronic illness
your chronic illness symptoms all your
doctor visits everything they don't know
what you've gone through
right all the different things that
you struggle with they don't know
what it's like unless they've
experienced it themselves and even then
it still might not be the same thing so
I'm chopping up some onions I'm throwing
a yellow onion here I'm throwing in the
pan
oh
let's get this in here
all right aw's cooking show right
we'll see if I can throw some things in
the air and not drop them this time drop
them on the ground
so I'm doing this I even have
for the close-ups on the board
that's all right
we'll make do what we got
so many event in there I'm also going to
get two cloves of garlic in here too
don't pop your finger off whatever you
do be very careful don't there's no
rushing
you don't have to rush when you're
chopping
right it's okay you don't have to rush
it's no rush
get a little bit of garlic a leak in
here you see that guys if you just came
on here making a recipe out of the book
Brain saver books making a recipe out of
there if you just got on here that's the
infamous protocols book that's saving
people's lives around the world right
now
people are digging the protocols book
you've got to check it out if you don't
have it
anyway there it is the recipe we're
making right there Asian inspired potato
Skillet
I can't get enough of potato dishes
potato Skillets anything potato you
can't get enough of it
they just come out so darn good now I
got all kinds of killer stuff right here
so I got the potatoes but they're
steamed they're steamed you don't have
to use a steamed potato you can just you
can slice it you know hard and crunchy
potato when you throw it in the pan or
I'll already hear the heat kicking in
right there I hear the onions starting
to sizzle
remember
right facing out the blade facing out if
you're ever going to do the garlic trick
I've watched a lot of people screw up
I've watched people that have gone to
all kinds of Chef schools and everything
and they do it this way right there they
do it with the blade facing towards them
you don't want to do that you don't want
to do the garlic crushing trick like you
see this right here because the knife
flips up real easy and I've seen a dude
go like that
you know what I mean like that and like
that you don't want to ever do that you
want to flip it that way it says it's
not going to flip up as easy going that
way so when you do the garlic trip
you don't want to do it that way see one
thing
see what I'm saying
I got a friend that says it every second
see what I'm saying I go yeah I see what
you're saying you know you see what I
mean see what I'm saying you know what I
mean like oh I know what you mean
that's all right
and then two seconds later he'll go see
what I'm saying look like oh my God
I see what you're saying
you know what I mean you guys all right
I'm gonna chop up this garlic right here
if you guys don't mind
a little chopping action right here
okay so I'm putting a couple I'm gonna
finely slice them
not gonna give them a super chop finely
slice
nice all right
let's go we're gonna pop a little bit of
hot pepper flakes in here if you guys
don't mind I'm gonna see if I can show
you right there that's what I'll do
I'll do it this way if you guys don't
mind good to see you we're making a
little bit of food something that came
out of brain saver brain saver books by
the way
the brain saver books
helping a lot of people right now around
the world the results are coming in
everywhere it's
unbelievable okay
I'm gonna put a little bit of this hot
pepper in this dish right here if you
guys don't mind
this is a hot pepper
I'm saying that because remind yourself
when you're playing with hot peppers
you're busy you got company and you're
just I'm just gonna put a little bit in
here you got company
you're not thinking you're like yeah
yeah oh yeah yeah exactly hey no sit
down over there I'll bring a drink in a
minute oh yeah let me rub that hot
pepper in my eye because I'm not
thinking ah
you run out
I'm gonna rinse my hand off
because I will rub my eye
all right
I'm gonna do some shiitake mushroom
I'm gonna do some uh
we're gonna do some shrooms man
some shrooms all right you got about
like I don't know we're gonna do about
one and a half cups of stocky
we're gonna thinly slice them
that's what we're gonna do
shrooms here thinly slice them
it's up to you if you want the stem on
there or not
totally up to you
okay
you can keep the stem on
you can take the stem off
I'm going to keep the stem I'm going to
put it in there
stems a little bitter got a little
better Edge to it but I can't help it
I like I like my mushrooms man
dude
are you looking at this guy you see that
I don't know if that's a mushrooms
kicking in man or that's really like
is that Santa Claus man
is it Christmas
I see the reindeer in front of them
King Nora says you saved my daughter's
life from autism I owe you my life and
my daughter's life
I love you more than you could imagine
on YouTube thank you seriously
you're gonna get me choked up
I can't tell you what that means to me
loss for loss for words over here
actually
Trista Marie Trista Marie oh my God dot
dot dot you are making my day I love you
and my heart has been with you thank you
so much bless your heart bless your
heart
I'm popping some mushrooms in here if
you guys don't mind
suicide man
what shrooms are those
Uma Cali
I'm a Cali good to see you
it's been a long time since I said Uma
what are you up to
it's been a long time
let's get the pan going a little bit can
you guys see this right here
if you guys just got here we're making a
dish out of brain saver do you have the
brain saver books I promise you this you
won't be disappointed when you check out
the brains here when you crack open the
brain saver books you're just gonna be
like
are you kidding this is insane
the amount of information in there is
just
it's just
beyond beyond
all right so we got some different stuff
here let's see what's next what's next
we'll put something else in here just
reading comments as we go along too
how are you cooking without olive oil
yeah you don't need to cook with olive
oil you just don't
you don't have to drown it in oil
olive oil
that's a great oil
it's not a bad oil at all
but you don't need to it's a ceramic pan
ceramic pan but you don't need to drown
everything in oil guys I'm going to read
out of one of the books in a little bit
and just getting this going I'm going to
read a little bit about adrenaline
adrenalized emotions
now the potatoes are steamed so you
don't have to add them in quite yet you
could wait a little bit cook down some
of the other stuff
so maybe we can go with uh
to put a little bit of these false
flakes in here got some dull slicks
nice
I love I love dogs love it Atlantic
way to go
I'm gonna put in a cup of water
you can do healing broth because that's
actually what it calls for it calls for
healing broth alternative is water
that's the alternative so I popped that
in here it's great I'm going to crank up
the heat just a little bit
I'm gonna get this nice and going all
right let's start chopping up some other
stuff maybe we'll go with
um
some of these sugar snaps you guys love
sugar snaps
it's one of my favorite sugar snaps God
they're insane
so good good thinly slice them
you can do it this way
you can put them in whole if you really
like
right get some of these in here
a lot of people react differently to a
situation that's happening in their life
some people their adrenaline isn't
really happening in the moment as
something is happening meaning something
like
challenging in the moment right and then
some people would hit some later
right before they go to bed
and their mind is racing
they're they feel like their heart is
racing right
I always check my heart beat right here
that's what I always do
foreign
kind of gets you connected to the inner
workings
even when nothing is going on right no
adrenaline at all is happening
let's get some more of these sugar snaps
in really quick
I think I'm gonna put a few more in here
this is cooking up nice
this dish is actually going to be done
pretty soon this isn't going to take so
long how easy does it get
think about it
you get company and you're like worked
on it all day long all day
really
you don't need to
I might put in
actually oh that's looking good
let's see the mushrooms in here you'll
see the sugar snap peas checked it out
you guys you see the onions in here
onions are from my garden you all see
some hot pepper I threw in here too
it's a recipe you can use uncooked
potatoes remember that you don't have to
use steamed potatoes I'm using steamed
potatoes in this one just letting you
guys know giving you the heads up on
that you don't have to use
a steamed potato you can use a raw
potato right uncooked potatoes nothing
wrong with that I'm gonna pop a couple
more of these in here
you can just chop a four at a time just
like this
Swatch your fingers
it's coming together
go with a few more
come together right now
little beetles going on
all right
I might read pretty soon
let's just see what else there is to do
thank you
I turned up the heat a little bit more
this thing's gonna crank
did I put ginger in this yet I think
that's at the end
for the sauce
we'll do some lime and ginger sauce at
the end a little maple syrup the whole
bit I think potatoes are next
just want to get that water kind of out
mushrooms will actually make a lot more
moisture in your pan in your plate in
your you know your pots and all that
so mushrooms will do it it's normal
and simmer with the lid on I'm not going
to simmer with the lid on in this one
I'm just going to let it do its thing
um
but we're just about there let me let me
slice up some potatoes here
usually I do
so I'm slicing these up
just like this
okay I'm gonna make these nice slices
once again this is a steamed potato
I don't want it to crumble I want these
like to be just like this if I make them
too thin they're gonna fall apart
okay
there we go
I'm gonna keep this little end in there
actually I'll take a little lens move
the little ends out
let me just get these ready why that's
cooking along
taking these little here we go
this is a russet I really like russets
the potato police are always on my ass
Nightshade Nightshade medical medium
stupid he doesn't know anything about
health it's a nightshade
foreign
and then fear and Chaos ensues right
you'll hear people they'll say I can't
eat a potato my whole body just flares
up overnight
you sure it wasn't all the bad oil and
cheese and sour cream and whatever
or you sure it wasn't the potato chips
you ate
was it those
come on now fly on the wall
if I can only be a fly on the wall
that can only be a fly on the wall
so many things you'll see
that people just aren't aware of but so
many things you'll see when you're a fly
on the wall
you'll see a lot of crap going down
be like what is that person doing oh my
God what
no wonder
what happened was
they had a baked potato at the fast food
restaurant
sour cream
and dangerous chemicals laced all over
it
and some crazy canola oil worse
something else even worse and that's bad
all right so we're cutting these in nice
slices right here
I'm still gonna eat these ends because I
know that the food police might be out
there and I I know I'm gonna get shamed
see these little guys right here right
but believe me um
those are great
hmm
that's so good
so
this actually helps to stabilize
adrenals believe it or not this dish
it's so good
foreign
it's a grounding dish it really is I'm
gonna throw potatoes in here any minute
I'm just gonna get enough of them
you guys don't mind
there we go
how is everybody doing
that's what I'd like to know
all right here we go
let's get these in
the skillet
now they're going to stick to each other
right
I'm gonna pop these in right here now
listen raw potato is the way to go
probably I'm using steamed tonight by
the way Saturday night
I thought I would pop on
I had to make myself some dinner anyway
I figured hey look let's do it together
I'm going to be careful with these a
little bit because these are the steamed
ones so I'm going to be uh pretty gentle
with these
let's just get some
Steam and some heat through there
good to see you guys
hello glad to see you guys as well
all right let's get these
nice and hot
I'm gonna make a hot sauce if you guys
don't mind we're gonna read a little bit
in a little while if you guys got on
here I'm not just going to be cooking hi
mattress service
I am also going to read out of brain
saver for free
I'm not going to create a course or a
program and charge you seven thousand
nine hundred dollars for even though
there's nothing wrong with that out
there anybody can do what they want I'm
not just dissing it
I'm just saying I'm gonna read for free
I'm gonna pop a few more of these in
here
I am at your disposal
I don't know why that makes me laugh
for some reason it does
Charlotte from YouTube adrenals
what if the stomach has been too
scorched by adrenaline to tolerate
adrenal brain shots celery juice most
solid foods or supplements completely
understand
then it's baby steps it's baby steps
it's baby steps
check out the monocleanse check out
cleanse to heal take the book to your
doctor after your doctor what's right
for you
ask your doctor what's right for you
but cleanse the heel has the mono
cleanses in there man
they're just incredible just incredible
let's make a sauce while this is cooking
up
okay let me get a little bit of a sauce
Bowl
foreign
did I say we're live
wait cut the video cut the video we have
to edit that out
ew spilled water on them emergency let's
edit it out so nobody sees it
we don't do that here
sharonelle says which book is the recipe
in
protocols insane book an insane book
I mean look I kind of just
my way-hearted about it and stuff right
I pretend it's no big deal
but what's in this book is just
it's unmatched
seriously these are the greatest books
in all health history
mark my words you read them you'll know
what they offer is more than just
recipes but the recipes are insanely
incredible all on its own
foreign
gone all right
let's whisk up some type of sauce
two tablespoons
of fresh lime juice
I hear some Canadian geese in the
background
powerful meditation right there
hearing the geese fly over
from when it starts
as they're traveling closer
and they're getting closer
the geese right it's not a great
imitation of some geese I'll have to
practice and I will later on believe it
believe me I actually will and the geese
are flying closer closer and then
they're leaving and you've got to tune
in you have to tune in as the geese are
leaving right
and even if you don't catch them with
your eyes
you just
listen until they go out of range
completely
talking about rewiring the brand that's
a great one right there
nobody knows that one
but that's what happens on these lives
stuff will come from Spirit of
compassion
it's mind-blowing
medical medium can you guide me to what
book
has info on gastroparesis
check out the monocleanse and cleanse
the heel cleanse to heal and brain saver
cleanse the heel and brain saver let's
squeeze some lime juice here
did I bring the heat down I did
it's good to see you guys
I'm just squeezing some lime juice it's
part of the sauce the secret sauce
the secret sauce anytime I go eat at a
friend's house and they say it's a
secret sauce I'm like
I'm like dude
dude I don't like that because I don't
know what your secret sauce is
unless I really try to spy or ask SOC or
something and I'm not in the mood to do
that when I'm like having a night out
for the moment which is one in a zillion
times right one in zillion years and if
a friend's like
is my secret sauce I'm like like what
what did you what crap did you put in
here
[Music]
I don't trust I don't trust
some people's secret sauces do you
sure I'll have that sure that's great uh
that's oh yeah a little sour a little
sweet
salty a little oily
yeah that's good can you tell me every
single thing that's in there because
I want to know
[Music]
and don't hold any of it out
secret sauce
like who knows
sure it's just mayonnaise
hey Debbie don't worry it's mayonnaise
it's um Worcestershire sauce it's uh
wow I love lime juice you guys
all right what else is going in there
maple syrup two tablespoons of maple
syrup
um
maple syrup
love the smell of maple syrup
two tablespoons of maple syrup let's get
that in there
I think I got maple syrup on my nose
producers edit it out aw got maple syrup
on his nose you know let's get him ready
again no we do it live we don't do that
all right
get a fork
two tablespoons of tomato paste
nice
that's what you want to hear right there
best sound ever if you're gonna have
something like out of a jar
best sound ever I'm trained
trained to hear that sound because if it
sounds like this
wait did I hear the pop is it did it pop
all right you guys we're gonna be
reading in a little bit just bear with
me if you can two tablespoons right here
some tomato paste nice
nice
I'm excited about that bam
all right right
get at these freshly grated Ginger
get a little piece
some strong stuff a lot of people they
don't like it
a lot of people do like it
I peel off the Skins when I'm making
recipes a lot of times right if I'm
juicing the ginger I'll leave the skin
on
a lot of times
right I peel it off for company and
stuff company's coming over
last thing you need is somebody doing
this like they're eating and they're
like this
really good really good
what was this in in here
you know that's just a ginger
skin don't worry about it
I'm gonna just chop this up pretty good
if you guys don't mind just bear with me
here
I'm Gonna Get This Ginger
chopped up here
you don't want big pieces in here you do
want to grate
it right now actually I probably do
um I actually do have one
double 07 MD great to see you
great to see you hey MF great to see you
back mm all my patients and myself are
absolutely pleased keep your sense of
humor up
I think I will I think I will keep my
surgery since you were up
all right let's pop a little bit of
ginger in there don't make it too crazy
a little bit more boom
heck no no secret sauces for me Erica
Brown said
let's go with a little bit of hot red
pepper flakes
you guys know me I do like hot peppers
uh I'm guilty of the crime of liking
Heat
foreign
just lost a little bit of hot pepper in
there
I think a potato went South and it flew
off two tablespoons of water in here
for some reason I have exactly that two
tablespoons of water right here
[Music]
I think I'm gonna mix this up I'm gonna
whisk it if you guys don't mind I'm
gonna do a little bit of whisking
now I'm gonna even put it in here
I'm gonna whisk it in here
I'm gonna do a little bit of whisking
you guys this is the sauce
this is the Asian inspired Skillet
potato skillet
insanely good like insanely good
check out the brain saver books brain
saver protocols I haven't talked about
the brain saver books and God knows how
long I can't even remember now you got
the protocols book you want this book
you'll see when you open it you crack it
open we're just doing the recipe right
there
the heavy metal detox smoothies the
advanced heavy metal detox smoothies
an extractor all the brain shot
Therapies
and even more than that more than that
can even be possible it is
all right we got the sauce
there's a lemon on here that was only in
case I didn't have the lime but I had
the lime
so if you're confused if you see the
lemon just please not to worry it'll be
okay I'm not using because you might be
like whoa do I need a lemon something's
wrong here
right
when the potatoes are almost ready
because you're using raw potatoes I'm
using a steamed potato they're ready
anyway
when the potatoes are almost ready stir
in the sauce
cook for three to two to three minutes
if you can
I'm gonna stir in the sauce
it's actually really exciting because
I'm hungry
if you ever hear anybody say I'm hungry
I'm bleep hungry I'm bleeping hungry
right there you go
you got you got it right there the sauce
is in there okay
there's a potato Skillet right there
Asian Potato Skillet now I'm gonna be
reading a little bit of brain saver
adrenaline
emotions
let it cook for a couple of minutes
pan still playing hot
there's no vinegar
fancy that no vinegar
vinegar
on every vinegar label whether it's
apple cider vinegar or not it should say
if you're concerned about losing your
teeth down the road
do not consume this product that's it
all vinegars apple cider vinegar
included even though that's the best
vinegar
all right
there's no vinegar in here
I think people don't realize they get
vinegar to death in their cooking
eating out and everything else what you
do is you chop up a little cilantro
I'm going to serve this this is coming
out great
there we go
let it cook for another minute
you might be able to find a plate
small plate I have a large plate
this is actually simmering up nice
but let's do this
let's do this
chop up some cilantro when we serve it
we'll just chop it up now though we'll
have it ready
put the cilantro out of my garden right
here okay
here we go
now here's what this is cilantro that
has been growing for quite a long time
you know how it changes
you guys know what happens to Cilantro
when it bypasses that certain moment in
time and then a few weeks later it turns
kind of frizzy
and then you get
coriander kind of seed going on that
whole vibe right
so this is but I love cilantro even at
this stage seriously chop a little bit
of cilantro that will go on after
and chop up a little bit of
pepper as well
hopefully my jokes are pleasing
this is a very hot pepper what I'm gonna
do is stay away from those seeds just in
case others want to enjoy
so what I'm going to do is cut this
pepper another one
yes I hope my sense of humor is pleasing
to the ears
so I am at your disposal and At Your
Service
I'm going to slice this up you don't
want to go too crazy you don't want to
shred it you kind of want it to stick
around you want people to be able to
avoid it if they want if you've got a
really hot pepper like that you want
them to be able to actually avoid it and
be like can I just move this hot pepper
out a little bit
foreign
it's like that Home Alone movie right
you got it on your hands you so well
that was aftershave right
smack it on your face and then you start
screaming
thing is with hot pepper it's it's legit
I can't tell you over the years how many
people were like
like
in trouble from it for so many various
reasons all right I'm gonna plate this
and then I'm gonna pop on some of the
you know the fresh stuff on top
here with Amber says look so good
samber
what are you making
Rose
I am making this recipe right here Asian
inspired potato Skillet I'm about to
Plate it then I'm gonna read out of one
of the brain saver books about
adrenaline and emotions
it's an incredible recipe
okay
how can I do this appropriately
now if you're familiar with medical
media medical medium uh cooking show
medical medium recipes you'll notice
that I do mess up a lot in different
areas there's always some crazy spillage
something hits the floor but it looks
like we're actually in a better place
I'm gonna shut that off looks like we're
in a better place right now with that
meaning like it's not happening or
but I would like to Plate it nicely
something that would be really
I was going to try to make it look good
you guys want to come over
you guys want to come over and and uh
I'm gonna do you ever see this in
cooking shows right everybody always
takes this and they're like
pork is in there right pork tenderloins
and everything else and they put some
kind of weird syrup syrupy like sauce
down on there right
and they clean it off
nice
let's garnish it
but let me just take a look
okay so my bad my bad
you'll see the garnishing here are
larger pieces of cilantro I had kind of
the frizzier parts and I chopped the
out of it is what I did on The
Cutting Board
the peppers though look good I think
that's gonna work so let's pop that on
I'm gonna pop a little bit of this fresh
cilantro right here
I gotta tell you I'm actually really
psyched to eat this
really really excited
look a little bit of cilantro on there
and then I'm gonna pop some of these hot
fresh hot peppers on here too
you can be that person to just remove it
with your fork Maybe
but don't remove them with your fingers
and then try to like fix an eyebrow or
fixed eyeliner or something like that
whatever
yep or some uh
that is it right there I am going to try
one of these if you guys don't mind
I'll try this little one here
oh my God
oh yeah that's insane that's insane
that is so freaking good
that is so good I'm gonna kind of stick
it over here
[Music]
I'm actually proud of this one I'm so
proud of this one
lined I'm going to do this
can I show this off
can I show this off a little bit
that is good
proud of that one right there so I'm
gonna just clean off the board for a
second a little bit
now what that dish is that dish is out
of the brain saver books
it's out of the protocols
Cajun inspired potato
Skillet yeah you're not afraid of
potatoes
did someone
give you misinformation
about potatoes so they give you
disinformation about potatoes did they
lie about potatoes
scary nightshade
so bad for us
come on it's not bad for us we know that
right I've written enough about potatoes
just over the years
and you know the thing is about medical
medium information
it changes the course of everything just
a decade ago everybody was scared to
death of the potato in the health
movement come on you guys who are
seasoned you know what I'm talking about
right come on people who just are in you
know they're in in it in the last couple
years whatever
they may not think so they may think oh
I heard good things about potato you
guys have no idea no idea how bad it was
and for so long right this thing's
really hot I'm gonna move this over you
guys
everybody was scared to death
scared to death of potatoes everybody in
the home yes Connie Gibson's is yes
eight explanation points I stopped
eating potatoes because the carbs but
now I eat them
all right I'm getting excited I'm
getting too excited
let's get the brain saver book out
page 90 is where I'm going
yeah this is no joke you got to be
seasoned you got to be in it for a while
throughout throughout the years to know
that potato was literally the Antichrist
it was the Antichrist
it was Satan like that's what the potato
was
they were evil
took a lot of years and a lot of
Summits and lectures and everything else
that I could possibly do and in the
books teach people that it's actually a
healing food
went back to my usual self
foreign
adrenalized emotions
so I'm on page 90 a brain saver
they're on sale amazon.com us like 50
off or something close to that which is
incredible
but I'm just going to give you the
forewarning or go to the library get
them for free at the library
I'm gonna give you a forewarning now
seriously your mind's gonna be blown
probably only going to be able to read
peace at a time because it's so packed
and so mind-blowing if you're somebody
that just wants to try to cut through
these books
you're just your head's just going to be
like exploding every minute because it's
like that
well pages but
The Refuge recipe on is it page 402 I
saw that right there page 402 of
protocols
hello
Adrenalize emotions
adrenaline heightens everything going on
in the brain electrically
because adrenaline is explosive in the
brain when it heads to the brain and it
hits those neurons those electrical
impulses it's explosive that's why
there's so many Adrenaline Junkies and
that's why there's so many people just
hooked on adrenaline that's why there's
people doing all kinds of crazy stuff
because of adrenaline right
when we get emotionally challenged on
any level and that could be anything
that could be anything
seriously when we get emotionally
challenged with anything
whether good or bad did I say good
even good stuff seriously
whether in a brand new relationship with
a partner
you know that brand new relationship a
brand new friendship
and you're just like oh my God oh my God
you're like me you're like me I'm like
you I'm like you it's a brand new
friendship a brand new relationship
right adrenaline's just like pumping
it's a good adrenaline
but still it can be tough right you need
to rest in between
you need to rest in between and do good
things for yourself
whether it's a brand new relationship
with a partner
how many times have I heard like the
first six months of a brand new
relationship
and it's like out of control right and
six months later or eight months later
things seem to kind of calm down they
seem to kind of calm down but that first
six months this first three months the
adrenaline is just pumping pumping
Lisa says on Facebook uh bad brand new
relationship
a new boss or in a new friendship with a
co-worker co-workers
whether with the excitement of going on
a vacation or taking time off to do
something we love whether deciding to go
skiing one day or riding a motorcycle
anything we do adrenaline plays a role I
know people they made vacations after
their vacations
they go on a big vacation they come back
they need a vacation so they go and take
a vacation after they had a big long
vacation
and then you need a vacation after that
vacation and whoa if they're fortunate
enough they can vacation all year long
but they gotta rest in between for the
people asking what cooking utensils and
food products they use check out my my
directory
medicalme.com
adrenaline fuel on the fire check this
out you guys I'm reading out a brain
saver you've got to have these books
come on
when we have a good experience
adrenaline is released from the adrenal
glands
when we have a good experience our
adrenals go
I don't have a lot of props with me
tonight but like they just go right
got two adrenal glands right here
you know so there's just like squeezing
you have a good experience they're going
they're off
you're going off
some limes
when that adrenaline touches electricity
there's no electricity in my body
there's no electricity in your body yeah
there is
we know that
when that electricity electrician yeah
you need electrician sometimes for that
electricity in the body when that is
your cut cut cut edit edit
we're live we don't do that
healthy adrenaline helps fuel the
electrical Grid it's undiscovered by
medical research and science that
adrenaline is filled with receptor
compounds so this is something that's
really Advanced so the medical medium
books are highly Advanced right
information in here
that you won't hear anywhere else
but there are receptor compounds in
Adrenaline these receptor compounds are
designed for the electrical Grid in the
brain only specifically for the
electrical Grid in the brain so when
adrenaline is released from your adrenal
glands it's flowing through your body
whether a good experience bad experience
it's flowing through the body these
receptors inside that adrenaline that's
pumping right
those receptors are designed for the
brain
these receptor compounds are designed
for the electrical Grid in the brain
when the compounds hit the electricity
of the brain your electrical impulse
they light up and ignite like fireflies
or like bugs hitting a bug zapper
so is that adrenaline is you know
entering the brain your brain is
receiving that adrenaline it just lights
up the grid
fireflies and bugs adrenaline is a
necessity in small healthy amounts we
required it in all everyday living and
functioning adrenaline behaves
differently
from oxygen while adrenaline Burns Like
Oxygen inside the body it does so with a
more rapid aggressive intense heat so
oxygen that gets inside your bloodstream
gets your brain actually Burns it gets
utilized
but adrenaline is much more intense
adrenaline's Fire doesn't squelch easily
with water and glucose although water
hydration and glucose are still critical
to address the brain heat from
adrenaline so here's something that
happens
a lot of people stroke out
I'm serious a lot of people stroke out
because it's all
timing
it's all like that Perfect Storm
chronic dehydration not enough glucose
in the brain not enough hydration to the
brain
and then the right amount of aggravation
all of it combined low-grade viral
infections immune systems down low in
this perfect storm and if they were just
hydrated a little bit more
could have made all the difference
prevent it you know that ischemic attack
imagine you're experiencing something
good skiing down a slope is that good
a lot of people love it
I mean
maybe I'm just a downer am I just like a
downer
you don't want to see people skiing down
the slope I'm like whoa whoa whoa break
breaking no could break a leg nope that
could blow look out
but I'm just worried about everybody so
that's just me I know people don't give
a A lot of people don't give a
and they'll just be like whatever people
do what they're gonna do but actually
I'm concerned take me to a ski slope
hanging out and I'll just be like whoa
just be careful whoa
someone just tore their ankle off their
body
your adrenal's pumping because you're
about to hit a tricky spot so when
you're skiing just say I'm just using
that as an example right here and you're
hitting heading for a tricky spot your
adrenals are just
just releasing and releasing
and that's what's you know that's
interesting because if you had an injury
doing something
right you may not feel that injury as
much as someone else feels an injury
because the adrenaline was pumping
during that injury
for the excitement of that challenge
alone it's worth it to go when you go
down the slope right that excitement of
the adrenaline it's worth it alone
Euphoria and Clarity come when
adrenaline is hitting the electrical
grid during a good experience
it puts you in the feeling of being in
the zone
even like it's like finding a new
relationship
you're falling in love
and you're just in the zone
that adrenaline is just pumping
Stacy Island on YouTube I missed you
it's so great to see you great to be
back it is
as your adrenals start filling your
blood with adrenaline all that
adrenaline gasoline
reaches your brain and ignites its
electrical Grid it's more adrenaline and
a more intense blend of adrenaline than
the gentle mild levels of adrenaline
hitting your electrical grid when you're
showering or brushing your teeth so that
leads to this if you're doing the
simplest things and
don't get me wrong brushing your teeth
is actually sometimes an impossibility
for somebody who's got chronic illness
and they're struggling they can't even
stand up long enough in the bathroom to
brush their teeth or they don't have
strength in their arms and so forth to
do so
that's something on the screen here so
yeah and
so the point is is that so many people
they don't have the ability to shower so
easy they don't have the ability to
function so easy it takes adrenaline to
do all that but when you're really
struggling with chronic illness
sometimes it's like impossible and it's
really hard
I've seen over the years people chronic
illness just the water hitting their
back or their head in the shower it's
just too much after they get out of the
shower and they get to their mattress
Island they're done for an hour or more
that was a big thing
see George Payne says
which one of the books is Anthony
reading
brain saver right here page 90.
as your adrenals are feeling start
filling up your blood with adrenaline
all that adrenaline like I said becomes
like fuel for the fire gasoline
it reaches your brain and ignites its
electrical grid
it's more adrenaline and a more intense
blend of adrenaline than the gentle mild
levels like I was saying of showering or
brushing your teeth or going to the
bathroom it takes adrenaline
to do number two
it takes adrenaline
to eliminate it takes adrenaline to
urinate
what about an
unhelming
yeah
what about an unhappy moment uh-huh
a lot of us experience that a bad
experience what about a bad experience
what about betrayal whoa
what is that in my back
I said knife
I had a knife in my back
what about betrayal what about getting a
message from your best friend that
reveals she didn't understand you after
all these years
everything you've poured out to this
friend all your vulnerabilities
weaknesses and soul Secrets it's as if
she never heard any of it and she
delivers a blow you never thought
possible
the adrenals release their chemicals and
an intense adrenaline blend geared to
power you through the moment of betrayal
rushes to your brain hits the electrical
grid and catches on fire
the reason you get this adrenaline fires
to provide Clarity faster thinking who
screwed me over man what faster thinking
and Clarity I need to know now
this is incredible information
haven't been in this book in a while
that's insane
the reason you get this adrenaline fire
is to provide Clarity and faster
thinking and the strength to override
any mental blocks or smaller injuries
already in the brain so many people have
smaller injuries in the brain they don't
know it all kinds of things in the brain
talk about that in the brain books so
you can be quick on your feet during
this this challenging emotional
experience you got to be quick on your
feet when you have an emotional
experience like that
the adrenaline fire is there to help set
you on A New Path power you to a safer
land and new experiences so it's not
like this terrible thing you're betrayed
and you got an adrenaline surge
but it's there to power you through this
adrenaline fire is also why when
somebody goes through an emotional
experience they can feel so drained and
worn out afterward that it's difficult
to function for months
that ain't no joke
when the adrenaline subsides from the
electrical grid feelings of sadness and
depression or brain exhaustion can be
elevated if you had a difficult
situation any kind of emotional
experience with somebody else any kind
of Confrontation abuse or any kind of
struggle emotionally with others
something happens betrayal you feel
sadness depression anger back to
depression back to sadness and then you
feel a brain exhaustion
and that can elevate
it's why bouncing back can take so long
so many people need to have time to
bounce back anytime to bounce back
Erica Brown says I know that feeling
from abuse also
it's just it's I it's so true
I'm sorry you've gone through anything
it's why bouncing back can take so long
and why some don't even bounce back
some don't even bounce back I mean
that's why we need to do things for our
brain and heal and do things and work on
our healing process
and some don't even bounce back
and why some
struggle so much if the brain is up
against acidity deficiencies poisons and
toxins which the books talk about like
in in detail it's all the harder to
recover from the intense adrenaline
surge of an emotional blow
incredible information brain saver right
there you guys that was paid 90 on brain
saver
there's so much information in here that
alone
it's just like a few paragraphs that's
it
there's so much in here yes we just made
the recipe I am going to have
a fun time eating it I'm excited
right
there's so much information in these
books check them out when you can
I might have a little bit of food really
quick I'm gonna put it on top of the
book I hope that's okay that's not a bad
thing though hmm
you guys
hits a spot like no other
keep in mind always
if you ever feel alone
if you feel like
no one understands you
and they don't understand what you're
going through
even if they're just you know their
hearts in it you know their intentions
are good and they want to understand
that if you feel alone and you feel like
no one gets you
struggling with the chronic illness
whether it's a fatigue or the brain fog
or the pain
keep in mind that somebody's watching
keep in mind always
whether it's the angels
God above
or even if you don't believe in God
something is watching it
from out there and up there
anyway
I love you guys dearly
incredible I'm glad we get to spend a
little time got to spend a little bit of
time together making a recipe
I'm excited about it I'm gonna have some
food
good to see you guys and I can't wait to
see you guys again