exciting i'm very happy to be here right
now and
i'm going to ask you guys if you want to
have dinner with me
a little later on so a live dinner
on tick tock okay just letting you know
if you don't want to that's fine i
totally get it
but it'll be fun and i'm making a
different kind of thing tonight
so making different kind of food so
that's going to be great that's probably
going to be
you know maybe after i get off here i'll
go to ig really quick
there's stacy nesbitt how are you glad
to see you here it's so
awesome and so glad you guys are coming
on
cool cool so yeah so i was going to have
dinner and make dinner the whole bit
and answer questions thoroughly i would
love if you guys come on with me
there's josh eldridge he came on here
just now um
and i want to answer a few questions
while i'm here right here catherine king
how are you
familiar faces everywhere you guys
incredible glad everybody's here
um so yeah it's exciting it really
is so i'm doing a tick tock dinner again
and gonna answer questions thoroughly
everybody's coming on and try to answer
some questions
um so yeah
so it's it's some great stuff going on
number one
is medical medium podcast at apple
podcast have you done the meditations
the five powerful meditations have you
listened to the potato episode the
neurological symptom episode
the anxiety episode then it goes on the
brain fog episode
air fresheners have you guys been
noticing that when you
order a piece of clothing sometimes it
comes
just reeking with air freshener and
you know fungicide and scented candles
and they just intoxicate us pressing
prince is here hello from australia
good to see you glad you're here amazing
are you going to come and have dinner
with me
because it's going to be doing that dana
golden
hey from houston awesome great place
great place
good to see you and i got some lemon
balm tea with me right now
great great to be here you guys bethany
richardson
please uh please struggling with bad
fatigue but nothing ever shows up
any recommendations um
what happens with that fatigue no one
realizes this out there but that fatigue
means there's something going on and i
it's really bad fatigue i've always
taught doctors that that's
called neurological lyme it's something
i termed myself
between spirit of compassion and i and
so that neurological
that literal neurological um fatigue
you can use either get like a
neurological lyme diagnosis down the
road which you know you can get any kind
of diagnosis so that fatigue gets worse
and worse they just don't know
and they'll just be like well you got
the severe fatigue we're going to have
to give it a label eventually
lorraine ells on here hi anthony over
here from england
cool wonder where in england that's so
great
it's a great place um and
so yeah lorena i lost my hypertension
diagnosis within a month of eating the
mm diet
whoa that's a good thing to lose that's
a great thing to lose lose your
hypertension diagnosis incredible from
eating an mm diet that's amazing so that
that fatigue is like a neurological
fatigue that's what i call it it's very
deep it holds us back and
if you have that neurological fatigue i
almost lost my mind
i almost lost my book almost went over
my shoulder and down to the floor anyway
in here i talk about chronic fatigue
syndrome and
what to do and i tell doctors all the
time what it is it's epstein-barr virus
so it's the monovirus but
you can't get tested for it easy because
it's in a different stage
it's not in that beginning stage of mono
it's in
a later stage and when it's in later
stage you have this fatigue and it's
from your old mono you had
years ago and that's how it works um
shawna what's your take on apple cider
vinegar
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
my apple
cider vinegar show it's my apple cider
vinegar podcast
if you haven't listened to it you have
to listen to it
medical mean podcast apple podcast it's
for free i'm not selling anything
and i'm not charging anything and
there's no commercials on it so i'm not
making advertising money which i could
i could probably get like 10 advertisers
on that podcast and just
beat everybody down with commercials 24
7 and make a bundle of money but i don't
want to do that i want you guys to have
an experience when you're on the medical
meeting podcast
and just not have to put up with that
stuff at least for now
maybe if i bring something on there down
the road you'll forgive me but i'm not
planning on it
claudine iaw got my son to drink the
celery juice every morning
and his skin condition is clearing up
miracle and you know what's funny you
know what's funny about that
all these naysayers and health gurus
that
hate the fact that medical media put out
the celery juice in the world they hate
the fact that celery juice
has been dominating the health scene for
quite some time now
they hate it and so they'll tell people
stay away from celery juice you
shouldn't be juicing celery juice oh
it's got too much bad or it's not good
right
meanwhile they're stealing some
some child's chance of clearing up their
skin
or a child's chance of healing or
mommy's chance of healing or someone
getting their life back they're robbing
people of that
because they're demented or something
because
they don't want people to heal and
there's just something terribly wrong
about that
this is so cool um jennifer fonz do you
know anything about pots and how can i
help my daughter the thing is about pots
is pots as always and i've talked
about this the doc you could tell your
doctor this i talk to i teach doctors
this all the time pots is viral
and um so it's low grade viral so if
i had if i had a friend or
someone else is that they're dealing
with pots i always say we've got to go
anti-viral or at least
take away foods that could feed the
virus so maybe take the gluten away a
little bit
and just move it aside maybe do
gluten-free things that could be helpful
maybe do take away the dairy products
and the eggs a little bit bring in more
avocados
bring in more potatoes and that could be
helpful just these little switches alone
are really really helpful um and then
b12 is really important too you can ask
your doctor if this will
be fine but b12 that's the vimer gp12
v is in victor i am as in mary ergy i'm
not sponsored i don't own a company i
recommend a lot of products and i get to
know
all these companies that are doing the
right thing and making sure the products
are incredible
but i don't i'm not sponsored i just
don't like that whole
route of being sponsored i mean anybody
else would love to be
they probably would love to be in the
health field sponsored because
that would be the greatest you think
about that you know they'd be like yeah
but i don't want to um
and you can get more information
anything autoimmune
anything like that you can get more
information in here i mean it's packed
with information if you guys don't have
the book
cleanse the heal let's cleanse the heal
elizabeth ruby i have ptsd depression
um it's awful to have that i
i talk about ptsd all the time i talk
about depression all the time
i have an anxiety show at medical media
podcast at apple podcast i have this
anxiety show that you might want to
listen to
meds and therapy no longer work any
suggestions i've tried anything
elizabeth if it was me that i had this
depression
and i had this ptsd i would
i would try to get something called the
toxic heavy metals out of
my body because the reason why we have
this
mystery depression this mystery ptsd
and even mystery anxieties because we
have toxic heavy metals
inside our brain and to get that metal
out of our brain
we need to make sure we're doing like
the heavy metal detox movies and things
like that there's a
heavy metal detox cleansing here
this is what i would do and it's in here
to get metals out so you can put
depression behind you
i'd also try the meditations they're
really healing
really powerful so the moon meditation
the stargazing meditation
the brain meditation medical medium
podcast at apple podcast it's for
emotional the emotional side
because you got the emotional side that
needs some help and healing
and then you got the physical side so
you take the toxic heavy metals out of
the physical side
and then you help the emotional side
with the powerful meditations and all
this information is from above
which is really cool you guys incredible
to be here
um answering some questions because i
always want to make sure i
get a chance to do that and then i'm
going over
to tick tock a little later and i'm
going to have dinner do you want to come
over with me and have dinner
and i'm going to ask i'm going to answer
questions and i might ask a few
questions
too am i
um georgina says anthony really look
forward to your lives i'm honored that
you
you are looking forward to him that
you're here it makes me so happy um
i just saw somebody that has lupus
california lupus patient
uh lupus the whole thing about lupus is
that
science research doesn't know the cause
of lupus just like science research
medical science research doesn't know
the cause of eczema lupus
fibromyalgia multiple sclerosis
hashimoto's thyroiditis hyperthyroidism
graves um the list goes on i mean i can
keep a chronic fatigue syndrome the list
can go on and on endometriosis fibroids
they just don't know the cause of any of
this stuff
so what happens is we end up getting
sick they put a label on it they put a
name on it
right and then we don't know the cause
or what to really do for it and then we
go fishing so then we go fishing let's
cast out the line
let's try this doctor out here let's try
another doctor out here let's
okay wait this doctor says apple cider
vinegar will help me
well let's try this nutritionist this
nutritionist says charcoal is going to
help me
i got a big one here it's a big fish
it's a nutritionist you want me to do
charcoal now and collagen okay let me
cast that another line cause that didn't
work that sucks and i cast out another
line
and i hook now i hook a dietitian let me
get that dietitian in
the dietitian wants me to be on eggs and
lots of protein but i'm still sick and
my endometriosis is getting worse
let's go fishing again oh my god cast
out another lime
and we're just reeling in another one
hey a functional medicine doctor
and now we're doing that what does he
want me to do oh wait a minute he wants
me to try a whole bunch of different
things
okay let's cast that another one whoa we
got an acupuncturist here we got
we got a oriental doc we got a whole bit
medicine we got chinese medicine doctor
here too
and we're pulling that in and that that
doctor wants us to try all these herbs
but it's all guessing games
and random crap everywhere but we're
still sick with our lupus
and how do we get better and in the end
many of them just take little tidbits
from original medical medium information
from 30 years ago
which is since i was there at the
beginning which is
get rid of gluten which came from
homemade really because no one was off
of gluten 35 years ago
and then do this and do this and this is
how it works and it's really kind of
crazy but what i'm saying is
it's not easy out there and
hey you know what can i say it's not
easy so we want to get people better
try to get the information with lupus
it's viral
and you want to get that viral thing out
of you
and they just don't know see when we
walk around with lupus nobody knows
um deborah
deborah burgett says hi anthony my
doctor says my vitamin b12
levels are too high in my body after i
started taking the b12
you suggested up to this point my b12
levels were always way too low
she wants me to stop taking my b
vitamins it might
be 12 any and take the b2 uh sub v12 any
suggestions on this listen to the b12
podcast i explain it all
when your levels are too high when your
levels are too low
so medical median podcasts at apple
podcast honestly you'll get the best
explanation from there
and unless you want to go to tick
tick-tock live after and i'm going to
thoroughly
go through all kinds of stuff there
while i'm making dinner having dinner
with you guys
but i would i would go to the medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast and
really
really like listen to all the answers
are in there about b12 and you'll be
like whoa
what and you'll be like huh so it's all
there
um katherine axe says thank you anthony
for everything
healed my mom last four years from
really bad alzheimer's with your
information
um incredible so you healed
your mom of really bad alzheimer
with this information i mean that that's
that right there is incredible i mean
it's incredible
absolutely incredible and honored to be
part of it
alicia elisa sorry diane says did moon
meditation last night
yay guess what i did the moon meditation
last night too
[Laughter]
cynthia c looking forward for another
podcast look
i'm looking forward to doing another
podcast i i got wrapped up
in the in the caffeine
the caffeine one i got wrapped up in the
um
the milk cheese butter bread makes your
dad
uh video so i've been i've been working
hard
on trying to get a different message
across so people can heal but i'm
working on the podcast too
so i am going to come out eventually
with another episode and lots of them
um marco o'neil your info works anthony
i am treating hundreds of clients
and they are healing mark that's
incredible
bless your heart it matters you're
healing others
that's the whole point uh incredible
absolutely incredible i've got some
lemon balm tea guys
um delicious i put honey in there this
time
so you know you guys um
in a little bit i'm going to tick-tock
live i got some food cooking
over here some food steaming i have
if you look in the back i got what seems
to be
some greens and some other things i'm
going to be playing with ginger
rosemary parsley some other stuff too
so i'm going to be you know doing all
kinds of stuff in there so i'm going to
be making my dinner
do you want to have dinner with me
because i'll be on tick tock live a
little later i'm going to go to ig and
i'm going to answer questions thoroughly
and i'm going to be
live like i am now i'm live now too and
i'm still answering some questions here
i want to help out in any way i can't
because i figure some of you guys aren't
going to go over there because you're
busy
and so i try to hopefully catch a
question here but in about
30 minutes i will be there at tic toc
live um
so looking at many different questions
you guys the link is in the description
too just so you know the link is in the
description
so when you get a chance i mean you got
the meditations to work with
powerful i got 17 new episodes at the
medical meeting podcast
and um it's really exciting the
information is there so you can heal
i'm heading over now i love you guys
and um look all i could say is look if
i don't see you till tomorrow or however
just know that have compassion for
yourself keep a light heart know that i
care
know that i want you to heal and i know
you can heal you really
can heal um janette says good morning
from australia
and deanna d deanna you're going to be
there
what's for dinner today i'm working with
a couple cool things i can't wait for
you to see
um courtney mars says we love you i'm
honored love you back
so uh so cool josh says loving and unity
amazing great message right there um
powerful he chodes here chota bless your
heart are you heading over to tick tock
live in about a half an hour
um incredible so
look you guys have compassion for
yourself pat yourself on the back
you're good you're you're you're a good
person you didn't do anything wrong
it's not your fault if you have a
symptom or you're not feeling good
michelle you coming over michelle l
you're heading over hope to see you
there
mark o'neill um that's an honor saying
thanks for your compassion
i know your compassionate man yourself
um
melissa says mom has alzheimer's got to
get the medals out
gotta get some medals out you do and get
some celery juice going
talk to your doctor if that's okay uh
for mom
and sit tracy tracy phelps i'll see on
tick-tock absolutely
um love you guys i'm going to ig are you
going to come to ig for a minute i'm
going to answer a couple questions there
deanna scott's mccord says see you on
tick-tock dianna i can't wait
heading over to ig love you guys