get sick what are the causes of sickness
why does everybody go around
looking for answers and they think they
have an answer but they really don't
have an answer and then they stay sick
another two months another six months
and then two years go by and then five
years go by and then 10 years go by i
remember people coming to my office many
years ago with 30 years have gone by
sick hashimoto's thyroid problems on
thyroid medications all kinds of blood
pressure problems all kinds of nerve
problems restless leg syndrome insomnia
you name it they're on pills they're on
this they got high anxiety they got
depression it's like how long you've
been sick been sick for 25 years i'm
like oh my god and then they get the
answers and things start going away and
as things start going away they go
anthony why didn't i find you 25 years
ago and i'm like well
since this is 25 years ago
uh 25 years before that i would have
been very little so the point is is
people just they go around they look
around if they're trying to find help
and they can't find the answers and yet
this is a special time and it's not
about me it's not because i'm special or
anything like that is because
we have answers now it's it's the
information i get from the source i hear
right whether somebody likes that or not
or somebody thinks it sounds kind of you
know crazy or whatever it is a fact it's
a fact since age four i've been hearing
a voice that voice tells me why people
are sick and what's wrong and what they
need and
thousands and thousands of people got
their lives back and man when you're
praying to god and you're down on your
knees and you're like i got no hope left
i can't go to work i can't function my
anxiety is killing me the answers matter
and that's what happened cindy lou cindy
lou what's going on you always leave
comments on
i always leave comments on the uh on the
youtube all the time right here you are
that was a quick kitchen clean right
yeah i know we just did the amazon live
you guys we made waffles ten different
ways it was crazy it was like peanut
butter waffles like almond butter wild i
don't know what tahini waffles that's
what it was it was refried beans waffles
where it was like
it was pico waffles it was like
everything nacho waffles man it was
crazy it was incredible cold white
spring good to see you right you see the
moose cold night spring may you see the
moose yeah
it's pretty funny right so
nat says anthony can you help me with
trigeminal neuralgia please been
following protocol for two months no
results yet so here's what happens now
with trigeminal neuralgia right i've
talked to a lot of doctors about this
that have come to me because they i know
doctors that deal with trigeminal
neuralgia and they in their cases lots
of cases and i've taught them a lot of
things and one thing that's critical to
know about trigeminal neuralgia
is that you can have the shingles virus
causing trigeminal neuralgia and you can
even have the simplex one fever blister
cold sore that you don't even see so you
don't even have the cold sore or fever
blister but it's in the nerves it's in
the cranial nerve so let's do this a
little bit because we're going to talk
about this now why do we get trigeminal
neuralgia
because of a low-grade viral infection a
low-grade viral infection and that
low-grade viral infection are these
little bugs right here that's the
low-grade viral infection right here
it's these bugs
and these bugs sit inside of us right
and so it takes time for some stubborn
stubborn trigeminal neuralgia cases take
time gotta make sure there's no gluten
there you gotta make sure there's no
eggs in there you gotta make sure
there's no dairy products you gotta make
sure that you're keeping the fats low
low you got to make sure and then
protocols what protocols are you on
right and that's important too
right
how far are you on the protocol what's
going on there if i had trigeminal
neuralgia i'd be doing the protocol and
i would be you know taking a look in
here and you'll see all the different
stuff with the protocol right here and
you make sure you're on your vitamin c
make sure you're on there b12 you make
sure you're on your your different
things that you need
zinc is critical too now ask your doctor
what's right for you but if i had
trigeminal neuralgia
i'd be
i'd be 100 fat free if it was bad if i
was suffering 100
no fats right
i'd be doing i'd be doing the papaya
banana mono cleanse possibly be doing
the heavy metal detox smoothie i'd have
that in there you know you can pick and
choose what you feel like doing but you
can get there one thing's for sure is
i'd stay away from the eggs the gluten
the dairy products if i had a
neurologist stay away from all of that
keep the fats down to zero if you can
and then get the antivirals in that are
in cleanse the heal right because you're
looking at knocking out that shingles
virus and that and the
simplex virus you're looking at knocking
those out so you can do a simplex
protocol you can be doing the shingles
protocol so that's the one you want and
cleanse the heal take it to your doctor
ask them what's right for you but the
shingles protocol so that's important
right there and and sometimes those you
know i'll tell you right now i've never
seen the needle move for trigeminal
neuralgia for anybody out there except
for medical medium protocols i've never
seen it move i mean i've talked to
hundreds of doctors for the last 35
years and trigeminal neuralgia is that
kind of thing that never budges unless
you do the right thing so there are
answers you got to stay with it you got
to you know learn how to chip away and
chip away until those viral that viral
inflammation is down and gone and when
it's gone all of a sudden you can chew
again oh my god i can chew again all of
a sudden you can start feeling better
what happens is
cranial nerves right here so cranial
nerves
the trigeminal nerve right that's your
cranial nerve so trigeminal neuralgia is
about an inflamed cranial nerve cranial
nerves are why people are sick with so
many different things
and this is just one thing right there
so
kimberly miller trying to get back onto
the mono cleanse
i totally get it it's not easy to get
back onto the mono cleanse but i'm
really proud of you for trying to do
that that's incredible right there um so
yeah you guys so let's talk a little bit
more about why we're sick just like
we're doing now and we'll keep on doing
that right there so
if you
if you're somebody that's been
struggling for a long time
you've been you've been trying to find
answers right
you want to know why you're sick and you
get answers and you get answers like
things like it's all in your gut or
something and that's not an answer i've
seen this so so many times with people
laurie says what causes a burning
sensation in the mouth when eating food
ebv or something else if i had a burning
sensation in my mouth okay
so if i had a burning sensation in my
mouth right
burning sensations i call it burning
tongue burning gums burning mouth right
that's that right there okay that's a
viral issue too so keep that in mind so
it's a viral issue when we go to the
doctors they don't know what burning
mouth burning tongue is they don't know
what burning cheeks are they don't know
what any of that is
and unless they're learning and they're
picking up medical medium information
because i've noticed that that that's
what's happening i noticed that the
clinics are taking mm info they've never
had
they're taking it right out of published
medical medium books and they're
starting to put it on their websites
like information that doesn't have a
study behind it but it came from
these books right so i noticed that
right now there's a big like thirst for
stealing information it's actually
hilarious but whatever
but what happens is when you go to the
best clinics and you tell them you've
got a burning tongue burning mouth
burning gums
and they'll just look at you like you're
crazy they won't know
they won't know that's also trigeminal
neuralgia and other cranial nerves that
cause the burning tongue burning face
you know burning face too burning face
burning cheeks
burning eyes optic nerves so the burning
eyes you feel like you got burning in
your forehead burning in back of your
eyes
all of that right that's all the cranial
nerves getting inflamed by viruses it
means people walk around with a lot of
ebv's shingles simplexes those are the
most common for that
right there and shingles is a big one
right there people don't know about the
shingles so cold white springs so maybe
you said burning of shingles yeah
definitely burning in joy clark i was
sick for 35 years of trigeminal
neuralgia with hope because i did not
have the mm information
i do not know how i survived now i am on
round 16 of the 369 cleanse yeah
zero fat is what moves the needle as
well as all the supplements when not on
the cleanse so trigeminal neuralgia is a
shingles problem so when i look at the
supplements i have right here right
these are the vimergy supplements it's
the best stuff out there so let me open
up cleanse the heal let's just hit
trigeminal neuralgia because people have
it and they don't even know do you guys
know that
they have jaw pain they don't know it's
trigeminal neuralgia they have burning
gum burning gum they have a funny
feeling on the tongue they don't know
it's trigeminal neuralgia
they don't know it's their cranial
nerves that's what happens right
so i'm gonna look for the shingles
section right here real quick see if i
can find it for you guys right
and
so it's important here it is a single
section right here so what's in the
protocol okay
got a few different things right here
we've got cat's claw so that's in the
protocol right here so the best cat
squad out there is the
is the vimergy cat's claw so that's it
right there okay so cats claw that's the
bimmer g1 vs victor i m e r g y dot com
i'm not sponsored it's the best stuff
out there
when you use cat's claw for viral issues
it could be anything like the restless
leg syndrome it could be like tingles
and numbness it could be neurological
fatigue where you're fatigued you guys
right you don't have an explanation to
why you're fatigued it could be ticks
and spasms and all kinds of different
you know um you know feeling creepy
crawlies on the skin but there's nothing
on your skin and you go to the doctors
all these neurological symptoms cat's
claws critical neurological lyme
multiple sclerosis
als and forget those forget those labels
you just don't know why you don't feel
good
and it's a neurological symptom cat's
claw is critical so that's a cat's claw
right there so if you look at the
shingles right here okay section the
shingles virus is the true cause of
trigeminal neuralgia frozen shoulder how
many of you guys ever had frozen
shoulder right ulcerative colitis how
many of you guys had ulcerative colitis
and many cases of neck pain jaw pain gum
and tooth pain tongue pain burning
sensations in the mouth burning
sensations on your skin
pain in the back of your head right the
pain in your back your head right
that too okay
migraine related pain mystery sciatic
pain your back's killing you you can't
sit on your wallet you got the sciatic
nerve pain in the back that's the
shingles right there okay
the shingles infection can happen with
no rashes
so what i love about this here's the
cat's claw right here it says two
dropper fulls twice a day in the book if
you're dealing with anything ask your
doctor it's right for you but that's the
cleanse the heel book it's a life-saving
book for so many people out there in the
world
two dropper fulls twice a day of cats
claw i'm not sponsored i don't own the
company i love when people are like oh
he must be the owner no okay i'm not
sponsored i don't own the company i do
work with wyman's and i'm proud of it
wyman's shop wyman's okay
right shop.wymans.com
right that's the wild blueberry juice
which is just incredible i'm going to
drink some in a little bit because i'm
actually thirsty i just did the amazon
live i want to have some some wild
blueberry juice i do work with wyman's
to make sure that that stuff sticks
around i mean what they have to do in
order to get that in a bottle is
unbelievable anyway
but i i don't i'm not sponsored by
vimergy but the stuff is incredible i
recommend the friends family so that's
the cats claw very important critical
when it comes down to healing
okay another thing for trigeminal
neuralgia i'm looking at really quick
here lemon balm it says four dropper
fulls three times a day four dropper
fulls three times a day now remember
this is for shingles frozen shoulder
ulcerative colitis many cases of neck
pain jaw pain gum pain tooth pain tongue
pain burning sensations inside the mouth
burning sensations on the skin pain in
the back of the head migraine related
pain sciatica pain mystery lower back
pain how many guys have that neuropathy
and even neuropathy
okay
and so what you do is
you can read the chapter okay and make
sure you read the supplement protocol
chapter before you start anything so
make sure you get cleansed to heal get
it free at the library all right it
costs more to print it if you go to you
go to amazon.com it's so cheap on
amazon.com right now it's 16.99 51 off
you guys
you guys have to understand something
right
i'm really really
like i get hopped up and i get
passionate about the symptoms and
conditions
because all i do
is feel
someone suffering someone's suffering
bad
no one gets it unless they had frozen
shoulder and they couldn't move half
their body for about a year no one gets
it
unless they're the ones that got the
burning skin
and the burning face and couldn't sleep
and had to take all these crazy drugs
crazy prescription drugs because they
can't even sleep their pain their their
jaw's on fire
it's these things that matter it's this
it's people suffering it's their chronic
symptoms that take them down and make
them feel like they're they're hopeless
it makes them feel like they're
worthless i've seen so many people
suffer when they're so sick for so long
and so what i do is i'm like you know
what who can i help today
like who can i help is there someone out
there that doesn't even know and realize
it and they just came on here like who
is this guy and i'm saying he there are
answers
there are answers get it free at the
library i don't care
it doesn't matter yeah you can get an
amazon dirt cheap cost more to print it
in from what they sell for but get it
for eat the library if you need to
learn how to take cat's cloth the right
kind learn how to get zinc in you
because people are so sick with all
these symptoms and there are answers and
ways learn how to do the right cleanse
man
if people only knew who were suffering
for five years you do the 369 what it
can do what brand is that for the lemon
balm
lemon balm is vimergy vicky so it's
vimergy v is in victor i am as in mary
e-r-g-y dot-com they're salt of the
earth i've become friends with them over
the years because they keep the standard
so high with the products every time i
i'm friends with a dozen supplement
companies out there right
because i try to build a relationship
and i build a relationship with them and
they say they're going to keep the stuff
really high quality and then they
totally screw me over and and and all of
a sudden they'll look at their bottle
one day and i'm like are you kidding
there why is there citric acid in here
so i call them up not vimergy but other
companies i'll call them up and be look
i thought we were had a i thought we had
some like a friendship i thought you
were on the same page we want to keep
this stuff clean for people and they're
like anthony sorry man but you know what
uh you're not the owner of this company
and we do what we want and and we're
gonna make our spirulina the way we
wanna make it and we're gonna make our
whatever it is the way we wanna make it
and you can't you we're not gonna have
you and your people who are sick like
tell us what to do and clean clean
supplements and stuff and that's what
happens i try to build relationships so
i could have communication i just
reached out to some other company that
that i thought i had communication with
and i don't have communication with it's
crazy and
and they're just like no we changed our
thing and what i can tell you is this
with vimeracy
they don't change
their quality standards are higher and
higher to the point where nothing on the
planet earth can touch their they're
like standard
it's just incredible anyway
all this stuff matters when you're
healing you can take a garbage zinc
and never heal
you can take a bottom of the barrel
junkies ink and never ever heal
i've seen this happen out there it's
like there is a way to heal with the
right stuff there just is and
information critical first michelle l
michelle oh hey
no one told me what the burning pain was
and i asked so many times say w
and that's how it is out there so
answers are really important you guys
and really important so let's talk about
some other stuff too right
i cannot find wyman's cat's claw i had
jingles no way it's wyman's blueberry
juice they got the wild blueberry juice
right the cat's claw is vimergy margaret
so it's v as in victor i-m-e-r-g-y
lorraine l good to see you i just saw
your comment fly up right there
it's the the wyman's is the wild
blueberry juice now i am working with
these guys you guys full disclosure on
that i am working with these guys i told
you that since the first day i showed
you the wyman's juice okay
and and what it is is they need my help
to make sure that because they're
killing themselves to actually
harvest these out of the field and press
them
throw them in a press
and press it for us like and i'm like
i'm on board i will do anything to make
sure people know about that
but you guys know that right um
vertigo let's talk about dizziness and
virgo michelle lewis let's go into that
a little bit cranial nerves
vagus nerves
if you don't have if your doctor rules
out a big old brain tumor right they
roll out you get they do the cat scans
they do the mris they don't see a big
brain tumor they don't see something
really in the way they're like we don't
know why you can't we don't know why
you're walking around like this
we don't know why you're walking around
like that as you're trying to get to the
doctor's office or your head's feeling
like it's spinning like this like that
you know
and
the vertigo or you just feel like you're
on a boat feel like you're on a boat
you're like and what happens is those
are vagus nerves
cranial nerves right there
they're inflamed
that's what i tell people in my family
or my friends that you know reach out
after 20 years and they're like i got
this vertigo
i hate to bother you aw but i just need
a couple of pointers i'm like dude have
you looked at the medical medium book
and got the vertigo information right
doctors reach out to me like what do i
do my patients that have vertigo a.w
and so you got to get the vagus nerve
inflammation down that's the key with
vertigo this is alive right now a quick
live on look there are answers there are
true causes viral issues cause vertigo
inflamed vagus nerves caused by
epstein-barr that's the reason for
vertigo right there
so
i have healed so much with this info
still have more to go but the more i
stay true the better i get wondering
wondering right wishing right
it's really cool handle wondering
wishing
so i got to tell you something right
that's the key
it's
it's how far you go it's what you do
it's how much you do it's there you can
take a little bit of the time but you
can get there you guys you can get there
you guys on tick tock check out cleanse
the heel you won't be sorry it's a
medical textbook that's saving lives
around the world millions of copies sold
around the world
the medical medium book series is the
most popular health series in the world
seven years running
that's what my publisher tells me
okay
and there's a reason
no marketing no marketing
no millions of dollars of marketing
money going in like the other books out
there
none of that it's because someone healed
and someone healed and someone healed
and someone healed and blah blah
blah and they learned not to eat eggs
they learned you know
i'm going to ig going ig i'm going ig
honey eggs eggs i want my eggs eat my
eggs eat my eggs eat my eggs eggs eggs
eggs eggs over easy eggs scrambled eggs
scrambled eggs omelettes omelets
scrambled eggs omelets almost protein
robot protein robot no egg robot egg
robot egg robot apple cider vinegar all
right apple cider vinegar apple cider
vinegar eggs eggs can i have levels
everywhere my eggs eggs i gotta go to i
j go to rj i've got energy
i'm putting tick tock back on try doing
that holding your breath the whole time
guys i'm going i'm putting telegram back
on putting tick tock tick tock back on
and i will see you guys soon
love you guys