I wanted the opportunity to meet people
who were going through their own healing
Journeys in the four years I've been
doing this I have seen so much healing
for the people who actually apply it and
keep going with it at the beginning of
my journey I can only drink a little
shot gloss of celery juice and now I'm
up to 32 o a day really just keep going
you know if you started and you're
doubting uh that's you know negativity
trying to pull you off your healing path
try it your body will start to thve and
you'll see a difference that gives you
the hope to keep going don't give up
yeah just keep going don't give up
believe in yourself you can do it
[Music]