foreign
yeah we're open today
yep
who's here we have a few different
customers today yeah hoot is here
yep
uh hootie's here Hootie coming right up
calm down hold on calm down
problems with hoodie
if you don't get hooties wild blueberry
juice there in time
you're in big trouble
oh yeah
who's flowing a long way to get here
okay so what do you need what do you
need
um we're not serving anything bird today
no
uh Hootie and who these friends are here
we're not serving chicken nothing with
wings no nothing no birds no we can't
serve anything like that
no Quail cartridge nothing no turkey no
turkey on the menu today at AWS Bar and
Grill
that's right you can get some onion
rings though yes that's fine all right
let me just keep on going here today is
a special day actually because AWS Bar
and Grill is serving a lot of different
recipes today
sure
come on in
you don't like owls why
what's the problem
they scare you
okay well maybe just don't don't go to
somebody else's Bar and Grill today okay
we gotta go
yes you guys
you guys don't mind that hoot is here my
friend and um listen today's day three
of the medical medium wild blueberry
challenge I'm really excited about this
day three day three we did it we're
three days into this thing this is
incredible oh
get a shot going this is the wild
blueberry juice right here still 10 off
which is incredible
amazing there's one down
one down one to go
nice
just let it resonate let it just take
over let it get to the brain let it get
to the body let it get to the
bloodstream
yeah it feels so good day three medical
medium wild blueberry challenge but get
this we're doing potato waffle right
here here we are
potato waffle I got my Waffle iron right
there let's just start making it soon
too oh
what else oh
okay
we're making this you guys I just want
to show you right here I'm going to try
not to knock over everything but we're
making this the potato waffle with wild
blueberry sauce have you tried it this
is right out of brain saver protocols
and I'm going to read out a brain saver
too but have you tried this up this this
this delicious recipe okay I'm excited
good to see you guys coming on it's day
three if you wandered in here of the
wild blueberry challenge we're making
recipes we're also going to make a honey
orange and wild blueberry refresher
that's exciting too all on its own so I
can't wait to make that
and will I be able to make it right we
will see I'm going to pour a little bit
more wild blueberry juice
now we have hoot here along with us if
you guys don't mind
coming right up coming right up don't
worry don't worry
coming right up
yes yes
okay I have some backup shots I know I
drank your shots
okay
Dr Leslie might be coming by later
I think Dr nesbit's going to give you a
checkup who
all right you guys so this is day three
I'm excited about this
Rumble is not working huh so Susan says
Rumble is not working bummer bummer
all right so here we go and if you guys
if you need to go to medicalbeam.com to
see me streaming live there we can do
that too so if you have any problems go
to medicalmedium.com
and you can do that so keep keep that in
mind all right you guys I want to start
now making the recipe I'm gonna read a
little bit too out of the brain saver
books this is special day it's day three
have you guys been experiencing the wild
blueberry juice inside of you the wild
blueberries inside of you have you been
feeling it what have they done for you
in your life post about it do reals
about it do stories about it I would
love to repost stuff because it's
incredible when you see people have
life-changing moments from the wild
blueberry juice and the wild blueberries
have you been doing each MDS all these
years have you been incorporating wild
blueberries into your life while
blueberries are different than
cultivated blueberries
so I want to run down a few things about
that too as we get going we're talking
about ancient food
ancient peoples
eating ancient food we're going to go
into that a little bit too that's
actually gonna going to be kind of fun I
think going into that so I'm going to
turn this waffle maker up a little bit
I'm gonna get it moving because I want
to get some waffles going so
here's what we're gonna do we're gonna
actually peel these are steamed potatoes
let's get these over here I got one big
bowl of steamed potatoes right there
look at that you guys
one big bowl of steamed potatoes really
excited about this Tyler says I felt
like I was glowing naturally High all
morning for my wild blueberry bowl last
night it gives me that feeling too like
it's just a natural high but when you
really break it down you're talking
about a food that has survived on this
planet for thousands and thousands of
years it has information in it survival
information it's an incredible resource
the wild blueberry so it's not like
having some cultivated blueberry which
doesn't give us that feeling and now it
never gave me that feeling of cultivated
blueberry so I'm gonna peel back some of
the skin
I'm going to peel back some of the skin
on
this potato these are steamed potatoes I
like doing it that way so you don't have
to take all the skin off you can you
know but I like doing it because you're
making waffles and you wanted a certain
texture
you know that's a great way to do it so
I'm going to put this right here in a
bowl
I'm going to peel back the skin on a
bunch of them I'm going to make a few
different waffles which I'm actually
really excited about
so you know a lot of people would be
like paleo man ancient man what do they
eat they eat meat meat meat that's what
it was it was all about hunters hunters
and gatherers but mainly Hunters
surviving on meat and meat alone right
you hear that all the time you know and
then the vegans are like no they're
Gathering they're Gathering they were
surviving on Plants right you know and
you know there's always that big
argument right there always happening
you got the animal protein side of of
the health movement then you got the
vegan side of the health movement
you have that and then you know sad
enough vegans they get scared and they
run back to the animal protein movement
the animal protein movement they'll do
the same they'll run back the vegetarian
or vegan or something but that's another
story another talk for another day
but what did people eat well it depends
on what part of the planet they were on
to begin with that's one right there
that's one place to understand
and that determined also a decent amount
but one thing's for sure berries were
growing everywhere on the planet that
anything can grow so berries have always
been around now
wild blueberries have been here for a
very very long time
so now what did ancient people survive
on now to begin with hunting was not a
definitive
factor that kept people alive back in
the ancient days so keep that in mind
okay because you can the amount of
calories and I actually taught about
this for over 35 plus years the amount
of calories you needed in order to hunt
was unbelievable you can't just hunt on
no calories we're talking about
traveling it's not like you go outside
your door of your Hut or whatever your
your little shelter and then you hunt it
five feet away
especially if the what the weather was
doing hunting would take a tremendous
amount of traveling where the animals
were in order to hunt right and then it
took physical physical strength to hunt
and to rhyme right and to carry the
Beast back as well so if you're hunting
it took a lot of physical strength to
carry the Beast back
this took a lot of calories
important to know so ancient people
right if they relied only on Hunting it
would have not survived
just the way it works they would not
have survived if they were relying just
on hunting and hunting alone
so that's an important thing to
understand because a lot of people are
like no it was all hunting and it was
all meat
but that's not accurate so then there
were times where
hunting was really really scarce and
it's been like that on this planet over
and over again
so what did ancient people really
survive on well first of all there was
always somebody they used in the village
or community
to taste test poisonous plant species
first and foremost there was always
somebody that had to do the taste
testing
98 of all the mushrooms growing on this
planet throughout these centuries were
toxic
so there'd always be a taste tester to
discover which mushroom may not be toxic
in order to allow a mushroom to enter
into the diet of ancient you know
ancient human beings ancient people
so
keep that in mind same thing with
berries berries were taste were taste
tested along the way right now there's
berries with really really dangerous
alkaloids these alkaloids would kill you
really quickly and sometimes kill you
really really slowly so keep that in
mind too so when it came down to ancient
people and food it was a lot of Hit and
Miss trial and error and that's what it
was about for many many times for many
many years thousands upon thousands of
years it was like that
so that's something to
think about
so a lot of people died
trying to find their way into what was
safe in The Plant World to eat now
there's a lot of plant species that if
consumed
your liver would shut down
or your kidneys would shut down
a lot of plant species
so it made it very difficult for
survival
depending on the region too
so once this was figured out along the
way what was safe what wasn't and there
were still lots of trial by Era
certain things were established certain
berries were established too
and that's important to know
[Applause]
all right so I'm just cleaning up my
board a little bit I'm getting some
potato it's all set right here all
skinned down
so what I did was I took some of the
skins off right here good to see you
guys
I see that someone said Wyman's yep it's
Wyman's that's what it is it's the wild
blueberry juice
is what we're using right that's the
wild blueberry shots right there it's an
incredible product I work with Wyman's I
support them I want the stuff to stay
around it's an incredible resource what
it takes to get them out of the field
this ancient food and then to actually
press them and to get them in the bottle
and what I love is all it is is wild
blueberry juice and that's what I love
just wild blueberry juice 10 off right
foreign
so nice
so these potatoes are already steamed
keep that in mind
I got the waffle iron heating up here
these potatoes are already steamed and
ready to go I am going to mash them
but I'm going to find my Masher
here they are
here it is and here's the potatoes so
let's go so I'm going to do a little bit
of potato mashing right now
now
ancient people ate a lot of shoots keep
that in mind
paolita says we can we can get wild
blueberry juice yes it's the Wyman's
wild blueberry juice right there
where can you get it Wyman's link is in
the description link is in the profile
w-y-m-a-n-s.com wines.com
that's where you find it right there
so
shoots were something that ancient
people ate what was a shoot
well you got shoots You Got Roots you
got rhizomes
you got mushrooms you've got Twigs you
got fruit like berries
ancient figs
depending on the region and where you
are but all regions there was always
some type of shoot you can eat
hence like the asparagus the asparagus
is a derivative from an ancient food
from an ancient shoot
and then you got tubers it's another one
too
so in these ancient Foods
throughout the centuries a lot of people
died trying out different rhizomes
different tubers
different berries different shoots
to get here it was a long road for
ancient people
it's not something like we see now where
it's pretty easy we got we have a clear
understanding of what we can eat and
what we can't eat
and even today we eat things we're not
supposed to eat after all's been said
and done we still actually eat things
that we're not supposed to eat how crazy
is that things are actually not good for
us and we still do that now
when you really think about that that's
amazing
that's kind of funny so I'm mashing
these up you guys because I'm making
waffles then I'm going to make a wild
blueberry sauce it's in the book right
here the brain saver books just want to
show you
talking about ancient people but we're
also making that right there
excited about it check that out
it's gonna be fun also making a drink
honey orange wild blueberry refresher
how insane is that
it's gonna be really fun
okay so I'm giving these guys a good
Mash you don't want your waffles really
lumpy you don't have to puree them
that's not what you want to do you just
want to break them up a little bit and
mash them some potatoes are softer than
the others this one right here is a
really firm potato the waffle recipe is
in the book Brain saver I'm gonna be
reading out a brain saver it's in the
protocols book
so I'm excited
so let me just now she's a little bit
more gonna make some good waffles
so
what did ancient man eat well Ancient
Man didn't survive on meat and meat
alone
if that was
the only option very little survival
would happen
so would often would often would occur
is the drying of things
so the way we survived and got here
today it was from drying
trying everything and anything that's
what it was about
okay we're just about there here just
about there there we go
all right all right all right crashed
crash
but that's why I like being live
you know I wake up in the morning I'll
tell SOC you think I'll let like knock
stuff over today
so she's like trying not to I'm like no
let's hope I do
all right
so let's make some waffles
yeah oops
so I'm gonna actually make these into
like a little ball I'm gonna put them
into the waffle iron I'm gonna bring the
waffle iron up here
we are alive
all right now I don't want this too big
because if this is a small waffle maker
these waffles are like thin
if I make it too big
it's just gonna be like trouble so I'm
thinking that's probably it right there
yeah nice all right
see if we could drop something else
oh sorry about that
you're getting upset because I'm
knocking all this over and
everything
are you getting upset
okay
oh
foreign
this waffle iron is
getting hot
it's flip hot
all right we're gonna pop this in here
you guys it was just
if you just got here
day three of the wild blueberry
challenge
day three
magically appeared or some of these
all right I'm gonna throw this in here
I can't help it I like to throw stuff in
the air
let's just
turn this around in a second but first I
have to do this before I do that so I'm
going to show you guys I'm going to
knock this
together now I might have made this one
too big of a waffle
do you guys like waffles these are
potato waffles
they're more than gluten free they're
grain free for people that are really
worried about grains
they're grain free
if you listen to my alien podcast
you guys medical medium
podcasts at Apple podcast did you listen
to the alien episode
that's an interesting episode it's got
good information in there
it's actually really cool
all right I'm gonna see what I got here
I'm not gonna open this up yet
I'm just pushing it down a little bit I
put more
batter in that one
grab myself another hand towel
all right cool
so I'm going to make another two
we got a couple to do
so
let's get back to ancient people's talk
let's talk a little bit more
survival depended on drying things
bottom line
wild blueberries were picked
during season
and then dried
before winter approached
if it was climate that was still
somewhat tropical or subtropical winter
still approached Seasons still change in
subtropical conditions places
regardless wherever the berry was picked
they were dried now certain berries
don't dry good
so if it's a wild raspberry it's not a
great
drying Berry
not a great survival
tool but yet all berries were dried for
the most part but not only that other
things were dried too
that's how survival happens I'm just
getting another waffle ready
just rinsing my hands
if berries didn't exist on this planet
there's a good chance
we may not have made it this far
because ancient people had to rely on
drying berries in order to make it
through seasons
here's a dried Berry right here here's
the Wyman's whole dried wild berries
which is really cool too by the way
check it out what did it look like let
me open this up
I'm gonna move my waffle maker over
want to look at these wild dried berries
right here
so that's how survival really happened
right there branching people
it was drying things and then carrying
with you as you traveled all the dried
items
these are the dried Wild lubers
pretty awesome
Theresa says thank you for making these
videos I want to make these videos I
want you guys to have information
I want you to be able to watch these
again if you wanted to I like the recipe
videos and that's what this kind of is
in the end really I'm making some
waffles
I think I gotta make the sauce that I
have to do pretty soon have you guys
tried the wild blueberries have you
tried the wild blueberry juice what have
you experienced I know what I
experienced when I have it
host any real stories or anything else
or posts of any kind and I at Medical
medium or tag at Medical medium or
hashtag medical medium whatever do both
so I could see it and then repost it
guys don't mind right
getting a little tipsy that's why I'm
knocking everything over
Dr nesmet might show up later
wants to do an examination on hoot
ew's Bar and Grill is getting pretty
messy over here
who's why you been so quiet
I'd never heard you so quiet it's the
craziest thing
Hoots usually making a lot of noise
okay I think I also need
[Music]
a glass of wine
it's getting crazy in here I think I
need a glass of wine too because who
wants a glass of wine that's it you
don't know how to speak owl
do you listen listen do you hear
wine
glass of wine
please
of course
and hurry up
hurry up fast okay I am
ah okay
I was gonna have the glass of wine but
apparently
glass of wine
all right let's get into it a little bit
I want to read a little bit out of brain
saver
perfect
all right
let's go you guys
waffle is not done yet
you guys you know
it's always like this at aw's kitchen
that's all I could say all right so I'm
on page 93 right here I got the brain
saver book have you checked out the
brain saver books anybody new here that
hasn't seen the brain saver books both
the protocols book and this one right
here there's two which is really one
it's a huge book originally publisher
couldn't publish it they couldn't do it
the printing was too hard became two
massive books filled with information
packed with information
and so these are the brain saver books
right here this is one of them a reading
out of it Amazon's selling them right
now get them for gifts for friends and
family you guys are 40 off right now
amazon.com us which is really incredible
and
I am happy about that so every day so
I'm reading page 93
so we'll get into it right now
everyday toxins and poisons inside the
brain are a large part of the brain's
limitations we experience so if someone
has a brain limitation of any kind
we're talking about toxins and poisons
inside our brain so if somebody has a
brain limitation of any kind
we're dealing with
some kind of toxin or poison that's
inside the brain
we experience so including emotional
limitations so if someone has emotional
limitations we got something that's
inside the brain that's in the way if we
have an emotional limitation
this is mind-blowing information to me
if an area of the brain is clouded
with an abundant level of poisons and
toxins
ranging from toxic heavy metals to
solvents to Plastics and other
petrochemicals to Pharmaceuticals
that have been there for 20 years 30
years to air fresheners
to fragrances descented candles which
get into the brain and beyond that area
of the brain that's clouded with these
brain betrayers
can almost go into a sleep mode
so what that means is if there's an area
of the brain filled with enough garbage
enough Pharmaceuticals enough toxins
enough poisons enough anything right
heavy metals petrochemicals all the
different stuff are up against chemicals
chemical solvents everything that we
breathe in every day everything we're
exposed to if there's an area in the
brain that's filled with enough of that
it can actually put that area of the
brain into sleep mode it dumbs that part
of the brain down and puts it into sleep
mode
it's incredible because you don't hear
that from research in science you don't
hear that from anywhere
it's just amazing information so this
doesn't mean we'll be sleeping so it
doesn't mean you're always going to be
sleeping just because you might have a
toxin or poison deep into the brain
someplace into this area where it's
actually putting that area into sleep
mode it doesn't mean that now you're
going to be sleeping
or that waffle smelling good at this
point
it means an area of our brain is not
functioning optimally so that means an
area of the brain is not functioning
good
so we'll rely more on other parts of our
brain
whoa see so when stuff gets gunked up
and junked up inside our brain we end up
relying on another part of our brain
that's less clouded and clogged up with
toxins it also means we'll be limited in
brain function you see a lot of people
out there they're struggling you've got
the brain fog they got all the different
brain conditions right they're
struggling because they're limited
because their brain is not functioning
the way it needs to function
in 10 years
you guys are going to see it
a lot of people's brains aren't going to
be working
five years now it's really kicking up
when emotional centers of the brain
become filled up and cladded with toxins
and poisons now that's the emotional
centers of the brain you guys that's an
entirely different area of the brain
we become more reliant on other parts of
our brain as a result we can become
limited in our emotional understanding
of others
that's when we can't really understand
others
because in our emotional center of the
brain there's some type of contamination
and that contamination can make it so we
can't be understanding on any level to
others
right do you ever hear those stories out
there
Waffle's still cooking do you ever hear
those stories out there
where it's like
the person to be like
my parents just don't understand me they
just don't get it or my stepdad doesn't
get it or you know somebody that my
stepmom doesn't get it
or my uncle doesn't get it my aunt
doesn't get it my brother doesn't get it
my sister doesn't get it and you ever
hear those stories out there it's like
you know the person's like going through
a lot they're struggling they're
suffering they've been through a lot but
for some reason siblings or family or
friends or best friends just don't get
it or understand at all what's going on
because that person that sibling that
Mom that Dad that the uncle that best
friend that partner whoever it is has
something clouding up that emotional
center of the brain you guys are reading
brain saver right now
which is Incredible Book to get to
people for the holidays and everything
both these books
two books
so we can become Limited in getting in
touch with our emotional state we can
become Limited in feeling and expressing
emotions Limited in harnessing emotions
too so if it happens to us it happens to
you it happens to anybody then all of a
sudden it's hard to even get in touch
with your own emotional state
you feel like you're always just lost in
that depersonalization kicks in too and
that's what happens when also
contaminants get into the emotional
centers of the brain
toxins and poisons clogging up the
emotional centers of our brain can also
mean that we become extremely emotional
without understanding why how about that
she ever meet anybody they get really
emotional they don't know why so now
they're going to somebody else to see
they're going to see a past life
regressionist now they're going to see a
therapist now they're going to see
somebody else now they're going they're
just like they're searching and
searching
because they don't understand why they
become extremely emotional and they
don't know why so they want answers
sometimes they get the answer that like
you know 300 years ago they were Queen
Victoria or queen somebody and they got
their heads chopped off and that's why
in a past life and that's why they're so
emotional because no one knows why
someone really is struggling emotionally
like that they don't know that inside
the brain
they got old Pharmaceuticals sitting in
there they got toxic heavy metal sitting
there they got all these other things
that are sitting inside the brain and
brain stem getting in the way nobody
knows so we got to come up with all
kinds of you know cool things I'm not
saying whatever I'm just saying that it
happens a lot
Reggie Natura says that was me before
medical medium
dreams can become very intense it's
another thing that happens too extremely
emotionally challenging where constant
dream After Dream After Dream evokes
emotions because the body is trying to
heal the emotional centers of the brain
so if you ever have struggling dreams it
depends on where all the toxins and the
poisons and everything is all inside the
brain and where and what part of the
emotional centers of the brain
but if you've ever had this
um there's there's a reason why that we
dream like we do because our body is
trying to out override it to do some
healing
so Ruth says there are people with
limited emotional intelligence
but seriously it is not always so
there's people with limited emotional
intelligence
everybody has Intelligence number one so
that's there
um that's not what you're saying that's
what I'm saying so your comment is there
are people with limited emotional
intelligence but seriously it is not
always about nutrition
but I know that's not always about
nutrition though it is talk though it is
toxic
we have many so toxic is what you mean
we have many paths that are connected
I'm not saying it's all about nutrition
medical medium information
is a vast amount of information so Ruth
what I what I recommend is you get the
books
did the brain saver books maybe cleanse
the heel tube maybe live a rescue and
learn about the incredible information
here including Soul information
including
you know other information too
but thank you for your comment and I'm
glad you're here I appreciate it and by
the way you're at the free Wild
blueberry
challenge were day three we're making
wild blueberries it's an incredible food
and you might want to get some wild
blueberries sign up for the challenge
too and you could actually get your free
grocery list and know what you need and
all that other stuff for it and you
could even re-watch the episodes at
medicalmedium.com
but what I recommend is getting some of
this inside of you so it gets to the
brain so then when you grab the medical
medium books Ruth
it'll help you actually open up so you
know what you're reading
Ruth says I think the information is
valid
well then guess what I am
I am proven wrong
and proven right
thank you
I'm proven both
proven wrong because I'm saying that you
need wild blueberry juice
and proven right because you said that
you like the information
um
Ruth I need some more wild blueberry
juice that's what I think
Brett Winters and by the way thank you
for your comment once again
Brett Winters aw what's the difference
between what you're talking about and
narcissism
what's the difference
well it all depends narcissism
is one aspect of how the brain works if
someone actually has problems but the
soul is always connected too because you
have four things going on so the problem
is with the brain and I talk about that
in the brain saver books
is you have your subconscious mind your
conscious mind
your physical brain and your soul they
all have to work together
in here
okay then that's critical to know
narcissism can be a blend of problems
so keep that in mind
and a narcissist
could also be a good person
so it doesn't mean they're a bad
narcissist versus a good narcissist so
keep that in mind too so all these
things matter
because that's about the soul
Soul subconscious mind conscious mind
and physical brain all these things
combine change everything
and then the Free Will changes
everything
amongst all of it you can have a very
evil narcissist out there
because they're free will
is allowing it or you can have someone
using their free will to be a good
narcissist
it's so vast the understanding and
what's happening
one thing for sure
if someone cleans up their brain
and they repair neuron damage
and they were already a bad narcissist
they might become a good narcissist
all right Free Will is the key Serena
said it
so
first of all I better get this waffle
out of the out of the waffle iron and
Ruth back to you thank you for actually
your comment and everything it was
really nice
okay
I'm gonna get a plate out right now
and I'm going to get a waffle out
you're not making a lot of noise
all right can you guys see this
I'm gonna open this up
foreign
I'm gonna make another two while we're
doing this and then we're gonna make
that's that's a nice waffle nice and
crispy it's hot
it's gluten free
it's dairy free
what else is it it's grain free
it's a potato waffle
it looks amazing
and I can't wait to
eat it so
crispy and hot I'm gonna put that in the
place
I'm gonna pop this in now
so let's make another
drop that down
squeeze it down you guys
right I mean isn't that waffle doesn't
it look good I can't wait to put the
wild blueberry sauce on it to be honest
I'm actually really looking forward to
it
guys I see people asking I do have a
supplements directory on medical
medium.com where I have kitchen tools as
well on medical medium.com check it out
foreign so I'm just kind of pushing this
down squeezing that waffle out so it
actually moves around
okay
place it back over here
just want more than one waffle
how's that look you guys see that on
there
all right
all right all right let's go back to the
book too you guys I'm reading out a
brain saver right here
I'm excited about these books have you
had a chance to find them over 100
recipes I'm making some of the recipes
the wild blueberry recipes in here as
you can see Wild blueberry is a big part
of the books
in some way shape or form because
of the power of the wild blueberry it's
really incredible food it's a wild food
and so I want to talk about this one
thing because people still bring this up
they say
wait a minute is the Wyman's wild
blueberry juice is it organic so let's
cover that for a couple of seconds too
because I did it the other day
so here's how it works with organic
farming
the crops can't protect themselves they
don't have the ability to protect
themselves
so they have to be sprayed constantly
so when it comes down to organic crops
they have to spray the crops many times
three times a week in many cases
so keep that in mind
so when it comes down to organic food
organic food has to be continually
sprayed in order for you to get
something out of it
if they don't continually spray
you're not going to get the food you
want it's not going to look good it's
not going to be good now organic crops
are sprayed with nicotine and copper
keep that in mind Copper's toxic
they're not using a trace mineral Copper
from a fruit or a vegetable that
naturally has it happens to be there
they're using industrialized copper in
the organic sprays
with nicotine and other things like MSG
now
when they spray organic crops
they're spraying those crops with
pollinator killers
that means the bees get injured
and other pollinators get injured
so
every time someone hits me with that
hole why isn't this wild food organic
and that's that's a problem why is it
organic
I said the other day don't give me that
holier than whatever thing about that
because you just don't know the
information so it's important so let's
step into it a little bit further
so
okay so wild blueberries
or wild food
tends to itself
almost always that means
bugs don't come and hurt the wild food
because the wild food will hurt the bug
keep that in mind
if there ever is a situation where there
is a bug affecting a certain part
of a field somewhere then yeah Wyman's
will use a spray but they won't use a
pollinator killer and then they test
their berries
and they test them out and they find
their zero percent pesticide residue but
here's the thing organic farmers don't
test their food for you as a consumer to
make sure you don't have any nicotine in
your organic produce
MSG in your organic produce and copper
they're not testing for that they're
under the blanket term organic produce
keep that in mind too
and so and then some of the people which
is really crazy some of the people that
will actually complain and say well why
does wild blueberry juice is not organic
that same person
eat at a restaurant two weeks ago and
had conventional sprayed food
that was sprayed though sprayed to
not like a wild food that really rarely
gets sprayed and they tested for zero
percent pesticide right instead they're
in a restaurant somewhere traveling
they're sitting there on their high
horse saying how oh oh why blueberries
aren't organic and they're sitting there
in some restaurant eating two or three
items in their dish that was completely
conventional and highly sprayed
so keep that in mind too there's a big
difference between organic and wild wild
is a food above organic no matter what
wild is above organic and that's the
incredible part of it all
but organic produce is sprayed three
times a week with pollinator killers
and that's not helping the bees
lyman's doesn't hurt their bees
keep that in mind
and they spray only when they need to
rarely depending and when they do they
monitor it and they don't use a
pollinator killer
and that's absolutely incredible because
it's a wild food and it takes care of
itself so this is like a really
important education on organic food when
I go to the store right
and I see some organic produce
I buy the organic produce but I don't
buy it ignorantly
I don't buy it that way I buy it going
that's probably got a load of copper and
MSG on it that's probably got a load of
nicotine on it
and I'm gonna wash my organic produce
when I bring it home because I know it's
got nicotine residue MSG residue and
copper residue I don't have to worry
about that when I'm drinking my wild
goober juice it's like freedom because
it's wild food but when I go to the
store that's what I well that's what I
see I see food because I have I see
everything right because that's that's
just who I am
and so I don't have blinders on I I'm
not allowed to have blinders on I have
to see everything for what it is
Janessa says I love when aw shines truth
through the brainwashing exactly
brainwashing
organic fields are so heavily Laden in
nicotine and copper it is almost
disturbing and disgusting but yet I
still choose organic food because
organic's better than
standard conventional
cultivated conventional produce organic
is better than that produce while food
is different it's above all of them
while food is above conventional produce
and above organic produce it's above
both of them
and that's how it works
really important to know because I know
that people get they get on their holy
horse and they're just like let's slay
aw let's take them down because he
doesn't know like what and they just
want to take me down it's like oh all
you're doing is just like
being like ridiculous because you don't
know what's going on and that's how it
works
and I'm gonna have a
nice little shot right here
all right
I'm gonna crack another bottle open
while we're looking into stuff you guys
I got I gotta start making a blueberry
sausage a little bit but I want to make
another waffle
all right you guys
all I have to do is take the time to
fully explain it's hard to keep up with
all the debunking
I already worked 24 7.
I'm already working 24 7 right trying to
get out free information do everything I
need to do and so it's hard to always
try to teach and explain and debunk
stuff misinformation it's so hard to
constantly do that
but what you'll notice is people get
hurt along the way right they get hurt
along the way
because they'll get scared about Misty
something they'll get some
misinformation and then they lose a
chance to even get what they need
and I can't answer every you know
everyone's
you know attack
I mean I can't tell you how many fake
stories there are
how much fake crap was made up about me
out there
and that's how Darkness works
they're the ultimate just whatever
and there's not enough time
in my day or in my week to just battle
all the
silly stuff Ariel says calm down ew all
right
but calm down
but yeah
the thing is it's important to know
because you know when I see that all the
time like it's not organic it's like
what anyway you guys I'm reading out of
brain saver right here and I'm making
actual waffles I'm excited
Hoots here with me who's been awfully
quiet but that's how who it is sometimes
so I want to look through I want to talk
about a couple other things in here that
are so powerful in this book right here
too okay
and
I'm in your emotional brain chapter
right here which is one of the most
incredible chapters in brain saver I
mean there's so many incredible chapters
in here
um and in the emotional brain chapter
it's so filled with with just incredible
information
and I want to read a little bit more in
a moment but let me get these waffles
going
all right let's make a wild blueberry
sauce first
got one more waffle in there that's
cooking right away
so two cups of Frozen
wow blueberry
I got some wild blueberries right here
let's get them into the pan
so we're going to do about two cups now
you can measure it
if you'd like I usually kind of know
what I'm doing with two cups it's pretty
easy straightforward but I do want to do
a little bit of a measurement for you
guys here
there we go
how many wild blueberries do you guys
eat do you have them in your hmds are
you eating them every day are you having
some of the juice
there we go we got the two cups we're in
here
[Music]
AWS Bar and Grill has got a lot going on
today
we're gonna do a quarter cup of maple
syrup
to get that in here
there we go
nice
nice quarter cup of maple syrup we're
making the blueberry sauce
wild blueberry sauce
[Music]
keep it together keep it together one
teaspoon of vanilla
are we at half time
one teaspoon of vanilla
there we go
nice
okay guys and then we're doing two
teaspoons of arrowroot powder
got my area powder right there check it
out
drop that in there
all right
let's mix this up a little bit
here we go
[Music]
we're at halftime
incredible
who
hoodie doesn't come around as often
[Music]
all right there we go
you guys ever heard an owl
that night have you ever been
blessed to hear in Iowa at night
it's really a beautiful thing
incredible
the secret mm music is that the secret
medical media music got another waffle
we should be good
foreign
guys I gotta make some orange juice
really quick because I'm going to make
the refresher so let's get into it
all right
got some oranges right here
[Music]
I'm excited about this because making
recipes out of brain fever is like
really like I'd rather do this than so
many other things right
I would rather do this
I mean really you know
so this is how the protocols
or actually this one's not so let me
just get this together here
let's just squeeze some orange juice
here
but I love making recipes out of the
brain saver book I'm going to be making
so many of them
I'm making the wild blueberry sauce out
of the brain saver book
so if you just enter here and you're
wondering where you are we're in the
brain
we're in the brain saver book we're
reading out of there we're also doing
the wild blueberry challenge day three
I'm squeezing some oranges right now by
hand I like to do it that way I like
being connected
to
this incredible fruit in my hand right
here I'm making the honey orange wild
blueberry refresher It's a Wonderful
drink
okay and I just need a cup of fresh
squeezed orange juice
we just got a little bit more to go
and we'll be roughly around a cup
by the way you guys Wyman's wild
blueberry juice is coming to Europe
early next year
I mean that's exciting to me
really is
and other parts of the world later in
the year how incredible
my son squeezed all of my oranges for me
so you're doing this too you're doing
the honey orange wild blueberry
refresher too your son's amazing squeeze
all the oranges for you that's
incredible all right we got a cup right
there
three
two
that's very special
all right so
we need a cup of
wild blueberry juice
we could do a couple of things we could
just add it straight to this
because
so we're going to add a cup of the wild
blueberry juice right to here
okay that's one cup of freshly squeezed
oranges that's one cup of wild blueberry
juice
too fun two to three tablespoons of raw
honey
spoons of raw honey let's do that
we have one tablespoon
we're going to knock down another
tablespoon of raw honey
great for the holidays
think about it right
any of you guys pressured to have to
drink champagne and wine and other stuff
during the holidays are you guys under
pressure at all I'm gonna do about two
and a half
are you guys Under Pressure to drink
like eggnog and all kinds of other
different things and what I love about
the wild blueberry refresher and also
the wild blueberry drinks
they're in the brain saver books
it's just an incredible option for
holidays like even if it's just holding
a glass
right holding a glass of of
what you know everybody's holding wine
and you got your wild blueberry juice in
your wine glass I mean even that alone
is amazing
so we're cooking up
everything here
foreign
so I'm stirring up my drink
ice is optional
so you can definitely like have some ice
that is optional
now what you want to do is you want to
serve this drink immediately by the way
giving it a good stir
all right
aw's Bar and Grill has a lot going on
here bear with me
and aw is
famous
for making a mess
it's got a control in here
I just want to mix this up a little bit
more
thank you
I want that honey to actually really
blend into the drink just right
all right I think we're getting closed
got blueberry sauce so while blueberry
sauce is actually coming around nice too
I just want to get a little bit of
orange peel here
you guys don't mind
all right
let's go
do you guys like to come over
then have one of these
that is an incredible Refresher
I don't even know what to say
I got the orange peel in there too look
at that right there you guys
there it is
I think it looks amazing
blueberry sauce is actually coming along
just fantastically
and I have to get the waffle now
and it's just about ready
here's another waffle
third in just so it's in there but
you guys there's the waffle right there
golden brown
there's no eggs in this waffle there's
no butter there's no nothing no Dairy no
anything
which is really incredible there's no
fat in this waffle too you want to put
my waffles right here
guys get a good look at that
get get the blueberry sauce going
are you okay who are you all right
who's hungry
want some waffles and some wild
blueberry
sauce too is that what you want
you guys know owl
okay what else
wants a mouse
on the side of the waffle
okay what kind of mouse
just any old mouse
hoot wants a mouse on the side of the
waffle beside actually a side of mouse
you like mice
you'll do what a rat
a wrap okay
I mean I I I maybe it was Bar and Grill
I don't think we have mice on the menu
but who you always do this to me every
time
can I try this
um
that's insane
that's incredible
so good all right so what I'm going to
do
is I'm going to put this on the waffles
right here
there we go
I'm excited
here we go
amazing
he put more on there if you want less
that's what I like right there
I actually like a little more than that
on top of my waffles
I like more wild blueberry sauce the
more the better
okay
right here you guys
amazing
that is an incredible dish right there
if you don't mind
something so good for you
it's not ladled in fat
and I say that really because what
happens is people combine all that fat
on top of everything and in everything
none of that's in here it's a potato
waffle
no grains
no Dairy no fat
and a wild blueberry sauce Alexandra
says the shots are making my brown spots
and skin tags disappear and more
incredible
I'm gonna take Hoots glass of wine
I'm gonna take some of this Refresher
so good I'm also gonna
dig into these waffles as well I might
make them all day actually
I think I'm gonna make waffles all day
long because I have plenty of batter
right here left over
Suzanne Boyer says what shots are you
drinking for that
right now
I'm drinking wild blueberry shots
what do you mean
can I
use my teeth on this one
can I use my teeth
I got I don't have four hands
I'm I'm having these shots straight wild
blueberry juice
okay
you guys I'm excited listen let me know
your experiences seriously what kind of
results do you get from wild blueberries
have you tried the wild blueberry juice
have you felt that some people say it
does all kinds of incredible stuff for
them
it's an amazing food watch day one and
day two streamed at medicalmedium.com
re-watch day one and day two I talk
about incredible things and such good
information what results are you
experiencing
uh put some stories out if you'd like
some real some posts and then at Medical
medium that I got medical medium and
hashtag medical meme so I can share them
too
you book both at the same time so I
could see them and then share them and
you guys with brain saver have you left
the review do you like the book have you
left a review on Amazon which helps
other people find their way on both
these incredible books right
and incredible recipes in these books
so we have just forewarning these books
are filled with so much information it
takes time to read it but everything you
will read will blow your mind and it's
way ahead of science and research and
these books are going to save a lot of
lives which I'm excited about so it was
worth every bit of the pain and
suffering to actually put them together
get on my newsletter
information about the light blast will
be coming up soon so get on the
newsletter so you can have a chance to
sign up
all of this is just wonderful stuff all
free free free
get the books for friends and family as
gifts and all that if you don't have
money to get the books 40 off at
amazon.com go to the library get them
for free doesn't matter to me so I want
you to have them
keep an eye on medical medium.com
because it is packed with information
and we're enhancing it constantly and
constantly we're doing so much there I'm
going to have some waffle if that's okay
now you can do so many things with
waffles now I always eat them by hand
right I don't use a fork with waffles
mostly I tend to like eat them like this
like like it was a little pizza
um
all right that's insane
so good
all right this is amazing
what huh what no huh
oh
now I'm just like I think I just
disappeared
look out for imposters you guys they
claim their medical medium Anthony
William
and you can now report in postures
at medicalmedium.com so if you see an
imposter they're claiming to be me
and they got my profile and they say
they're me and they're offering
consultations and all that which I don't
do
report them at medicalmedium.com I got a
little section on there
amazing
so good have you guys tried this
Rita says it's like pizza
so good
looks delicious
I love the blueberry sauce too the wild
blueberry sauce
when you can have something like this
that's that healthy that that's good for
you
it's a whole nother game
[Music]
insane who are you okay
who don't worry
I know there's no side of mouse and
there's no you want a rat
who do you want a rat
who I know you're mad at me
um
right
you guys
um Dr Nesbit finally came in he just got
out of surgery
Dr Nesbit would you like
Dr Nesbitt would you like a piece of
waffle
don't worry about Dr Nesbit
who likes Dr Nesbit because Dr Nesbitt
is a bird
you know
you're so good
Dr Nesbitt
Dr Nesbit is upset he feels like he
wasn't invited
he crashed he crashed the third day
I remember
incredible wild blueberry wobble
I don't care what anybody says
this is incredible
don't ignore hoops
you know
you guys I love you guys
thank you for hanging in there for the
ride
yep
well
all I can say
all right
Dr Nesbit
wants to go
all right guys
God bless you
please go back here