please I'm making something I call a
medicine guacamole really important to
see because when you see me make it how
I make it and everything you'd be like
now you know why it's medicinal it's the
medicine guacamole so I'm making hummus
making nut milk too making nut Butters
and here's what I'm going to tell you
guys okay I'm gonna show you the scam
that you guys are being scammed every
day in The Nut Butter world you see
what's going on right there I can't wait
to go into detail on this it's going to
blow your freaking Minds see that what
is that oh that's a lot of oil but why
and where and how come it's in my nut
Butters it's in all of your nut Butters
that's right can't wait to give you the
whole rundown on that this is going to
be a really fun time look at that oh
whoa what's up with that exactly you see
that oil right there you guys are
drinking all that oil uh-huh let's go
into it a little bit so I'm making three
different kinds of nut Butters I'm
making talking three different kinds of
guacamole I'm making a hummus and I'm
making something else I don't know what
it is I'm not sure celery juice and the
nerve acid gut stabilizer okay making
that two medical medium parsley shot so
what do I have in front of me on my
celery I got this incredible basil right
here I got these collard greens hot
peppers Rosemary oregano parsley got
some thyme lemons and limes right here
and of course the avocados for the
guacamole is this what we're gonna be
doing let's get on to it so right here
you guys this is the mm-1500 100 off 100
off on the machine right now this is an
incredible machine it is the medicine
maker I call that the reason why is
because it extracts to such a degree and
what happens with other juicers like the
basket juicers that everybody gets
suckered into because they think it's
easy or something to use what happens
with like the basket juicers is it's
deficient juice so you're drinking
deficient juice so you think you're
getting juice in you that's providing
something for you but it creates a
deficiency over time because it's not
extracting enough of the nutrients the
mm 1500
extracts such a large quantity of
critical nutrients literally leaves dust
behind to that degree almost and you
guys know I work with the mega and
everything this is the mm 1500 so I
can't wait to show you I'm going to make
some celery that's one thing all on its
own the one thing I want to run by you
guys
is the who's who is drinking celery
juice every single day
most almost everyone in Hollywood
drinking celery juice supermodels
drinking celery juice every single day
for their skin for their hair for their
nails everybody
that someone out there doing whatever
that's going on that you see out there
public figure Stars Hollywood people
whoever it is supermodels rock stars
most of the majority of them are
drinking celery juice every single
morning and there's a reason because it
is helping them get you know onto their
game the way they need it now for the
chronically ill it's critical celery
juice that's the whole reason reason why
I got the celery juice out there all
these decades is because for chronic
illness it's an integral part of helping
people recover very important to know
now here's what happens with celery
juice when someone just does one cup of
celery juice one glass of celery juice
once in a while it's not gonna do enough
you gotta stay committed you've got to
be distant disciplined you've gotta know
that you're worth it you got to know
that your life is worth it that you are
worth healing you need to know that your
body can get what it needs from things
like celery juice one of the incredible
medical medium tools which is celery
okay so I want to go into that let me
just run some go run some uh celery
juice through here
I'm pumped up I am totally pumped up
because I got people coming over later
and I'm making guacamoles for them in
the whole bit I figured let me just make
it happen for everybody I want you guys
to see it now you're wondering how am I
making guacamoles I'm making it with the
mm 1500 and your mind is gonna be blown
because I'm gonna show you how to make
guacamole with this machine not just one
variety three varieties all right so
let me get a little bit of celery juice
going here okay
and grabbing this grabbing a screen now
you want to strain your celery juice
keep that in mind this is the mm-1500 if
you guys are looking for a juicer it's a
hundred dollars off right now okay Mega
choosers.com you can see the link in the
description Link in the profile all
right so make sure it's the mm 1500
though important thing to understand so
right now
I'm gonna run some celery
here we go
this machine
cold press masticating juicer
with a triple auger
gets the nutrients out without damaging
or scorching
the vegetable or in this case the herb
what you're making right here is herbal
medicine that's what this is herbal
medicine you're making an herbal elixir
in herbal drink celery is not a
vegetable it is an herb Powerhouse
[Music]
all these things are important to know
it isn't just for crutus hay it isn't
just for dipping into something if you
use it this way you can change your life
if you're suffering from autoimmune
chronic illness eczema psoriasis
dermatitis skin problems rosacea
Vitiligo chronic fatigue syndrome
fibromyalgia any kind of autoimmune
disorder whatsoever multiple sclerosis
any kind of condition celery juice is a
critical part of healing so important to
know if you're dealing with mental
health issues OCD
um bipolar if you've been diagnosed with
bipolar depression anxiety Panic mystery
neurological symptoms which basically
everything is a mystery neurological
system out there
um in the medical world in the health
world so neurological issues tingles
numbness ringing in the ears dizziness
balance issues tightness in the chest
tightness in the throat all kinds of
weird feelings vibrations Tremors ticks
spasms you feel vibrations when you're
laying down
insomnia sleeping problems that people
don't realize are neurological all of
this celery juice is critical for
thyroid disorders hypothyroidism
hyperthyroidism anything to do with the
thyroid cyst nodules
celery juice is critical for
you see how important it is reproductive
disorders right ovarian problems
POS
endometriosis celery juice is critical
for it these things are really important
to know it's a hundred dollars off it's
the mm 1500 I'm cruising because I got a
lot of stuff to do I got three
guacamoles to make I got a hummus to
make I got three nut Butters to make and
I'm gonna show you guys how you're being
scammed so badly it hurts with the nut
Butters buying nut Butters is so abusive
The Nut Butter business is so abusive on
the customer yes you don't know it but
you're being abused when you go and buy
that nut butter and I'm gonna talk about
how it sounds like crazy but it's not
wait till I describe how it works what
goes on with nut Butters in the whole
bit so I'm really looking forward to
showing you guys
you know the thing is the transparency
is not out there every food we eat every
pack of food every bottle of food
transparency is not out there all kinds
of different things it's just not there
so it's important that people know
what's going on
now what you're seeing right here is
high compression this mm-1500 you guys
know if you have a 1500 or a 900 what
you see right here is really dry pulp
because of the compression someone might
say oh well look it's not going all the
way through oh yeah well there's a
reason why it's held back a little bit
because you're looking at high
compression you're looking if you can
see here with this camera right there
you see how that camera's on there you
guys right now how sick is that this
isn't wet and sloppy pulp this isn't
just wet drippy sloppy pulp this is dry
way drier than anything out there those
basket juicers it's a rip a total
rip-off it doesn't get the nutrients out
it doesn't squeeze the juice out you got
to be extremely wealthy just to throw
your stuff in there and let the basket
thing spin around and you're gonna be
wealthy because you have to buy so much
more produce to make a juice now but if
you're somebody with chronic illness and
you need to heal and you need to recover
and get your life back it's important
that you have something that's not only
extracting the nutrients that you need
to heal but you need okay you need juice
that's free and clear from any kind of
other contaminants you don't know that
are in the basket juicers it's a whole
nother thing all on its own and then the
cost for buying loads of produce and
getting very little juice out of it
putting way more into the basket and
getting very little juice that's not the
way to go so anyway already I got some
juice right there
so
I'm going to shut this down
I got a nice little screen here you want
to strain your celery juice the reason
why you don't want to pull you want
don't want pulp in there you don't want
too much grit in there the grit and the
pulp slows down the digestive process
you want this stuff going Lightning Fast
into your bloodstream Lightning Fast
into your body so it gets to your bones
it gets to your brain the electrolytes
get to the brain that's what you need do
you want your neurons firing and you
want them devouring all those minerals
and Trace mineral salts and all the
different nutrients that are in the
celery juice you want your brain your
brain stem and your neurons to suck it
up and devour it and bring it in and
tune up with it that's what you want
it's critical so all right
nice nice nice first of all I want to
show you one thing okay I want to show
you the pulp
you guys if you just came on here I'm
making three guacamoles and making a
hummus and making celery juice right now
I'm gonna make three nut Butters I'm
gonna show you what's going on in The
Nut Butter world that'll blow your mind
and I'm going to show you pulp that's
not wet and sloppy it's not and this is
very fibrous celery right here really
fibrous when if you're gonna go and
spend money on celery okay and it might
not be the juiciest batch this is not a
juicy batch of celery I remember when I
bought this right here and I looked at
it I was like your spindly you're skinny
and spindly and small the stalks there's
not a lot of juice in here probably been
you know sitting in a warehouse for a
little while before it got into the
store and even with all that I squeeze
the hell out of what I put through there
because of this machine the mm-1500
right I'm going to show you the pulp the
pulp isn't wet and sloppy so if I take
this pulp out of here there's nothing
wet in this right here so let me just do
this
you're not seeing all this wet and you
know the juice and the wet pulp critical
to know all on its own so I'm putting
the pole back in there right now
okay
all right and let me just pour this
juice into a
let's find something now you guys
boom all right
if you just got here
you guys are gonna have some fun I'm
gonna have some fun I'm making three
guacamoles one called a medicine
guacamole and I'm gonna show you why
you're looking at different forms of
medicine right here when you dedicate
yourself you have some discipline you
fight for it and you give your body what
it needs and you let that stuff into
your body what can happen is miraculous
life changing events in someone's Health
Mind Body mental health physical health
that's the celery juice right there
boom boom boom fresh off the press I'm
so pumped about that as I almost spill
the whole thing but we're live and
that's how it rolls all right and
we got the pulp which is dry 1500 mm
1500 hundred dollars off on this machine
right now it's the mm 1500 Link in the
profile Link in the description wait do
you see what it does I'm gonna make some
nut Butters because I know you guys are
eating nut Butters I see it out there
all the time people are having peanuts
and almonds and almond butter and Tahini
and all of that and you guys know I work
with the mega because these machines are
amazing this machine is I don't know but
the other ones I'm saying this is the
1500 that has the high compression that
squeezes the nutrients out that's what
I'm talking about right there pumped all
right I'm gonna make a parsley shot
nerve gut acid stabilizer Right medical
medium brain shot therapy I'm gonna move
this juice over right here you guys
don't mind
okay so I'm in the brain saver protocols
I'm gonna find it I have it marked
because this is a big ass book look at
this nerve gut acid stabilizer right
there
I just want to read that really quick
even though we're gonna be making
guacamois and everything else
use the stabilizing shot if you're
looking to strengthen your vagus nerves
who's looking to strengthen their vagus
nerves
Tremors shakes spasms
tingles numbness tightness of the chest
panic attacks anxiety
that's just to name a few who's looking
to strengthen their vagus nerves there
we go nerve gut acid stabilizer
if you're dealing with gastric spasms
flatulence chronic gastritis mild acid
reflux or other digestive disturbances
for including acute acid reflux right
you're looking at the nerve gut acid
stabilizer you feel your food is not
digesting and you want to change that
over time and build it up if you feel
like your food's not breaking down
nerve gut acid stabilizer
if you feel you have poor nutrient
absorption if you've been told you have
a microbiome or gut microflora condition
or problem which everybody gets told
that
they really don't know how to get people
better they don't know why they're
really sick but everybody's in the
microbiome microbiome take this take
that and this this this this 10 doctors
later 30 vials of blood here 10 vials of
blood here it's just so sad what's going
on out there you've been told you have a
microbiome biome problem right you still
don't know what's wrong with you you
feel as if you're toxic or your blood is
toxic that's what I love about this
nerve gut acid stabilizer we're going to
make it helps with the blood toxicity
which is a big deal talking really fast
here because I know I have so much to do
you feel that your liver and lymph are
toxic
stagnant and sluggish
you're feeling an acidy stomach acidity
Sensations in your throat or mouth or
acidity feelings throughout your body
your body odor is more noticeable than
usual
you're dealing with chronic nausea or
chronic bloating how many people are
dealing with chronic nausea or chronic
bloating out there I know a lot of
people are dealing with that it's awful
sometimes their bloating is so bad
they're out to here and they're just
bloated it's just oh God it's tough
you're trying to repair an acidic body
system and you make your body more
alkaline through the gut stabilizer so I
just wanted to read a little bit about
this next thing I'm making the nerve gut
acid stabilizer okay from the medical
medium brain shot therapy in protocols
right there
let's get into it
so I'm going to run some parsley in here
and I'm gonna get this ready right now
together
okay
there's a dedicated support line at
Omega so when you go there it's a
medical medium support line just so you
know for the mm 1500 900 you'll find the
information on this machine in the
description link is in description link
is in the profile
cmm1500 people
don't juice
like the medical medium Community juices
people don't put wear and tear on their
Machinery on their juicers like the
medical medium Community does
there is no community in the world that
runs stuff through juicers day in and
day out like the medical medium
Community there are people in this
community that are running brain shots
right here every single day two three
brain shots a day they're running two
celery juices a day
every single day they're doing this the
other juicers out there will never stand
up for that ever the basket juicers will
never stand up everything gets dull and
it falls apart it can't handle that
intensity it's not possible that's why
the mm-1500 is here it's here to handle
that and people don't realize that they
don't know how much juicing how much
dedication towards bringing back health
because the medical meaning Community is
a community of people that that were
really really sick bedridden big
difference between being not so sick
versus really sick with chronic illness
and chronic mystery illness not just a
little stuff here and a little stuff
there which is fine too because that's
that's hard on people and I understand
I'm not demeaning or undermining or
belittling that on any level but the
majority of the people in the medical
Maine Community Came From Hell
and back they were deep in the woods
deep in the dark woods with no sunshine
and they fought their way out and they
crawled and they fought and they
scratched their way out and they got to
the woods line and they entered into the
sunlight in the field because they found
answers and tools like such that we're
talking about right here like the right
juicers and the rights of doing celery
juice every single day and doing the
brain shots and so forth and so much
it's all right
I'm just gonna knock out that pulp right
there so I want to run some celery get
the nerve got acid stabilizer going
all right
probably gonna be a little bit of
celery still going in here too
parsley is really really tough
you need a powerful juicer that doesn't
destroy the nutrients but still juices
The Parsley okay sometimes you might get
a log Jam in here
when you're dealing with this much
fibrous material like the stems but the
stems of the parsley hold
these incredible minerals that help
bring people back
someone's someone asks me family friend
or somebody gets a hold of me and
they're like a w what do I do about this
or that and I'm like are you doing the
parsley shot are you doing the nerve gut
acid acid stabilizer
so right now
what I like to do is I like to do a
couple of different different shot
meaning like I like to do this once
twice three times a day
[Applause]
I'm running parsley through here
parsley is not easy to juice and this is
totally crushing it it is crushing it
and here's what's amazing the parsley's
coming out dry which means you're
squeezing out all the nutrients
what you'll hear out there is people
saying oh you want to just blend
everything you never want to juice
because you you um you lose all the
fiber and all that stuff but not when
you're sick and you need an infusion
you need a main line when you're sick
you need a main line of direct nutrients
and when you're using something like the
mm-1500 you're getting that many
nutrients out of it
you're getting a main line
directly into your system
all right so
foreign
probably one of my favorite things to do
is make the parsley shot which is the
nerve gut acid stabilizer I like the
nickname you know the parsley shot
just putting a little bit more in there
parsley gets thick
really thick in the container
now I'm not straining this one I want
this one real thick you can strain it
you can use the strainer which is fine
I'm gonna put a little bit more
you guys if you just got on here I'm
going to be making three different kinds
of guacamole on medicine guacamole I'm
gonna make a spicy hot guacamole I'm
gonna make regular standard
guacamole
a basic guacamole
all right
I got that to go through
why am I so excited today
all right
okay
one of the reasons why I'm so excited
this is practically dust
this is ripped to shreds
This is Dusty dry you can see the like
it literally as if it was a dried herb
did you ever play with dried herbs and
you see all like the dust and the powder
that's just coming off of the dried herb
have you ever seen that do you guys see
what I'm talking about good luck with
any other juicer ever seeing that you
will never see that in any other juicer
it's literally air drying as we speak
The Parsley fibers this has been ripped
to shreds but masticated crushed
carefully not overheated
this is unbelievable the nutrients that
just came out of there these are the
things that make or break
these are the things that make or break
you know I hear people out there say hey
I did mm I did it didn't get me better
and when you look and you see they did
all this cacao they ate every other day
they were doing too many fats they were
having too many cheat days which I
understand I'm not judging anybody they
weren't on any real protocols from the
medical medium information and then they
weren't juicing that much and they were
using maybe the wrong thing like a
spinning basket juicer and they got
ripped off and they didn't know it's not
anybody's fault it just happens out
there
and they don't realize would you do
something where you make the nerve gut
acid stabilizer where literally The
Parsley turns to practically dust dry
when you see you see that
do you realize what you're getting in
you
it's profound it's a whole nother game
whole nother situation for healing whoa
Okay so
I'm gonna get a little spoon in here
just mix it up
okay let's pour it in a shot glass
if you guys just got here we're making a
lot of things but this is an important
one right here let's go maybe we can get
a close-up on that one too
never know there it is you guys you got
the close-up right there boom check it
out
that is
the medicine right there
it packs a punch it has a bite
it's all medicine
it's smooth
silky but strong but powerful
send it down
sounds good nice
feels good
all right
okay
you guys have to understand something
very important
the fiber in a plant
we just poop out
that's what we do
now fiber is important inside our diet
but we get plenty of fiber plenty of it
you can eat an apple and get plenty of
fiber
you can eat some leafy greens to get
plenty of fiber but we're talking about
creating medicine the fiber we don't
need when we're trying to actually heal
ourselves of ailments
gut spasms gut problems Crohn's colitis
IBS
celiac
chronic fatigue syndrome fibro right
rheumatoid ra
all the different conditions that
everybody is dealing with every single
day
dizziness blurry eyes mysterious
problems ringing in the ears
vertigo tinnitus
whatever it is we need medicine it's so
important
but people will say well what about the
fiberate there the plant stem the fiber
is there to get the plant in the air
so that the sun can hit it
so the fiber is to erect the plant
so it's straight up and it finds its way
to the Sun
and in this case you don't need
all of the fiber you need the medicine
that's within the herb
in this situation right here this
machine
completely annihilated
that parsley in a good way in a profound
way it took out nutrients a nutrient
spectrum that you would never get eating
parsley and you would never get juicing
with other juicers it created a nutrient
profile for you to move the needle
all right
let's get going let's make some nut milk
that's the next thing I'm gonna make
some almond nut milk if you guys are
okay with that
just gonna move some stuff out of the
way
there we go
all right
mm 1500 is going to be at work making a
nut milk right here
what I'm doing is I'm going to put a
screen on here
that
okay and I have some soaked almonds
right here
okay
time to make some nut milk
excited
all right
let's go
I soak these almonds
you might be somebody that's not into
making your own nut milk if that's
if that's what your jam is not doing
totally fine
but you can make your own nutmo
if you guys hang out I'm gonna make
three different nut Butters
a hummus and three different guacamoles
with the mm-1500
this is the biggest sale on this machine
ever so far it's a hundred dollars off
the price is unbelievable for what it
can do for you and what what
it has to offer
the price can't be beat
so I'm making some pure nut milk
wait a minute here you know what I
forgot
ah
I forgot the natural flavors and the MSG
and the carrageenan I forgot to put that
in here ah bummer I forgot to put all
the poison into the almond milk you know
the kind that's in the bottles of almond
milk out there the kind that's in the
cartons all the poison in there the
undisclosed hidden ingredients you don't
even know about plus the natural flavors
which is MSG and toxic stuff plus the
carrageenan plus other garbage crap I
forgot to add that in here
darn it this is too pure what was I
thinking
what was I thinking
someone tell me please
I forgot to put the poisonous crap in
here
and everybody's drinking and eating
every day
so what I love about this machine is
because it has an ability to pulverize
to such a degree it's going to extract
nutrients out of those almonds that you
wouldn't get from the traditional
store-bought almond milk you get out
there every day you go and you go in
there I'm gonna get some almond milk let
me go get get another bottle of
poisonous toxic almond milk
my body deserves only the best
let me grab a cup of coffee and a
chocolate bar on the way out
all right the rest of that in there
all right
got some almond milk
ready
let's go
I can put this in a lot of different
different containers and so forth but I
might go in here instead so
let's see I'm looking oh
good to see you guys if you just got on
here I just want to tell you something
right I just made a parsley shot which
is a nerve gut acid stabilizer I made a
celery juice I'm gonna make three
guacamoles I'm gonna make a hummus I'm
gonna make three nut Butters and I'm
gonna show you something in a little
while that's mind blowing but I just
made an almond milk right now
fresh
wow
wow look at that
look at that
can you guys see this maybe we can try
to get a close-up too if we can I don't
know if we will be able yeah
yeah
we got a close-up right there
are you like them apples
all right
nice can I can I sip this is that okay
um
all right
[Laughter]
okay
I'm gonna tell you right now
if you get this machine and you make
this almond milk and then you take a
store-bought almond milk and you do a
taste test difference you do this one
and then you do that one
and your mind is going to be blown
I'll tell you why you taste pureness you
taste cleanness you don't taste the
poisonous crap they're slipping in there
and the poisonous flavorings that you
don't even see because they don't even
disclose it
like you don't
you don't taste that
um
whoa
you guys
that is so good all right okay okay calm
down calm down
I'm going to stick this back here if
that's okay
all right
next on the list
roasted almond butter
hazelnut almond butter
roasted cashew almond butter
but first i'm gonna have to torture you
guys a little bit not because I want to
I don't want to but I have to deliver
important critical news
to you
[Music]
take a good look
take your time
take a peek
I'm even gonna do a close-up down here
I'm going to put this one down here
okay
this was never opened
the plastic is still on the top
the plastic
is still on the top I need you to know
this
you guys this is worth every single iota
of your brain cells
this is worth every single moment of my
brain cells
our brain cells are working together in
unison right now
your brain cells and my brain cells are
Computing what you're seeing I'm
computing
my brain cells let's get into it
see that peanut butter
that oil
is not from those peanuts
see that almond butter
that oil
is not from those almonds
you can't see this as it isn't clear but
it's an unopened Tahiti
and the oil on top of that unopened
tahini is not from those seeds
it's not
from those seeds
I hate to give you the hard
true
but it's not
this is one of the best lessons you guys
can have
because the oils that are placed in all
the nut Butters
to save the nut butter company's money
declines your health
it declines your health and wellness and
well-being
this is a tahini right here
better yet let me get a shot glass out
you think the oil in all your tahinis
all your tahinis
take a look
that is straight oil and that's not from
your sesame seeds
this is part of why people can't heal
they think they're doing something good
for themselves
but they don't heal this is why vegans
don't heal and they go back to eating
eggs
this is why vegetarians and people who
are really mindful about their health
this is part of why they don't heal it's
simple things like this that they don't
know
and the medical medium has to
show the truth
that is pure straight oil but not from
those sesame seeds in all the tahini
bottles and jars that you guys have is
added oil that comes from someplace else
it's bulk cheap low-grade rancid oil
it's in all your nut Butters and your
tannies
and that's why it is absolutely critical
you learn how to make a nut butter
if if you don't want the machine if you
don't want the mm-1500 even though it's
100 off fine then don't eat nut Butters
choose not to eat a nut butter because
it's better and safer for you not to eat
enough butter
because of what that is right there
you know
let me get another shot glass or
something like that I think I got
another one somewhere I'll just rinse
this one out real quick
all right
the oil you're looking at is not from
those nuts or those seeds
it is added to save the nut butter
company's money
it cheapens it
they're putting old rancid oil that
comes from bulk nuts from around the
planet
it's like people who are eating animal
beef right now right they're animal
protein eaters medical medium
um
uh is Pro
vegan plant-based animal protein
vegetarian whatever and you just gotta
come here get the information learn how
to heal if you want to be an animal
protein person fine if you want to be a
vegan fine but this is important to know
for vegans plant-based people and for
animal protein people
what are people doing now who are eating
animal protein they're really concerned
and worried about where their beef comes
from where their meat comes from right
they'll say they want the local butcher
that cuts a piece from that one cow they
don't want chopped meat from a thousand
cows Blended together so when they have
a hamburger
they don't want a hamburger that has the
DNA from a thousand animals
I mean that's original medical meme
information though that I brought to
that world
though regardless
you 30 years ago that was a mind blower
for people when I said that a hamburger
will have a thousand cows in it
it was like literally 35 years ago it's
one of the one of the things I was
telling people they're like that doesn't
make sense but it does
but here's the thing you don't want your
nut Butters
to have almonds
right
from one Orchard
but oil
from a hundred different Orchards or
some Orchard on the planet somewhere
else
you don't want it so separate and you
don't want it added into your nut butter
you don't want oil added into there
it depreciates your health
it's not good for your heart
it's not good if you have chronic
illness
people are eating all the peanut butters
all the almond butters all the tahinis
all the cashew Butters all the hazelnut
Butters and don't realize it they're
drinking oil that's declining and taking
down their health and they don't even
know it this is the death by a Thousand
Cuts
this is the mm Death By A Thousand Cuts
so I got another shot glass out here
and I just poured
two shot glasses this was never opened I
can do it to four different tahini
companies five different tahini
companies this was never opened I just
opened it for you and I just poured
two of these sesame oil shot glasses
I just poured four straight ounces of
oil that wasn't from those sesame seeds
and you guys will be drinking it when
you take your tahinis out you'll be
drinking that and you don't even know it
and I'm gonna be careful with these
because these are going to Spill and
what a mess they're gonna make so I'm
gonna put them maybe over here
let's hope uh
that's an almond butter that's never
been opened look on top
that's not the the oil from those nuts
that's a peanut butter never opened look
on top I'm gonna open it right now and
I'm gonna show you something
there's
the lid never been opened right there
there's the safety lid
I'm gonna move these over for the moment
let's get started
there's so many different things that
stop us from healing when we're really
sick we have to go all the way sometimes
we have to incorporate more tools and
more tools and then we got to be careful
and we have to weed out the crap in the
garbage because there's people out there
they're doing some mm but they're also
doing whey protein powder which takes
down your health there's people out
there they're doing mm and they're doing
all these nut Butters which sure nut
Butters are pretty good it's not the
worst thing now Butters are good for us
in so many ways right but they're
drinking gobs and gobs of old
dilapidated rancid oil that came from
other places in the world and was bought
in bulk in a cheap way and then
impregnated into each bottle
and so these things knock us down
there's a thousand things out there in
the health world that chip away at
people while their bodies trying to
fight to survive this is the mm-1500
it's 100 off let's get into this let's
start making some nut Butters right now
let's go
I'm gonna use this I'm gonna turn this
on
Godspeed
[Music]
all right which one do I want to make
first
let's make some almond butter
there we go
look at that this is roasted almonds
whoa look at that
take a look you guys I gotta do it nice
and even so I can get a nice even stick
look at that what maybe I can get a
close-up to in a minute
whoa that's insane
that's what almond butter is supposed to
look like there it is everybody and then
spinning basket can't do that the
spinning basket juicer they can't even
juice
um vegetables properly
what's a medical medium live without a
little fun
look at that
take a look
the thing is when it comes down to being
sick every little bit counts
every little bit counts that means if
you're going to eat a nut butter
you want to make sure you're not totally
being screwed over or taken advantage of
or ripped off or your body
being betrayed
The Nut Butter companies are betraying
people
bottom line
look at look at this Nut Butter right
here look at these roasts look at the
roasted almond butter going through here
look at that
that's insane right there you guys see
this
probably one of the most mind-blowing
things
from the mm-1500 link is in the
description link is in the profile
Victoria Smith says what is the point of
companies to put oil in their nut
Butters confused while they add it
because they use less nuts which cost
the nut butter companies a lot of money
they use less nuts but bring in cheap
bulk oil that cost them pennies pennies
and then they mark up the price of your
nut butter jar stick it on the Shelf at
Whole Foods or whatever food store and
you pay for rancid old oil
how's that for an explanation
oh fact
[Music]
all right you guys I just made some
almond butter right there let's get a
close-up on here
look at that is that just sick
right where's all that disgusting oil
that's added later and here's the
problem it's you can't you can't be sure
that they're just adding plain old oil
they could the oil could have garbage in
it crapping it it's bulk rancid old oils
in every nut butter out there
that's what nut butter is supposed to
look like right there mm-1500 boom if
you guys are sticking around I want to
make some more Nut Butter but I want to
do even more than that I want to make
three guacamoles I want to make a hummus
this is the mm 1500 it's 100 off I don't
know if they're ever gonna do a hundred
dollars off again
usually it's sixty dollars off forty
dollars off or 80 off the biggest I've
seen is 100 off Baseline says it's so
messed up and they say on the jar oil
separation is natural evil
I can say so much about that comment
meaning amazing comment I can say so
much about that I could go to town on
that but I gotta kind of like keep it
contained
got to keep it contained a little bit
all right
[Music]
hazelnut
butter
hazelnut butter
is there a happy hazelnuts right here
the happy hazelnuts
so happy hazelnuts
okay
all right
now why should we even care about all
that added oil I'll tell you why
diminishes your health
lowers your immune system
burdens your liver and your heart look
at this beautiful hazelnut butter coming
out of here
heavy on the liver and pancreas
now I'm gonna pack these in little jars
too
pure hazelnut butter
no attic toxic oils if you guys just got
on here you have to see this from the
beginning so you know what's going on
I've seen people they're like I don't
put anything in my body that shouldn't
be in my body but let me just eat all
this nut butter oil that's rancid and
dumped into here and ripping me off in
my body's Health taking away my body's
health
and they don't even know it
running some hazelnuts through here here
we go
I'm gonna pack them into jars in a
minute but I'm just gonna actually just
get them into their nice beautiful Bowl
so let's get a close-up on the hazelnut
right here
look at that
is that just gorgeous and I'll give you
guys over here a close-up you guys here
on Tick Tock IG
nice little close-up as well all right
let's keep on doing it roasted cashews
let's go
now
when you make your own nut Butters it's
a game changer
now if you're not going to eat nut
Butters
and you're gonna buy a store-bought one
once in a blue moon don't buy it
don't buy it
it's not worth it
if you give nut Butters to your kids
your children your family members
that you want
then you want something that works
you want you to make your own
fresh clean
non-rancet oils no oils in there rancid
oils thrown in there to cheapen it
you guys link is in the profile link is
in the description
I'm just making some roasted cashew
butter
and then we're gonna move on
now here's the thing though there's
people that can't have they don't have
any options so what I recommend is if
you buy a nut butter
if you buy a nut butter which is fine I
recommend pouring the oil out
that's something you can do pour the oil
out like I did so if you see enough
butter you like because you're going to
eat nut Butters and you don't have any
other way to do it you don't have a
machine that makes your own pour the oil
out
so when you get a nut butter
it's important it doesn't get rid of all
the oil you know I have a friend the
other day that said listen I'm gonna eat
enough butter no matter what I said okay
then then here's here's some good nut
Butters
it's still going to have this oil in it
it's still going to be oil that's just
bulk oil that's cheap that's from other
places around the world that's how it
works but dump the oil out if you can
try to dump as much oil
you possibly can out
and that's what I tell friends and
that's why I've even said people come to
me like look aw I'm gonna eat nut butter
no matter what I go I got you totally
understand there's some brands that that
I like then anyway they're like you know
some Brands out there I've talked about
I say look you can look at this brand
that brand but I tell people I give them
tips if you're gonna have it anyway dump
the oil out so what you want to do right
there
is you want to dump that oil out
it's still not going to get rid of all
of it by far but it gives you a better
shot because there's people that are
going to just go and buy it anyway so I
want to just give them options if
they're going to do that anyway all
right so we just did some
um roasted cashew butter that's roasted
cashew butter
now here's raw cashews you can make a
raw cashew nut butter as well so there's
raw cashews
into
some little jars really quick I could
pack this one in so here's the cashew
butter right there
no
[Music]
there we go
guys so great to have you in my kitchen
I'm honored you're here
so what I'm doing is putting it in these
little jars and then I put a lid on it
you might be able to see this on a
close-up too it looks really cool
so I'm packing it down with my hands my
hands are clean
I wasn't out at the post office or at
the store or grocery store and I was
opening up all kinds of doors out there
and had my hands on the shopping cart
and carriages and now I'm putting my
hands in here so I can put all those
little buggies that I picked up
somewhere on my hands in here but no my
hands are clean
I'm actually packing in this Nut Butter
right there there we go look at that
can put the lid on it
boom
let's get the lid on straight okay
there's one right there let's get
another one
you guys are making three guacamole soon
I mean look is it just me or I care what
I put in my body
I mean I know that right is it just me
no it's not just me it's you guys too
I mean if you're really if you're really
chronically sick
everything matters
all right so I just packed some nut
butter in here now what you can do is
you can pack it down in there
like this
here we go
I mean I'm doing it quick
a real quick
version of it right there
and I'll do the other one in a little
bit let's get moving I want to make you
guys a hummus
which I'm totally
truly truly excited about
all right do a quick little cleanup
we're moving along
I have a mess on the floor
I have a mess on the floor and I have a
towel on the floor and I'm kind of
kicking it around right now
and I want to get rid of these
nice
all right you guys
Let's Roll
time to make some hummus who eats hummus
just want to ask you guys
something you eat once in a while is it
something you eat a lot of now I don't
like to buy store-bought hummus because
of all the stuff that's in it the amount
of junk and garbage that's in a
store-bought hummus it's really scary
actually frightening to tell you the
truth okay so I got chickpeas right here
I want to show you guys
you can make black bean hummus lentil
hummus these are garbanzo beans
chickpeas this is the kind of hummus I'm
making right now
it's going to make a simple hummus I'm
going to take orders what would you like
in your hummus is there anything
particular you see I got different herbs
here
um I got lime lemon do you like lime in
your hummus or do you like lemon in your
hummus
do you like garlic in your hummus
I think what I'm gonna do is grab a
garlic clove now and get it ready
how much garlic do you like in your
hummus
you like a lot
or a little
I tend to like a lot
but I've seen you know people where it's
like whoa too much that's way too much
garlic I don't like my hummus with that
much garlic in there okay now what
you'll see here is instead of putting
tahini I am going to put sesame seeds
one thing you're not going to get with
sesame seeds is all that added
gnarly oil you're not gonna have that
it's just the seeds plus the sesame
seeds have so much flavor you can just
add a little bit into your hummus in the
mm-1500 and it'll actually grind it all
together it'll get that flavor all
through the hummus so that's what I'm
going to add I have people coming over
later they like salt I want to
accommodate anybody whoever comes over
and I will make them anything they want
I promise that the hummus would have
some salt in it
so I'm going to find the salt in a
little bit here it is
all right
in a making decision right now what do I
want in here lemon or lime I think I'm
gonna go with a lemon
and I'm going to cut that lemon in half
and get it ready there we go
okay
and the other decision is am I going to
put herbs in here
yes I am I'm gonna do a little bit of
Basil
we'll see we'll see
maybe none at all
all right
Let's Roll
extremely low-fat hummus
hummus in the store usually has a mix of
canola and olive oil
canola oil declines your health
I've written about this for years in the
medical medium books
right
I'm gonna drop some sesame seeds down in
here take a look you guys is that insane
sesame seeds down in there I'm gonna put
a pinch of salt down in there too I'm
even gonna drop some lemon juice down in
there look at that
it's crazy
I'm gonna drop a clove of garlic down in
there too in a little bit
here we go
let me drop a clove of garlic wow
it's insane
so good
[Music]
okay
look how incredible that is you guys see
this
is that insane
right
homemade hummus out of the mm-1500
I'm gonna drop a little bit more sesame
seeds down in here get that flavor but
you're not burdening it with all that
fat you're not killing your pancreas
one of the things that happens out there
is people their pancreas just takes the
licking and takes a licking and one day
their pancreas says I can't do it
anymore you've been killing me without
realizing it
okay let's get some more lemon in here
nice
real nice
this is gonna taste so good I got that
one big clove of garlic in there
I'm gonna make a big one
because uh I think Bryce might be
showing up
I don't know if you guys remember Bryce
he's actually transformed ladies not
doing so good
make sure you get the mm-1500
not if you're trying to if you're saying
oh look I'll go to Omega I'll go get
this juicer he might end up not getting
the mm-1500 make sure it's the mm-1500
for all these reasons that I've already
showed you since the celery juice and
the parsley and everything else
[Music]
I'm gonna pop in a few more sesame seeds
how incredible is that
seriously
[Music]
trying to do this like nice and
click here I'm doing this one without
fresh herbs
I'm just doing a straight
hummus
for my guests lemon
a little bit of salt
[Music]
there you go
and garbanzo beans
[Music]
there it is right there all right
voila nice
make sure it all comes out
perfect let me move these sesame seeds
I'm gonna give you guys a play-by-play
you move this ball
who knew like taking care of yourself
could be fun
so fun all right let me shut this down
we have a hummus right there
creamy creamy hummus
and you can put a fresh herb on top let
me do that
so I'm mixing it up a little bit just a
little bit of a mix
look at that
see if I can get you focus right there
okay
and I'll show you guys so I'm just
mixing it a little bit there we go
okay
all right
you can put fresh herb on top of this
just a little bit of fresh basil on top
real quick
if you want it in a bowl like this but
I'm gonna put it in like this great
display
I'm putting a little bit of Basil on top
and I'm just going to squeeze some
additional lemon on top too
there we go oh just got lemon in my eye
how many people get lemon in their eye
there it is that's the hummus from the
1500s
right
I want to show you guys I'm going to put
it in here
foreign
a nice scoop it on top I want it nice
and tall
I'm just going to go right here
you guys if you stick around I'm making
three guacamoles there it is right there
gorgeous little display for people
coming over
that's a rice cracker right there with
no oil or anything doesn't have any of
the bad oils in the crackers and the
chips right but that's the little
display right there
link is the link for the 1500 the
mm-1500 juicer a Nutritional Center
is in the profile and the description I
see people asking about it
all right
now we're going into the heavy duty
we're making the guacamole
yeah
I'm a little nervous I gotta be honest
I'm a little nervous
guacamole time
all right
I'm gonna use
this bowl right here
okay I got some avocados I want to give
you guys a couple of avocado tips
when is
I've showed you this before
you'll see there's a butt where the stem
was so the avocado was hanging off the
tree and the stem went like this and it
was attached to the avocado and then
when they Twisted it off or it was cut
off the stem
the avocado Growers it left the piece of
the stem right there and what I see
happen with people's guacamole is
they're not prepared to bite on such a
hard knobby thing and when people make
their guacamole that knob see I just
took it off
then knob goes in the guacamole
so many people
had that happen a friend of mine was at
a restaurant in La and was eating
guacamole
with his friend
and he watched his friend bite onto that
very thing
that was in the guacamole and like bit
it
injured themselves bit their tongue bit
their lip it was the weirdest thing he
said it was the strangest thing they
took a look at what it was and they went
they were like we want to show you what
was in your guacamole and they're like
that's weird how did that get in there
that's because chefs do it all the time
as they're making and preparing
guacamole that knob actually ends up in
the food
and so many people's guacamoles here's
another one right here
I'm taking this one off there it is make
sure you remove it before you start
making your guacamole in your bowl or
whatever you're doing all right cutting
open these avocados
preparing them really quick it's easy
and we're gonna make
a really basic good guacamole at first
so right now I'm doing this
let's get another one
wonderful
okay
all right
so
there's the avocado half I'm just taking
a spoon you can take any spoon you want
in there removing that
I'm gonna put that down in there
these are not fermented these are not
spoiled
what happens to a lot of people is they
buy them dark do not buy your avocados
dark like this unless you're taking a
risk because you're gonna this is one
that actually is over ripe in my hand
you buy these over ripe you get a bad
experience what happens is the avocados
fermented it's spoiled it'll have dark
spots or if it doesn't have dark spots
in there it could be fermented anyway
and you have a bad experience a poor
experience with your guacamole not even
realize it you're eating spoiled rancid
old avocado and you don't even know it
so what you're seeing here these are not
these even though there's a dark spot
right there these are still good
there's a difference between a dark spot
and totally Rancid
it's you can actually take out like a
little dark spot if you want but there
we go
all right
I'm gonna do some lime
maybe uh let me crack open another lemon
I'll do a blend of a little lime and
lemon with this one here
okay
all right so the attachment for this if
you've done the if you actually own the
mm 1500
do you own the mm-1500 there's a little
attachment right here
trying to get it out there it is that's
the one I'm making hummus
that's the one I'm making guacamolean
it's this little attachment you'll see a
little bit of the hummus left over in
there
see if I can push that out
I'm gonna put it back on the front
okay
this piece on
here we go
all right let's roll three hummus that
not hummus is sorry three
guacamole's to make
we're live
it's a little bit of that left over and
then we go
this is so great
pop another half in
I'm making a basic one
for people that just like a basic one
that's all they like
they don't want anything in there they
don't want medicine in there they don't
want
anything fun in there they don't want
spicy they don't want anything right
they just want salt
and lemon
a lot of people have the most basic
guacamole
and that's fine
or they want lime
I have a lime right here
so what I'm doing popping these pits out
let's keep it coming
there we go
I'm gonna squeeze the lime in there
a little bit of lime down in there like
that you guys see
and I'm gonna put a little bit of salt
down there too
salt and lime
all right this one's done
let's pop in some more in here
there you go
foreign
that's a lime
a little bit of sea salt
that's just a plain
clean guacamole
what you won't find in there is like
cheese milk sour cream
any kind of crazy oils olive oil is
added into guacamole all the time it
shouldn't be it should just be like
fresh and clean just like that you can
put fresh herbs on top if you like
okay
I'm gonna put it in this guacamole Bowl
and then pop some fresh herbs on top
and a little bit extra lime
a little bit
Sprague
there of sea salt I kept the garlic out
of this one this is a real basic one
and then you can put any kind of fresh
herb you want
cilantro basil anything
foreign
cilantro basil
chives
all right
and I'm gonna pop some lime on top
because as you know guacamole
it's going to be sitting there for a
while and I want to keep it looking as
fresh as possible and there we are right
there that's going to go in this tray
I'm gonna get another one rolling now
okay
all right next
this next one is the medicine guacamole
the difference with this one is it's
going to have a lot of intense herbs in
it
you want to make the most out of every
meal you have
so what I'm doing is cutting open a few
avocados really quick
I didn't want to pre-cut them because I
didn't want them oxidizing you know when
you actually open an avocado if you let
it sit too long it starts to oxidize I
didn't want that to happen so you guys
got to hang in there while I just knock
out a few of these like this real quick
there we go
that one's a bad avocado
bad avocado
that's a good one right there
let's get another one
got one right there a little iffy but
I'm gonna hold on to it
of course is they're dropped all the
time on the floor and then the produce
guy comes around and he puts them back
up and then people come around and they
they're going to get their avocados and
they drop
a whole bunch on the floor and that's
one thing that happens or they squeeze
them people go in and they're squeezing
their avocados all the time all right
let's roll
so I'm putting herbs in with this one
give me a lot more intense
if you guys just got here this is the MN
1500 it's 100 off I don't think I don't
know if they'll ever do that again
100 off is definitely pretty crazy
I've not seen a sale on this model this
unit
ever like that
I'm gonna put some lemon in here too and
lime
get some lemon juice going
nice
here we go
all right
this is going to be a fresh herb one
kind of making a mess today there we go
all right
let's get some fresh herbs in here
first of all basil extremely medicinal
you run a little bit of that in there
this isn't for the faint of heart I
challenge you guys for a medicine
guacamole
can you pull it off
medicine guacamole there's two types of
basil there's a Thai Basil and regular
standard basil I'm gonna put some
Rosemary in this one
straight Rosemary
from my garden right there look at that
Rosemary is extremely medicinal as well
I'm gonna put lots of Rosemary in there
I'm gonna put oregano in here as well so
this medicine guacamole is going to have
some serious oregano right there
boom
and then last but not least I'm going to
put sage in this guacamole
incredible
blows my mind
making this as quick as I can
because I want like guacamole
I'm gonna get some lime in here
foreign
there we go a little bit of salt
but this is the herb one right here you
guys
it's hanging up a little only because
these avocados are extra extra soft
today
[Music]
let's see what we can do
there we go
nice
nice nice nice nice
that oregano
big hunk of it in there I'm gonna put a
little bit more
basil in there
and then I'm going to put some thyme in
there too
nice
this time is already dried it's from my
garden
okay
let's get a little bit more of this
avocado
now
one's eating out their guacamole
that
has this much herb this much medicine in
it they're not having guacamole with a
lot of rosemary thyme Sage
two kinds of Basil
there we go
all right
I'm gonna move this over
oh
there it is you guys now this is a
medicinal one
it took a little time because I want
enough herbs in there and I want the
kind of herbs obviously these are all
fresh garden herbs all the stems
included some of the stems were included
too
which is
really serious I'm gonna spray a little
bit more lemon on top of this
foreign
amazing
I want to show you guys what I got
yep I have lime in there but I want to
show you guys take a look
there's a simple
regular guacamole
lime and sea salt and there's the
medicine one right there
Sage rosemary thyme two kinds of basil
and oregano
big difference when you're having it
like this so if you're going to be a
guacamole eater if you're going to be
eating avocados take advantage of
putting the medicine in it
so it's not just like
by itself of course you can have avocado
by itself it's it's still a powerful
beautiful fruit
there you go
I don't want these to slip off the tray
but can you guys see
foreign
I want to make one more guacamole
this one's kind of like real edgy really
spicy
this one's going to be really edgy so
let's go let's work on it
getting some avocados out now
there we go
that's a decent avocado right there
pop the Pips and pits out real easy
see guys on the spicy stuff I'm a real
like I like hot pepper I like different
kinds of hot peppers that's just me you
know I know that a lot of people don't
like that or their stomach can't handle
it
um I have like one of those stomachs of
Steel
this is great for football season by the
way party season holiday season
if you're taking care of yourself during
the holidays this is a great way to do
it
just getting some avos ready right now
okay you guys
yeah that nut butter thing just blows my
mind even till now it just blows my mind
when I think about it what I like about
the mm1500 is
I mean you can knock out so many
guacamoles like this
if you have your stuff ready you could
just boom knock these babies out
so we've got another one here
all right
turning the lightning speed for you guys
all right let's roll
this one's a spicy hot one I'm gonna get
these cayennes
so one Cayenne in a guacamole this size
is already probably too spicy like one
of these
I'm gonna put
three in there
okay
it's going to be really hot really spicy
I don't recommend doing that though like
at your house if this is what you're
gonna do just put like a little bit if
you're into it but don't overdo it
foreign because that's a lot
all right let's roll
it's gonna be the spicy one
here we go
when it comes down to chronic illness
and someone's really struggling
if they
if they give their body what it needs
their body
knows
it knows you're trying to give it what
it needs
it knows you're working hard on it
communication with your immune system
is important because every time you do
something good for yourself tell your
body that you're doing it
I am going to make a medicine guacamole
talk to your immune system I'm going to
make a medicine guacamole for my immune
system
[Music]
I'm putting a garlic clove in this one
so not only is it going to have the
Cayenne
the garlic in it as well
[Music]
now
what happens is that if you're going to
be not eating avocados that's fine if
you're going to be doing something like
the 369 or the 28 day cleanse without
the avocado if you're going to be doing
a 369 or a mono eating cleanse without
avocado because you're working on a
deeper level of your healing process
that's incredible
but if you're gonna eat a guacamole in
between or some avocado on a salad and
make it as medicinal as possible
all right got the garlic clove in here
let me add some lemon in here too
let me add some lime in here as well
and I got to get the Cayenne in here
I'm taking off the
bottoms
[Music]
it's gonna be hot I'm actually getting a
little bit worried on how hot this is
100 off the link is in the bio and in
the description
on the mm-1500
so that hot pepper just came out
a little bit of sea salt in there and
then we're good
all right you guys
I see people asking about the machine
asking about like what the sale is it's
a hundred dollars off on this machine
link is in the bio link is in the
description check it out when you get a
chance
what the heck did we make we made
extremely hot spicy three cayenne pepper
guacamole right there let me get it into
this little Bowl here
there you go
I'm actually nervous about that one
that thing is going to be a real hot
let me get the tray out here we go
that's the real spicy one right there
you guys I'm gonna try it
a little nervous
um
I need something drank
I gotta drink something hold on guys
that thing is freaking hot
you guys I got celery juice I got celery
juice that I was drinking before I went
on this live
I just have to have some I just I have
to
because that is really really hot
I'm gonna take this piece of broccoli
and I'm gonna stick it in this really
spicy guacamole here
um
yeah those are from my garden those are
hot peppers from my garden and the herbs
are from my garden
well that's insane
oh that's that bites you
I mean you guys there's probably some of
you that like eat so many hot peppers
you think I'm like probably a wuss or
something and you're saying like well no
aw is a wuss because you just put three
big cayennes in there and it can't be
that hot
but for some reason this Cayenne have
been growing in the garden has been
insane it's it's actually not every just
because if you go look up cayenne I'm
like right
and you look at the heat units right and
you're like oh what does it have and it
says it'll have 95 000 or it'll have
whatever it'll say
I mean don't quote me on that whatever's
out there but just so you know one
Cayenne can be a lot hotter than another
Cayenne one Cayenne plant can be an
entirely different heat level than
another one depending on the soil
and so many different factors for some
reason these cayennes are like dangerous
they're way hotter but I'm gonna have a
little bit more because I can't help it
foreign
flower jasmine says best part of a mega
masticating juicers
as Foods flying out of my mouth is it's
very quiet doesn't wake up the entire
household while juicing
you guys I'm sorry if I'm quiet because
I'm actually burning up
hold on I got a guest coming
if you guys are okay I got a guest
coming
um to be here any second any minute
let me show you what I made before my
guest comes
I don't often have a guest
whoo
that's freaking hot
I'm doing a hot dance right now
like
I can't sit still because I'm my
freaking head is burning up from that
pepper all right what was I saying
I want to show you what I made
guacamole a really spicy hot one with
the Cayenne right
two other guacamoles right here
one that's a basic one which I haven't
tried yet
did you ever take an onion
I'm in a crazy meditative state right
now I'm in a state of
uh
Agony and Bliss from that hot pepper and
at the same time
I don't know I just feel really good
right now I'm gonna try this basic one
did you ever do this with an onion
um
sorry about that
okay you see this you take an onion
wedge
now you might not want to do this and
there's some onions that are like extra
hot
they're not like on the sweet Edge this
one's like this one's edgy it's hot it's
not so sweet
you want to be careful so what I do is I
take onion wedges just like this and I
use it as a dipping tool and I bite the
onion just like this okay
um
so good
right okay that's the basic guacamole
and then I want to check out
I want to check out this one here I'm
going to take this carrot wait
I'm gonna take this collard green from
the garden
this is so good and I'm going to have
the medicinal herb one
right here in the collard green let me
give you a close-up on this too if I can
see guys I put it right inside the
collard green just like that
that's the herb one the medicine one
there it is I'll show you guys up front
and you can put anything in there you
want you can put any of this in there
but I'm just gonna actually I'm gonna
take some asparagus
this is raw asparagus and I'm going to
put the raw asparagus
Spears a couple of them right in the
center and I'm gonna eat it like a
burrito this is a Collard wrap with the
guacamole the medicine guacamole
okay that's insane
hmm
that's too good
I hear a knock at the door
you guys
I gotta guess just hang on
I'll be right there I just gotta let him
in
hey how you doing man what's going on
is everything okay
are you all right you don't look stupid
you sure
are you uh
how long you're here for you want to say
hi to everybody
are you uh
are you gonna say hi to everybody Bryce
Bryce
Bryce this one
you gonna say hi to everybody
whoa
UAW
why is the floor so slippery man you're
disgusting
I knew you were a pig
where's your pig pen HW
uh
I just got back from Burning Man
and we were trapped there for three days
and burning man I got a new tattoo on my
thigh
some some lady gave me a tattoo on my
thigh at Burning Man and she pierced my
neck and she almost hit my artery
but she said it would be a good piercing
and she was on like ecstasy man she gave
me some with some psilocybins ever since
they took it I can't see still
assignment right
who aw can I have some of the grub
what is this
I love you with onions hot there's a too
hot of an onion aw
William
um
Frozen
I'm just talking
I'm just talking to myself
did you ever eat eat the hair when you
grow too much hair on your your your
head in your face and you just end up
getting it in your food yeah all right
I gotta go lay down I think I'll go to
Louisiana you know hummus hummus hummus
oh yeah
oh
so I was playing in the mud at Burning
Man
and uh and some
some people jump me and we were rolling
around in the mud
and uh
they they said I smell really funny
when I was in the mud with them for
hours
and then the government said they were
closing off Burning Man and not letting
anybody leave
we just sat in it until we froze to
death
um
really good
we've got the monkeys
I'm gonna go to Munchies I need the
hummus
that always worked for me I hate
guacamole I like the munchies with the
hummus they're so good oh there you go
I'm gonna go
I think I think I have to go have to go
to the bathroom
oh
remember your hobbies here
what kind of party are we having today
always love to know
do I go over here
yes we just got into Health pretty
recently
you know about four years ago five years
ago and I became a podcast doctor you
know you just bring on guests that
doesn't mean anybody heals
did you bring on ghost
yes we promote all kinds of things whey
protein powder and charcoal
what else all kinds of stuff hmm
[Music]
what is this freak out
what can this be a w
it's the milk of the Gods
what is this
is this colostrum
yes yes I'm one of the podcast doctors
that believes in colostrum you need to
know that they kicked the little calf
away did you and they don't let the calf
get the first Mother's Milk
they kicked the calf away yeah you
should see them as they kick the calf
they grab the calf and the calf can't
get to the mommy and guess what all the
classroom gets bottled up and sold to us
podcast doctors yes and then we
recommend it and say you should be on
colostrum I know I know as if it's
supposed to be good for us yes is this
the classroom that we're getting now
from all those Farms that are kicking
the cabs away
um hmm
oh
I dare say that's the best colostrum
I've ever had so good but I see
something else here oh I think this is
my wine is when I come here aw4 is the
one very good very good you can smell
the wine you can smell
hmm
huh
very good I bought a Vineyard last year
did you know with inflation the price of
inflation we have raised glasses of wine
to a hundred and two thousand dollars a
glass someone told me it should be fifty
thousand dollars a sip yes and this is
my favorite Brew right here hmm
delightful yes
so I'm a podcast doctor that decided to
start eating better about five years ago
like the rest of them and oh I dare say
anybody who's been in the health moving
for 30 years they don't know what
they're talking about it's just us guys
they went from uh conventional stuff
into straight into the movement where we
sell all kinds of things and then we
talk about heavy metals and whatever now
that we hear out there yes or the
podcast doctors that have moved in oh
okay okay
some hummus
there better be lots of nutritional
yeast in here we're still a nutritional
yeast yes we do we have a whole menu of
nutritional yeast on all of our websites
now there better be lots of nutritional
you said I better go I better go I have
so much to do I have patience waiting I
will see you all
yes
well thank you guys are always so glad
you're here
yeah no you can you can get to your
patients right away
indeed
hey guys
this has been a great great day watch
this from the beginning if you get a
chance if you accidentally get this far
if you somehow got this far
check out the rest of the show
so you can learn all about the mm-1500
link is in description link is in the
bio so great to be here with you guys
today
did we really Elaine says my man did we
really do three guacamoles a hummus nut
milk three nut Butters did we really do
all that and then some here's the nut
Butters I still gotta pack another Nut
Butter unbelievable Melanie I love my
mm-1500 and so do I freaking love it
hands down love the mm-1500 Jeanette
says you are the only one that has
helped me to get healed it just took six
months of uh for full recovery for from
your protocols I did take discipline and
determination and it's a miraculous heel
and I gotta tell you something don't let
people throw you off the trolls the
people that are constantly trying to
take down medical medium in the
community the people that put doubters
out there the people that say I've been
doing this and this don't get thrown by
it you stay on course learn the
information work on your healing process
you can get there there is a way to heal
so many people people have by the
thousands and thousands and in the
millions around the world people have
healed benefited their lives they've
moved forward from some of the most
debilitating conditions that were
tearing their lives apart keeping them
down and they moved forward and they
healed you can do it it's real people
are doing it every day with the medical
mean information and the books in the
medical medium series please know that
option is there for you in your life it
is in your hands and you can actually
heal and move forward and try not to get
distracted by all the that's
happening of everybody trying to put in
their two cents unfortunately with some
of the most non-helpful stuff that you
could ever use that derails people and
sends them down the wrong track
constantly and delays their healing
process by like a year two three four
sometimes ten
is really it's really it's really
intense I'm
well you know what I'm kind of a glutton
so instead of drinking because the hot
Pepper's so hot I'm gonna eat more hot
pepper because I can't help it
that's all thanks for making me laugh
Fabian says
great name I love that name
it's a powerful name you guys incredible
thank you for being here
and just know that I care I love you
guys
on IG Dr Kerwin says I reversed my
Hashimoto's with a W and SOC thank you
Anthony
you can heal you can move forward you
can get your lives back
you can do it it's there it's in your
hands have patience take your time while
blueberry dream says I have multiple
sclerosis and celery juice and medical
medium information help me heal my brain
lesion that cause double vision
it cause double vision
ishwild says every other juicer I burned
out the engine in a few months because
no one juices like the medical medium
community and those basket spinning
basket juicers do not do the job and
they make the neutral they make the
juice nutrient deficient they make the
juice nutrient deficient
how blazing says love my Omega mm-1500 I
have two and I have two as well I love
them so much they are so incredible
Giza said ew is a great multi-tasker I
try my best but most importantly I am at
your service I am at your disposal
Ness says I want that machine where can
I get it link is in the profile link is
in the description
you can find it you can find it off at
medicalmedium.com it's there it's the
mm1500 don't
lose out on the hundred dollars off on
this machine
100 off in this machine
Andrea says I'm on a holistic dentist in
Italy
say I'm a realistic dentist in Italy
every morning I drink celery juice I
suggest to remove all the metals from
the mouth
an incredible dentist right there
drinking celery juice you know what I
hear all the time like what serves you
what's sir remind me when I said I am at
your service
people say oh it doesn't serve me oh it
serves me this like serves you serves
yeah Petty says hi Anthony I have just
been on my holidays I had no celery
juice for a week I felt lethargic in my
Eczema flared and back and my headache
too gone my energy back in one morning
because of your celery juice coming back
and one morning your headache felt
better your headache gone you're feeling
better that's incredible
truly is
goes Monica says parsley shot is a
lifesaver I will concur I will concur
with that I like saying the word concur
I just like it instead of saying yeah I
agree I concur
let's see memo Berry says I love my
mm1500 great to see you Anthony great to
see you too
it's an honor to be here some spicy hot
pepper man that's spicy hot guacamole
it's kind of thing where you can't help
it but you want more but then you're
like whoa and then you're like what and
you're like whoa it's pretty intense
Dr bujobi left this
here with Hannah good to see you CJ
saved my life years
uh four years down I haven't missed a
single day in these four years
a bell should ring for that that's
incredible
help with Haley heal with Haley I'm
literally
I've literally never heard of making
guac in a juicer so cool
it is cool it's cool it's flipping cool
it's bleeping cool it's freaking cool
if I wasn't on air I would say it's
cool
stand cool
it really is you guys incredible I will
see you guys soon
and thank you for being here it was a
great chance to spend some time with you
guys
God bless you
take care