epstein-barr has caused a lot of
problems in a lot of people's lives
for a lot of years
untold
suffering
decade after decade after decade you
guys
thyroid conditions
hyperthyroidism hypothyroidism
hashimoto's thyroiditis graves disease
right that's just a few
eczema how many people suffered and
still suffer today from eczema
vitiligo right that's not a fun one to
have
not at all
psoriasis another one that's not a fun
one lupus multiple sclerosis how many
people
suffered
with symptoms that led to an ms
diagnosis
and how many people suffered from
neurological lyme for so many years
we're talking go back all the way 10 20
30 40 50 years ago and the untold
suffering
of people with lyme disease
is just unbelievable
epstein-barr has caused a lot
of damage
along the way
and has really really toppled a lot of
people over their lives changed the
course of the lives relationships broke
up because of epstein-barr marriages
broke up because of epstein-barr okay
tragedies happen in people's lives
because of epstein-barr
people lost their jobs in their careers
because of epstein-barr people lose
their chance to go to college in
university because of epstein-barr
people lose friends because of
epstein-barr and don't even know it and
nobody knows it's because of
epstein-barr epstein-barr has literally
raped and pillaged and destroyed and
damaged a lot of lives along the way and
science researchers sat there like we
don't know why anybody's sick it's the
body attacking itself we don't know why
nobody knows why anybody's sick
and meanwhile people have fibromyalgia
with hashimoto's thyroiditis with raging
eczema with a lupus diagnosis with the
neurological diagnosis neurological lyme
diagnosis later with restless leg
syndrome with unexplained migraines the
list goes on you guys
and if that's not enough all the
fibroids are created by epstein-barr you
guys all the endometriosis and the
fibroids
and the and the ovarian cysts and then
the cancers
all the non-hodgkin's lymphoma all the
different lymphomas right all the
different reproductive cancers
all of that i mean so what happens is
epstein-barr has literally created so
many problems
for so many years we're talking about
epstein-barr live right now live on
youtube live on facebook live on rumble
live on tick tock live on telegram it's
good to see you guys we're talking about
how to battle that steam bar like how to
take it down
how to take it down
you know
i'm gonna give you a little disclaimer
right now okay here's the little
disclaimer okay
i was told and i was screamed out i was
yelled at articles were written about me
over and over again making fun of me
because i was the epstein barr guy
epstein barr what does that have to do
with anything what does epstein barr
ever have to do anything that guy's not
a doctor he's not a licensed
professional that guy's nobody why does
he keep on talking about epstein-barr
year after year why does he put all
these books about epstein-barr out like
what is this epstein-barr fixed every
epstein-barr causes everything
epstein-barr is the cause of everything
and why are you sick oh he's the epstein
bar guy he's so wrong he doesn't know
anything oh he's really dumb he's crazy
too epstein barr and guess what
when you used to look up in the past
anybody would look up what causes this
disease what causes guillain-barre what
causes fibromyalgia what causes this in
autoimmune what causes this and all you
saw years ago when you would look it up
the clinics would post on the internet
what they thought would cause all these
diseases and it always said the same
thing cause unknown
cause unknown
or we think the body is attacking itself
or genetic well guess what
post medical medium books the internet
has changed everything
all the major clinics without any
evidence or or data or or any kind of
evidence on any level
which because they don't they have now
taken all the diseases all the major
clinics and they've taken medical medium
information that epstein-barr
could be causing all the different
conditions like fibro and hashimoto's
and guillain-barre and multiple
sclerosis and all these things and i
thought i was the crazy epstein-barr guy
that nobody would
think was was legit or something
they still don't have it totally right
because they say i've seen bars a
trigger
or linked to
because they can't go all the way
because if they go all the way they're
going to discredit the whole body
attacking itself theory which is
grandfathered in and you can't go
against that theory if you're a doctor a
practitioner or a clinic but the clinics
took
published medical medium information all
the clinics the major clinics now in the
world have have poached and taken
medical medium documented information
medical medium publication material that
was all pre any of it and they've
rewritten history now
it on the internet
medical medium brought up the whole
thing about the plague being the plague
creating reactivated epstein-barr well
they took that too after the fact after
it was published so here i am the
epstein-barr guy articles out there lots
of articles about the medical medium
ripping me down and tearing me apart and
telling me that i didn't know what i was
talking about and i'm not a really smart
guy because i'm just a medium
or a psychic or something and he doesn't
know anything about epstein-barr then
how come the major clinics you know the
one like mayonnaise
you like the mayonnaise clinic
right you guys know the mayonnaise
clinic you guys know what i'm talking
about
right so the mayonnaise clinic
has now re-changed it we changed
everything with no science behind it
they have no studies that show an
epstein-barr bug actually doing anything
and the mayonnaise clinic now
has literally because all the functional
medicine doctors that work alongside the
conventional doctors in the mayonnaise
clinic
they literally take
the medical medium epstein-barr
information
and they rewrite it the way they want to
see it but they take it all
and it's kind of crazy how it works when
you think about it little old me this
little old medium guy that's just not
important in the world and has never
done anything for anybody and whatever
these big clinics with billions of
dollars behind it for some reason all
their all their doctors have to litter
and the researchers have to go to
medical medium books
and they actually have to take it out of
here
and put it on the internet so we're
talking about the four stages of
epstein-barr that's where we're at right
now
and it's not just mono it's not just
mono we're talking about right we're
talking about epstein-barr which yes
puts you into a mononucleosis state
we're going into that a little bit
good to see you guys we're live right
now this is a fun day we're going into
ebv we got some information we're going
to talk about how ebv works inside the
body we're going to talk about what ebv
feeds on
we're going to talk about how to destroy
and kill ebv how about that too we're
going to talk about how to annihilate
ebv so ebv doesn't ruin your life
or ruin your life down the road
it's pretty simple
you can come into this world
with epc bar
right
you can come into this world with
epstein var
and you can leave this world
with epstein-barr
okay
you can come into the world with
epstein-barr
and you can leave this world with
that's how it works
in the womb
you can contract epstein-barr it's where
a lot of people contract it
from their parents
and then
we can die down the road many many years
down the road
suffering from epstein-barr
or
you can contract epstein-barr and
annihilate it and kill it
and that's what you want to do
you want to break it down
destroy it and that's what you want to
do okay
the end says you're just trying to make
money
well i hope you're talking about
somebody else because you can get the
book free at the library
so deanne
i just want to give you a recommendation
can you go to the library and get the
book for free and help somebody
and stop being kind of like a jerk and
actually help somebody and maybe maybe
save a life
unless that wasn't for me and that was
for somebody else that could have been
for somebody else the end if that's for
somebody else i'm totally grateful for
you
epstein barr
okay in stage one you cut contract
epstein-barr
right in stage one it sits in your body
and floats around is what it does so
when you first get your first epstein
bar like
you kiss somebody and you end up getting
epstein barr or you kiss somebody or
you you're on a public toilet seat and
you pick up efficient bar you're in a
restaurant a chef cuts their finger and
bleeds in your food and you catch two
epstein bars you can catch two epstein
bar varieties in one shot just from a
chef cutting their finger in the
restaurant
right
so you get your first epstein bar your
second epstein bar it sits in your body
and it floats around and it could float
around for a long time six months two
months a year two days
it can go into
mononucleosis within two days it can go
into mononucleosis six years from now it
can go into mono ten years from now but
it can float around and what happens is
it floats around until you have a weak
spot
and that weak spot is could be anything
trauma an emotional hardship a divorce a
breakup a friendship a relationship a
fight with a co-worker stress financial
stress whatever it is and then you break
your your immune system starts to weaken
and break down and break down and break
down
and when it starts to break down
we get in trouble you guys see a bunch
of supplements in the front someone
might say hey look what's he trying to
do i'm not sponsored by the companies
and i purchased these
i purchased them so these i bought
and paid for and i'm not sponsored
so
the point is here i want to just get
that on the table right now before
someone thinks is he just trying to do a
sales pitch today right
and the books they're so marked look so
low on amazon right now
so low
it's like
ridiculous so i'm just laying it which
is actually a good i love that they mark
it so low i want people to get it at the
cheapest price they possibly can so
we're on epstein-barr right now you guys
forced four stages of epstein-barr we're
talking about
we contract and catch mono it sits in us
and then our immune system breaks down
when we have some kind of trauma
or maybe exposure
any kind of exposure chemical exposure
breaks down the immune system
right scented candles with fragrances
breaks down the immune system so any
kind of exposure pharmaceuticals break
down the immune system right there
okay
when it breaks down the immune system at
the same time it can also feed the
epstein-barr virus right so you can also
feed it so the virus loves to eat things
it loves the perfumes colognes chemicals
and perfumes colognes chemicals and
scented candles it loves to eat them
giving you a rundown loves to eat metals
and pharmaceuticals it loves to eat
copper
copper you're drinking out of copper
thermoses you're going to feed your
epstein bar and you will guarantee
eczema and psoriasis down the road
if you want a hundred percent guaranteed
to get excellent psoriasis down the road
i promise you this and you can just be
like whoa
i don't need his crap i don't need to
hear it i'm going to leave i don't want
to hear this guy telling me i'm going to
have eczema just because i drink out of
copper thermoses but you will
you will and you'll remember this day
because if you're drinking out of copper
devices
what's going to happen is
whatever ebv inside of you is going to
feed off of that copper
and you're going to have epsilon
symptoms down the road like eczema
psoriasis
this is an important day right here to
talk about this because people don't
realize the suffering that's happening
out there you guys know you guys know
but the suffering's unreal to how many
conditions and symptoms and autoimmune
diseases and neurological symptoms are
growing
at a rate no one can even keep their
finger on no one can even keep the pulse
on like i'm serious you guys
it's no joke out there multiple
sclerosis ra eczema psoriasis do i need
to say more lupus do i need to say more
right fibromyalgia right do i need to
say more all these different conditions
anything with autoimmune you got the ebv
behind it you got an autoimmune label
you got the epstein-barr behind it
neurological lime you've got the
epstein-barr behind it
and yeah you can you can just say hey i
don't have to listen tim is fine
but when you're really sick and you're
down on your knees and you're finally
praying to god because now you're so
sick you're just praying to god like oh
my god i'm not just sick i'm actually so
sick you got the information to fall
back on
it's here right the information is here
you just came on and you're wondering
what does he know well
the clinics all around the country and
the world are taking medical medium
information about abstinent bar
published here first and now they've
rewritten history on the internet
and they're attaching epstein-barr to
everything
meanwhile i was laughed at for years for
being the epstein-barr guy
by naysayers and haters
so we're about saving lives medical
medium new edition is right here this
book has saved a lot of lives over the
years it's well known for that which is
incredible and a lot of doctors use the
information all around the country and
around the world so let's go a little
bit into this how does epstein-barr work
stage one it goes in you
when your immune system gets broken down
it goes into stage two
mononucleosis
mononucleosis is stage two is what it is
you guys
that's what happens right there
stage 2 is mononucleosis
and so when you're in mononucleosis your
immune system is battling so now your
immune system is at war right here so
keep that in mind so your white blood
cells are at war
with
your
invader
so you got the invader
and you got your white blood cell that's
mononucleosis right there
you don't think you had mono but all you
had to do was have a scratchy throat and
fuel under the weather that's all
you may think you didn't have
mononucleosis but in college you might
have been sick for two weeks what seemed
to be like a cold and you were coughing
and all flammy and not feeling good and
tired that was mono
mono
it comes in so many different ways it
doesn't mean it's a serious mono where
you're sick for three months with mino
or six months because many people are
sick with mono for three months six
months two months eight months
you can just be sick with mono for just
a week but you had your motto and your
immune system went into war with the
variety of epstein-barr that you've been
infected with
after were infected with the epstein
barr and we went into war
your immune system eventually overcomes
and it pushes epstein-barr
away
epstein-barr doesn't leave the body it
stays in your body and then it enters
into
your organs now what epstein-barr likes
to do is it likes to head into the liver
that's the number one place epstein-barr
likes to go it's the liver so keep that
in mind right there
esteem bar loves the liver
after mononucleosis stage two it goes
into the liver and it camps out and
hides out but it also can go into the
spleen
not only can it go into the spleen but
it can go into the reproductive system
too so keep that in mind as well i've
seen bar likes to go into the
reproductive system
so it heads into
the uterus
it heads into the ovaries and now we
have pcos
so epstein-barr starts to cause problems
like pcos endometriosis and fibroids
because after
stage two mononucleosis it camped out in
the reproductive system spleen and liver
that's where it likes to be
as the time goes by it could be years it
could be months depending on how low
your immune system it could be years
that go by maybe it's even a decade that
goes by something happens
an epstein-barr
ends up
proliferating
it could have been proliferating because
it's actually feeding off of chemicals
it could be
it could be growing in numbers because
it's feeding off of all different kinds
of exposures it could be growing in
numbers because you were told to eat a
really healthy egg diet
and so when we're told that look you
need to be on eggs that's what you need
to be do you think you know you think
you're doing the right things and then
the epstein-barr feeds off of the eggs
every time you're eating the eggs it
feeds off the eggs and then out of
nowhere a relationship problem happens
something occurs
your life gets toppled a little bit
emotionally and between the bad foods
that feed the virus plus the emotional
things that are happening you end up
having another bout of mono but it
doesn't feel like that
the virus
takes advantage of a lowered immune
system and starts to head to where
to your thyroid
now you're a candidate for down the road
to have hypothyroidism so now you're at
your functional medicine doctor's office
or regular doctor's office or your
naturopathic doctor's office he's
running some tests she's running some
tests and she's like hey um i think you
might have hypothyroid
i think you might have hashimoto's what
no one realizes that was actually
epstein-barr it got into the thyroid and
it created hypothyroidism
hyperthyroidism it created hashimoto's
thyroiditis hey you might actually have
a cyst on your thyroid you might
actually have a little tumor on your
thyroid
you might have a nodule on your thyroid
no one realizes that's the epstein-barr
see how it works you guys
so now we're in stage three stage three
of epsinbar virus is your thyroid that's
when the thyroid conditions can happen
and they may be overlooked completely by
your doctor because you can have a
hypothyroid problem and it not even be
detectable so many doctors know that now
they're learning that now
this is all medical medium information
this isn't me researching stuff so if
you hear copycats out there in research
papers they've taken it from here or
books or whatever or people on the
internet
this has always been medical media
information since i was five years old
and it hasn't changed it's always been
consistent
and not contradictive
so hold the whole point is here we're in
stage three of epson bar so you guys on
telegrams good to see you guys on tick
tock glad you guys are here too on
youtube facebook rumble
so
stage three of fcm bar is when the
epstein bar
sits inside the thyroid
camps out
and creates eventually hypothyroidism
hyperthyroidism graves
right cysts nodules tumors
hashimoto's thyroiditis but you may not
even see the numbers
yet it takes years sometimes for
epstein-barr just to sit into that
thyroid but here's the next problem
the next problem is is it sits in your
thyroid it starts to break down your
immune health more and more as time goes
on and we get more and more exposure so
now we're in stage three epstein barr
and we're eating more eggs than that
what's what we're doing because we're
taught to eat more eggs
you showed his healing says so much
stolen medical medium information out
there but then they want to use it to
point people to their crappy products
or their pharmaceuticals or their fake
genetics their
theories it wasn't like this five years
ago each other it's turned into an
insanity out there everybody's using
medical medium info that was published
and documented by medical medium first
they're all using it every influencers
are using it they're actually writing
things post about it out there and never
and never anyone's
even saying where it comes from it's a
doggy dog world
everybody's trying to sell something i
have i have respect for that i mean
anybody wants to do whatever they want
to do i
i'm not to judge him i can't judge
anybody
but i will say this
just doing people who are sick of this
dish in this justice because what
happens is when you're sick and can't
find your way back to know where the
information is and how are you going to
heal they're going to say oh you've got
epstein-barr oh really i do i finally
have an answer what do i need to do you
need to do charcoal okay let me take all
this charcoal
and then you get sick and you die in
five years or eight years or you get so
sick you can't function
wait a minute i have seen bar what do i
need to do apple cider vinegar okay
great you gave me the answer at 17 bar
let me take all this apple cider vinegar
or some other crappy product so what
happens is people end up getting totally
taken because they don't know where the
information comes from and then
i care because the suffering suffering's
great out there
so in stage 3 epstein-barr when the
epstein-barr virus is in the thyroid
what happens you guys is that the immune
system can break down again we can go
through a divorce we can go through a
relationship breakup we can go through a
great loss we can go through a lot of
stress we can go through some hard
struggles everybody goes through a bunch
of stuff
right or we're getting exposed we're
getting so exposed by so many toxic
chemicals chemicals we're getting more
metals in us we're getting more metals
than ever before we're eating lots of
tuna we're getting whatever it is that's
happening we're getting exposed we're
told to have fish oil capsules right and
we're getting exposed so what happens is
eventually your immune system cracks
maybe the last ticket
the last problem that was created maybe
the last problem that like the straw
that broke the camel's back
maybe the straw that broke the camel's
back
was here you are your immune system was
weakening you're 40 years old you're 35
years old your immune system is
weakening right
and then
all of a sudden
you think you've got a tick bite or
something because you're so sick you're
getting neurological symptoms and the
neurological symptoms
are getting worse so now you're at a
specialist now you're at a neurologist
now that you're at another doctor but
you don't know it which you have instead
of lyme disease for some reason it won't
stay up there today instead of lyme
disease
you have epstein-barr
that's what you have
you got the ebv
the tick is the trigger but there's a
lot of other triggers
maybe a divorce was a trigger maybe a
car accident was a trigger maybe a
stressful car accident was a trigger
maybe the loss of a loved one was a
trigger maybe something else was true
maybe a beast thing was a trigger maybe
something was a trigger the tick can be
a trigger because it knocks the immune
system lower and then
the epstein bar that's been sitting in
your thyroid in stage three
goes to stage four
what people don't realize
is that the majority of people walking
around with neurological conditions and
symptoms
are stage four
ebb
they're stage four
stage four
ebv is not like stage four cancer
it's stage four ebv
what that means is it hit the nervous
system epstein-barr leaves the thyroid
you guys on tick-tock
it leaves the thyroid when your immune
system is broken down
and it heads to the nerves
which nerves the vagus nerves so let's
go into this a little bit one of the
places
and you you'll you'll be mind blown with
this
one of the places
that have seen bar heads
is the nerve channel in the ear
so stage 4 epstein barr
means
the bug
will go into the inner ear and when it
goes into the inner ear it affects the
nerve channel in the inner ear
and then you get tinnitus and ringing in
the ears how many people do you know
have the popping fluttering buzzing
hissing poofing
sound and ringing sound and vibrating
sound in the ear and they have all these
problems with their tinnitus and
everything else right that's from
epstein-barr bug
that's what it is that's stage four eb
bug
i have to use that
that term
okay i talk about that in the first book
right
so if you look you guys if you're if
you're hanging on for this show we're
doing the four stages of epson bar check
out medical medium new edition or
cleanse the heal and learn about it it's
really in detail here too okay that's on
amazon it's a great gift for people you
know if they're sick
if you got the ringing in the ear you
got the tinnitus or get it free at the
library get it free of the library you
got the tinnitus in the ring in the year
you got the bug that's stage four bug
another place it goes is in the vagus
nerves so the ebv bug goes into
the vagus nerves when it goes there
you've got the vertigo the dizziness the
vertigo the feeling of being on a boat
the rocking on a boat you got all that
and on top of that
epstein barr can create anxiety because
of the phrenic and vagus nerves get
inflamed they swell
so when the vagus nerves and the phrenic
nerves swell you guys you get the
balance problems
you get the vertigo
you get the feeling on a boat you get
the dizziness you get the anxiety
this is medical medium information about
anxiety and got anxiety
and now you see out there epstein barr
causes anxiety someone wrote about
something or really because there's no
science that shows it and it was
published here first
or epstein-barr has something to do with
vagus nerves
vagus nerves when they swell up you end
up getting the anxiety so what happens
is the virus in stage 4 releases
neurotoxins the neurotoxins go to the
vagus nerves swell them up and you end
up with anxiety that's why people have
the panic attacks that's why people
can't they got the panic attacks they
got this they're sweating profusely
they're nervous they feel like they
gotta run around or they can't handle
they can't sit still or they're just
trapped with their stomach flipping the
whole bit
and the fact that they're even trying to
link the vagus nerves to anxiety that's
medical medium information originally
so
we're in stage 4 epstein-barr right now
fc bar can create tinnitus ringing in
the ear when it's in in stage four it
can create vertigo and dizziness when
it's in stage four you guys it can
create a lot of problems and what
happens is as we get older we start
getting all these epstein-barr symptoms
and then we get these autoimmune
diagnoses you can end up with any kind
of diagnosis lupus and r.a and
neurological lyme and fibromyalgia and
chronic fatigue syndrome and people
don't realize this is all epstein-barr
related and it's stage four epstein-barr
this is neurological symptoms caused by
epstein-barr so what are we gonna do
about it this is stage four
we gotta learn to kill
the bug no one knows how to do that the
reason why so many people got their
lives back with medical medium
information the reason why lives were
saved around the world the reason why
when it was first published and this
information got out there people were
like oh my god i now i know what's wrong
with me i can't believe it
i can't believe this
and the reason why they're learning now
like
what's happening now like because of the
plague the reactivated epstein-barr
comes from medical medium information
right people are like oh my god it's
like i know the answers now so what do i
do the one thing about
the mm info
for getting our lives back is you not
only know the cause but you know what to
do
to take it to the level you need to go
to the heel like how do i how do i crush
the epstein bar i have ebv i'm the one
with lupus i'm the one with fibro
i'm the one with eczema i'm the one with
these conditions how do i destroy this
epstein-barr how do i take it down how
do i get my life back
i got the dizziness i got the ringing in
the ears i got the pain in the body i
got the fatigue like how do i get my
life back i didn't know it was
epstein-barr not only did i not know it
was epstein-barr i didn't know you can
kill it
it's critical to know
that you can kill it
if anybody's asking about pandemic info
or anything like that i talk about
reactivated ebv in this book right here
where it was published first medical
medium publication
the deal is
it's like there's something we can do
for it and about it so let's get into it
right now
how does anybody know
how to knock down ebv
out there
when there's nothing out there that can
help anybody figure that out they don't
know what kills off ebv they didn't even
know ebv causes all these problems i
just ran by you guys
but what i have seen
from the source of information that i
was blessed to have starting since age
four
was i've seen miraculous results
when you use specific things
for these conditions
when you're going after ebv
and so i talk about this so let's go
into some basics right here
if i had
epstein-barr and i was struggling
suffering and i had the thyroid problems
and i had all these other conditions and
i had the ringing in the ears
and i had the dizziness and i had the
aches and pains and the fatigue and i
had even more than that the eczema
psoriasis or whatever it is all combined
or an autoimmune diagnosis
then i'd be doing some really good stuff
here w green says well you've helped me
to fix all the boat rocking anxiety and
tinnitus bless your heart so glad you're
here
yeah age four age four
so what i've learned okay
because i'm a student
is what i am
right
i'm a student
of the source of information the source
that since age 4 has been teaching me
i'm a student and a messenger
is what i am
and so all i can do is tell you what has
worked
what the information that was delivered
to me how it helps so many people
and that's why the mm info has the
street cred that's why it has the street
credibility
that's why it's net it's known out there
in the world because it works right i'm
the messenger for it but it works
so what do we do so if i had
epstein-barr and i was suffering and
struggling
i'd make sure i was on zinc
been 35 plus years trying to teach
people to take zinc right it's critical
that's what i would do you ask your
doctor what's right for you i'm just
going to tell you if i had epstein-barr
i'd be taking the liquid zinc sulfate
this is the best one this is the vimergy
i'm not sponsored
but it's of emergency fees and victor i
am is in mary e-r-g-y
vimergy.com that's the zinc i would take
there's no additives there's nothing
like that in there it's the best stuff
there is
i would take golden seal
is what i would do
like for me if that was happening to me
and i had all these problems i'd be
doing four dropper fulls twice a day
and i'd be doing that periodically but i
got protocols in the book i'd be doing
two dropper holes twice a day if i was
somebody i maybe i would do one but i
would do a little something maybe you're
somebody that doesn't take any
supplements you do six tiny drops twice
a day
but that's what i would do right
that's what i would do
i would take licorice root
periodically ask your doctor what's
right for you i'm just telling you what
i would do and what i recommend my loved
ones
and friends
i would do licorice root and the quality
matters because if you don't have the
right stuff you can't knock down that
ebv
it takes the right things to knock down
and crush that bug yeah if you don't
have the right things then you work with
other stuff
you work with protocols like the foods
you take it on that angle
the one thing about medical medium
information
is that you can literally start with
celery juice
and start knocking down bugs
you might be so sick though and have so
many bugs going on for so long you might
need a little bit more and then a little
bit more and then you take it to the
next level to the next level
i see a lot of people jennifer says
quercetin quercetin
is a fine enough antioxidant but you'll
see it's not on the list of things
because it doesn't knock down
epstein-barr
so what it does though
is the vitamin c
that's critical
right that's critical
so that's that's a really important key
right there you'll see a lot of times
out there what people have done over the
years if they they've taken medical
medium information from the books a lot
of doctors right
and they've used it so it's given them a
platform
and then like a lot of internet doctors
that are selling a lot of things and
stuff like that gives them a platform
and then they'll sell corset tin but
quercetin doesn't knock down
fsteen bar
it doesn't do what it it's that's not
enough to really knock down epsine bar
but the vitamin c is right so that's the
micro c the one that really
is gentle and powerful right that's the
vimorgy if anybody wants to know right
there that's bimrgy.com i'm not
sponsored it's just the stuff that works
these are victor i am as the mary e r g
y energy.com
ray
lysine
it's critical epstein-barr is a herpetic
family virus so it's a
it's the herpes family that's what it is
and a lot of people that have ebv also
have simplex they got the fever blisters
they got the shingles viruses they got
hhv-6 they've got cytomegalovirus so
lysine is critical it's critical to
knock down that epstein-barr or anything
else in the herpetic family
that's another aspect that has to be
there another piece
by the way vimergy came out that
elderberry syrup which is
insane there's nothing like it out there
i mean what's it's incredible it's only
elderberry syrup that has a mulberry
extract in there and vitamin c and a
mulberry extract
so that's something that's mind-blowing
right there i just told a family member
that for their kids they should be doing
a couple of teaspoons every single day
when they're not sick of the elderberry
syrup as an immune system support right
now now that we're going into all the
flues all the that whole thing and we're
going into that time time of the year
through the winter in a lot of places so
i got all my friends i got my family
family members friends everybody i know
i got them on the elderberry syrup like
one teaspoon for maintenance every
single day or twice a day two teaspoons
their children one to two teaspoons
right you ask your doctor what's right
for you but that's what i have family
and friends and that's great too and
it's helpful for epstein-barr which is
really incredible right
so
memory came out with a new product right
here now it doesn't look like it's new
because it's lemon balm so it's just
like the lemon balm here but this is a
10 to 1 ratio
highly highly potent
so if i had
dizziness and vertigo and tinnitus and
aches and pains and fatigue and anxiety
and depression and anything else that
was neurological
i would be doing that one right there
too so i would be doing the ten to one
ratio as well it's really potent potent
right so they just keep on upping their
game
all their stuff's incredible but they
upped their game incredible for anything
epstein barr
amy batchelor
all these supplements are wonderful easy
to take and gentle on the gut they
really are amy they really are gentle
that's that's one of the greatest
reasons why i love them
i'm super sensitive and do well with all
of them thank you anthony amy thanks
you're the greatest
bless your heart amy
so
low quality supplements gives
good quality supplements a bad rap and a
bad name so many people are burned so
bad from the bad stuff that
the low quality stuff ruins it for
people
because then they just won't even try
the good stuff they won't even know
john smith they went from four to one to
ten to one and didn't raise the price
and that's really something
it is and the thing is with it i'm
probably
yeah i know they're probably hurting
from that one too
exactly but other companies they would
just they would never do that other
companies would never do that
things with energy actually care and
that's the difference they actually care
you know
so but the bottom line is this is one
potent form
of like
relief i'm offering friends that have
high anxiety
it's like they take it around with them
all the time and they they're working on
their esteemed bar they're working and
knocking down their epstein barr
recently i just had a couple of old
friends reach out they're like oh my god
i should have listened to you 20 years
ago
i never did anything for my epstein bar
i got now i got the hashimoto's i got
all these other problems it's like
anthony i got this i got that wrong with
me
i got like they don't know what's going
on with my liver now and i don't feel
good now i have autoimmune
and that's what they're saying and now i
got all these different problems i got
numbness and i got tingles in weird
places
you know and they're like i'm like look
get on the ten to one get on your your
zinc get on your licorice
okay all these things matter
all these things matter
tests for epstein-barr do not always
show up so if you have the epstein-barr
the test may not show up because the
test tap because the epsilon bar
technically has to be in the blood
for it to really ring and pick off and
then the virus loves to sit inside
organs and hide out in the thyroid in
different organs that's why it's really
hard i explained that in detail of where
the confusion is with epstein-barr
you guys i'm going to talk about
epstein-barr more
i'm heading off to instagram
and i'm turning tick tock back on i'm
turning telegram back on
i'm heading off to instagram
if you don't have the information arm
yourself with the information to protect
yourself make sure you have a copy go go
to the library if you don't want to go
to amazon and get it on sale go to the
library get it for free allison yoga
land hey i can't imagine if i never had
listened to you you have saved my life
over and over again alice thank you for
being here dr fawn md yes tests are
unreliable
you take blood not organ cells to test
blood tests are a snapshot in time my
god that's that's wise
that's wise information from a medical
doctor right there an incredible md dr
faun by the way i'm honored you're here
dr fond truly honored to see you know
so
you guys i'm going to talk more about
protocols for epstein-barr on instagram
so i'm going to head off to instagram in
a couple of minutes i'm going to talk
about more about the protocols and stuff
like that we're going to run through the
stages again maybe we'll talk about some
different things with it
and i'm excited to help in any way i can
i love you guys and oh by the way
did you guys any of you guys catch
baking the cookies i baked all the
cookies i baked the sugar cookies today
and i baked the uh raspberry i made the
raspberry thumb print cookies on amazon
live of the medical medium cooking show
it's a different show you guys it's an
entirely different show the link is in
profile link is in the description you
might want to follow me on that amazon
live show because it's the medical
medium cooking show live and i'm it's
really cool and follow my newsletter you
guys on tick tock if you haven't signed
up to my newsletter please do if you can
okay my newsletter is at
medicalmedium.com and sign up to my
newsletter so you know what i'm doing
know when the amazon lives are know when
my lives are the link is in profile link
is in the link is in the description so
check out that check out lambs on live
medical mean cooking show you guys i'm
trying to do everything i can to help
you guys in any way possible
because it matters
i don't like knowing you guys are
suffering
in any way all right i love you guys
i'm gonna go on ig in a few minutes i'll
see you