what's in the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie I'll tell you cilantro
barleygrass juice powder
spirulina
dols wild blueberries we're talking
about the five ingredients right there
that's the five ingredients that creates
the heavy metal detox this is the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie at airwan this is an incredible
smoothie it's a functional smoothie
there's smoothies out there that are
great they're healthy people drink them
you know there's all kinds of fruits and
vegetables and smoothies this is
different this is wild food in here
which is extraordinary and so what
you're looking at right here is a lot
different than smoothies in general are
out there this isn't a protein smoothie
this isn't a whatever smoothie those are
great no this is functional this has a
real purpose a purpose that moves people
forward this is the medical medium heavy
metal detox smoothie at airan