I want to talk about an announcement
okay the Gaia heel conference is
November 9th I'm going to be speaking
there okay you can get tickets tickets
are limited check out the link in the
profile Link in the description go to
Medical medium.com you'll see the banner
on my website so you'll know hey that's
how you can get there get a ticket if
you want to be there live to see me okay
I'll be doing a light blast there link
is in the description link is in the bio
for the guia heel conference I'm going
to there live speaking tickets are
limited you could also see it live
stream so I just want to let everybody
know about that
[Applause]
[Music]