so we're talking about the blood-brain
barrier
and information no one's ever heard
about on the blood-brain barrier we're
in the brain saver books I'm excited to
be here you guys
so have you opened up your brain saver
books have you been looking inside take
your time there's so much there there's
hundreds of symptoms and conditions
there's cleanses like the brain shot
therapy cleanse there's a lot of
information by the way we're doing the
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge or
the brain shot therapy challenge next
week I'm letting you know Thursday
October 17th so get ready for that every
single day I'm gonna be making a brain
shot
and you guys will be making a brain shot
if you want to join it's incredible it's
free it's going to be really cool and
we're going to get that instant relief
from those brain shots we're gonna make
them and we're gonna take them and it's
gonna be incredible it really is
so I just want to give everybody a
forewarning on that now I also want to
give you one other four warning right
here
is that if you do partake in the brain
shot therapy brain shot therapy cleanses
in the brain saver books be prepared to
be taken off guard what I mean by that
it's going to catch you off guard
because
you don't get instant relief and
alternative medicine and brain saver
books you're getting instant relief from
this tool which is really incredible
it's an entirely different experience
and the medical medium books gives
relief to people in so many ways like
there is instant relief in the medical
medium books like the shock Therapies
incident relief for so many people with
the shock therapies right and
but when you see in the brain saver
books you're going to see additional
shock therapies that give powerful
relief so what is this brain shot I just
saw a question what is this brain shot
well in the medical medium books
there is something called brain shot
therapy and brain shot therapy cleanses
now these are incredible powerful
tools for healing okay so I'm just gonna
go right to it and just give you since
you asked a question which is awesome
here we are
so many shots there's 30 shots
by the way the books are 40 off of
amazon.com us right now 40 off
okay before we go into the brain shots
real quick you guys we're talking about
the blood-brain barrier I'm not trying
to send us off course but we're talking
about the blood-brain barrier a little
bit information you don't know about it
but we're talking about also the brain
shots branch that therapy but I want to
tell you guys okay Lynn Robinson says
please can you give me a shopping list
I've had to send both books back twice
so a shopping list absolutely of course
the challenge
is going to be easy to figure out the
shopping list because sign up to the
medicalbeam.com sign up to the
newsletter so you can know when the
challenge is going to be in the shopping
list is going to be in the in the
newsletters so sign up to the medical
meme newsletter so you can get that
information
so I want to tell you guys
these books are 40 off on amazon.com us
but it's not just that it's incredible
Michael says money money money why don't
you give your information for free I
love that I want that I want that I want
to frame that right there Michael
so Michael's telling medical medium
money money money why don't you give
your information for free
you're such a genius Michael thank you
for telling me that because medical beam
information is all free and you can go
to the books you go to libraries to get
the books for free
everything's for free for medical media
Michael so I'm not trying to be snarky
or anything like that but everything is
free the books cost money to make so if
you want to purchase a book if you want
to purchase literally Bibles that are
over 600 pages each
and there's like a hundred recipes and
they're packed with healing information
if you want to purchase these you're
going to have to pay something because
it costs way more to print it so yeah
money money money that's right
everything's for free I don't actually
charge for courses
I don't have a paywall in my website I
have a large website
that's one of the most popular Health
websites in the world
and you don't have to spend a dime there
there's no pay walls
there's no
um there's no subscription fees and
monthly subscription fees
there's nothing like that
medicalmedium.com is a free website with
free information I pay
for all the help
is what I do I pay out of my pocket for
all the help I need to build the website
to create all the free information it
costs me thousands of dollars thousands
I pay out of pocket every day so Michael
everything's free for you and I'm the
only one in the health field that has
this much going on that does that
okay and it's just and here's the thing
my podcasts are for free there's no
advertisers and commercials I'm the only
podcast that's a number one podcast out
there in the world one of the number one
podcasts out there in the world the
medical meme podcast
there's no commercials and advertisers
and I get in trouble for that you're not
allowed to do that you have to be a
Roman when you're that big up there in
the world you have to do what the Romans
tell you you have to do what Caesar
tells you
and they tell you you better have
advertisers and you better have
publicists advertisers agencies Brokers
and I don't do any of that no one on the
planet does what I do and that's a fact
it's free free free Michael
free
all of it no Health Guru guy no Health
Doctor guy no podcaster doctor guy no
Health author guy does what I do not one
does what I do it's all free people need
to understand the difference
then that's just a fraction of how free
it is I could go on I could talk about
it with you for an hour I had a huge
promotional guy company guy reached out
to me and said why do you do this you
need to charge for everything under the
sun you'll have one of the most popular
podcasts in the world one of the most
popular websites in the world and you
are all free and that is going to get
you in trouble down the road
and I'm like so what it's free so
Michael back to your comment money money
money why don't you give your
information for free
and by the way I match your service
that's your service
back to the brain saver books that was
fun
brain server protocols and brain saver
you guys
40 off amazon.com right now us
Tara Appleman hundreds of hours of free
YouTube lives reading out of the books I
don't use advertisers in the YouTubes
too hundreds of free articles on the
medical mean website hundreds of hours
of free podcasts on and on in Ontario
Appleman thank you God bless you
and what's crazy is
I'm also the only YouTube channel
that doesn't have advertisers and
commercials huh one of the only YouTube
channels
that's at the level of being you know
whatever where we're at and I don't have
that
anyway thanks guys for hearing my
my little spiel about free free free
free free oh yeah don't buy the brain
saver books just wait until they're in
the library and get it get it out for
free I'm okay with that because I just
want you to have the information
okay
Claudia says what's Ace who's Ace who's
SOC who's SOC
all right
brain saver books you will be blown off
your seat Michael Charles hey my man no
ads in podcasts yeah number one podcast
with no ads and commercials you guys
you're not allowed to do that did you
know that
you're not allowed to do that you get in
trouble you're not allowed to do that
because it's a mob out there
it's legit you have to have that and we
don't do that all right nobody knows how
the inner or inner workings work
it costs to print the book and the
publisher has to distribute them around
the world if we don't have the publisher
print out the book and pay we don't we
have to pay for the paper and print it
out to get it out to the world and it
can't get into the people's hands for
them to heal so there has to be a charge
for the book to some degree I can't even
believe I'm explaining this
when a guy like that says why don't you
have everything for free I can't even
believe I'm like even saying this right
now they have to say this
it's crazy
it's so you can get it into your hands
because someday the the internet may not
be there and someday things like that
may not be there and you need it in your
hands
and you you lose electricity then you
don't even have ability to find anything
online
that's how the world works it's
important to have
a hardcover book
all right you guys check this out
we're talking about the brain shot
therapy cleanses because someone
originally asked what's a brain shot
okay
brain shot therapy right there part
three
in the medical medium brain saver books
all right
brain shot therapy
medical mean brain shot therapy medical
medium brain shot therapy offers instant
relief while you're working to fix
problems on a deeper level in your brain
and nervous system and body
but those brain shots they not only give
instant relief but they also help deep
inside to heal over time which is really
powerful
your brain and body have a quick
response to medicinals delivered in
liquid form especially when it's coming
from above the information center
synergistically combined just the right
way designed to be highly absorbable in
the mouth these brain shots reach the
brain fast so these brain shots because
we're doing the brain shot
therapy challenge next week Thursday
October 17th mark it down in your
calendar it's for free
just so you know
when you do the brain shots they get to
the brain really fast they get into the
bloodstream really fast they cross the
blood-brain barrier really fast really
quickly that's why partly why they give
people Relief really quick too
and it's the chemical compounds the
phytochemical compounds in the brain
shot therapies that actually reach the
brain really quick this is incredible
information
who offers this
when you go out there and you're looking
for stuff it's just like eat better crap
out there no processed foods eat better
you know books or whatever this is
incredible information here we're
talking about the blood-brain barrier
today I'm going to be reading out of the
brain saver books
okay
our brain shots are we talking about
you guys who have the books there's a
pathogen exposure brain shot let's take
a look real quick pathogen exposure
brain shot toxic fragrance exposure
exposure brain shot negative energy
exposure brain shot you try that hey
Michael the guy that said that why don't
I have everything for free when you get
the brain saver books try the negative
energy exposure shot
heck yeah
it might get whatever demon that's in
you out of you
whatever whatever demonic possession
that was in you
that that shot right there might knock
that demon right out of you
negative energy exposure shot
might send that demon flying
yeah
mold exposure shot
is this why people don't like me because
then I get snarky like that I get like
so sarcastic all right
mold exposure shock
I'm not perfect you guys I am not
perfect when I got the gift at age four
to receive this information that's in
these brain saver books when I got the
gift at age four when SOC started
speaking to me
I wasn't chosen because I'm perfect
far from it
I'm a human being like everybody else
I mean I'm a good listener so I received
the information I get it down here so
you can take the books and heal and move
yourself forward like so many millions
have but I'm not perfect myself
personally
EMF and 5G exposure brain shot
whoa
right
radiation exposure brain shot plane
travel anyone here's the crazy thing you
can take plane flights for like 20 years
you're flying on the planes
you have 20 years of radiation in you
you're glowing in the dark
it's gonna be good to get the radiation
out wouldn't it radiation expose your
shot toxic heavy metal exposure shot oh
yeah
could be anything maybe you took some
antibiotics a couple of months ago all
the toxic heavy metals and antibiotics
boom
pesticide herbicide and fungicide brain
shot therapy let's see what else we got
going guys what a beautiful day it's
Saturday is it Saturday
pharmaceutical exposure shot yeah maybe
you had maybe you're dealing with
Pharmaceuticals
read between between the lines on that
pharmaceutical exposure shot too
Chemtrails exposure shot
oh [ __ ] I said it
we got the shifter shots
sea Trails exposure shot
okay we got obsessive thoughts shifter
okay how many people have this obsessive
thoughts
racing thoughts OCD what about OCD
anything like that you're just in that
you're trying to rest you've got
something that's eating away at you you
got thoughts coming in and you can't
break those thoughts maybe you said some
you know something to somebody
maybe you said something to somebody and
you just were like regretting it why did
I say that why did I say that I finally
got a hold of that person on the phone
and why did I say that how did that
happen
whatever it is obsessive thought shifter
boom you got to bring in the obsessive
let's read what it says you guys we're
talking about blood brain barrier today
and haven't gotten to it yet but I want
to get to it we're going to be digging
into this book on blood brand barrier
now we're in this book right here okay
get ready for this
try this shot when you're trying to
break repeated painful thought patterns
resulting from a difficult situation or
hardship those repeated painful thought
patterns that just are coming and coming
in and coming in and coming in and
you're trying to break those and you're
like how do I break those
Kelsey box says love the shot therapy so
much I'm honored I really am
because I love them too ready for this
you experience chronic OCD do you guys
know anybody with chronic OCD oh see
these brutal
brutal and I have an incredible OCB
chapter in these brain safer books when
you read these chapters you will be
blown away line for line information
it's out of control
you're experiencing chronic OCD or
you're going through a relapse or
heightening of OCD symptoms okay here's
how it works with OCD your OCD is
calming down a lot of people your OCD is
calming down coming down and then boom
you gotta relapse you know it's a
relapse you know it is and it's coming
in that's when you do the obsessive shot
thought shifter right there boom that's
when you do it
okay check this out right this brain
shot covers all forms of varieties of
OCD can I speak good today all varieties
of OCD this brain shot actually covers
obsessive thought shifter let's do
another let's talk another about another
Point ready
oh check this out
interesting a song you don't want to
hear anymore keeps playing in your head
how many songs have you heard in your
head you don't want to hear anymore
did you ever get trapped With a Song in
your head did you ever
it happens to me did you ever have that
where you got a song in your head that
just won't stop like you can't stop
hearing that song it will not stop
and you're like I need this song out
do the obsessive thought shifter blast
that song out
get ready for this one
repetitive thoughts that are disturbing
you and they continue to replay what
about a repetitive thought that's
disturbing you did you guys ever have a
repetitive thought that disturbs you
Elaine says OCD is awful oh yeah
for sure
repetitive thoughts that are disturbing
you and they continue to replay that's
when you bring the obsessive thought
shifter boom you bring that baby in
right there
okay there's another one
repetitive thoughts are causing you to
make repetitive actions
the thoughts coming in Escape they won't
stop
you're not hungry anymore you already
ate but you keep on going to the same
food you're gonna go to the food you're
you're you're not even hungry you
already ate but you're gonna go and eat
the same food you're gonna go and eat
more of it no but I'm I'm not hungry
anymore get the obsessive thought
shifter in knock it out
you ready for this
you're hearing voices in your head or
experiencing thoughts that are upsetting
how many people they hear voices in
their head
a lot of people hear voices inside their
head
or they're experiencing thoughts that
are upsetting so how about that maybe
it's not voices but they hear they're
experiencing thoughts that are upsetting
them so the thoughts keep on going in
and out and they're upsetting them and
upsetting them thoughts are going all
around right that's when you break out
the obsessive thoughts this is one of
the most incredible tools
the the books are so packed even if you
just discarded everything all that
incredible information and all the tools
and just had obsessive thought shifter
it's that incredible it's that
life-changing
you ready
unproductive or Highly Questionable and
maybe telling you to do things that
aren't good or smart so you hear
thoughts in your head or you have
repetitive thoughts that are
unproductive Highly Questionable and
maybe telling you to do things that
aren't good or smart you hear a voice in
your head that's telling you to do
something that's really stupid or to do
something that's really bad for you
get the obsessive thought shifter in
there right away
let's keep on going through these a
little bit more
Nicholas said holy crap Kelsey box says
does it work for songs that get stuck in
your head
but yeah that's the whole point yes the
obsessive thought shifter you get a song
that's stuck in your head knock it out
Laura says notify the seller and request
a new copy you mean there was a copy
that was damaged from whatever you got
it from or something or you got like the
wrong book yeah definitely notified so
mood shifter that's an incredible one
all on its own you guys dealing with
mood issues do you know anybody that has
a mood issue it's a struggle for so many
people
PK says I have all of those
saw that right on YouTube
nerve shifter
that's a big one right there
very different
nerve shifter ready when you're feeling
shaky or anxious you guys ever felt
shaky or anxious get the nerve shifter
out telling you right now boom take care
of it get the nerve shifter out amazing
If you experience random spasms
Twitches ticks or shifting or moving
pain throughout your body that's a great
way to do it right there boom incredible
when struggling with any kind of
neurological onset or episode if you've
got a neurological episode kind of
kicking up something kicking up yeah for
sure bring this one in Nerf shifter
how but how G shots can stop thoughts
can't get that so you can't get like how
a g shot can it's not a Juice shot
a Juice shot is just a regular Juice
shot
this is Advanced information synergistic
synergistically put together from Above
This is not man-made
if it's man-made yeah then you just got
juice
yep if it's man-made if it's man-made
information then yeah just everybody
stays sick in the world and they stay
sick until they get so sick and then
they someday somehow find a medical
medium book and it all makes sense and
they start moving forward
there's a physical problem with the
brain
the brain shot therapy cleanses and the
brain shot therapy shots
are incredible
powerful
historic information because it's
history being made right now from above
to help change things
to help you heal it's unbelievable this
nerve shifter
to break a nervous feeling about the
moment you're in the future or something
to happen you know what I told
you know what I told my
note I told my parents
God bless them no one I told my parents
told them this the other day
I said Mom and Dad
I got this gift at age four
we all know
I pour my guts out
I spent the life of trying to get the
information out there and there's always
going to be somebody that's just not
gonna understand and they're just gonna
think it's just a regular old health
book of
a fruit or a vegetable or whoever or
what
I've come to the realization there's
going to be people that are going to get
it and there's going to people people
that are not going to get it I come to
the realization I was telling my folks
that there's people that are going to
know what's in these books
and they're going to understand and
there's people that are never going to
understand it and they're never even
going to get the books
anyway a thought is not intangible it
runs in electricity read the books to
learn how it works physically in the
brain it's Advanced information now
let's just answer a question someone was
asking
so what it is is like
you can have the greatest books in
history the greatest Health books of all
time which are the brain saver books
but you know in your heart that not
everybody is gonna gonna get the book
these brain shot therapies physically
give the brain what it needs so that's
another answer to the person's question
it's like what
how do these work it's because the brain
shot is designed to physically give the
person's brain what it needs to overcome
that obsessive thought to overcome that
nerve twitch to overcome that betrayal
and broken trust moment to overcome
something that they're dealing and
struggling with that mold exposure that
pharmaceutical exposure that heavy metal
detox that heavy metal exposure sorry
whatever it is they're designed to
actually
shift the person's gear their stabilizer
shifters and exposure shots
powerful Lawrence has just ordered your
book amazing
incredible TJ says I can't wait to try
it
aisling says I tell everybody about you
I'm honored thank you for being here
let's go into some stuff we talked about
the by the way one last thing the brain
shot therapy challenge is going to be
next week October 17th
look out for my email sign up to my
newsletter so you know when it's coming
what's going on so let me just say this
point about all this
thoughts are not separate from what's
happening in the brain physically that's
where everyone gets it wrong if the
brain doesn't have what it needs and has
things disrupting the neurons and it's
in the way of your thoughts
everything's going to get out of place
all right let's move on to the
blood-brain barrier a little bit I'm
going to put one book up here
we got some stuff to do let's get
rolling
so I'm in this book here
blood-brain barrier chapter you guys
with me any of you guys got the book
right now and you can open it up and
just go into the blood brain barrier
chapter have you even looked at that yet
because whoa and each each page is
packed just insane blood brain barrier
page 184 in brain saver
our human body is not geared for the
levels of exposure we experience on this
planet that's something that you have to
digest and let it resonate our human
bodies your human body all of our human
bodies were never Geared for the level
of exposure that's here on this planet
right now
the blood-brain barrier
the blood-brain barrier never
anticipated the Industrial Revolution
and the classified medical industry
pathogen Revolution
our blood-brain barrier because I've
heard people say oh nothing gets through
the blood-brain barrier it's like oh
really
everything gets through the blood brain
barrier sadly enough
almost everything
so the our blood brain barriers never
anticipated the Industrial Revolution
were up against or the classified
medical industry pathogen Revolution
were up against our blood-brain barrier
had no idea that was coming ever
the human blood-brain barrier
convincing us that we're equipped to
handle any toxins that come our way is
like convincing us that our human body
is equipped to handle nuclear waste
that's just mind-blowing to me
we created on the planet so we should be
fine hey we created nuclear waste on the
planet so we should be fine our
blood-brain barrier will handle nuclear
waste no problem because it was created
on the planet
sure blood brain barrier can handle
everything it will be good
everything bad that's created on this
planet will be fine because it was
created on this planet
our blood-brain barrier should have no
problem protecting us against nuclear
waste or any other toxic material right
or blood-brain barrier is incredible it
could stop anything it could stop
anything
if you guys just came on here reading
through the brain saver books forty
percent off Amazon
dot com us right now 40 off take a look
make sure you get a couple of these
because it's a set
books are huge
get ready for this no one is measuring
the levels of toxins are in our
environment in relation to how our
bodies handle and receive them no one's
measuring toxins are in our environment
you could be driving down the road and
there could be a town or city truck
spraying
some dangerous herbicides like they do
on the side of the roads and you can
just have your child sitting in the
passenger seat with your window down and
literally just take it all in that
herbicide right when you're driving down
the road no one's measuring anything
anywhere
mosquito sprays being dropped all over
this planet on Everybody by helicopters
no one's measuring that
Kaelyn says can we do brain shots on the
369s yes you can you can bring in the
brain shots while you're doing the 369s
you don't have to stop your medical
medium protocols to do the brain shots
really good question Caitlin thank you
for that because I forgot to tell
everybody that my bad my bad my bad my
bad
you can keep your 28 day cleanses you
can keep which is medical medium you can
keep your medical medium heavy metal
detoxes you can keep whatever you want
you can keep your medical medium three
six nines advanced
you can keep your medical medium
right all your medical medium your
monocleanse your morning cleanse
you can keep those too you can be on a
medical media monocleanse
and still do your shots
I'm a brain shot therapy
medical Industries don't want to admit
there are toxic heavy metals in our
brain did you know that they don't the
industries don't want you to know you've
got toxic heavy metals in the brain they
don't even want to entertain the idea
never mind that we're living with
inflammation in our brain from pathogens
everybody is publicly known medical
research and sense so what you're going
to learn something in the medical mean
books that's going to be mind-blowing
this alone in the mm books the brain
saver books is going to blow your mind
there's something called publicly known
medical research in science and the
classified medical research and science
these are the only books out here in
history that are actually distinguished
distinguishing distinguishing
distinguishing that's it the difference
not a lot of words going through my
brain right now to get this out to you
guys
so you need to know that there actually
is a difference there's two systems
built these books describe and detail
what that all is
which is incredible all on its own
hell yeah on day nine good cool you're
on day nine absolutely
so check this out
these books are the only books in
history so far out there that are going
to talk to you about the truth and tell
you about the classified medical
research and Science and the publicly
known uh medical research and science
and what the differences are
by the way brain shots are in day
brain shots can be yes used on day nine
of the 369 that's okay
I'm hearing information from SOC I'm
trying to read the books I'm trying to
I'm trying to answer questions
I'm getting readings from Spirit of
compassion on a bunch of you guys
because it happens automatically and
there's nothing I can do about it
at the same time getting information
from Spirit of compassion at the same
time trying to read the book at the same
time trying to express everything
I might bring some
balls out and I could juggle them too
maybe while we're doing all that I could
try that
I do had a shovel
had no time to practice
medical Industries don't want us to
admit there's toxic heavy metals in our
brain they don't even want to entertain
the idea never mind that we're living
with inflammation publicly known medical
research in science are in the infancy
stages of recognizing a chronic illness
dude dude
publicly known medical research and
science are at their baby stages just
recognizing chronic illness could be
pathogen related
if they're that early in the process of
understanding chronic illness how
advanced can they be in understanding
our body's complex mechanisms like the
blood-brain barrier you mean to tell me
it was just a couple of years ago before
medical research and science started
adopting medical medium information
about pathogens and all that it was just
a couple of years ago they don't even
know how the blood-brain barrier works
a lot of you have questions about timing
of brain shots the questions are
answered in the brain saver books so you
guys if you have timing questions all
about the brain shot Therapies
they're in the books the information's
in there
totally I didn't leave that out I made
sure that these books were jacked up
with that information
our blood-brain barrier was not made for
any of this we act like it's an
impermanable structure that has no
limitations what you'll find in
alternative medicine if anybody even
utters or spits out the word blood brain
barrier it's as if it's an impermanable
force on its own and nothing can pass
through it
we act like it's an impermanable
structure that has no limitations
nuclear waste anybody
Dr Sherry green unfortunately Medical
Science has messed up in many ways that
comes out every day now absolutely not
only that here's how it works and I talk
about it in the brain saver books you
get sick okay here's what it is
you're born
you're here you're a baby
you grow up
and you're taught that
science has it all sewed up you go to
school science knows everything you go
to university science knows everything
and then someday you get sick
and then you think science knows
everything I'll be fixed tomorrow I'm
sick now with all these crazy symptoms
I'm just gonna go to a doctor my mom and
dad are going to take me to a doctor and
I'll be all fixed tomorrow and then
you'll realize uh what
uh autoimmune uh what this that I'm not
being fixed what pills do you want me to
take Mom Dad what did the doctor say so
then you're coming out you're like a
college student now you're learning if
you're sick as a college student you're
learning uh I thought science knew
everything and then you go into your 20s
and you're like I'm so sick I can't work
now or I can't function and then you
learn that science let you down and now
you're like 27 years old and you're sick
and you're like what was I sold all
these years that science and research
knew everything I've been to 20 doctors
I'm 27 years old I've taken 20
medications I've been to 20 functional
medicine doctors
and I'm still sick
everybody thinks just Industrial Waste
and solvents and toxic heavy metals
don't exist in our body but they cross
the blood-brain barrier I learned that
nothing could cross the blood-brain
barrier either in school health with Liz
oh my God
it's in Oh My God moment like oh my God
exactly
you know this is a moment where like
this bumblebees lying around and it's
alone and it finds another bumblebee
that and it's like another bumblebee
right butterflies flying around and
butterfly finds another butterfly
we always get all the validation from
you
Health with Liz I just want to say this
okay that wait uh
Amanda says this means we don't need to
blame ourselves for our own depression
or anxiety that's the whole point too
because everybody's blamed on it
everybody's blamed on it health local is
you're right you were taught that
nothing can get through the blood-brain
barrier
everybody's taught right that nothing
gets through the blood brain barrier but
they're wrong
I talk about what gets through the
blood-brain barrier these books are
incredible
wondering Wishin says the dream shot
tastes amazing the dream shot which I
personally love
I take the dream shot
I take the dream shot before I go to bed
I take the dream shot a little bit
earlier than that too I take it twice
actually so a lot of times I'll take a
dream shot at like
10 o'clock at night then I'll take the
dream shot like two in the morning
before I go to bed
why am I up till two I'm working
wake up at six then I get my four hours
of sleep depending that's a good day
foreign
all right
enough about me it's not the Anthony
Williams Show it never was
about answers and about our suffering
all someone has to do is use the term
blood-brain barrier to make us feel like
we're protected it's like you're
protected you've got your blood brain
barrier
and yet the reality is that all these
and more inevitably cross meaning toxins
you guys cross our blood-brain barrier
many Pharmaceuticals are specifically
engineered to cross our blood-brain
barrier even the Pharmaceuticals show
this is mind-blowing right here nobody
knows any of this it doesn't matter what
podcast doctor talks or whoever no one
knows any of this look at this even the
Pharmaceuticals not designed
with it in mind to cross your
blood-brain barrier
cross your blood brain barrier
interesting so you can be taking
Pharmaceuticals and they're not designed
across the blood-brain barrier but they
cross the blood-brain barrier
what is the dream shot are our animal
rescue
the dream shot
the brain shot therapy the dream shot
get the books
take a chance be the judge yourself
get the books I promise you this your
mind will be blown blown
let me put it this way prepare yourself
when you get the books
if you know anything about health your
mind is going to be blown if you don't
know anything about health your mind is
going to be blown
our blood-brain barrier was designed to
keep natural mostly bodily toxins out of
the brain so it was designed only for
natural bodily toxins
that's the only thing our blood Point
barrier was designed for nobody knows
this oh Paul says what is a break a
dream shot a dream shot let's go let's
find it
dream shot
I'm gonna find it hang on here it is
right here
dreams shifter shot that's what it is
you're looking at it right there get
ready for this Paul
stay on please
this shot can be taken at any time of
day or evening if you wish to take it
before a nap or before bed you're
welcome to make the shot earlier in the
day and save it in the refrigerator
until you're ready examples of when to
use it include Paul
check this out dude examples of when you
use it include when you want to use your
dreams as a gateway to understand your
soul and your Soul's past how insane is
that by the way Paul join the brain shot
therapy challenge next week we will go
in depth and I will answer your
questions get in the medical medium
newsletter list to get your grocery list
and ready for the challenge it's October
17th but get in that list soon because
we're going to be talking about it
before then all right all right all
right Get Ready Get Ready Get Ready all
right
just kidding hang on ready
check this out you want to use your
dreams as a gateway to understand your
soul and your Soul's past you guys want
to use your dreams as a gateway to
understand your soul
or am I just stupid like is that just a
dumb thing to do when I was getting this
information from Spirit of compassion
right and spirit of compassion said
they need a dream shifter they need a
dream shifter
was like what are you talking about
I think it was something like three in
the morning
and I was just sitting at my desk and I
was writing feverishly to every word
that was coming through right and then
Spirit of compassion said we need a
dream shifter and I stopped and I said
what are you talking about
Renee says you're going to make me cry
check this out about the dream shifter
if you want to understand your soul and
your Soul's past you take the dream
shifter at night Allison said this is
incredible I need this screenshot the
dream shot is one of the most
mind-blowing parts of the brain saver
books
it's just one it's one of the most it's
just there's so many you ready you're
having difficulty dreaming and want to
dream how many people have a difficult
time dreaming and they want to dream
take the dream shifter right how about
this you want to decode now this right
here blows my like hat off you want
ready you want to decode the meaning of
your dreams and gain more insight into
your dreams I love that dream info in
the brain saver books too
it's in the brain saver box
ready
dreams are regularly waking you up and
you don't want to be woken up by your
dreams take the dream shifter how about
this one you're fearful of going to
sleep take the dream shifter shot
over this one you're trying to reach
others through your dreams oh my God
okay check this out you guys know that
medical medium information has a street
cred it's consistent it's not
contradictive and it works you guys know
that millions of people heal from
medical medium books I'm just I'm just
telling you this for a second because
check this out millions of people have
healed from medical medium books they're
all incredible books right
because they work
the information in the medical medium
books work
everybody knows that except for the
haters and naysaters but everybody knows
that check this out so if it says in the
medical medium book
you're trying to reach others through
your dreams
and that means that's possible so yes
that's possible that's what I mean how
incredible is that okay how about this
one
you're trying to enter other people's
dreams
yeah that's what I'm talking about right
there
how insane is that okay here's another
one too you're not sleeping enough this
shot can help you heal through your
dream process in this short amount of
sleep you're getting if you're somebody
that's not sleeping good you can't sleep
good and you're only sleeping for a
short amount of time that's when the
dream shifter shot comes in so you can
get maximum maximum rest in that short
window of sleep
I've been using it to get by I have
extremely short window of sleep because
I'm working too hard and in that seven
day schedule a week and working too hard
I'm like doing this the dream shifter
all right back the blood brand barrier
my apologies
our blood brain barrier was designed to
keep natural Mo mostly bodily toxins out
of the brain
that's all it was designed for was it
designed for anything else
you guys 40 off on both these books take
advantage of it as soon as you can
amazon.com us when someone has a little
too much uric acid oh get ready for this
one the books are so mind-blowing it's
hard to focus on just one topic I'm
actually like scrambled eggs right now
because there's so much going on
you can spend a lifetime reading these
books over and over again and I promise
you you'll be like I never read that
before this book
Jen coffin said it did the energy
shifter yesterday gave me lots of energy
before going out incredible
Jamie says I'm making my heavy metal
detox smoothie right now and there's
seven heavy metal detox cleanses
including Advanced cleanse in the
medical medium brain saver books
when someone has a little too much uric
acid
build up because a kidney is weakened a
lot of people have weakened kidneys
without knowing it for instance that
uric acid is not supposed to permeate
the blood-brain barrier
if someone gets a cut that goes deep and
leads to a skin infection then that
person could develop the beginning
stages of sepsis in which case the blood
infection is not supposed to cross the
blood-brain barrier the blood-brain
barrier is for when you get a cut and
you get some kind of sepsis or infection
the blood-brain barrier is when you got
too much uric acid building up in your
kidneys and system because you have a
weak kidney the blood-brain barrier is
for normal bodily toxins like normal
ammonia amounts of ammonia in your body
certain things that are inside the body
the blood-brain barrier tries to stop a
lot of the sin doesn't stop all of it
but there's the natural stuff that
occurs inside our body the blood-brain
barrier is trying to stop but the
blood-brain barrier doesn't stop
anything else
if someone ingests a toxic plant that's
been on planet Earth for 10 000 years
and was never meant to be human food the
blood-brain barrier is there to hold
back at least some of those poisons who
knows that
who knows that
Deborah says thank you for all the free
info you share that guy Michael doesn't
think I have any free anything my rent
just went up to 300 this time so I need
the adrenal stabilizer totally
understand
you need the free information you guys
need the free information this isn't a
game
Julie says since starting the shots four
so far surely whoa four so far you're on
Facebook I haven't needed to take my
daily afternoon nap
boom
this is what these are incred tell
people you guys tell others tell them
tell them
just listen to this one little part
yes I know listen I know your time is
valuable
I feel bad that I come on here and I'm
like I'm trying to take up all your time
today
but listen to this part okay
I have a lot of respect for you guys
people don't realize this a lot of
respect for your life what you're doing
what's going on in your life what you're
up against
you've got a lot of respect
you deserve all the respect
okay you ready okay if someone ingests
the toxic plant that's been on planet
Earth for ten thousand years and was
never meant to be human food the
blood-brain barrier is there to hold
back at least some of the toxins in an
effort to prevent the brain from going
into toxic shock no one on this planet
knows that
and you can't make up this stuff
can't make up almost 1300 pages of
literally scripture from above
that becomes Advanced Medical
information that science research ends
up stealing down the road and proving it
right but never proving it wrong
our blood cerebral fluid
barrier is also over taxed cerebral
spinal fluid which surrounds the brain
and spinal cord is supposed to be pure
with no contamination that's the gold
standard that's the gold standard in
this time on planet Earth our cerebral
spinal fluid is not pure so our spinal
fluid's not pure
okay all of us got dirty spinal fluid if
we're getting exposures
okay
let's keep on going a little bit more
about that was pretty cool that's the
gold standard and this time on planet
Earth
our spinal fluid is not pure it's
harboring chemical soups from Industries
pathogenic byproducts toxic heavy metals
and more a thousand years ago cerebral
spinal fluid May simply have had some
toxic heavy metal contamination but
that's about it for the people living in
cities drinking lead water back during
the Roman days
spinal fluid had a whole different
Purity hundreds of thousands of years
ago today we walk around polluted I
can't scratch how much information is in
the blood-brain barrier chapter there's
more paragraphs and more information
it's just it's each line is jam-packed
if you guys think this is just a
blood-brain barrier book you're wrong
it's an everything book it's loaded with
so much information
I mean seriously
I just want you guys to know
okay
symptoms and conditions let's hit it for
a couple of seconds you guys got
symptoms your pain and suffering
enlightened right here your pain and
suffering enlightened you guys got
symptoms
there is a quote right next to it
there's quotes all through the book let
me read a quote in today's world
getting a symptom or condition becoming
chronically sick is The New Normal
or at a place in the world where you're
either not so sick or very sick
everyone is dealing with something
everybody is facing at least one symptom
whether they call it a symptom or not
whether they realize their health is
challenged or not
Anthony William
hey dubs aw
so I'm in the symptoms and conditions
chapter
and it's packed
I don't know I don't want to bore you
reading off
dozens and dozens and dozens of symptoms
and conditions
but they're here and then I'll I'll take
a look and I'll paw through it a little
bit and see what we got but there's so
many symptoms and conditions I mean it's
actually unbelievable when you think
about it
right
and I mean it's just incredible how many
[Applause]
I mean it's ADHD ALS right but
information about anxious anxiousness
autism right I'm just skimming through
balance issues and dizziness Bells Palsy
brain abscesses brain fog brain
inflammation remember you might not even
realize what you have wrong with you
until you read the book
people walk around sick and they see 20
doctors say they don't know and then
they read something in here like oh my
God now I know what's wrong with me
and there's an eating disorder chapter a
bipolar chapter a depression chapter an
anxiety chapter and an OCD chapter for
God's sake this section right here is
mind-blowing you guys brain lesions
white spots dark spots scar tissue and
calcifications inside the brain in
detail of what's going on what the cause
is it's an it's basically a whole full
chapter of it which is unbelievable
foreign
breast implant illness which I'm on
right now breast implant illness is a
term for a broad spectrum of symptoms
many of them neurological such as
fatigue tingles and numbness restless
legs heart palpitations dizziness eye
floaters brain fog anxiety weakness of
the limbs people suffering with breast
implant illness have spent decades
trying to be validated trying to be
heard the breast implant illness is
incredible
Jamie says oh my God that Viral brain
chapter oh yeah that Viral brain chapter
is packed in just it's mind-blowing
seriously it's mind-blowing
it's really incredible when I think
about you guys we're live right now by
the way this isn't a recorded video I'm
live
I know I'm I can tell you because I'm
going to tell you right now I'm going to
lift my right arm up and if I wasn't if
we weren't live right now I wouldn't be
able to do it I'm gonna lift my right up
we're live right now
it's a live test
you know that'll determine if it's live
or not live I'm gonna hit my hand on the
top of this brain right here if we're
live right now and I go do that that
means we're live we're definitely alive
right now
definitely alive
but we are live
all right breast implant is a huge
section breast implant illness
bulimia burnout
atrophy to the brain hypoxia Cushing
syndrome dementia depersonalization
depression or dysphoria difficult coping
dysautonomia dyslexia Eating Disorders
encephalopathy
excessive sweating hyperhidrosis fatigue
fibromyalgia focusing concentration
gastroparesis Galion Beret headaches
somebody might not even know they have
glue ombre but they've been suffering
from guilla ombre from the last 10 years
read the book find the stuff that's in
here
hemisphase should neglect right left
neglect
hunting him's disease inflammatory
myopathy intercranial hypertension
people don't know they have intracranial
hypertension then you read the book and
you're like holy crap this whole time
ahead intracranial hypertension and my
doctor didn't even know the books are
there to help you find your way you have
to look into them insomnia
itching and burning itching and burning
crazy itching and burning people can't
describe it like they don't know what
the answer is they've been to 20 doctors
joint and muscle pain learning
disabilities and disorders the
information's in here long haul sea and
long-haul flu long haul sea
Long Haul flu
lupus Lyme disease
oh my God the triggers for Lyme disease
right there the triggers for life you
guys
the triggers for lime let's go into it
severe C that's your trigger for lime
extensive blood draw
that's a trigger for Lyme getting all
your blood drawn
Mercury based Dental amalgams fillings
trigger for
whatever
um for for life this is not for blood
draw blood draws a trigger Mercury and
other forms are a trigger blood draw
chapters a masterpiece let's head there
pretty soon
continue toxic mold exposure pesticide
herbicide exposure insecticides in the
home flu
mild sea death in a family broken heart
taking care of a sick loved one all
triggers for Lyme it just keeps on going
on I love the addictions chapter I'm
addicted to the book
to the books
what is Long Haul flu
it's a medical medium term been there
before long haul C
you get the crap beat out of you when
you catch the flu and then you don't
recover even though the flu is gone
that's a long haul
it's like when the C beats the crap out
of somebody and they're not recovering
and they're like sick for six months but
nobody knows why and then all these
theories happen out there but long haul
C Long Haul flew
detail of what it is what's really
happening Meniere's disease memory and
loss issues memory loss issues
meningitis migraines mitochondria
myopathy mood changes motor skill
disorders
dyspraxia multiple sclerosis
got a comedian first came out with the
cause of that and then you see it out
there now it was taken from these books
from all the medical mean books Milan
nerve seat damage chronic inflammatory
demyelation right mystery fears and
worries narcolepsy
mystery nausea and vomiting
neuralgia
neurological asthma it's a medical
medium thing right there neurological
meaning like the information it's all
medical medium neurological asthma
knowing what asthma is when it's
neurological it's like a game changer in
somebody's life there's a micro dosing
chapter you guys you got to read the
micro dosing chapter if you want to be
mind blown read the micro dosing chapter
I could do this for hours there's so
much information in these books hours
and hours and hours there's an alcohol
chapter
Eureka man there's an alcohol chapter
Neurosis numbness and tingling
neuropathy neuritis obsessive you know
OCD compulsive disorder orthorexia
Dr Fawn Medical Doctor MD an incredible
medical doctor science has validated
what aw says about long C
I am extremely blessed to have you on
here and say that incredible medical
doctor
who practices
and and just does incredible work
creative Hearth my blood showed I had
perfect health but I was sick blood
tests don't prove anything I'll talk all
about that in the medical medium brain
saver books you can learn so much about
that
I have a whole section about that very
thing in the blood draw chapter
orthorexia overeating Parkinson's
disease personality disorders psychosis
pots
books are packed you guys
they're packed
I don't even know what to say
I don't even know what to say greatest
books of all time tell others that
they're the greatest books of all time
post about it if you can the greatest
books of all time the greatest Health
books in history
however you want to phrase it but they
are
they are and you'll know when you're
holding me and know when you'll read
them you'll know you'll know
truly
truly incredible
I'm so excited about this
anchor shifter wow Sheila it's an
amazing shifter
there's an EMF section okay let's here's
what's cool about the EMF section in
here it's EMF information no one's ever
heard before
not EMF
anyway moment of silence
Jennifer said I love if you discussed
marijuana
I'm not a big marijuana fan I don't use
marijuana myself personally I don't I
never did
but these are the but there's a micro
dosing chapter that I think you might
like then
a micro dosing chapter I'm not judging
anybody who smokes pot
or whatever eats pot or whatever you
want to do vaporizes whatever I'm not
I'm not I don't judge anybody for it
every time now and then I might be like
you know hey man
what
but I'm just kidding
I got a friend that smokes a lot of pot
I haven't seen him in a while
Botox section in the books I talk about
Botox
oh yeah yeah here
my friend does yeah the one when I what
the one I had here
you mean my friend that came on live
yeah no I know he's like
he's like crazy and Tall right the
friend I had on here PTSD
repetitive strain repetitive right
strain
restless leg syndrome sadness yeah
sadness
Uma Kelly says ocean wait a minute no
ocean is just one of my other friends
there's another friend I had on here Uma
you can't oh my God Uma you always know
everything that goes on on these
who's the other one is it Bryce
who was it it's Bryce
Uma it's Bryce
oh no
Rhonda said I am amazed how neutral you
manage to remain considering how
inflammatory a lot of these issues can
be
Rhonda
I stay as neutral as I can but the
haters are big
the amount of crap talk out there on
social media about me is unbelievable
behind the scenes and in front of the
scenes
people try to tear down the mm left and
right I got the kick me sign on my back
my butt's been kicked so hard so many
times it's sore Lynette says are you a
Christian I'm wondering since you say
the info comes from above I know you say
from SOC but I struggle to understand
this as a Christian
I really do like a majority of your info
and have four of your books as listen I
will say this okay
that you being here means the world to
me okay because I know that some
Christians they'll be like he's the
devil
it's like okay well
a lifetime of work getting people out of
wheelchairs
saving lives
bringing information to people so they
can heal
and then choose whatever religion they
want to choose in their life
it's not easy to partake in a religion
or religious belief system or anything
if you're so sick
or not here
my job is to make sure that everybody
gets healthy
heals
get strong and they can believe in
anything they want to believe in
what I've always told Christians
is
what about profits out there
Christians believe in Prophets
I do know that
that's something that Christians believe
in
and if you look into the medical medium
books you'll find there is
a message always
from the scripture down here so you can
look and find it
I'm going to do a show
about Christianity at some point in the
medical meeting podcast I just haven't
had the chance I have all eight of your
books I love them
amazing
William Miller it's Bryce
Cold Light spring says it seems prophets
only existed in biblical times
but I can't see the rest of the comment
oh there it is which is kind of weird
Trisha Marie with a Christian background
all of this makes complete and perfect
sense to me
I think a lot of Christians use medical
meme information
I really do
I know there's some that just they can't
get around they can't get around it and
they're like I just can't look at those
books or something and I still have
respect for everybody in them it's all
good
check out the alien podcast when you get
a chance
you guys Have you listened to the alien
podcast at Apple podcast
check out the alien podcast
tonight is Tick spasms in dystonia
Tourette Syndrome tremors
alien podcast at Medical medium podcast
on Apple podcast trigeminal neuralgia
vertigo the books are packed with a
tremendous amount of information you
guys detailed from front to back
RR animal rescue aw you have amazing
stories to tell I have enjoyed your
interviews on other podcasts Etc and I'm
amazed at the energy you give to this
cause and one of the reasons why I don't
do a lot of podcasts okay so let me just
tell you how it works every single day
we get emailed
Right medical medium all kinds of um
publicists all kinds of podcast people
all kinds of TV show people all kinds of
agencies all kinds of Networks TV
networks I'll cut mainstream TV networks
and they're always emailing saying let's
do the medical medium series on
mainstream TV let's do can you do all
these podcasts people want you on they
want you on if I do all that I'm not
going to be I'm not going to be able to
create this
it's not going to happen if I go when I
do all of that go on all these podcasts
all these TV interviews all this stuff
I'm asked constantly
if I go and I go and make it the Anthony
Williams circus show and I go on all
that stuff you guys and spend all this
time and go in the Limelight
these aren't going to get done
these are not going to get done this
won't be in your hands
so I I do very little out there
Melissa Davis as a Christian I have no
trouble believing that Spirit would
choose a strong person to relay an
important message
and hijacked his entire life I will tell
you that that's exactly factual
everything you just said about me is
that yes my life was hijacked
am I strong don't know
when I was on the when I was on um
Oliver and Kate Hudson's podcast I
talked about a little bit about that and
Oliver
Ollie said you know like there it is
there it is that's why you were picked
anyway
Lorraine house is grateful for your
office chair
maybe someday it'll be in a museum
anyway you guys
um the point is this I didn't want to
make it the Anthony Williams Show out
there and I can go and do all that stuff
I can fill my entire schedule I just
want to say this I can fill my entire
schedule
with TV appearances podcast appearances
TV series
all of it I can hop on a plane and fly
around everywhere and be in every Studio
to Kingdom Come
I can
and I can do that for years and talk
about how I hear Spirit of compassion
and talk about all of that but I'm going
to make it the Anthony Williams Show and
then these things will never be produced
ever all these things won't be produced
they just won't be made they won't be
produced it won't be possible it just
won't happen
it just won't happen because this is the
scripture right here and my job is to
make sure I do this and try not to do so
many appearances anywhere once in a
while I'll break and do something I'd be
like all right I'll do it
let's cleanse the heel by the way
you know I look at this book and I say
thank you for turning so many lives
around healing so many people and saving
so many lives thank you because you've
saved so many lives I say that to that
book right there and I sit at my office
desk and I say thank you for saving
millions of lives around the planet to
you too because without you so many
people would have not gotten off of
mattress Island I say thank you thank
you thank you and I do I'm grateful
that's why
and then I'll say the soc thank you to
even though you've hijacked my life and
made my life very hard
it makes sense all of it builds up
builds a pond and doesn't contradict so
that's the whole thing all the medical
meaning books build and build upon each
other with the new information coming in
but never contradict
medical me I just I just want to say
this last thing I've said it before
ready medical medium information is not
common sense
because none of the medical medium
information was ever common
originally
it was unique original and brand new and
then as it got out there and the
millions of people partooking it and and
spread that information around much of
it became common
meaning like common knowledge but
medical meme information just makes
sense it's not common sense
by the way clean your books if you guys
want if you get a dirty book
from Amazon or somewhere because their
conveyor belt got greasy
because their conveyor belt got greasy
put a little dish soap
damp cloth not too wet you don't want to
soak your book because then you're gonna
have a wet book and you clean off your
covers you they're all brand new when
they leave the publishers
right the printer and they leave the
publisher they're pristine
no odor
no air fresheners no scented candles no
perfumes no colognes no no whatever
they're pristine and what happens is
they go into like the Amazon places and
what happens is the conveyor belts are
greasy they're all filled with grease
because they have to grease The Wheels
on the conveyors
and then
the books get thrown on the conveyor
belt and you might get some grease you
have to clean it off they'll come out
beautiful you guys leave some reviews if
you can I hate asking for reviews
but it keeps the trolls like from
getting ahead ones that did not purchase
the books the ones that never read the
books the ones that just don't like
medical medium because they don't like
my face they don't like my voice they
don't like what I'm doing whatever and
look out for imposters yeah if you can
if you can leave a review that would be
incredible because it helps other people
find it and then say oh my God this
person said this that I I'm gonna take a
look I'm gonna take a chance
and look out for imposters
there's some imposters saying some
terrible things and doing terrible
things to people they say they're
Anthony William or Williams
they pretend they're the medical medium
and then they offer consultations I
don't do consultations
and they offer consultations and then
they say terrible things and do terrible
things to people
and so please look out for imposters
this is the official Anthony Williams
standing in front of you right now I am
not an imposter DM you know DM people at
they what they do is they DM people
sorry the imposters DM people asking for
money and worse things
it's a sick
people
so and they'll ask for you know money
and they have websites and they pretend
they're Anthony William the medical
medium and then he asks for stuff I
don't know it's just bad it's bad
Lorraine L it's sick and it is indeed Dr
Fawn MD watch out for anyone who calls
themselves medical medium
well Michael yes my friends my oh Uma
yes my friend was having consultations
for a few months until he realized it
was an imposter
my God it gets me so upset
I need this [ __ ] I need a shifter
my God
that that gets me so upset to know that
you have a friend that literally was
dealing with an imposter for months God
knows what was happening
I gotta pick a shifter out for myself on
that one I think it's going to be this
one right here
I'm gonna pick the trauma shock and loss
stabilizer because I'm really upset
about that
it's heartbreaking because they can mess
so many people up and the imposters have
messed up a lot of people up I need a
shifter when I'm done here I'm gonna
make a shifter I'm going to make the
trauma shock and loss stabilizer I want
to read what that is please spread the
word about the books too and everything
you guys and spread the word about
imposters too if you can so here's a
check this out this shot is supportive
tool for any kind of emotional upset did
you hear that I just got emotionally
upset
umakali told me that her friend was just
taken advantage of by an imposter for
months and that actually does hit me
like hard
so it says here this shot trauma shock
and loss stabilizer this shot is
supportive tool for any kind of
emotional upset emotional challenge or
emotional stress I would classify that
as emotional stress knowing people are
being hurt by other people like that bad
people
so consider using when you're given
challenging news or you receive any
emotional blows
you're dealing with any kind of
emotional upheaval it's an emotional
upheaval for me because
Uma had a friend that literally dealt
with an imposter for months I can't even
tell you how that pisses me off
Nicholas says message Tick Tock to
complaining about them taking medical
medium off their site yeah they
permanently bam bammed me banded
they said I'm banned Tick Tock kicked me
off
they kicked me off when I showed him the
brain when I showed everybody the Brain
book
and then they kicked me off because I
showed him the Brain book
like what kind of world are we living in
evil world it's evil Renee says there
was someone on Tick Tock who was saying
he did readings I was like no thanks God
all right so you're dealing with any
kind of emotional upheaval yes I'm gonna
use this one
okay okay you ready you ready
Tick Tock kicked me off of tick tock
but they won't take down all the
imposters there are medical medium and
postures on tick tock
taking advantage of people
doing terrible things and Tick Tock
purposely leaves them up but kicks me
off
and that's why I need the trauma shock
and loss stabilizer
so many it says your given challenging
news or receive any emotional blows
you're dealing with any kind of
emotional upheaval
if you've lost a pet or a loved one If
you experience any kind of loss well I
lost my Tick Tock um account
that I worked hard creating all those
like funny videos and stuff
you've been diagnosed with a chronic
illness or you heard something
challenging about your health it's great
to use this one
local and world events are affecting
your life I like the troubles to shock
and law stabilize for that you're going
through emotional turmoil within your
family or difficult friendships
Rhonda says you're not living till
you've been banned
that's really funny you're not living
until you burn the candle at four ends
like I do too
I don't recommend that it'll kill you
okay
amazing
you guys I just sit here with you guys
all day there's no question now
someone asked which book do you pick
which book do you pick first which one
do you get which book is it
which book do you get
boom
you get both you have to get both books
because it was one book
publisher couldn't print it too big too
heavy you can't have a 15 pound book
they said and they're right
guys
Ida says the world is evil
both books truly
I could play with these books all day
because they're the greatest books of
all time I literally can just I have
them I take them everywhere it doesn't
matter what I'm doing I take them
everywhere you guys I keep them on my
counters I have them everywhere I have
them in the kitchen I open them up for
recipes there's a hundred recipes in
here okay wait I'm not gonna go yet
you guys
this is insane
there's like three recipe books in this
book there's 12 books in both these
books six books in each book six books
these should be 500 books
Susan Horan says you need both books
they have different information in them
correct you guys brain detox tonic that
I can't wait to try again brain fueler
smoothie fueling the brain wild
blueberry yogurt whoa applesauce or a
pear sauce peaches and cream
um 20 banana mango this is uh
respiratory it's banana mango and wild
blueberry
brain saver salad brain armor salad it
keeps on going spinach soup famous
medical medium spinach soup whoa bring a
saver wraps
asparagus spinach dip stuffed Tomatoes
I'm just going through some of these
40 off amazon.com us
okay guys
gonna show you
I can't help it just playing around my
books all day all right all right
you know you guys I love you dearly okay
and I would I will sit in my office
chair
sweating my ass off
stress to the max
listening to SOC blow my brains out
for months upon months upon months
sacrifice life and everything else
around me
self-care down the drain I don't care as
long as you guys get these and we got
them here
I have an energy a life force the living
words or weapons of the light and
they're in these books
fact all right
you guys
Anthony you need a new chair
love you guys much