we are
everybody is different
but not like they think
everybody is different this is really
important to talk about today
every single person is different
let's talk about why
everyone's soul is different
if your soul
experiences a hardship
betrayal someone stabs you in the back
someone lets you down somebody breaks
your trust
something terrible happening in the
world right
exactly
tragedies
anything like that
if your soul
experiences that
that's what makes you different
than someone else
right
because your soul is unique to begin
with
and then the experiences
that your soul goes through are
different say it's a breakup say it's a
relationship
right say you were cheated on
how many people were cheated on
right
how many people were betrayed how many
people had their trust break
trust is a big one that's a big one
so many people go through so much with
trust and betrayal and hardship and then
we get sick
and we don't come out of our sickness we
don't come out of those physical
symptoms so we got these neurological
symptoms and we don't come out of it
it's like wait a minute i've been to my
second doctor i've been to my third
doctor now i've been to my neurologist
now i'm going to another doctor and then
a pulmonologist and then i'm going to
another internist
and he's writing out more scripts to see
other doctors and rheumatologists i'm
going to now
and we lose trust we lose trust in
everything we lose trust in our body we
lose trust in the people around us we
lose trust in
what's happening in our world we lose
trust
we thought we were safe and then we're
not safe
we get let down all the time
and then we get hit with anxiety and
depression and everybody's anxiety and
depression
is different
is different anxiety depression is
connected to the soul not just
physically
and everybody's physical reason for
anxiety depression is different than
another person too
it makes us all different
it does
but what isn't different is your heart
beats
and it has a function
and that's where we're the same on the
same as you you're the same as me
that's when it's not really
an individual thing where no no no no
your heart is different
our hearts are meant to beat and pump
blood they're meant to pull blood
up through the liver they're meant to
have blood travel through the body and
pump through the body
our hearts are spreading oxygen around
through our blood our hearts are working
the same they're supposed to work
they're same and then all of a sudden
someone's heart
goes awry and someone's heart goes amiss
and somebody's heart has a problem
but that's where we're different
because there's something that could be
different with that person that made
their heart not work right that's
different than another person where
their hearts doing something different
but what is the same is the heart
function we're supposed to function the
same way
you know how else we're the same
we're the same because of swallowing
we're supposed to be able to chew our
food and swallow right
well that's what we're supposed to do
our brain
sends a message
okay
our vagus nerves are getting messages
and then we're swallowing
right
but if something goes wrong inside the
brain
that's when it gets different that
person can't swallow because something's
wrong inside the brain
yet we're all the same with the
functions
we're supposed to have two legs
and then someone loses a leg
that's a dif that's what makes them
different but we're supposed to have
these bodily functions you're supposed
to be able to go to bathroom like
everybody else
okay
our stomach is supposed to hold food
every single person's stomach on the
planet is supposed to hold food
that's what makes us the same
right
that's what makes us the same our
stomach is supposed to hold food we eat
our food we're supposed to chew our food
but when something goes wrong
and neurologically we can't chew anymore
or
we have gastroparesis
because of a problem
and that's what makes us different right
but we're all supposed to function the
same your pancreas does the same thing
my pancreas does same thing you guys
your heart does the same thing my heart
does your liver does the same thing my
liver does
words we're lit our livers are doing the
same thing
unless something gets in your liver
and impedes it
if something impedes your liver
that's what changes that's what makes us
different
our physical functions are all supposed
to be the same your liver is not
supposed to do something different than
my liver no way
it's the suppo it's supposed to do the
same thing your kidneys are not
your kidneys are supposed to do
something entirely than my kidneys so
entirely different so all of our kidneys
are supposed to do something different
than everybody else's kidneys that's not
how it works your kidneys are supposed
to do the same thing
someone else's kidneys are supposed to
do and every other person on the planet
and the billions of people that are on
planet earth your kidneys are supposed
to function the same they have the same
role in the same job
there's no
individual there's no
bio
individual with that
but then
your colon is supposed to work the same
as my colon your colon is supposed to
work the same as somebody else's colon
they're supposed to work the same
they are
michelle l you're right except many
women are different that's so true
exactly
peristaltic action is supposed to happen
for everybody so all the billions of
people on planet earth peristaltic
action is supposed to be the same it's
supposed to work the same
okay
you eat your food your vagus nerves send
a message to your intestinal tract your
intestinal tract twists like this and
then your food starts moving along
because your intestinal tract is
twisting it's supposed to do the same
thing everybody else does everybody down
the street everybody down the block
everybody in another state everybody in
another country everybody on the planet
is supposed to have the same function
it's the vagus nerves receiving a
message boom via neurons neurons send
that message to your vagus nerves boom
vagus nerves go into your intestinal
tract and all around your colon and it
makes it go
right right
like the sound effects
that's what it's supposed to do for
everyone you're no different than that
person i'm no different than you i'm no
different than that other person see
it's all the same
right there unless
something goes wrong
unless now you got a bacteria like
streptococcus that's inflaming or eating
away at your intestinal lining or you've
got something that's eating away the e
coli that's eating away at your colon
lining and now you got diverticulosis
and now you've got inflammation now
you've got problems or if a virus eats
away at the lining of your in your colon
and now you've got colitis so it's a
shingles virus causing colitis that's
what starts making us different that's
what is making us different right there
your colon is supposed to work
exactly umakali
i see people saying that we're all
different but all of us have the same
anatomy and physiology what's different
is what we've been exposed to like
toxins and bugs
exactly 100
right that's exactly it
so what makes us different
is those things you know what else makes
this the same
blood
we all have blood in us
and when you take too much blood out
like
what they did to the lyme community
for 40 years
i can't tell you how many people who
died that didn't need to die from lyme
disease
because they were bled to death at their
doctor's offices let's take another 30
vials let's take another 20 miles let's
take another 40 vials i can't tell you
how many people lost their lives from
getting too much blood taken
cancer people who had a fighting chance
to recover from cancer had the blood
drained out of them so they had no more
immune system to fight the cancer and
then they died earlier
lyme disease multiple sclerosis als any
any kind of illness really
i've seen people with
chronic fatigue syndrome die because
they were bled to death
because we all have blood
and here's the difference about the
survival of somebody with lyme disease
or someone with chronic fatigue syndrome
me the difference is how much blood did
someone else get taken by their doctors
versus somebody else that got blood
taken one other doctor took only 12
vials from their patient every time they
came in which is still bad enough
another doctor took 30 vials
that patient eventually died
that made that situation different but
the blood
we all have
our souls are unique
that's for sure
no soul is the same
no soul is the same but physically our
bodies are supposed to function the same
the organs function the same your brain
is supposed to function the same
all these things
are supposed to function the same your
adrenals are supposed to do the same
thing someone else's adrenals do okay
you need adrenaline for every single
function in your life you need
adrenaline when you go to bathroom you
need adrenaline when you say hi to
somebody
do you know that your adrenals actually
do a little squirt when you meet
somebody
do you know that hey how are you hey
nice to meet you great to meet you hey
how you doing yeah hey great to meet you
your adrenals go bam
bam
just like that every single person who
comes across somebody else and says hi
to them or meets them in that instant
their adrenals go
and shoot out a little bit of adrenaline
it doesn't matter if you're nervous or
not when you're meeting that person
that's what happens
every single person that goes to their
doctor's appointment same thing their
adrenals go
from white coat
syndrome right there
right everybody you go to the dentist
office and they're about you know you go
in the dentist office and they're
looking in your mouth and everything
your adrenals are starting to go up a
little bit
you go take a shower your adrenals are
going you go to the bathroom it takes
adrenaline to go to the bathroom
everybody's adrenals do the same thing
they all do that they all release
adrenaline when we go through all these
different experiences right
it's how it works
now our souls have
experiences that come from before this
physical body by the way that we don't
tap into that we don't we don't connect
with
but our soul's got experiences from this
lifetime too makes us different
the soul that we that that we enter this
earth with
has
experiences which make it unique so our
souls are so unique they are
what makes them really unique it's
interesting because you can tell
somebody hey
if you want to heal this is what you
need to do but their soul might be like
i don't want to do that
i'm going to go do something else so
that's their soul is just that's the way
their soul is built
like souls also help us make decisions
they help us make bad decisions too in
the world too
souls do a lot our soul is different
everybody's soul is unique why would you
take a right when you could take a left
no you should have gone left
you know up the mountain instead of
right down the hill
or you should have done this you should
have did the soul just plays a role in
so many different decisions we make
we're so unique because of that our soul
picks our hobbies
what we like what we like to do the kind
of fun we like to have right some people
don't like to sit on the beach and other
people love the beach some people like
to be on boats some people hate to be on
boats that's the soul right there
that's the soul some people like to
watch a sunset people like to only watch
a sunrise some people like to watch both
right some people like to drive cars
some people like to be passengers in the
cars some people like to go out to see a
movie some people just want to watch
movies at home some people like to have
popcorn some people hate popcorn
whatever it is the soul does play a role
in so many different aspects of our life
but our physical body
our physical body
becomes really different when you get
pesticide
sprayed on you from your neighbor when
you're breathing in scented candles that
you don't realize are highly poisonous
when you're
getting
heavy metals from certain
pharmaceuticals and that's another thing
that makes her physical body different
pharmaceuticals that can make her
physical body different
someone can be on a lot of
antidepressants a lot of anti-anxiety
meds somebody can be on a lot of
different medications and it builds up
and it builds up a lot of painkillers
and it builds up and it builds up
sleeping pills and it builds up right
the whole bit and it builds up inside
their liver and it builds up inside
their organs and their kidneys and now
they have a problem but that's what
makes them different than somebody else
who wasn't on all those medications it
made them physically different that's
the whole point what does somebody have
what kind of bag of tricks bag of goods
do they have inside their body what's
sitting inside their liver what's
sitting inside the kidneys what's inside
their brain how many metals are inside
their brain
that determines too
on how somebody feels julia says i will
have to rewatch this video tomorrow
you guys were alive right now
so
wellness is important because your
depression can be different than
somebody else's depression you see how
it works your anxiety is different than
somebody else's anxiety
everybody has
a different situation of what's
happening inside of them both both
toxicity levels and both pathogenic
levels that are inside their body that
determines
which way things are gonna go
definitely which way things are gonna go
and all that is important to keep in
mind
so
one thing we have to always remember
though okay
it's your experience is different than
someone else's experience emotionally
if you've been let down if you've been
betrayed if you've had a hard time if
something happened in your life man
only you know
only you know what that's like
something terrible happened something
going on so you're under pressure
whatever it is something you were peer
pressured into doing maybe something
that's gone wrong in your life maybe
some hardships maybe some struggles
maybe some losses you lost some serious
things that mattered in your life
whatever that could be a loved one of
course which we don't ever want to lose
or a friend
or something that was important to
your existence
your resources whatever it is we lose it
plays a role in our soul and it shapes
our soul and it changes our soul right
there and no one can touch that man
that's so
unique to part of your soul your
experiences of what you've been through
the letdowns you've had the broken trust
any of that
the struggles emotional struggles
all that's tied into the soul so deep
and nobody could touch that nobody can
go near that because you know what
that's you that's yours that's your
individual experience is right there
that's what those are
and they're powerful
they're valuable too really valuable
life is short here on planet earth boom
short
that's right
you think 50 years 60 years 70 80 years
90 years
i think that's a long time
gone
that's it
real fast
life is real short
it really is i get it when you when
you're 20 years older you're 22 years
old you're 23 years old or something
like that you think man you think life
is forever you think you're gonna live
forever you think
life here
is like
you know you'll be here for a thousand
years
when you're 19 years old or 25 you're 28
years old you might think you're here
for a thousand years
until you reach 30 and you start going
30 what the heck is that 30 i'm now i'm
30.
and it starts to kind of almost shift a
little for a lot of people but not quite
yet
life goes by
really really quick
it's a blip of time
and our soul
is still
there
it doesn't die
we lose our physical bodies and that's
the same thing we all have in common
we're all the same
every last one of us is all the same
we breathe
we live and eventually we die
we leave
every last one of us you ever look back
at the old antique photos
go in a bookstore and you're looking
through books and you see some old book
and the book is all these people and
they're all sitting there by a farm and
they're all like this with some rakes
and shovels and they're just wearing
these strange clothes right
and it's black and white photos and it's
like 1919 they're all gone
they're all gone like that
we're all the same
all of us
every last one of us on this earth were
the same
every last one of us or sisters or
brothers were all the same big family
and we leave here and it goes quick
but what makes us different is our soul
and
physical experiences that change the way
your bodies function through this ride
right
thing is about
if you ever worry about leaving this
place down the road always remember your
soul lives on forever
your soul lives on forever and you're
aware
you're aware
your soul
has all the information
it's an embodiment all on its own
and it never dies
ever
anything you do good here
anything the smallest little thing the
smallest deed whatever it is
your soul gets to carry that with you
you tell somebody hey
try the celery juice
and they start getting their life back
boom that's like gets in your soul
you tell somebody
anything or you help them with anything
you help somebody across the street you
help somebody
go in front of you in a line
whatever it is you pick something off
the ground in the grocery store that
someone just dropped she's he's the
smallest things the smallest things
the tiniest things
save a moth a moth flew into the house
and you grab it
and you cup it like this and it's just a
moth for god's sakes and you take them
off and you let them moth out and you
watch that ball fly away and maybe that
moth only has a year or season in it
but you let it go when something happens
inside your soul and you take that with
you
that's what powers our soul that's what
powers our soul
when it comes down to our physical
problems though
and our physical
abilities and all that that change is
really fast you get some heavy metals in
the brain which i want to do a heavy
metal detox cleanse
challenge sometime i don't know when but
i want to focus on it because metals are
so critical
you get metals of the brain copper
aluminum mercury changes everything and
the next thing you know it got the brain
fog and the focus and concentration
problems depression anxiety meaning
mysterious depression anxiety you might
have anxiety because of what's happening
in the world the unjust
the unjust evils that are happening in
this world and that's a different kind
of anxiety or the unjust evils that are
causing depression right now
i've always said evils on this planet
there are evil evil demonic people on
this planet that have no respect for
human life i've always said that all
these years
and
when that interferes with any of our
lives on any scale whatsoever can create
some depression anxiety because it hits
the emotional centers of the brain and
then we get injured and i talked about
that and cleanse the heel a little bit
about that emotional injury in our brain
and how it works we get a little scar
tissue on the brain and that makes you
different right there if you're somebody
that experienced a hardship
and that emotional center of the brain
got whacked and hit hard then then that
right there determines hey you got that
injury that's specific to you and now
you have a depression that's different
than somebody else's depression no one's
depression is exactly the same metals
can be in a different part of the brain
than somebody else and an emotional
experience can be in a different part
the emotional centers of the brain than
somebody else
and everybody has a different
situation going on
what i noticed about some people out
there that want to destroy
the futures of people who need their
health back
what i notice is
some people will browse the brass
through medical medium information
and they'll pick and choose some things
out of medical medium they won't
understand the message from medical
medium information they don't understand
that i'm a messenger i'm nobody
i'm nobody
nobody that's what i am
people say oh medical medium i'm nothing
nothing i'm a messenger
i'll be here today gone tomorrow
down the road but what will be here will
be the information that i messaged out
from above
that information will be here
it'll be there to speak in a light in
hopes to save more lives
in hopes to save more lives
because i'm just a messenger in the
moment in this time in history so i can
deliver this information from above
i'm nothing special
for some reason
i was given the ability to hear
and
survive
that
torture of hearing a voice
and bringing information that's
different than any other information out
there in health
and
i think it angers a lot of people
because a lot of people see that medical
meme information is the only information
that's different
and all the other information in
alternative health
is the same
it parrots the same
it's like all the same stuff
then medical medium information is
different
because it's different
and it's healed so many people it's a
threat
it's a great threat to the industry
then the industry likes to
come up with all kinds of different
tactics
people need to understand that
as a messenger it's not about the
anthony williams show if it was going to
be the anthony williams show
then i would have just made it the
anthony williams show and did selfies 24
7 and
made it all about me and
hey look guys i'm down at the beach
right now and got my selfies out and a
whole bit and been about look it's the
anthony williams show and by the way
here's health too because i'm into
health
i'm a health obviously i'm into health
too and the anthony williams show
if it was going to be about the anthony
williams show i would have done a bunch
of different tv show series like i've
been asked to do and i'm like well you
know what yeah i want to get the
information out there but i don't want
to make it about the anthony williams
show because i'm a messenger
i'm not supposed to be a star of any
kind
i'm not supposed to be
anyone
i'm supposed to be nothing
but yet a voice for the chronically ill
a voice for spirit of compassion
so i can deliver the message out to
people so they
don't
end up
in a situation like so many people are
so
i was looking right
and
i saw
i'm on my phone right now okay you guys
so i'm on my phone right so i'm just
going to to uh
a review right
so here's a review just came out a
couple days ago
okay
the title of the review is that
everything in this book works when for
over a decade nothing else would so
this person says when over a decade
nothing else could
right this is an amazon review
so
the review is this thank god for the
information in this book it has
literally saved my life i had been to 21
doctors
21 doctors
i get it when you're 20 years old and
you just have a bellyache once in a
while a little bit uploading which is
still not good
maybe a tiny bit of acne
maybe a little bit of fatigue and you
run around to your functional medicine
doctors and the functional medicine
doctor says oh your gut dysbiosis is
happening and you need a little this and
try a little of that you think you got
it all down and then you go and you put
a post out
thinking that you have everything down
right
but when you're somebody that's been to
21 doctors and you're really sick and
you're really ill that's what medical
medium information has been for all
these years
so thank god for the information in this
book it has literally saved my life i
have been to 21 doctors prior to finding
the books written by anthony williams it
was his celery juice that first peaked
my curiosity so i went to
medicalmedium.com to research when
literally in the in the first two
paragraphs on his home page at the time
all the answers i had been looking for
fell into place and made perfect sense i
found that no wonder doctors couldn't
heal arthritis because there is no such
thing as autoimmune
my health problems were there because of
a virus not because my immune system was
attacking me and getting
into attacking me right
and the review goes on and on
but it's somebody who's been to 21
doctors
and the thing about medical medium
information i was always a messenger to
just make sure that hey
if you're in that position you got a
shot now you know here here it is so it
wasn't supposed to be the anthony
williams show
it was supposed to be
i'm a messenger i'm nobody
i just have to make sure people have an
opportunity get that information
bring it down
be able to voice it
and be able to back up the chronically
ill
and make sure that i'm a voice for the
chronically ill too
[Music]
the other day
someone brought up bio
individual okay
medical medium they said
does all these things wrong
and they said medical medium does all
these things wrong because their medical
medium information is different than any
other information in
the health field
yeah it's different it's geared to save
lives
it's there for when you see 21 doctors
and 25 doctors 21 doctors that's a small
amount of doctors
medical medium information has been here
for people who've seen 50 doctors
actually a hundred doctors
one person
said they went to 400 doctors in 20
years
before medical medium information
not only gave them a fighting chance but
reversed their problems
uma says i've seen people use mm info to
heal and then turn against mm and go
sell zeolite or alkaline water machines
absolutely in fact the sabotages
sabotage on the medical mean community
are people very angry
because
medical medium healed them and then they
wanted to sell their alkaline ionizer
water machine
medical medium doesn't support ionizer
water machines because
that will make you neurologically sick
the plates inside the machines
they start to decompose you don't see it
decomposing but they do they oxidize
and you get sick and twisted in the
brain from alkaline as your water water
my job is to protect the chronically ill
but what that did was create a bunch of
enemies so that the enemies that sell
the machines start getting people to
post
and then you see a bunch of people that
don't know any of this that go whoa i'm
not going to go near medical medium then
i won't look at his book i i'll go
somewhere else
that's a mark on your soul man
when you do evil things like that and
you turn people a direction that they
could have gotten help and you turn them
away from that
some evil intentions
that stays in the soul you do evil crap
that stays in your soul
for eternity
so
so what happens is it brings on a whole
bunch of hit jobs and hit post and stuff
like that right so let's just let's just
read one that came out pretty recently
this post is titled what does the
medical medium get wrong
we'd love to hear what medical medium
gets wrong this is interesting
right
okay let's just read one of these things
the body needs acidity too much
alkalinity can cause more infections low
hcl and poor mitochondrial health well
that doesn't really sum up too much
right there
so medical medium gets what wrong kind
of confused with just that one all on
its own
so this person is saying
the body needs acidity here's the
problem everybody's so darn acidic
they're losing their bodies
this person is an amateur i guess and
they just don't know this
we're so acidic we get osteopenia
osteoporosis spinal stenosis
we're so acidic that our brain bathes in
acid
and atrophies as the ears go on
we're so acidic that we burn out our hcl
our our own hydrochloric acid and
stomach glands we're so acidic
that we ruin
the other acidity
which is hcl
so this person says the body needs
acidity oh it does actually we're
desperate to get out of acidosis
for somebody to say this and say what
medical what the does the medical medium
get wrong so they're trying to correct
me with this one they're saying the body
needs acidity medical medium
too much alkalinity
do you know how hard it is to get
alkaline
you have to be eating leafy greens every
single day you've got to be doing your
celery juice you've got to be cautious
on you got to keep dairy out of your
diet right
you got you got to watch out for
chemical poisons and toxins it's not
easy to get alkaline but this person's
acting like
alkalinity is like easy to get to and
that we need to be acidic instead
if you take this person's advice it's a
nightmare how's anybody gonna heal let's
move on to another one
okay well this is a fun one right here
veganism has a time and place just like
all other therapeutic diets so what this
person is saying
is that i must be straight vegan and
only vegan and that's all i ever support
is vegan
let's just clear this up for a little
bit right now
do you know why the vegans don't like
medical medium out there the the staunch
veganism world
because i support animal protein eaters
did you know
that the plant-based movement and the
vegan movement despises anthony william
the medical medium because i will not
solely and solely only support vegans
i'm hated by the vegans yes i know so
many of you guys are vegan but the vegan
movement you guys know the vegan
movement hates medical medium because i
don't sit there and talk about all the
vegan talking points and the vegan
propaganda and i'm not just 100
i the medical medium platform or
community or the medical medium
information supports all walks of life
that eat all kinds of different ways
there are animal protein people here
there are plant-based people here
there's macrobiotic people here there's
vegetarians here there's people that eat
dirt there's people that eat animals
there's people that eat just blueberries
there's people from all walks of life
here
but this person puts out in their posts
to make sure they twist the minds of
others
that veganism has a time in place just
like all other therapeutic diets so
anthony williams
must have it wrong then because he must
be just a one size fits all just vegan
because that's what they're claiming so
let's move on to another one if you guys
got a second
this is kind of fun ready for this one
vinegar is not inherently bad
oh it's not
okay
if a person has a problem with vinegar
they may have low hcl oxalate issues etc
really to who's science what science can
prove that or even say that
someone's just throwing theories
that are in the alternative medicine
world
and they're just throwing it into the
bag here so what does the medical medium
get wrong apparently the medical medium
has it wrong the
vinegar is actually good for you
so let's cut into the vinegar a little
bit
yeah you're welcome to have vinegar and
i always said
if you're gonna have vinegar apple cider
vinegar is the best one there is i've
written it in my books that it's the
best one there is but if you're
chronically ill
and the needle's not moving you better
get rid of the vinegar because i want
you to have a fighting chance to heal
you can be welcome to be here in the
medical medium community you have all
the apple cider vinegar you want and i'm
gonna love you i'm i'm not gonna judge
you and i'm gonna be on your side and
i'm gonna say good job you're you at
least you're doing the apple cider
vinegar but listen if you got those
aches and pains fatigue and tingles and
numbness and your and you got the brain
pains and you got the brain fog and your
back hurts let's get rid of the vinegar
if your teeth are starting to crumble
and fall apart let's get rid of the
vinegar if your bones are starting to
thin out you're getting osteopenia let's
get rid of the vinegar because the
vinegar will literally destroy your
health
but by no means do i ever punish anybody
if they want to be in the community and
have vinegar tara appleman hey tara
i love when people use the phrase one
size fits all to describe medical medium
information mm info is the only thing i
found that is not one size fits all
tara
it's true
so
this person clearly who wrote this and
posted about this hasn't watched
instagram lives or facebook lives or
rumble lives hasn't read the medical
medium books but they did a hit job and
they haven't listened to the podcasts so
they did a hit job
and since i bring in the soul into this
stuff you know that just sits in your
soul you do a hit job on purpose when
you didn't do your homework or know
about the other person so you
intentionally did something evil and
then you got your crowd of whatever
followers behind it and they all think
it's real
that intention is dark
what would actually possess
a person a 20 year old or whoever that
does this what would possess them to do
dark malice intentions like that to
derail people of healing when they don't
even know the information or they ever
even read the books
and that stays in the soul forever
they may not think that because you
think you're indestructible when you're
20 years old and you think you got it
all down because your functional
medicine doctor taught you a few things
about gut biome which is really theory
gut microbiome and we can talk about
that all day on how that works because
if you're really ill those gut powders
don't do anything you have to learn how
to heal
mollyanne marsh says i'm glad you are
addressing this
i have to dispel the misinformation to
help people avoid the traps because
these are trapped set by people
let's go and do a couple more if you
guys got a minute
i really appreciate it
okay
you guys are gonna laugh at this one if
you're if you know medical medium
information you're gonna laugh at this
one catherine says and that crowd healed
with your info too and now they're
bashing it catherine i know because
people that were actually commenting in
that crowd healed from using medical
medium tools and they're sitting there
bashing it
we have bad things happening in the
world right now we have evil immense
evil destroying
people's lives right now out there
okay
immense evil an evil immense evil
machine
is trying to destroy
people's worlds and lives right now out
there
if you're up on everything that's
happening
right
but
on small levels
smaller levels
this is people who post this garbage
are trying to destroy people's worlds
too
when you think about that
or trying to destroy people's worlds
okay
so it's unbelievable
brianna says i seen this gal's post
post like this really does mess with my
head
like makes me think i will never heal
and doing things wrong
brian i'm so sorry i know
and that's the post we're probably
talking about for sure right now
so let's go into a little bit more
but before i go into these pieces i just
want to say there's an evil machine
trying to literally destroy
humankind right now we know about that
but this is on small levels that destroy
lives too
when you put stuff like this out there
when you don't even know what's in the
books or the podcasts or understand why
someone's even sick and you put a tax
like this out here and you alter
people's perceptions and send them down
a direction so they can't heal people
are going to be poisoned when they see
this they'll never think oh well maybe i
should look at a medical mean book
that's that's the number one new york
times bestseller that's healed people
around the world
maybe i should never look at that guy
maybe that guy is ugly maybe that guy
does look weird
you guys first of all i'm not young i'm
an older guy
second of all i don't have fake teeth i
don't have
implants in my my teeth and face i don't
have filler i don't have cosmetic botox
or whatever it is i don't do anything
like that
you know
all the guys in the health movement
right now
that are a half of my age are getting
all that stuff
and all the guys that are my age in the
health movement right now they don't
have any teeth
it's all implants
so
yeah and i'm not
yeah i'm a runner
i'm a bicycle
i ride a bicycle right
but i don't
do you know weights big weights because
i'm not trying to build mass if i wanted
to i could just spend two hours three
hours a day and do that but i have to
work
i have a job
all right so let's go in just a little
bit plus you won't get good bike rides
when you do that and you won't get good
runs you won't be able to run the miles
you want to run when you're too bulked
up
i know guys that are so bulked up
friends of mine are so bulked up they
could run a half mile
they can't run 10 miles real quick in
the morning and then get back to work
they can only run a half mile and then
they're dragging
all right
look that's off a beaten path so let's
oh let's talk about another one right
here right here's the one that's
interesting you guys check this one out
from the from this post from this person
he does not state that binders should be
used when ingestion when ingesting the
heavy metal detox smoothie so you're
going to tell me how my heavy metal
detox smoothie should work is that what
you're gonna do
is that this person is gonna do this
person's gonna give me direction on how
my heavy metal detox smoothie that saved
lives is gonna work
so oh
um let me just listen to you then
what am i doing wrong with my heavy
metal detox smoothie that's been saving
lives for decades
uh okay let's talk about you want me to
put binders in there
okay what are binders charcoal
clay
chlorella fulvic acid
you want me to put humic acid you want
me to put these binders in
um those are theories they don't grab
toxic heavy metals
there's not one study that shows
charcoal grabbing or binding onto a
toxic heavy metal
there's not one study that shows that
you need a binder
there's not one study of any of that
because first of all the heavy metal
world of toxic heavy metals causing
problems originates from 35 years of my
work of teaching people
and the heavy metal detox smoothie
that's saving lives
has
spirulina in there
barley grass juice powder in there
cilantro in there while blueberries
pecked in from wild blueberries
pectin's a binder
pectin's a binder it's got two cups of
wild blueberries in the heavy metal
detox smoothie
the point is is someone sitting here who
doesn't even know how metals work or
anything and they're telling me i don't
address binders
april 10. i got put on binders by my
health coach really didn't help me and
can i tell you april
binders
i've seen it hospitalize people
i've seen people use binders like
charcoal and clay and end up in the
hospital with crohn's and colitis serum
severely suffering and they had
literally lost two three months of their
life they were in the hospital because
the clay got into their intestinal tract
and colon and stuck into the walls and
they were in agony and needed to be put
on morphine
i don't use charcoal and clays for a
reason it can destroy people's lives i
don't like them i told people why many
times corella is also highly toxic and
carries bacteria 90 of the time and i've
seen kids that were on chlorella from
their practitioners literally in
hospital beds because i'm morphine
because the corella had bacteria and
almost killed them
it's in my books this stuff
so i have a person here that's so
experienced i'm not trying to be
sarcastic but so experienced apparently
it says he does not state that binders
should be used when ingesting the heavy
metal detox smoothie are on his detox
lenses
jamie says your heavy metal detox movie
helped me get rid of my panic disorder
yeah and if there were binders such as
charcoal in there your panic disorder
would have got worse because the
charcoal is so agitating to the central
nervous system into the vagus nerves but
this person would never know this but
this person's post garnered a lot of
attention
and there's so many people turned off
the medical medium information that
could save their lives
and i'm not thinking about my livelihood
because i tell everybody
get it at the library for free i don't
care if i can't turn the lights on
anymore
get it in the library for free
but here's what's funny the person that
put this post out and the first be other
people too they start investing in other
stuff you start becoming part of that
whole mlm pyramid stuff and
and
you know
whatever ambassador stuff and they got
their own plans
of why they're doing what they're doing
evil intentions
keeps a mark on your soul you do
something terrible for a reason it stays
in the soul whether you know it or not
and it lives there
and we have to contend with it someday
let's go a little bit more oh here's a
good one now let's go into this real
quick
all right
right
he states that blood draws
are blood or bloodletting
vampirism he states that blood draws are
blood letting and vampirism this is
dangerously false as blood work can give
us
essential information when did dr faun
good good to see you dr fun did i ever
said to people never to get blood work
did i ever dr font
md
did i ever in
all the decades of doing this and
anywhere else in my book should i ever
tell somebody never to get a blood test
to ever say that it's not helpful in any
way
what i've said is the same thing i've
always said
you get too much blood drawn when you're
pregnant you damage the baby when you
get too much blood drawn when you have
neurological lyme it can send you
backwards for months you get too much
blood drawn when you're chronically ill
and you can remove a part of your immune
system and not bounce back i said
there's a way to do it you have to learn
how to do it
you can ask your doctor for blood work
and learn how to protect yourself
medical medium information
is about protecting yourself
you can listen to the podcast the blood
draw podcast so you know how to protect
yourself
too much
amigo 500 says too much damages the
immune system
tear appleman says no complete
misunderstanding twisting your words
exactly
so important to know dr fond he said to
avoid taking too much
but this person has scared a lot of
people with this one because all of a
sudden i look like a guy
that never wants you to go to your
doctor and get blood work that's insane
definitely get your blood work
but i always recommend doing what i
recommend friends to do
is you ask for half files or quarter
miles
and you'd be cautious to how much is
being drawn when you're really
chronically ill because i don't want you
to have to go backwards and backwards
and backwards and then you think your
celery juice made you sick
michelle l details matter
so i'm gonna read a couple more if you
guys don't mind right here's one right
here
this is a good one
eggs are not the unhealthy
everyone
is bio-individual so eggs are not the
unhealthy
everyone is bio-individual
creating food fear is dangerous
okay
you know why everybody
who
has been there and done that out there
loves medical medium information because
it allowed them to eat fruit for the
first time in their
sick chronically ill lives
medical medium information opens the
floodgate to all the herbs it opens the
floodgate to all the leafy greens it
opens the floodgate to every vegetable
it opens the floodgate to all the fruit
it opens the floodgate if you want to
still eat animal protein okay it opens
the floodgate if you want to do even
some grains and oats medical medium
information is not about
food fear or fruit fear
it's about making sure that if you're
chronically ill that you stand a chance
you can actually heal and recover
and if you know what to avoid when
you're really sick yeah i got friends
that eat eggs
i don't say anything because they're not
sick
you're sick
you got a problem
you're going to get in trouble so i want
to talk about something you guys i want
to actually drop something on you guys
that's important right now a few of the
haters that were in the medical medium
community that got their lives back that
posted about how they got their lives
back for years
healed used all the medical meat
information drank their 32 ounces of
celery juice did their heavy metal detox
smoothies
avoided eggs and everything they got
their lives back and then they left the
community and they got mad at me
i don't know why
but they got mad at me and left the
community and then started up their
alkaline ionizer water machines oh
that's why i forget
they started their other stuff they
wanted to do and then as time went on
they started doing things like eggs and
things like that again and then they got
sick again
they got sick again
because
they healed because they avoided eggs
because they had a pathogen
and then they started tanking the eggs
like eating a lot of eggs
and then they started to digress in
their healing because they were making
themselves sick again and they started
developing symptoms a lot of people go
through that process but they never
correct anything they never say okay i'm
gonna do a post and say you guys i had
the best four years of my life i could
run five miles now i could run and jog
10 miles i can do all these things i'm
happy my kids are happy i'm better no
one has to worry about mommy dying
anymore being sick i got my life back
and then i diversed i tapped the guy i
ate all these bad foods that then i got
sick again but but here i'm gonna tell
you guys what happened he was right he
was right
and and and here all i have to do is
clean things up a little bit and get my
life back no one corrects anything no
one fixes anything
i don't know if it's pride or it's ego
samantha says they will twist and mold
all
what you said to suit their own agenda
absolutely
so here's another one right here
there is no scientific evidence for
cluster salts in celery juice however
ever celery juice can help some people
science hasn't studied celery juice yet
this person doesn't know this yet but
science has not studied celery juice yet
i have been waiting forever and when
they do study it they will find the
things in there and then they'll talk
about it just like harvard and other
places studied epstein-barr recently and
found out that medical media was right
that epstein-barr is the cause of
multiple sclerosis and now seven years
later
after i published it
they're doing
papers on there now right well the same
thing's gonna happen with celery juice
give it time and when you're 20 years
old or 22 years old or whatever you are
yeah seven years from now and 10 years
from now you'll see that celery juice
has special things in it and guess what
you'll never fix this you'll never say
you guys i did a post seven years ago on
my ig and i did that post and i i ripped
this guy apart and i made people not
drink celery juice anymore i made them
doubt celery juice but i'm not gonna fix
it you guys i'm not gonna go back and
fix it and tell everybody i was wrong
medical medium was right
and that this whole time science finally
did discover it because i had people say
bad things about medical media when i
said multiple cirrhosis multiple
sclerosis was caused by epstein barr and
people ripped me apart you guys
including people in the science
community they ripped medical medium
apart years ago because i stood up and
said epstein-barr causes ms but guess
what now that they discovered it is true
no one's coming back and correcting it
no one's putting articles out and saying
oh my god
we ripped apart aw seven years ago and
and we wrote these bad articles about
him and we said all these terrible
things but look he was right he he
actually does hear he is a prophet he
does hear from from spirit of compassion
and we're not gonna correct it we're not
gonna say he was right
that's how evil works
it's part of how evil works and
it's in your soul
the people who do this
they keep that in their soul that they
had intentions that are that dark what
does that say that says when you leave
this place no matter what happens you
take that with you and your soul just
floats around out of here as you leave
and it harbors all that ill intent and
all that corrosive attempt intent and
and
and all of it and malice and just
everything and it holds on to it and
that's what you have to have in the end
this for being like that's what these
people have
here's one right here
gut infections and pathogens can still
feed on fruits veggies starches etc
despite what he claims
no one knew a pathogen fed it's medical
medium information
she's actually taking medical medium
information
and throwing it back at me
i'm confused wait a minute
science of research didn't know that
pathogens ate anything
this is it doesn't exist
i've been talking about it for 35 years
the pathogens eat food but everybody
laughed at it
science doesn't believe that a virus
eats
but here this person throws medical
medium information published in medical
media books and and talked about in
lectures for years throws it back at me
and says gut infections and pathogens
can still feed on fruits veggies and
starches that's funny because pathogens
don't feed on anything says all the
science in the world including
alternative science
this person took
mm info that's unique and put it in here
as if it was known and threw it back at
me as if i don't do it
this can act this is actually like
twilight zone
let's take a look at another one a
strict vegan diet can cause blood sugar
imbalances and gut dysbiosis for certain
people
who said
and by the way it's damaging false
information this person's putting out
there
defamation
and damaging false in information by the
way
thank god
i'm not like somebody else some of these
other people did you know if you say one
little
bad word did you guys know this you say
one little bad word about doctor
and doctor
and doctor in a podcast and doctor
you guys know the doctors i don't have
to say their name you say one bad word
you're just somebody on a post that you
just don't all of a sudden like dr john
and you'd often don't like dr gunner
and you say one little thing in your
post
do you know how fried you would be
your whole account would probably come
down
but did you know that i i don't do that
i let people speak their stuff and say
their stuff and put it out there and
defame me and put all this
this wrong information
and i let them do that
because i believe in like freedom
i let them do that
but all the podcast doctors would come
down on this person tomorrow
and they'd be in some serious trouble
you'd see some pr marketing people you'd
see some publicist you see some people
coming down on these people and oh my
god would they get served a whole bunch
of stuff
so this person's take advantage of
taking advantage of medical medium
kindness
sick
here's something a strict vegan diet can
cause blood sugar imbalances and gut
dysbiosis for certain people strict
vegan diet
i sit here until i'm blue on the face
and tell people you can heal if you're
eating animal protein
you can heal when you're plant-based you
can heal if you're vegan
but you gotta look you gotta look out
for that nutritional yeast whatever you
are you gotta look out for that vinegar
and you gotta look out for that caffeine
because that could be the bridge that
stops you from healing the bridge that
breaks and stops you from healing
i told you the vegan people have hated
me for years yes there's vegans in the
medical meeting community just like
there's animal protein people in the
medical media community the vegan people
have hated me for years the vegan people
because they don't think i support
veganism and they hate me for it this
person's acting like i'm one of the
vegan like
parades out there
dysbiosis no one knows what's supposed
to be in the gut by the way
who who like no one has an exact um
there's no exact science to dysbiosis
so here's somebody that's just
throwing out whatever okay
here's one right here he states that
there should not be fruit fear yet
creates fear around
other food groups
where's my coffee
where's my espresso
where's my bars of chocolate
because i want to caffeine my baby
so my my baby has an addiction now to
caffeine it goes through shakes and
withdrawal inside my woman i don't even
know it i educate people
on how to protect so you can protect
your second baby and your third baby and
your fourth baby
so they don't become heroin addicts when
they're 15 years old and 18 years old
and they don't become junkies when
they're 21 years old and ruin your life
i educate people so i can protect moms
and babies and children i educate people
about food groups like caffeine
and other food groups
and so
anyway it goes on and on and on
and there's plenty to be had too
so
but i'm going to talk about this again i
think i'm going to go to ig
i'll go to ig i'm going to put tick-tock
back on too right
ignoring them is best
their time and andy says i i understand
that like honestly ignoring them is best
right
true
but when you watch a lot of people that
get hurt
and they
they'll never actually find their way
when they get really sick like
chronically ill because they'll always
be poisoned there'll be something inside
of them that says no i don't know where
i heard it
but i heard he just he's bad
and it's sad
i'm a fighter i'm a fighter for the
chronicle
not a fighter for myself
if i was a fighter for myself i would do
other things i guess
i'm a fighter for the chronicle
and that's what i do
and that's what gets me
helene says you don't create fear that's
nonsense you educate with the truth on
what is real food
and what is nutrition thank you for
being here helene
you guys we're gonna go i'm glad we
covered a lot of different topics we
talked about seoul a little bit we
talked about this fun stuff we talked
about all of it
um i'm gonna go on ig
we'll talk about this stuff there who
knows what's gonna happen all right