we're live right now you guys we're day
two
day two of the medical media morning
cleanse challenge i'm making some food
as you can see i got caught in the act
of looking for some knives right now
and we are ready so you guys i'm excited
about this because
we are doing it are you guys feeling it
yet morning crunch challenge or what
everybody have the book right here okay
the morning cleanse challenge is in here
all right this is day two of the morning
cleanse challenge i'm really excited
about this because we're working on
healing we're working on moving
ourselves forward incredible we're live
on tick tock live on telegram live on
rumble facebook youtube
and
we're gonna be talking about the lemon
water we're going to talk about what it
does inside of us we're going to talk
about celery juice a little bit we got a
potato skillet cookie now why would a
potato skillet be on the cleanse list
how's that possible
how are you going to cleanse with a
potato skillet as an option i'm making a
liver rescue smoothie too which is
another thing i'm doing as well
liver rescue right here if you guys
don't have liver rescue
you might want to consider it this is an
incredible book in your collection to
heal and to find answers and learn about
your liver this is an incredible book so
i'm doing liver rescue smoothie out of
liver rescue how awesome is that we're
doing the cleansing heal morning cleanse
challenge so there we go i'm excited i
got the pan on it's hot we got a lot to
talk about too because we're not messing
around at all today
so you guys
i'm guessing
that you haven't had
your fats in the morning right because
that's the medical meat morning cleanse
challenge you're not supposed to do your
fats in the morning
right
i'm
gathering you're you're not doing that
right i'm gathering you haven't had your
avocado toast until afternoon
i'm assuming
which could be dangerous because like we
all know right
we've heard that over and over again
what is it you can make an ass out of
you or ass out of me or assuming like
gets all messed up or something like
that all i can say is i'm assuming you
guys aren't doing all the cacao butter
and the avocado and the nut milk and nut
butters and the bacon and the ham and
the chicken in the morning a lot of
people eat chicken in the morning it's
the craziest thing i've ever seen but
they're eating chicken in the morning
don't do that this is the morning
cleanse challenge you're keeping the
fats away right
did i get that right about the assuming
thing how is it maybe you guys can let
me know with a comment so i have it
straight out what is it like if you
assume or something it makes an ass out
of you or something or makes an ass out
of me or something goes wrong i don't
know what it is but let's go i got so
many things
so many things to talk about this is
serious so what happens is that
everybody
showers right
does everybody shower
you guys wash your hair
guys so what i'm doing is i'm chopping
up some peppers right here get some bell
pepper ooh sizzling in the pan
nice see how i did that right there
so we're day two of the medical media
morning cleanse challenge
everybody showers right
everybody takes a bath
everybody washes their hair
you guys ever wash your face
wash your face right we do that okay
what about your clothes
you wash in your clothes
at all
wash your clothes
how about that
right do you guys wash your feet
you guys wash your underwear
at all or do you guys wear dirty
underwear you guys wear dirty underwear
for months and months and months
just curious i'm popping some peppers in
here got some bell peppers if you guys
want to check this out we're making the
potato skillet because it's an option
you can actually tank and still cleanse
how's that possible
i'm going to give you a reason a couple
reasons why you can still cleanse while
you tank down the food right
see you guys wash your hair you washed
your face you washed your underwear you
guys washed your feet
right guys wash your body
right take a bath
right
you guys brush your teeth
no one brushes their teeth
we're gonna make this potato skillet
here
you guys wash your clothes
or do you leave
your clothes really dirty
you guys ever wash your car
right some of you guys watch your cars
right
you ever wash your dog
a lot of people wash their dogs right
never assume
anything because you're making an ass
out of you and me pajama says
all right that's how it is cool cool i
gotta get that right you know if i'm
gonna say that somewhere i better be
saying it right
marianne says
i don't wear underwear
nothing wrong with that
dannon says left out loud i don't wear
underwear either nothing wrong with that
either
there isn't
so you guys we're day two of the medical
media morning cleanse challenge we got a
lot to cover if you guys on tick tock
want to hang around i'm gonna make sure
this is fun and informative educational
because guess what we need to heal
umakali's laughing right now lots of
smiley faces on there
you guys are just
you guys are here today we're having
some fun we're making potato skillet
what you see is bell peppers cooking in
the pan but how can you cleanse make
eating a potato skillet i'm going to
show you because there's a way to do it
all right
got an onion right here you guys i have
to be honest dr faun md
i gotta be honest okay
all right
i was really really excited about the
cleanse challenge okay really really
excited you guys don't know what the
cleanse challenge
is and you came on here and you're a
lookie-loo
you're a lucky little you're kind of
like scooting around social media who's
this guy right here
right you just
exited the twilight so
because the twilight zone health is what
everybody's in right
it's where nothing makes sense out there
it makes sense here
medical medium information makes sense
so you left the matrix
when you entered here
right
because this is about answers it's not
about guessing games it's not about
mysteries this is about knowing why
we're sick we're doing day two of the
medical medium
morning cleanse challenge
so i want to talk about this thing right
what's the first thing you think when
you see a homeless person
first thing i think is what what is
their health condition right
because i just feel awful
for them right
another thing i'll think is
right
is
there in some pretty dirty clothes
okay and
their clothes haven't been washed in a
very long time
god knows when they've had a bath
and you just feel bad for them right
and
the next thing is
you know
anybody's like oh well we don't have
that in common right we're always taking
care of ourselves we're always washing
our clothes we're taking showers we're
taking baths
we don't have that in common but we do
have something in common
outside of being a human because
homeless people they're humans too
obviously even though they're not
treated like that
what we have in common is
we can get dirty on the inside
all the trash gets built it built up on
the inside is what it does
you guys get what i'm saying right
i know people they're squeaky clean
squeaky clean so much it annoys me
because i go weeks without showering or
bathing when i'm finishing the book
deadline and i'm laying on my office
floor tongue hanging out of my mouth
after working 72 hours with three hours
of sleep trying to make the deadline
but
i've seen people out there
other than that i don't normally do that
right
i want some clean clothes right a little
bit but the point is
okay you guys what i got right steaming
up right now is
onions bell peppers
we're cooking this up we're gonna pop
some asparagus in there now too the
point is
this is really important what i have to
tell you
okay
i know people that are squeaky clean i
mean i'm talking
they're like scrubbed head down to their
toe
they shower twice a day
but their insides are disgusting
their insides are gnarly
the outside might be clean the inside
disgusted
i'm going to put some garlic in here
their liver is dirty their blood's dirty
their intestinal tracts disgusting and
gross
they're gnarly they got ammonia
coming all out of them
right
they're not clean internally they're
filled with everything under the sun
they get old adrenaline
seeping out of their pores
and that stuff just sits in there and
sits in there
and it builds up as the years go by
and we never cleanse it out we never
cleanse it out
how do you clean the blood nancy asks
medical media morning cleanse challenge
is one way to start cleaning the blood
and that's what we're doing right here
if you guys don't have what you need
first thing you need cleanse the heel
book
make sure you get the book it's on sale
51 off it costs more to print it's at
amazon.com us look forward to other
places like book depository or wherever
you are
okay get it free at the library free by
the way this morning cleanse challenge
cleanse is free you guys are gonna learn
a lot today i'm hoping this is gonna be
fun
how do you eat well with a low income
you have to eat
no matter what right
so potatoes potatoes
right so if i couldn't get any food see
this beautiful food right here so if i
couldn't afford a red bell pepper
if i couldn't afford some lemons
i couldn't afford some beautiful oranges
you see right here in the front
okay
i'd buy sacks of potatoes is what i
would do sacks of potatoes is what i
would do
let's get this cooking down a little bit
we're making the potato skillet this is
gonna be fun potatoes inexpensive
with calories
and you can
actually work on your healing process
eating potatoes
bananas are another one too
i tell a lot of people that don't have
any money go to the produce manager and
say are you guys actually going to be
tossing out all those bananas that no
one's buying a lot of produce managers
they'll go and they'll get some bananas
that they're going to toss out and they
literally will give you cases of free
bananas there's a lot of guys that will
do that out there look for a store where
they'll actually help you and give you
some free bananas how awesome is that
so what you're looking at right here as
i'm cooking is we're day two of the
medical media morning cleanse challenge
i'm making a dish that you can eat
on the morning cleanse challenge that
you can tank and actually get like feel
like you just had some hearty fuel which
is really awesome
okay really important now this recipe
is then cleanse the heel right here okay
we all can afford this or the basics at
least thank god goodman says goodman
girl says
incredible
incredible so we're here right now we're
live you guys just in case people think
it's actually recorded actually we're
live jan mcbride says but don't potatoes
have high glycemic index that can cause
alzheimer's
no but that's misinformation
from people in the health industry that
will cheat you jan out of healing so
someday you do get alzheimer's and
that's what that is that's
misinformation out there in the world
and it's really sad
it's sad what they do out there okay so
potatoes are a healing food and when
they rob people of that information it's
really sad because
how are they going to heal
what's incredible is alzheimer's is on
the rise and and it's rising fast right
and
potatoes not on the big list for people
to actually eat you know people with
alzheimer's don't eat potatoes
people dying of alzheimer's aren't on a
potato diet did you guys know that
people on alzheimer's
all right are on
butter they're on
cream
they're on oil
right
they're on chicken
they're on chicken soup
yeah people with alzheimer's dying are
on chicken soups you know that's like
one of the recommended things they could
be on as chicken soup imagine that
you're losing your mind
you're getting sicker by the month
and you're eating chicken soup
i know i know everybody swears by
chicken soup but i'm just trying to tell
you it doesn't fix alzheimer's
no one's on potatoes with alzheimer's no
one's on oranges with alzheimer's no
one's on papaya with alzheimer's i can
guarantee you that there isn't alzheimer
patients out there on papaya getting
their mind back there's not alzheimer
patients doing the medical media morning
cleanse usually they're not you know
unless they learned about it through a
family member family member takes the
medical mean warning cleanse to their
elder who has alzheimer's and that's a
different story but normally it just
doesn't work that way can potatoes cause
constipation
uh no they can't so what i'm doing is
i'm gonna get some potatoes out now that
are steamed they're gonna go in the
skillet
we're gonna get them going over here
we're just cooking this down a little
bit
what causes constipation is an inflamed
intestinal tract it's why we're even
doing this you should listen to the
potato podcast at medical medium podcast
at apple podcast so
an inflamed intestinal tract right here
okay
an inflamed intestinal tract
is why people have constipation so
that's important to know
so what you do is you have to realize if
you're inflamed
but first of all you're gonna have a
sluggish liver if you're inflamed all in
there and you have constipation that's
first first and foremost to understand
it's critical information right there
but if you have inflammation somewhere
inside your intestinal tract your small
intestinal tract your ilium if you have
if you have inflammation in your helium
down in here on the right hand side okay
where you're where your small intestinal
tract links into your
large large intestinal tract if you're
inflamed in here that's where the
constipation comes from
ninety percent of constipation cases are
because you're actually sick you've got
an inflammation going on here
so potato doesn't cause constipation
but other foods like dairy products and
butter and stuff like that will cause
and gluten too because it'll feed
whatever the inflammation is causing
this whatever the bugs are it's causing
that helium to be inflamed right there
i want to answer questions you guys i
want to be as helpful as i possibly can
so i'm excited about this
so we're in the morning cleanse
challenge so let's talk about it a
little bit did you guys do your lemon
water 16
to 32 ounces of lemon water okay
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water first
thing in the morning
as you wake up so you guys on tik tok
this is critical right here the
information is right here all right go
to the library get the book for free
or amazon.com us this book has saved
lives around the world and when you read
the book you'll be mind blown and if
you're not sick enough yet
if you haven't gotten sick enough yet
at least you know the book is here for
you for later on so if you're somebody
that's like oh what i'm doing is fine
whatever and what i'm doing is good
that's good fine but when you're ready
and if you get sick enough and you're in
that kind of condition down the road in
critical shape but for some reason
that's what medical medium books are for
before the people that are really sick
that's what they're famous for
they're these books
are famous and known for people who are
really sick because they didn't have any
answers or ways to get better and that's
that's what's happening with medical
medium information it's for the really
sick people this is the morning cleanse
challenge if you're not sick or sick
enough yet you still might want the book
because you're gonna be mind mind-blown
so get it when you can 51 off amazon.com
us or get it free at the library
personally
go to the library get it for free
tell people every day
it's okay it's okay with me because you
know what if it means you healing and
getting that information man am i on
board 100
so right now i got this skillet going
right here we're doing lemon water too
so i'm just mixing this up a little bit
this is cooking down nice we're about to
add the potatoes in a minute
16 to 32 ounces of lemon water right
here first thing in the morning flush
out the liver that's what you need to do
it's really critical squeeze that lemon
right here put a half a lemon in here if
you want the prevention realm says hey
good to see you by the way the ultimate
preventative care thank you incredible
all right
and tick tock somebody said they drink
their lemon water
too because their joints hurt or their
joints hurt and they should be drinking
lemon water that's what it is
so
lemon water make sure you're flushing
somebody on tick tock says when they
drink lemon water their joints hurt
right so i want you to be i want you to
be your own detective okay
so your joints have never hurt
you don't have a joint hurting problem
you've never been the doctor for your
joints you're not seeking help for your
joints you're not on medication for your
joints you're not on anything
so you're just going along everything's
perfect life is perfect everything's
fine you drink some lemon water and your
joints hurt
i want you to be your own detective
so nothing's wrong nothing ever happened
you don't have one achy joint your
joints don't crack when you wake up in
the morning and you get out of bed and
you're cracking along you have no joint
pain whatsoever you can do all the
squats you want and the jumping jacks
you want joints are fine
right and then you have a little bit of
wet lemon water here and my joints are
perfect they've never had a problem ever
in my life i i've never had a complaint
never even asked a practitioner about my
joints let me have a little bit of lemon
water here
ow oh my god my joints are hurting i
better make a comment right there my
joints are hurting i've never had a
joint problem in my life i've never even
told anybody i never even told my spouse
or my family member or my friends or my
loved ones i never told anybody my
doctor i had a joint problem whatsoever
not one joint issue and then i had a
little bit of lemon water
my joints are hurting again what the
heck's going on here i want you to be
your own detective
because you can you can you can figure
things out when you're when you're your
own detective and realize
lemon water's not making your joints
hurt
okay
inflamed
joints are from pathogens so that's
important to know 16 to 32 ounces listen
if your joints are hurting and you don't
have cleanse to heal
it's sad
see you can do two things
you can wait another 20 years
before you can get cleansed to heal
because the book will be around
it'll be around
you can wait another 30 years and get
the book then get the book 30 years from
now
how about that right give the book 30
years from now
you get the book five years from now
we can stay sick stay sick and just play
around play around we can get the book
six years from now let's do that let's
wait six years
all right let's go talking about lemon
water we got that going on we're day two
of the medical media morning cleanse
challenge we're having fun let's get
some potatoes in the skillet we're
pretty much we got these sauteed down
nice look at that
nice
nice get the lemon water out of the way
sandy chad hey sandy
love the book lost 10 pounds with the
advance so what sandy's talking about is
the advanced 3669 cleanse
incredible thanksgiving i'm really glad
you're doing it it's an amazing cleanse
in there we're doing the the morning
cleanse and we're in the morning quinn
challenge day two but sandy was doing
the 369 incredible lost 10 pounds of
that carry
so how cool i have lemon water every day
and i have ra
and my joints never hurt when i have
lemon water quite the contrary thank you
thank you anthony incredible carrie i'm
glad you're doing that
i love that i love that anne beyer
healed from fm
no more joint pain you healed your
fibromyalgia incredible proud of you
guys this isn't this is amazing right
just so you know when doctors know this
if you get one patient better in a year
your hero heralded as a god
medical medium books have gotten
millions of people better all around the
world
all
around the world i remember so many
doctors contacted me
wanting to talk to me and i'm like
what's your what's your heel rate
what's your heel right what's your heel
rate and they would be like
well last year we saw about so many
hundreds of patients
and we got two people better at least
partly better and i'm like oh my god you
got to do better than that
you need everybody responding and
healing you need everybody moving
forward that's what you need so why
don't you start doing this get them on
the lemon water get them on the celery
juice which we're doing next get them on
the right things
learn the protocols here you go and i
would teach doctors and all of a sudden
they'd be like
medical medium
we have five patients already recovering
in just one week
we've never seen that before we're
actually we're actually competing with
other practices with other medical
practices out there they've never seen
that before too everybody wants to know
what we're doing
we got 10 more patients better 15 more
patients better and that's what it was
like
check out the book when you get a chance
so we're day two so what you're gonna
find what you're gonna find is in this
skillet i'm making potato skillet right
here and here's the potatoes they're
steamed already
what you're gonna find is there's no oil
in here
you can still cleanse if you ate this
before noon
okay this is one recipe you can do but
you can still cleanse
if you ate this before noon
lavon ward says lemon water first and
then celery juice yes and we're going to
do some celery juice in a little bit
it's just that i'm trying to make a dish
too so i'm chopping up some potato right
here and it's going in this skillet
don't add oil
whatever you do
don't add vinegar
no nutritional yeast
not going to cleanse if you're putting
vinegar in there i can tell you that
right now okay
so we're going to get another steamed
potato and cut these up
so we're dicing these potatoes up okay
you don't need to cook with oil i know a
lot of you guys think you have to cook
with oil you've just been trained to
cook with oil you don't need to there's
no oil in here you can cleanse and still
eat this dish
if you guys just got on here we're about
to make the liver rescue smoothie we're
finishing a dish right now which is the
which is the potato skillet we're about
to make a little celery juice too so we
got a lot of great stuff we're doing
okay
i'm going to throw another potato in
this
skillet
now with lemon water you can't have the
lemon water hot you can't put lemon in
hot water i need you guys to know that
this is really important to understand
critical tip right there
okay
you can't do
you can't do the hot water lemon thing
and cleanse so when you wake up first
thing thing in the morning and you have
your 16 to 32 ounces of of lemon water
to flush your liver and flush your body
right
when you're flushing that liver first
thing in the morning okay
you can't put your lemon juice
in
hot water so you can't put your
living
okay
living hydrating
calcium rich trace mineral rich
phytochemical compound rich
juice lemon juice in hot water or you
kill
you kill what's in here
and then it won't flush now you can have
tea if you want you want herbal tea and
put lemon in there that's perfectly fine
but it's not going to be a flushing
agent it's just going to be something
else which is what you can do that's a
different story
someone asked on tick tock why no no why
no nutritional yeast
nutritional yeast
is toxic yeast is toxic
so we're not supposed to be consuming or
eating yeast okay
so yeast contains msg right
don't get confused you're going to think
well no that's not true because i keep
on looking up on google
on google right
i'm on google here
nutritional yeast is really good for us
it offers so many fortified vitamins and
nutrients
and it's great for your kids too look
here's a mom
putting nutritional yeast
on her children's food making a nice
recipe of nutritional yeast
and she's a very healthy looking mom
and she's all happy and the kids are
eating their treats and it's all great
they got nutritional yeast in there what
people don't realize
is
it damages the brain over time it
weakens the brain
nutritional yeast has glutamic acid
naturally occurring but it's a bad bad
glutamic acid it's an irritant on the
central nervous system so if you've got
chronic illness nutritional yeast will
send you downhill
it will stop you from healing
so that's just one thing about
nutritional yeast if it's a nutritional
yeast day i would talk about it all day
long but we got to move on you guys i'm
excited we're day two medical medium
morning crunch challenge
so let's make some celery juice
this potato skillet is cooking up nice i
got potatoes in here
and
i got red bell pepper
yellow or orange bell pepper i got the
yellow bell pepper i got asparagus in
here i'm gonna pop some spices in real
quick i got garlic in there too which is
great i'm gonna put a little bit of
cumin in here if you guys don't mind
right
a little bit of a bit of
paprika
get that in there some chili powder too
which i like in the skillet
you're gonna do spices i'm gonna do red
pepper flakes in here as well
so
i don't know if you guys like spices
but i'll put a few in here some red bell
peppers
got that
what you're gonna notice about this dish
is there's no oil in here there's no fat
in here there's no bacon in here there's
no ham in here right
this is a fat free
skillet so you can cleanse
katie perez says hypothyroid gone
incredible healing up the thyroid that's
on facebook amazing
so i'm letting this toast up let's juice
a little bit of celery over here if we
got some room
so
how many of you guys are juicing celery
did you guys have your celery today
celery juice now remember eating celery
is fine but it's not going to do what
this can do this is an entirely
different situation
when you're juicing it
you're cleansing you're healing you're
restoring
celery moves the needle important to
know
it moves the needle
critical information right there
so the first thing you do is your lemon
water 16 to 32 ounces second thing you
do 15 to 30 minutes afterwards is you do
your celery juice
even if
you're only gonna do
four ounces of celery juice
six ounces of celery eight ounces of
sugar juice right
you guys can i ask you a favor can you
hit the thumbs up
can you share the live
spread the word get people healthy
so i'm running some celery through the
juicer as we speak
you can do sweet potatoes ivana says
sweet potatoes you can do sweet potatoes
in the skillet
you can do we're doing a lot of things
right now you can do sweet potatoes in
the skillet
you can do winter squash in the skillet
this is a plain potato skillet right
here
i got spirit talking to me
i'm reading comments
i got a potato skillet cooking i'm
juicing celery
answering questions i'll post the recipe
today on ig on facebook after the live
the skillet recipe
celery juice is a critical part of
healing moving the needle
and
people doing everything under the sun
and then they just take some celery
juice and boom that starts happening
did you put water in the skillet didn't
have to i had the pan hot good question
i had the pan hot right
didn't even add water you know why what
i did was i put the onions and the bell
peppers in first
and i let them cook down
47 anderson says i just ordered an omega
mm-900 hds and received it two days
later super fast incredible incredible
by the way
i'm only going to tell you guys this
once
and once only okay
the mm-900 hds this is the last day it's
on sale i'm not going to say another
peep i'm not going to say another word
and after tomorrow or when tomorrow
comes and everybody's screaming saying
what celery juicer do you use when's the
next sale i need a juicer i'm i'm not
gonna get emotional or react i'm not
gonna scream out of the window of the
car
i'm not gonna feel bad for anybody
i made that decision where
i already feel bad for everybody
suffering from chronic illness but if
you miss the sale
i don't know what to do anymore i don't
everybody gets upset when i talk about
it and then when i don't talk about it
everybody's upset i can't
win
so we got we're juicing right now
jessica says you're amazing thank you
for all this love my omega juicer
so
as you can see i didn't use a container
for my pulp
you see my pulp hanging out
claudia says the only man i know that
can multitask
i'm honored
you know what i always say i'm a fly on
the wall
or yeah i pretend to be the fly on the
wall
but what i'm on here you guys are on
there spirit of compassion
tells me all kinds of stuff spirit of
compassion told me somebody had a hot
chocolate this morning
and you know what i'm not gonna pick on
the person
but out of all things to have this
morning on medical media morning clench
challenge day two they had a hot
chocolate
i don't care
but you know what
it's okay
all right so
i know i'm not supposed to spy on anyone
using spirit compassion but i'm just
saying that that's what's very fast is
that brits it's very compassion said
someone had a very large hot chocolate
not even a small one
heather lee says what's the name of that
juicer lincoln profile link is in um
in the description heather and and
you'll see the discount when you check
out 72 off the mm-900 hds this is the
last sale day
all right we got enough celery juice
that's for sure it's the omega mm-900
hds it saves you money and i'll show you
why real quick you guys i know you've
seen this 100 times right
the pulp that just came out
is dryer
and so what that means is you just saved
money right there okay
i'm going to shut this off right here
got a multitask
you just saved money so that's dry pulp
right it's much drier so that's the
mm-900 other juicers that are there's
juicers now breaking into the medical
medium community because that's what
happens everybody gets mad about they're
like okay let's get into the medical
media community and sell our and
stuff and we'll pawn it off on everybody
and distract them well those juicers
that are trying to break into the
medical meme community don't do dry pulp
they're just a ripoff
letting you know so
the mm900
all right we got the celery juice
let's do this
what else is spirit of compassion saying
we're trying to have a little fun today
too right
he said someone had eggs this morning
who's doing the medical media morning
cleanse challenge
they were told by their doctor that they
need eggs every day so what they did was
they had their lemon water they had
their eggs
and i feel bad for them because they're
not cleansing
mel every morning i don't need a
weighted blanket anymore
ears are less sensitive skin cleared up
no yeast issues it saved me
mel
i'm at your service bless your heart god
bless you i'm so glad you're feeling
better
so glad you're feeling better
lavon says really
no need to cook with oil you are helping
us tremendously
you're on youtube right
you don't have to cook with oil
you don't you can cook with water i
didn't even use water in this one
i didn't i chopped up some peppers i
chopped up some some onion i put it in
here you guys are sauteed it down the
moisture from that came up i threw my
steamed potatoes in here still
sorry skillets done
getting ahead of myself
all right we got it let's put let's
plate this up it's gorgeous
we also have this we also have to
get the celery juice strained so i want
to show you guys that too so this is the
skillet right here we're going to put a
little bit of cilantro on top
this is just beautiful okay can you
imagine you can still cleanse
if you ate
this before noon
you can still cleanse
how is that possible well one reason is
you had your lemon water
you had your celery juice
you're not eating pork
you're not eating oil
you're not eating eggs
you're not eating cheese
you're not having butter
you're not having avocado
i know that's a healthy fat i get it i
know but you put your but it's still a
fat and it stops you from cleansing
you're not having avocado you're not
having nut butters right
you're having a fat free meal and guess
what for everybody worried about insulin
resistance
there's no fat in this meal to create
insulin resistance
you can eat potato oil free and get rid
of diabetes
people don't realize this so if you guys
just came on we're gonna actually make a
liver rescue smoothie we're gonna strain
some celery juice right here we're gonna
do this so i just want to plate this if
you guys are okay with that
i'm gonna plate this skillet up right
here
there we go
let's put some cilantro on top
we're having fun
we're having fun so what i'm going to do
is move this over for a second here
let's get some cilantro chopped up
i like putting fresh cilantro on top of
a skillet
it's a great thing to have
all right put a little bit on top of
this dish
there we go
you don't need a lot if you don't want
it
you can have this
even afternoon that's okay you can have
it before noon because it's fat free
there's no fat in that so that's that's
important to know so you can clean you
could cleanse okay that's incredible
about it
okay there you go
i just want to show you guys a close-up
right now
so this is the
the recipe you'll find this recipe right
here
you'll see the recipe
it's in book one i stand corrected
i told you guys it was in cleanse the
heel it's in medical medium book one and
that's the skillet recipe right there
it's incredible
all right
so this is just one option
you guys
one option to still cleanse and have an
incredible dish
in the morning
let's get some lime on it
you can squeeze a little bit of lime on
there
right
squeeze a little bit of lime get it to
taste so good
right
and then we're gonna put a little lime
on the side too there you go
that's it right there
you're watching it right now and you can
still cleanse
how crazy is that
exactly
joy clark says
it's heartbreaking that i have trust
issues with my doctors
my nutritionists why are they not
helping us they say insulin is from
carbs to sugar anything you put in your
body spikes insulin please help me have
faith
so joey clark this is how it works it's
not sugar that gives somebody insulin
resistance it's fat so it's fat in their
bloodstream so what they don't realize
it and this is why diabetics stay sick
and stay sick and stay sick you can get
rid of type 2 diabetes that's the
easiest thing you can do it's it's if
someone came to me
right
and they were like i got this type 2
diabetes what do i do it's like
you can say the magic word and it's gone
you just have to do a few things you
have to keep the fats out of the diet
for a little bit you have to bring in
other foods i talk about this in the
medical medium books right and you can
get rid of diabetes i mean it's really
easy to get rid of type 2 diabetes
that's just boom gone
important to know i mean
they don't have it right it's why
everybody stays sick
sugar's what is what your brain
has to thrive and live on you know a
diabetic that falls into a diabetic you
know pass out
a diabetic diabetic pass out on you know
a football field or
or on a baseball diamond or in a bus or
just in a hallway somewhere in a school
the only way to revive them is to put a
little orange juice in their mouth
because their brain has to get a little
bit of sugar
so you have to know that they have it
wrong about diabetes
and
cleansing is just you know it's a part
of it is you you have to cleanse out all
the bad stuff you have to give your
liver a break your pancreas a break and
that's what the morning cleanse
challenge does so it takes somebody to
that place of healing so that's the dish
right there let's keep on moving i mean
there's a lot of information i can drop
on diabetes but we we don't have the
time get the books so that you have that
information so you can learn how to heal
completely with that
so we're doing a liver rescue smoothie
but i want to actually just strain this
really quick
so this is the celery juice we just used
if you guys
just if you guys throw everything out
everything you're learning here
and you just do your celery juice
the needle moves
just that alone right
if you throw everything out here and you
just do the liver rescue smoothie i'm
gonna make you
you'll move the needle
if you throw everything out here and
just do the lemon water every single
morning you'll move the needle in some
way somehow medical medium tools are
powerful and when they're all combined
they take somebody all the way to the
finish line the chronically ill that's
the whole point there's a question
about kitchen tools so go to
medicalmedium.com you'll see a directory
kitchen kitchen directory okay and a
supplement directory and other things so
you know the different stuff
that that uh medical medium recommends
all right so let's strain the celery
juice and let's keep things rolling
along you guys good to see you guys on
board this is day two the medical
meeting plans challenge and guess what
it's free
did you guys all spend five thousand
dollars did you did you use your credit
card to spend five thousand dollars for
this cleanse
no
you guys it's free
we're here let's do it together
right get the get the books at the
library
i'll say it a thousand times
because you know what happens is new
people come on and like uh he's just
selling a book i'll be like dude get it
at the library get it for free
michelle says you have an amazing vibe
thank you
that makes me laugh
because so many people also say he's
doesn't
thank you on facebook i really
appreciate it some people like me some
people don't but here's the thing
whether anybody likes me or not or they
like my face or they like the way i look
or don't or they think i'm ugly or they
think i'm okay or whatever they think
or they don't like my voice or whatever
it is the information's here for you
guys to heal or day two of the medical
mean morning cleanse challenge what you
just witnessed is i strained the celery
juice right
so that's important to know i strained
it it's herbal medicine the celery
juicer you just saw is an herbal
medicine machine so that's a medicine
machine that's a medical device right
there
important to know you made celery juice
celery juice is different than green
juice
it changes everything so let's make a
liver recipe smoothie that's next
all right
okay you guys
liver rescue smoothie
liver rescue smoothie is an incredible
medical medium tool i'm using it today
in day two
right
the morning cleanse challenge
you can do the morning cleanse challenge
and not have a liver rescue smoothie
you don't have to have a heavy metal
detox movie either
you can do the morning cleanse challenge
with literally a potato dish
you can do it
you can do it which is lemon water
celery juice and a piece of fruit
like a papaya i might cut open right now
if i get a chance
so that's what you can do you can just
do some fruit fruits healing too it's
mostly healing look
the most powerful way to do a medical
medium morning cleanse
no matter what would be like your lemon
water your celery juice your heavy metal
detox smoothie or a liver rescue
smoothie and then some fruit before noon
right
and
and so that's the most healing way to do
it here's the liver rescue book we're
making a live rescue smoothie just so
you know incredible book it's on sale at
amazon.com too all right get it free at
the library as well
i want people to know where it comes
from the information so you have it so
i'm going to put pattaya in here
dragon fruit you guys see
tick tock do you guys see the dragon
fruit telegram you guys see the dragon
fruit good to see you guys on telegram
i'm honored you guys are here
everybody see it rumble facebook youtube
right so pattaya let's get it in here
okay liver rescue smoothie we're
starting
we got it in here fantastic all right
next we're going to do a cup of wild
blueberries you guys see these
right wow blueberries here we are
so we're making the liver rescue
smoothie we need the wild blueberries
going in here
by the way you guys i have to tell you
i'm honored you're all here truly in my
kitchen
delia says i love you think you work
really hard to help people with your
knowledge and empathy i'm honored truly
i am i am so i got two things in here so
far that's on youtube thank you for
being here truly
it means it means so much to me it
really does i'm going to put a banana in
here
more than you guys know
pop a banana in here
in the liver rescue
smoothie you can put two bananas in your
liver rescue smoothie you could put one
in there you can put two in there i'm
gonna put two in here
all right
so then i'm going to blend this up
there we go
[Music]
goes on here
let's give it a blend
all right
[Music]
rescue smoothie coming up
one
wish shot of whiskey
glass of gin
coming up just kidding
i do not drink
and i do not support
alcohol
see you guys
soupy girl asked a question on rumble
can the skillet be prepped for the week
absolutely
nothing wrong with that at all
[Music]
level rescue smoothie right here isn't
that funny whiskey that's the last thing
your liver needs right this is the liver
rescue smoothie the liver rescue
smoothie has whiskey in it and gin in it
and it has a rum in it
no it doesn't
it doesn't have those in it
okay please know that so we have
a little rescue smoothie right here
it has pattaya in it wild blueberry in
there frozen wild blueberry it has
banana in there
it's an incredible incredible smoothie
yeah a vodka yeah
listen you don't have to have the liver
rescue smoothie
you can have just papaya so let's get a
papaya out next okay you guys
this is a papaya mara doll papaya you
guys can find any papaya you you like
that you can find all right so i'm
cutting off the end right here
ria lindard says question
since i travel a lot for work is it okay
to freeze celery juice in and take it
with me during my trip and drink it
later yes it is it's not the best but it
is on facebook you can do that yep
so i'm cutting off the cap right here as
you guys can see if you guys just do
fruit you don't like papaya spirit of
compassion just told me two or three
people said they hated papaya
i don't know how you know what it's kind
of funny i'm so used to this kind of
thing that it doesn't like to it doesn't
wear me out it doesn't three three like
very picky nice hairs are like which is
fine don't worry we're like i hate
papaya well i hate papaya try it though
if you really want to try to have it
listen you don't like papaya
let's go with an orange
let's eat an orange you don't like
papaya that's fine you don't like an
orange
let's have banana right there
right there what's that banana kendall
says aw gets tanked on the weekend while
driving his car off a cliff yelling the
juicer is on sale
you're almost 100 right
you're about 98 right on that that two
percent you miss
is i get stoned too with the alcohol so
i'll get tanked with the alcohol and
then smoke a dupi then go over the clip
i'm lying
and i'm making i'm kidding because you
guys know i don't smoke weed i don't
touch the stuff i never touch this stuff
never did this stuff
and i'm not making fun of anybody who
does it i'm not
yeah man this is a really good papaya
right here
hey did you know that
did you know that the aurora borealis
is really just kind of like a it's like
a
transport
where aliens actually they come in
through the aurora borealis
did you know that someone on google even
said something about that
you want the link
no alcohol i don't do it i just go on
celery force
that's what i do
spirit of compassion just told me
there's there's some stoners that
actually
don't
they said i just did the
stereotypical thing and that a lot of
weed smokers they're they're on right
where they don't act like that right at
least they don't think they act like
that
at least they don't think they act like
that yeah i got your number
okay
papaya right here i like to scoop the
seeds out you hate the seeds but they're
really spicy amberson says i want the
length
there's no length there's no length
so that's papaya you can have papaya in
the morning too so that's something you
can do as well okay
um kelly says aw can explain
what does the body mean i think it went
up there so quick wait what do you say
okay
anyway i don't know why the comments
have to cruise so fast but they do try
to catch them where i can
boom
that's your papaya scoop it out you can
do this you ready
you can scoop it out this way right
[Music]
take your spoon
scoop it out just like this
right here
the juice is going everywhere
okay
take a knife
if you want
and do this with the knife right
see
right
run the knife like this do not have your
hand like this and do the knife like
this i always do it that way but do not
do not do that the knife will go through
and hits your hand
just like that it actually hit my hand
but it didn't cut me so you see how that
works right there take the spoon and you
can scoop out and it just comes out
it comes out like cubed into a bowl
really nice right there
love it love it
why is your papaya green
okay good question
that papaya is ripe
somebody else's green papaya might be
hard as a rock
and not ripe
the kind of papayas i've been getting
lately they ripen inside even when
they're green with slight yellow on them
but see you have to know about papayas
because you can let it ripen more but
these were ripe but that's just the kind
of papaya it is so
here's what i'll do
let's put it in a bowl
right here
here's a fruit bowl you can make out of
papaya do it with other things if you
want to so what i'm doing is i'm getting
these little squares in here like this
right
see i'm scooping these out you guys
all right there you go
and you can you can scoop this right
down to the rind with a ripe papaya just
so you know
right down to the rind i mean look i
could even do better than that but i'm
kind of just trying to get a lot of
things done we still got to talk a
little bit about what the cleanse does
for you
and okay
we got some nice papaya in that bowl
right there scooping it right down to
the rind and you can even do even better
than what i just did that was kind of a
quickie right there it wasn't really you
know and here's another half i mean you
can go to town with that right now
now we got a banana let's chop up a
banana right here
make sure you have the book so questions
can be answered because i can't answer
every question in a one hour live i just
can't right
there's the end of the banana i just put
it in my mouth
right
there you go oh my gosh that makes sense
i struggle timing cutting them open oh
totally helena
my god it's the one thing
what you have is papaya and banana bowl
right there
if you do
your lemon water
your celery juice
papaya banana just like this before noon
like
yeah like really
or if you do your lemon water your
celery juice
and your liver rescue smoothie right
wherever that went
whoa
okay
you do your heavy metal detox smoothie
whoa
every morning whoa if you're sensitive
to celery juice just do a little bit
amount two ounces four ounces start
where you want that's okay you can start
where you want you would do what you
want to do right there remember
because i could sit here party with you
guys
all day long it won't even cover
an inch
of this book
just know that it's a medical textbook
with answers
but you know to get the book now and get
it 10 years from now
after you saw 100 doctors
get it 10 years from now that's fine
just know what's here for you okay know
what's here for you
amazon.com us right now
51 off or go to library and get it for
free
and
last chance for the juicer sale today
that's it right there for the celery
juicer model
and
we're going to talk about what the
cleanse does for you for a moment here
everybody's walking around and their
adrenals are getting toasted
stress
toxins everything else under the sun
you're bringing your adrenals back when
you do the medical media morning cleanse
you're bringing your adrenals back
critical right there
everybody's running to the doctor and
they're getting their blood sucked out
of them
every day
well let's just take another 20 vials
out of this patient oh you've got
symptoms of all kinds of strange
symptoms you got fatigue let's take
another 12 vials out of you hey let's
get another seven vials out of you let's
bleed you to death so you don't have a
chance to heal
learn about
you know blood draw medical being
podcasted apple podcast right the blood
draw episode
but it could save your life so you might
want to check it out it could save your
life
i can't tell you how many people
neurological line died
because they just bled them to death i
can't tell you how many people with
cancer died really early or died
instead of healed because they've led
them to death i can't tell you how many
people
um just suffered with fibro for the rest
of their life because they were bled to
death
another another appointment get more
blood get more blood get more blood and
your life force gets sucked out of you
all your white blood cells get sucked
out of you bex phillips i have dirty
blood that's what the doc said
it's medical medium information bex
so the doc obviously secretly follows
medical medium because it was published
first for medical medium talked about
first for medical media and prime
example of how this information gets out
there
and i'm glad it did
but i'm
unhappy if the doctor didn't tell you
where it came from or maybe the doctor
did that's why you're here but either
way thank you for being here
the bottom line you guys is there's ways
to help and this is a way to help that's
all the medical media morning cleanse it
helps to bring you back if you're
somebody getting a lot of blood work
if you're somebody
that's struggling with a lot of problems
if you're somebody that's having bone
problems you're losing your skeleton
you're losing your bones you're losing
your skeletal system
renato banana says the amount of times
they drew blood from my mom within the
six months she underwent cancer
treatments was absolutely insane
they do it
not the doctor doesn't do it on purpose
i think the system is rigged to do it
purposely that's what i believe
but that's my opinion
you know everybody has their own opinion
i'm pretty sure they're trying to kill
people with the blood with the broken
blood system that they have check out
the podcast you can get half miles
quarter vials just got to ask for it's
happening now because medical medium
people are losing their bones they're
weakening they're thinning they need the
morning cleanse
important to know right there
every single day we're so acidic we're
pissing out a piece of ourselves we're
pissing out our skull
we're pissing out of our skull
what that means is when you go to
bathroom in the morning when you're
urinating
tiny tiny
bits of your skull go out at the same
time because we're so acidic our skull
dissolves so when you're 65 and you get
into a car accident you got a fractured
skull when you wouldn't have had a
fractured skull when you were 45 under
the same car accident
are you guys
did i torture you guys enough
i am at your service i swear
i'm at your service
okay i'm at your service
i am
i love you guys very much we're going to
ig in a little bit just give us a little
bit of time to
clean up this mess we're on day two of
the medical media morning cleanse
challenge
so proud of you guys i know you guys are
working hard
get the book if you don't have it
anyway
have the information
and don't do your avocado toast
until after 12 o'clock if that's what
you do
all right
if you're somebody that eats all kinds
of fat which everybody does every day
their diets are just loaded with fat do
it after 12 do it after 12
stay on the morning cleanse challenge
okay so
this is the advice
from spirit of compassion it's obviously
not mine how else would i come up with
new material that no one's ever heard
before on the planet over and over again
for 35 years completely
redefining the health system the the
alternative health system as it is how's
that possible it's from spirit of
compassion
and it's not because i'm a smart guy
because i'm not a smart guy
i'm just a messenger
i love you guys and i'll see you soon
and you guys on tick tock i'm turning
you guys back on you guys on telegram
i'm turning you guys back on in just a
little bit and then i'm gonna turn ig
back on and we're gonna try to have some
fun
love you guys