facebook youtube uh
tick tock and clubhouse supplements i
take in a day
so what does a w do what does the
medical medium do
i'm asked that all the time like i want
to do what you want to do might won't
mean i want to do what i do but
i'll tell you what i'm going to do and
what i do so that's what today is about
it's about
how i take my supplements what
supplements do i
take in a day not just that a couple
other other cool things too
as well so it's not just supplements
we're talking about
a couple of other little supplemental
tricks that i do
glad everybody's coming on good to see
everybody so i'm excited about this
chris what are you doing hey chris
seaweed hero how you doing
glad you guys are coming on rosanna
you're coming on everybody's coming on
here
michelle l i think i saw ashley kibben
good to see you guys coming on and
this is fun right here lorraine now good
to see kathy owen
it's great to have you guys coming on
here because this is a fun one for me
because i never get a chance to do this
it's like i always show you guys
different things different medical
medium tools different ways to heal of
course all kinds of powerful information
but i don't go like into exactly what i
do
personally right it's something that i i
haven't had a chance to spend time on
and i think you know if it's helpful if
it's interesting
hang in there while we go for it for the
ride and i'm also going to share
other information obviously on how to
heal answer a couple questions of some
you know and all that so let me get
started so
in the morning the first thing i do is
obviously
lemon water right so i got the lemon
right here
it's the first thing i do in the morning
right
it's actually obviously a medical medium
healing tool flush the liver
but i do this before i take any
supplements you know so i
squeeze a little lemon in a glass of
water 16 to 32 ounces
that's the first thing i do you guys
know that we talked about that on the
mono cleanse talked about that medical
medium
morning cleanse right but
let's go into other parts i actually do
teas in the morning
so that's something i do too so i'm
going to show you some of the teas i do
i do a really strong peppermint
brew in the morning i'll do the rose hip
hibiscus
right this is a traditional medicinal
let's do the raspberry leaf so i make
really strong bruise of tea so i'm going
to do that in a moment
yeah that that we're going to talk about
and
i'm going to show you some other things
as well so let me get a cup of tea going
right now first of all
got my cup right here so this is a
different
kind of episode this episode of what aw
does
so i got some hot water that i just
brewed right
you guys are you guys doing tea every
day at all
so what brands will begin with with the
tea
i'm talking about traditional medicinal
okay i'm gonna be talking about vimergy
that's the brand right here of
supplements that i
admire the most because of the quality
and all kinds of other reasons and i'll
talk about that so i'm going to show you
that too
i got the weinman's wild blueberry juice
it's something i do every single day
i'm not sponsored by traditional
medicinals
just a little forewarning there not
sponsored by these guys
i'm not sponsored by vimergy this is
stuff
i do every single day okay i am working
with wyman's to make sure this stuff
gets out there in the world because it's
incredible right
all these different reasons i've talked
about that before but
so as far as the t's go i make a really
really strong brew and i'll do
i'll do multiple teas in a day okay so
that's something i'll do
so i'll get a really strong hibiscus
rose hip in the morning
what i like about the rose hips is it's
great for the immune system
and right now we have to keep our immune
system strong so what you'll find
in here is a lot of powerful immune
system builders and boosters right and
i'm going to be doing
multiple lives on this topic right here
not just what i take in a day but i'm
going to do it a million
immune system builder one i'm going to
do a baseline supplement one two
so i'm dropping some tea bags in here
so there's one right there and
there's two right
okay and then three
right so i'm doing three rows hip with
hibiscus
so i usually do this sometime in the
morning you know you can
i don't know what you guys you know if
you do any teas in the morning but
that's one right there
i'll drop some honey in there too
yeah that's hot water
so i'm gonna drop some honey right there
so that's that's one of
now i do a lot of tea just so you guys
know a lot of tea which you won't see me
doing is green tea
you won't see me trying to destroy my
adrenal glands
and what you guys are going to be doing
what's going to happen out there is you
guys are going to be
they're going to try to brainwash you
guys they're going to try to brainwash
you to have your green tea
to make sure that every woman's on green
tea or matcha tea or some kind of coffee
and i talk about that being bad right
and all that stuff
but it do you see me drinking green tea
do you see me drinking matcha tea right
do you see me drinking coffee you don't
see that there's a reason because
green tea matcha tea coffee those are
adrenal destroyers for women especially
for women
good to see you guys healthy liz good to
see you
so those are adrenal destroyers
annihilators so it's funny how the
industry the health industry works okay
it's one thing the caffeine industry is
one thing right
but it's not just that it's the
alternative medicine industry and the
alternative medicine medicine industry
is
is such a game like a tricky
game and it's a game to really hurt
women more than people know and men too
so they'll just push all that caffeine
into women
and they'll age them quick now i don't
know why alternative medicine loves to
do that but they do
and it's all paid for stuff it's all
paid for
stuff just you know so there's that game
so which which you won't see
in my morning or my day is you won't see
teas that are you know that are
caffeinated because you don't want that
you definitely don't want that that's
important to know
so i'm going to do another tea right
here okay i'm going to get this hop
right here
hotter so
and that's so good right there i'm gonna
do another tea
so i drink multiple teas in a day one of
the teas i drink a lot of is red
raspberry leaf
okay and i'll do the same thing i'll do
three tea bags right there
and this is a great way to get
minerals trace minerals in you guys this
is herbal medicine so i'm all about
herbal medicine
but i'm not about stupid herbal medicine
there's a difference and i'll go into
what that means
uma do you do you do tea after celery
juice sure
yeah 15 to 30 minutes later absolutely
i definitely do
so i'm going to do another cup of tea
right here
using herbal medicine properly is how
you heal
just so you know using herbal medicine
properly is how you heal and i'm going
to cover
a whole bunch of different things that i
take i got all the supplements here
right here
all the different stuff that i do every
single day
i take lysine every day jody k
can you overdo it with supplements i
heard too many can affect the liver
too many useless supplements
too many supplements that aren't good
for people to take
there's a big difference like
supplements and then there's crap
or supplements and trendy garbage or
supplements and um
junk so let's give you a couple of a
couple of things fish oil
yeah you can overdo it any of it's
overdue because it's terrible for you
right
so if you're like well i'm taking my
supplements i'm doing my fish oil well
that's that's that's a disaster
because of of the mercury that's in fish
oil and i don't care what anybody says
there's mercury and fish oil in fact
it's even worse than what people believe
because they try to remove mercury
artificial and then it makes it worse
because you have the homeopathic version
of mercury inside fish oil which goes
straight to the brain
straight to the brain stem okay so
so that's just an example right there
like sodium bicarbonate bentonite clay
apple cider vinegar gummies like all
this is garbage colostrum
collagen right zeolite all of this is
garbage and so
yeah you can overdo it when you do
zeolite because you like you're not
supposed to be doing
you can overdo it when you do whey
protein powder because you're not
supposed to be doing it
you can overdo bentonite clay because
you're not supposed to be doing it you
can overdo humic and fulvic acid
because you're not supposed to be doing
it because this stuff isn't good for you
and that's the scam of the alternative
industry too
it's all they have to give you so much
to choose from
that you shouldn't be doing because it's
it's garbage
if your doctor wants you on it be on it
okay but i wouldn't go on it i wouldn't
put family and friends on it i wouldn't
put any of the people that have reached
out to me throughout the
throughout my life you know i wouldn't i
wouldn't put anybody on that so
so i'm doing red raspberry leaf right
here i'm doing there's herbal medicine
and then there's herbal medicine
that's not smart there's lots of that
out there
keep that in mind
hi anthony astrid says i've healed my
migraines that i've had for more than 30
years
i am so grateful for your information
and your help so astrid
you're seasoned you know what's going on
out there with products and everything
else so you're obviously doing the
medical medium tools you healed your
migraines
and the not so sick people they play
around in the land of
supplements that aren't good for you and
they can do that when they're not so
sick when you only have a headache but
not severe migraines
you can play around with all the
different thinking out there and all the
different bad supplements out there
so question on tick tock
i think it's a question can you mix the
teas you can
you can't i don't mix them but you can
so what kind of tea is that
okay so that's red raspberry right here
is what i was just doing
red raspberry leaf from traditional
medicinals okay
and that's the rose hip one medical
medium directory medical medium
dot com you can find on directory so
let's talk about other stuff i do so i'm
just showing you some teas
and i drink the teas all day so into my
supplements so i do
i do the tinctures right i love
tinctures i got a shot glass right here
because that's how i take them
i got some water right here too okay
so every single day i take um tinctures
so you'll see them right here i'm going
to kind of show them right here there's
the metal leaf there's the lemon balm
so lemon balm every single day for me
and i'm not telling you to do what i'm
doing i'm not trying to say hey do what
i'm doing you listen to your doctor and
whatever you choose to do
in your life right that's the best lemon
balm out there
and it's in tincture form and it's the
vimergy right
and what i love about lemon balm okay
it's incredible for the cranial
nerves now i stress my cranial nerves
out really bad do you guys stress your
cranial nerves out really bad
your vagus nerve right your facial
nerves your trigeminal nerves right
all your different nerves do you guys
stress yours out because i stress mine
out and i know a lot of people have
inflamed nerves
they got the anxiety they got the
depression they got the trigeminal
neuralgia they got the headaches the
migraines the aches and pains
i love lemon balm because it's such an
incredible powerful tool for this this
is vimergy if you want to know it's v as
in victor i
am as mary e r g y dot com
vimergy.com what i love about vimergy
you could go straight to vimrgy.com
these and victor i am e-r-g-y dot com
right
i'm not sponsored but i love love
love this company and what they do
gentle but
powerful no fillers no garbage no
nothing
and i and and that's the thing it's like
that matters to me
but also really potent at the same time
as gentle so
the lemon balm is an incredible healing
tool for so many people
no citric acid no natural flavors no
alcohol it's it's really incredible so
let's go into this a little bit
how much do i take right
so it's just moving this around a little
bit so you guys can see
okay so how much do i take
try not to let disaster happen over here
like spilling everything
so that's one dropper full right there
maybe somebody you're just taking one
dropper full maybe somebody that takes
a one drop one drop
right and but this is what i do so i'll
put
two dropper fulls two full dropper fulls
right
three
four
five
six so i take six full dropper holes of
lemon balm right there
put them in a shot glass that's what i
do that's my shot glass right there
and i add a little water
huh put a little bit of water in there
so i just made a lemon balm
shot that's what it did it's a lemon
balm
now this is a tool used correctly right
here
it's the right kind of lemon balm right
kind of lemon
lemon balm product and already that's a
win-win because what people don't
understand is you get a lemon balm out
there that's an alcohol with natural
flavors or anything you get a lemon balm
that's
not not it's got fillers in it or it's
just a weak
weak version you know nasa says zeolite
is garbage i read that it is okay in
your book medical medium i'm glad you
asked that i'm going to cover that too
why that was there
because just like i will i will drop
anything that i think changes if a
product is changing
they're dead to me that's it and there
hasn't been a zeolite out not even to
this day i know everybody screams the
light and all the stuff
they're not good okay in my opinion
they're not good
and they dehydrate they remove
important trace minerals there was a
zeolite
that was okay enough at the time when
dulce wasn't present
right but it's it's not okay enough
and what people do is they do large
dosages of zeolite the whole thing and
they're using the wrong zeolites
and and um so yeah so
the only reason why i offered zeolite at
one point there was a certain variety of
zeolite out at the time
and small dosages it would help get
some debris out of the intestinal tract
but it can't cross the barrier of
intestinal tract it can't go into the
bloodstream
it can't very easily it can't go into
places you need to go in
and the z lights today are not the right
kind so i just want to just
make that clear and how that works so
but what you'll find
is the heavy metal detox smoothie which
is the spirulina
and the barley grass juice powder right
heavy metal detox movie
that's helping people heal around the
world people are trying to
hop on that boat that bandwagon so
they'll say hey
do the z light 2 with your heavy metal
detox smoothie
and then they try to take credit for
what the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie does
zeolite in the last 20 years hasn't done
anything for anybody somebody has lupus
or ra or hashimoto's they
keeps with their ra their hashimoto's
their neurological line they keep with
their lupus they keep with their
conditions
zeolite doesn't change that same thing
with like humic acid fulfilling acid
it dehydrates the body it doesn't give
back
it takes and it doesn't get people out
of sickness
medical medium info is about getting
people out of sickness
disease illness struggles
symptoms and doing it right so
you know there's people out there the
user of all medicine they use it wrong
so i'm showing a great way of how to use
it can ask your doctor what's right for
you but this is how i use it for my
friends and family so this is a
lemon bomb okay shot right there
and i take this every day
if you're watching this on youtube give
me a thumbs up if you want
so that's a lemon balm shot now i take
those throughout the day
kathy hill will the lemon balm tea be
just as good
as the tincture it's not as good as the
tincture
but i like the lemon balm tea and i like
traditional medicinals lemon balm tea
that's the peppermint right there
but it's not as good as
the tincture but it's still helpful so
if you have the lemon balm tea drink it
drink it drink it if you like that
that's fine but this is more of
heading to that that extra medicinal
that
powerful level of a healing tool
so that's why i do it with the tincture
takes it to that whole another thing
so that's what i do with the lemon balm
i do that every day so the thing is the
question is i've never showed you guys
this
i never have yet of like how i do
something for myself
put the name of the company to buy its
vimorgy it's v is
victor i m e rgy.com
so that's what it is that's the name of
the company
right there it's vimergy that little
symbol on the bottle
right v isn't victor i m e r g
y dot com that's where you get them
which
ones will help with joint pain
and listen this is going to be one of a
few lives i'm going to be doing i'm
letting you know
if you're going to cleanse the heel
you'll find joint pain and cleanse the
heel
and you'll see which supplements to use
for joint pain so if you guys have a
symptom or condition or any kind of
illness right
you can find it in the cleanse of heal
book
okay bring the book to your doctor ask
your doctor what's right for you but
you'll see supplements and dosages
i'm going to go into detail on that on
another live not on this one though this
is more like what i take
what i take in a day good to see you
guys coming on i'm excited about today
because this is
even this is like real personalized
stuff this is my personal life this is
how i take care of myself
and i i don't know i've always showed
you guys stuff i do and stuff i eat
right
but i never go as far as like really
showing you exactly what i do
so this is like a personal episode right
here which is it's fun it's cool to do
this i like getting real
real close with you guys on all this
information so
so i do i i need a lot of lemon balm
okay now i love it for anxiety i don't
have anxiety or an anxiety condition
what i have is stress tremendous amount
of stress that's what i have
i'm finishing up a book right now i'm
getting three hours of sleep right now
you know i'm working really hard so
if you're under stress emotional turmoil
maybe relationship issues whatever's
happening in your life
maybe you're just worried about
something i always recommend to my
friends and family the
lemon balm is what i do so
um and this is how i take it so i do six
dropper folds
and i take that like four times a day
so four times a day what i just showed
you guys so
that that's how i take it so that was
one right there
so later on i'll do another round
i'm not saying you guys do this talk to
your doctor what's right for you
you can be somebody and just take this
much
like i have friends and i'd be like just
take six drops
or six drops and it's gonna be really
helpful for your anxiety i say to my
friends it's gonna be helpful for any
anxiousness
any kind of stress dale says
could you say again where to order the
lemon balm it's a vimergy vimergy.com go
to their website vias and victor i
am as mary e rgy.com go to their website
i'm not sponsored by these guys these
guys
are not paying me i'm not sponsored i
don't own the company
very important to know if i owned a
supplement company it would say medical
medium
across the bottle it would say
medical medium supplements this is just
the one
that i use and trust so i wanted to show
you guys
so i would do another round of these
it's like this
right six more of that
irma lemon balm is really helpful with
panic attacks and
house mm info exactly
it's medical medium info it's
really powerful for panic attacks it's
wonderful for
anxiety and all of that and so what i
like about lemon balm
if try not to i'm just gonna say this
try not to get overwhelmed
with what you see me do just giving you
a little four one one
little disclaimer okay did i'm
personally showing you one may be one of
the reasons why i don't show you guys
what i do
is it could overwhelm you you know
that's all because you might say wait a
minute wait a minute
do i have to take all these supplements
what i have to do
six dropper fulls of this what that's
not what this is
i'm actually just saying you guys i want
you to have a window
into what i'm doing in my life i want
you to have a window into how i'm taking
my supplements
and this is the window right here so i
do
four of these a day six dropper fulls
in some water is what i do
you may be somebody that takes one
dropper full it's amazing just one
dropper full
much light and love energy has always
been good to me
they listen to you they really do that's
what i love about them they care about
you and they run
heavy metal testing on all their
supplements they do by an independent
independent testing
organization not one that's not
independent which all the others do
that says everything right there linda
says can you say
something about vitamin b12 how much and
how long to take i'll go to b12 next of
what i do
that's the vimergy b12 i'll talk about
why i take it
okay all of that so let's head there let
me get the shot glass out
now b12 i take orally a lot of times i
just put it directly in my mouth but i
also do the shot glass too
so go into that a little bit i want to
mention something though
about uh vimorji being good to you okay
because i know you said that right
and they've always been so good to you i
want to tell you how i even
like went into this whole thing of why
this is my one of my favorites okay
because the quality is is far surpass
any
spirulina so this is spirulina the
reason why i mention this is because
i used to i used to be supportive
of pacifica spirulina right so west
coast spirulina
and a couple of things went wrong there
all right
one of the west coast companies they i
found
something in their bottle and
i never spoke about this before but i
found something in their bottle
it was a little piece of plastic that
was this big
like a little tiny thin square
that was the color of
the spirulina i could have accidentally
swallowed it
and i and and because of spirit of
compassion i didn't
i never told you about this story it's a
private story it's like only my family
knows this
a couple of my friends i told the story
right and
so like i went to the bottle with the
spoon
and it was so thin and small by far
anybody else would have swallowed that
and i i was really upset so i was like
well what do i do
it looked like it could have been maybe
one of the fresheners that are inside
these things
but something was wrong this was so
easily
a problem and so i called the company
told them who i was on the medical
medium
you know i left a message on on your on
your you know at your company before
and i promote your products your pacifi
pacific spirulina i have thousands of
people
out there that you know come to me for
help you know all these things over the
years thousands of thousands of people
and i i like a good product so i know i
can help people right
and you know i've left messages before
and they've ignored me
and it's the first sign when the
companies ignore me right
and then when i found this piece of
plastic this piece of
this dangerous thing in there i reached
out to them
it's like give me a call back i found
this in this and this they never did
and i was like that's it done
no recommendations for me it's over
you know strike two and then the oceans
got more polluted recently just in the
last few years the last three years
the west coast water is so polluted sea
life is actually
being forced to come closer to the shore
and that's why so many people are with
their videos and their cameras like oh
my god i see another shark
i see another porpoise i see another i
see another whale i see another this the
reason why is because there's no more
ocean left out there in the west coast
because it's it's a garbage patch now so
everybody's everything's being pushed to
this to the
edge and so i'm done with the whole
pacifica
spirulina done like i can't even tell
you
and that's the best stuff on the market
right there is the vimergy which is not
pacifica and it's the best stuff so it's
vimergy v
i m e rgy so talk about that in a little
bit
this is this is like more purse this
whole i i
i'm always personal with you guys duh
right i always am
but this is more like okay what is a w
doing what where's the fly on the wall
on aw
like who's gonna be the [__] where's the
fly on the wall
with aw at ew's house right so yeah
can you say something about vitamin b12
how much and how long to take this
vitamin b12 and blood can be on a high
level
what do you recommend i noticed that i
needed a little bit every day
without i get symptoms okay here's the
things you get symptoms right
if you don't take it but yet you have
high b12 right
see that's the problem the industry
doesn't know alternative medicine
doesn't know
how b12 works with this okay
is that it's okay if levels are high
do what your doctor says though your
doctor doesn't like something you just
listen to them i'm just telling you that
what i would tell my family member if a
family member
had high b12 i wouldn't say stop
taking the b12 because it's helping your
symptoms get better because
what they don't measure and what they
can't measure
is how much b12 your central nervous
system has so what i tell my family
members
is you keep your b12 high
so that your central nervous system is
getting enough b12 which is your cranial
nerves
your brain stem your brain stem that
your brain stem is getting enough b12
how important that is to get enough b12
right
and and because they can't measure
how much b12 your vagus nerve needs
you guys see how important this is they
can't measure how much b12
your phrenic nerve needs okay
all in our nerve needs right your
cochlear nerve needs they can't they
can't
um your tibial nerve your you they can't
measure
how much these nerves need right sciatic
nerve
it's not you know whatever and it's not
cranial but trigeminal nerve facial
nerve they can't measure that
so your symptoms
can get worse even if you have high b12
and the wrong kind of b12 won't even
absorb
properly so and that's the other thing
this is the adenosil cobalamin
methylcobalamin b12
so i take this every day to get the b12
i need
i'm on lots of b12 i mean what i do and
have to have to conquer on a daily basis
like the amount of of stuff i have to
conquer on a daily basis
when i'm up against every day it's just
it's it's
it's absorbing you know that kind of
i mean you know you need that health of
liz only learned
this from you never learned this
neuro never learned this in neuro class
i'm honored list it's
incredible and thank you for being here
today by the way your support uh is so
helpful
what are the right kinds of b12 okay so
there's a lot of b12 products out there
alcohol's in there okay preservatives
are in there
it's all the bad preservatives and b12s
keep that in mind
msg natural flavors are in b12s okay
and then there's cyclobalamide that's a
bad b12 there's other there's other b
12s so even if you have the right kind
of b12 like
methylcobalamin doesn't mean it's the
right kind of b12 because
of how it was processed made the the
quality of it and everything else right
but the right blend is adenosine
cobalamin and methylcobalamin that's the
right blend right there
and that's it it's avemargee.com v isn't
victor i
am ergy.com i'm gonna say their name
because you guys
a bunch of people are gonna be like whoa
where do you get that you know what do
we do whatever whatever so i'm letting
you know
and if you just came on here i'm not
sponsored by these guys i'm not the
owner of the company
if i owned a supplement company i say
this all the time if i owned a tea
company supplement company or whatever
you'd see medical medium across the
front
right so what i'm doing here is
four dropper fulls of b12 right
murray hell taylor why did you switch
the b12 you were recommending two years
ago
because i always go to the better the
better b12
that's why i don't think it was two
years ago it could have been
three years ago um
could have been four years ago not sure
how long ago uh
but when a better one comes out i don't
have loyalty
to the one that's not as good there's
something to be said about that i've
seen people what happens is people who
are involved in the supplement world
right um the meaning like they're being
endorsed or paid or sponsored
or they own the company right they even
if their product is garbage they stand
behind their garbage product
so i don't have that loyalty i'm not
chained
to a company for loyalty if the b12
product is not as good and there's one
better
then guess what i'm on to the better one
and guess what
i'm gonna stay with that and stay with
that end state with that
that's what i do this is the b12 right
here
um but if they change for the worst if
any company changes for the worst
bye bye bye bye that's just the bottom
line
because i always got to think about you
guys that's what it is it's always got
to think about you guys
well if i was chronically ill i want to
make sure i have the best opportunity to
heal
and i have the best stuff there is so
that's four dropper fulls of b12 right
here in the shot glass
you guys just came on here this is what
i do you talk to your doctor whatever
you guys want to do
i'm just saying this is what i do right
here me in my life personally okay
i take the best stuff is what i do i
only take the best stuff
personally inside my body everybody says
the body's the temple the body is the
temple
body's temple yeah let's treat it that
way
which re reminds me of something right
so that's four dropper fulls of b12 i
take that um
i take that twice a day sometimes i'll
do six dropper holes
if someone does a half a drop or full
it's going to help
it's going to help if somebody does that
much
if someone's on a like a budget they're
worried and they're like well i don't
want
you know i'm not under a lot of stress
right now i just want to take a little
b12 just take a little b12
i tell friends you could just take a
little bit of b12 right there you can do
a quarter dropper full or something or
since you can just do that a lot of
people they're really sensitive
and that's what i love about the vimergy
products because they're force sensitive
people
a lot of people are really sensitive
they only need to take a little
so you know little is is good they get a
little bit in them
that's fine quality matters
cheap crappy junk out there
really holds people back it holds them
back from healing i've talked about this
for years
so garbage products holds them back
holds their healing back
so and that happens all the time right
so all right move on a little bit i just
showed you some lemon balm
shot right there the b12 right there now
i take b12 also orally so i also do it
this way too every day i'll drop four
dropper full just like that i'll try not
to get it on my yellow shirt
so okay let's move on to more of
now like a medicinal shot right
let's go into that realm okay so i'm
exposed i get exposed
if i you know like
i like to keep my immune system strong
so every
day if i get especially if i'm getting
exposed in some way through work
or anything like that
chelsea floyd first time i had liquid
zinc from my local health food store
it made me throw up i bet it did i bet
it did
but it was not good for sensitive
stomachs i bet it wasn't it's one of my
biggest fear out there of all the
junkies
zinc out there was nervous to try the
vimergy one
but it was so gentle no issues chelsea
that means everything and that was the
zinc world before
vimergy came along right that was the
zinc world
the zinc world was you take zinc and you
get nauseous you get sick or you just
you can't
you know because of all the citric acid
in it and all the garbage and junk in it
that's what that is and that's why i
love the vimorji
of emergency zinc it changes everything
it allows somebody to have a chance to
actually heal and and to take something
for the further problems now if you guys
you don't know medical medium
information inside cleanse the heal i'm
just going to give you a reminder is
almost 200 symptoms and conditions right
diseases symptoms conditions
in the back of the book with supplement
dosages recommendations on what to take
in dosages
so i'm just letting you know okay
there's a chapter that you should read
if you ever get there right that you'd
read and it says
what you need to know about supplements
and for the record that is still on sale
at amazon.com
us for 16.99 51 off
which blows my mind i told you i feel
like angelic forces are involved with
that
because like i still can't believe
they're pricing it under what the book
costs to print and it's a medical
textbook
it's just it blows my mind
okay so if you guys just got on here
it's an honor to have you on here we're
in my kitchen we're doing
something a little bit more personal
today even though you know everything we
do is personal
and and you know how much i care about
you guys love you guys
but this is more about like me and my
like what am i doing where's the fly on
the wall for me
because that's what it's about like so
let's go into a little bit let's do kind
of a
this next little thing so what i'll do
is i love licorice
okay i love it for my for my adrenal
glands
i love it for my adrenal glands you know
what about aw's adrenal glands
okay what about what about his adrenal
glands okay
so i love licorice for my adrenal glands
right there my adrenals
are pumping because i'm dying out fires
a lot
dine out a lot of fires and that's three
dropper fulls
of licorice now what i recommend is you
talking to your doctor
about licorice is licorice okay for you
to take
i talk about take the book to your
doctor and you'll you'll see where it
says licorice and how many dosages and
what how much licorice or whatever to
take
bring it to your doctor ask your doctor
about it you know and
that's that's what you can do lorraine
it's pretty cozy right
yeah i know it is i feel i feel that way
too
quality in licorice matters i'm gonna be
straight up about that another thing
again like the quality
matters means everything with licorice
working like working okay
no alcohol no citric acid but the
quality of licorice itself
right it in the resin involved in the
licorice
it matters right to how it works so what
i love about licorice it's anti-pathogen
antiviral anti-bug anti-pathogen
why is everybody sick
with mystery illness because
their nerves are inflamed from pathogens
from viruses they talk about that in the
medical medium books right
and so their nerves are inflamed from
pathogens
so keep that in mind details matter dale
right on
this is details this is details
okay so i just put three dropper fulls
of licorice in there
all right now i'm also gonna put
okay a little bit of goldenseal in here
because that's what i do
i'll do licorice and some goldenseal
so i'm going to do three dropper fulls
of goldenseal
that's the vimergy goldenseal okay
anna sophie please the doctors again
[Laughter]
yep so there we go we got that i put the
golden seal in there
right now what i do is i take some cat's
claw now
there's times some days that it changes
with me okay
it changes with me and well you know
what dr nesbitt might come in here
in a little bit might bring on dr
nesbitt
he's a board-certified surgeon
and a board-certified
right board-certified uh cardiologist
pulmonologist too he's a board certified
md all right put two dropper holes a
cat's claw in there okay
all right you're someone's asking what
would um
dr desmond i might bring dr nesbit on
but i want dr nesbitt to ruin this
personal moment
with us right now anyway in here i talk
about goldenseal
in the different right tear appleman
right dr nesbit
okay if someone's really viral they
you know i talk about that in this
section here
someone's really viral i love goldenseal
but i talk about dosages do smaller
dosages i go
that's why this part is so important to
read so
important to read okay
dr nesbit is a very qualified
doctor by the way i'll bring him on a
little bit
if i could find him
all right let's just keep on going i put
cat squad here i put licorice in here
i'm having too much fun
golden seal i like to do two weeks on
two weeks off
depending and i talk about that in the
book okay licorice root i like to do two
weeks on two weeks off
sometimes i'll do licorice fruit
straight and not take weeks off
sometimes i'll do golden steel like that
too
but it says in my book you do it two
weeks on two weeks off it's a great way
of doing it
so i have this right here okay so we got
that what else do i put in here i don't
put the nettle in at the same time
and so i put the golden seal right
i put the ashwagandha sometimes in but
i'm going to hold off lately i've been
doing that by itself so i'll show you
that in a second
this is cats called licorice root
cat's claw licorice root goldenseal
now i held off my supplements today
i held off my supplements today because
um because i was doing this
now i think we were able to locate dr
nesbitt
i told you he's a board-certified
surgeon and really good one he's highly
qualified too
he's probably one of the best doctors
i've ever taught and i have talked to
thousands of doctors over the last three
five years
but dr nesbitt is one of my favorites
he's here today he's just
coming on up dr nesbitt we're doing a
little supplement protocol
today on um tick tock there's tick tock
up there
uh you see health with liz up there yeah
she's cool right
dr nesbitt dr nesbit it's been
he's been monitoring we have a mosquito
nearby
dr hezbot there's a mosquito floating
around right now
who figures when we're live um
so dr nesbitt what do you have to say to
everybody
anything good can you tell me
first of all hold on uh
hold on guys doctors but i just don't
like this mosquito and i don't want it
to bite you
i heard it fly by me all right okay
i think we're okay do you guys like
getting bit by mosquitoes because i
don't
all right let's see all right so that's
nice what do you have to say to
everybody
all right so dr desmond hopes that
everybody's taking good care of
themselves that they're
that they're spending some quality time
their loved ones or with you know by
themselves
they're actually getting some outside
time
if the weather is good if the weather is
good all right dr nesbitt might have to
go
how much goldenseal susan says how much
gold and steel
first of all this is my doctor just so
you know dr nesbitt takes care of all my
health needs
i want everybody to know that most
qualified doctor actually
and dr nesbit is my personal doctor and
he gives me my recommendation so what
what soc
dr nesbit just said spirit of compassion
is the one that gives me all my
recommendations
and i kind of threw spirit of compassion
under the bus just now by
saying dr nesbitt does well dr nesbitt i
do listen to you at times cause you do
give me some opinions
your doctor's opinion dr desmond says
yes he's
uh dr desmond says yeah he likes me on
the licorice root so that's one thing he
likes me on and lots of b12
all right doctors but we have to get
back to work okay what you're not going
to see
dr nesmet says he's not going to say
anything sarcastic and
we're going to not bother the trolls
today okay that's
what's going right now you guys um so
okay let's get back to work this is fine
ah
let's see house of liz says you have
cleanse to heal
i don't think you're talking to somebody
else emma says
your mono cleanses helped me like
nothing else has ever
i'm sorry i ever doubted you
that you know it's incredible i'm
honored and
uh people doubt me they do i know i know
it's just it's amazing but they do and
the funny thing is is
i i think i think you just have to be
sick enough you know to just
go around merry around and and that's
just
what i talk about at the colts out there
because there's a difference
like this is not a cult those are colts
out there how they do it they do the
brainwashing they got the power and the
money behind it and it trickles down and
everybody gets
brainwashed it's really sick how it
works um
and when you really learn the medical
medium tools and how to use it and
you're not dabbling in it what's going
to happen is here's one thing too
you'll run across somebody dabbling in
say somebody new and you'll run across
somebody dabbling in the medical medium
tools
and they're dabbling so they're not
really seeing results because they're
also doing all this other stuff they're
doing their colostrum and their in their
collagen and their fish oil and their
protein powders and their msg which they
don't know in their caffeine
and they're alkaline ionizer alkaline
water machines
they're doing all these things that are
poisoning themselves right
and then they do they dabble with a
little bit of medical medium
and it's keeping them a little stable
but they don't realize it but they just
don't know better and then
someone runs across them and be like oh
medical medium's not doing it for me no
and then you that's it you lost your
chance because you're gonna be like i
doubt it i doubt that guy's
got info the whole bit even though
millions have healed
it's just unbelievable let's go let's
keep on moving forward we've got another
shot glass so
so ashwagandha
sits a medical medium tools ashwagandha
right
it's it's always been i've always liked
ashwagandha okay
in the sense where it's a medical medium
tool
because of some of the reasons why we
hear about ashwagandha
stems from medical medium for 35 years
okay and it's just like cat's claw cat's
claw
is used in neurological lyme disease
right now for neurological lyme
that's because of medical medium it's 35
years of teaching
lyme doctors fighting for lecturing
about cats claw for
viruses and bacteria and stuff so
ashwagandha is kind of the same thing
now
i take ashwagandha every day
so can i put the supplements in orange
juice yes you can i put in water you can
put it in orange juice of course you can
definitely can why take supplements
separately or together okay
you can take them all together if that's
what you do if that's what your doctor
recommends
um you don't have to do anything i'm
doing course not just do what your
doctor says
but with me is the lemon bomb shot i
take
separately i use it as a medical medium
tool separately
so yeah cold white spring says dr
nesbitt
have you been laying eggs
all right so i'll take it separately as
a medical medium tool that's what i'll
do
i mix herbs that spirit compassion is
telling me to do in that moment too
and and that's how i live my life you
know i'm hearing information from spirit
of compassion
since age four if you don't know that
about me if you guys want to learn that
you can learn it in the books and
that'll be
in books if you want to learn about that
medical medium new edition right there
check that book out read origin so you
understand how it works
okay quality matters there's so many
junkie ashwagandhas out there it's
unbelievable there's junkie ashwagandha
powders there's junkie
ashwagandha capsules and and tablets
bad tinctures and
that's a problem all on its own so
that's something to look out for too
and and that that's
junky ashwagandha can make somebody sick
by the way
really sick so there's a dropper full of
ashwagandha i usually take a dropper
full of
ashwagandha once a day
i tend to not mix it remember alcohol
and additives and citric acid
and msg and natural flavors that's the
stuff that's really bad
there's bad powders out there that have
even that in there
not only they're just junky powders they
got a lot of dust in them
so the one thing you'll find with
powders like ashwagandha powder and
herbal powders what you'll find is
there's herbal dust in those
powders and you guys are eating dirt and
don't know it
that's how it works you're eating dirt
then
and so what happens is when you're
getting all your herbal powders
right okay and you're doing that herbal
powder and herbal
tablets and and many times herbal
capsules
you're eating herbal dust you're eating
herbal
dirt you're eating you're actually
eating
dirt and dust mixed with your herbs
and people don't realize that and that's
that's that's
that's something that gets in that
people don't even realize it yeah
it's how it works um but yeah there's so
much to talk about i mean i can cover a
million things and i'm trying to
trying to harness myself a little bit
because i want to give you guys
enough time on what i take but i can go
on forever with so much and that's
what's cool we're going to do
a series of these over the next like
week week and a half two weeks
there's people out there that will say
i'm doing medical medium
but they're not they're doing
supplements
that are bad that medical media would
never recommend
okay so that's they're using companies
that cut corners
and that's another thing too so one of
the biggest scams and supplements if you
want to know
one of the biggest scams in the
supplement world is putting a little bit
of something into the supplement
a little bit of cat's claw a crappy one
a little bit of nettle crappy one a
little bit of
ashwagandha a crappy one a little bit of
this junk right like garbage little
pieces bits and pieces
now you've got a fat capsule or a powder
that has a little bit of everything and
that's how they rip you off i know how
the supplement industry works
they scam you by putting a whole bunch
of stuff in there
slapping a label on it here's our green
powder
mix it's got all these different things
in here it's got alfalfa in it it's got
this in it that in it
and it does the list a little corella in
there and it does this list down the
line
and you get a little speck and that's
how they bank
they rip you off because you can't get
better with this you can't get better
you can't heal you can't recover with a
speck
of something that's not even a good
quality you can't recover
with just a speck thrown in there so
important now all right so there's the
ashwagandha
okay so i did one dropper full sometimes
i'll do a drop or full twice a day
sometimes i'll do two twice a day today
i'm doing
one probably twice a day
if you're not so sick you might get a
tiny benefit from that technique of
just a little bit of garbage in these
supplements so a powder
or a capsule and you're just getting a
little bit of that
product in the capsule a little bit of
that product in the powder
and you might actually benefit as a not
so sick person meanwhile if you clean
your diet as a not so sick person
you take enough junky supplements you
might see
some difference but it's when you get
sick
that's when everything changes that's
when all the junk and garbage out there
will take you down so let's move into a
couple other things
got the licorice right did some cat's
claw we did that so we can talk about
some capsules i did some b12
if you guys just got on here this
vimorgy.com vs invictor i
am e r g y dot com you go to i'm not
sponsored by these
guys but i'm showing you what i've taken
today and how it works 5mthf right there
i take that every single day 5mthf it's
a methylfolate right
best one on the markets of emergency one
right
so i'll take one capsule a day
sometimes i'll take two pop one down now
well let me get a little cup i'll use
this
so can't use that
and that's what i like about live
so i'll take a 5 mthf right
that's funny i didn't know there were
holes in this but you know what there is
because this is a water bottle
so it's a 5m thf i take every day what
else do i take
i take glutathione every single day
there you go that's of image glutathione
now i don't have a chance probably to
give you every little bit about these
but let's go into some other stuff i do
at night
so what if i can't swallow pills if i
was somebody that couldn't swallow pills
right
i would get the powders for one at
vimergy
okay that's what i would do for one so i
would get everything
like the powders and vimergy the barley
grass powder or the spirulina and then
the liquids of course i would do right
and then
tease like i was showing you guys at the
beginning the t's right
and then i would open a capsule so let's
go into that next
okay let's grab a cup here let's open a
capsule so
magnesium that's something i take every
single day
all right so
so i would open a capsule is what i
would do
like that and i would take it that way
with open capsules and i would mix it i
would mix it with oj it would mix it
with anything you want to mix it
some water some coconut water is a good
way to mix it right there
so let's talk about zinc for a little
bit so zinc shock therapy is a medical
medium tool
i talked about that i might and like i
said this is just about what i take
in a day i'm going to be doing more
lives
as we go on throughout like the next two
weeks about this stuff
so when it comes down to zinc
i'll put zinc in here
the pdf that i put out went around about
sink helping for the pandemic
that's how the zinc thing caught on
liquid zinc sulfate's the right one to
use
now what you're gonna see here's how
medical medium information works okay
here's the zinc we're using here's how
medical medium information works
is medical medium puts info out
it spreads around through the books and
through social media
okay and then other people change their
supplementation around medical medium so
all the other companies
change their supplementation around
medical medium they start putting things
in their probiotics now because
probiotics don't work
they never did but they start putting
like a little
speck of this like lysine in a probiotic
because of medical medium
they put a little speck of zinc in a pro
probiotic or they're putting these
different immune system ones they'll put
a little bit of vitamin c in something
now so they're they're making
all these different formulas out there
but ripping people off
is what they're doing they're making all
these different formulas and they're
ripping people off
and that's how they do it out there
they'll put a speck of lemon balm in
something
a speck of zinc and something they'll
add it now into their
collagen so now collagen powders because
medical medium hit collagen powder so
hard right because i wrote about it in
the books i talked about how collagen
doesn't repair
skin you actually need the building
blocks to create collagen
in your body right you guys and because
medical medium was the first to put
that out there that collagen itself
doesn't fix your skin or your body
or tissue it's it's the building blocks
to make so that your
body makes collagen so that was original
mm info now everybody stole that
info not citing it and now they're
creating products for collagen building
now that isn't collagen
they remove the collagen and they're
putting all these medical medium tools
and products down so that's how it works
the medical medium puts something out
there
like for instance zinc all right
zinc is out there because of the whole
the pandemic now they talk about
it's important with the pandemic you see
doctors talking about zinc
that originated from medical medium info
you know all these years and then the
pdf i put out
the 35 years of doing work so i'm
letting you know how mm
info goes around how where it originates
and i'm allowed to say it
because the proof is there
documentation's there and the proof's
there where it originates with medical
medium all of this stuff
so there's somebody new here
it is what it is
patrice bennett how are you anthony why
do you think
other vitamin companies are not as pure
as vimergy
oh money money money money
money that's what it is
right so because it you can cut corners
as a supplement company
you can cut corners to the point where
you couldn't even believe
and your margins are unreal you can use
cut
corners with fillers and you can cut
corners with with lower
did you know that did you know
supplement companies have a choice
to use high grade and low grade did you
guys know that
when you're a supplement company and
you're buying your product
bulk you can buy the different levels
all supplement companies don't buy the
highest level
they don't they buy the lower levels
and they won't go up to the higher
levels
so they give you junk that's how it
works it's one of the scheisterest
sheisterous scheister businesses out
there
supplement world shyster business
of like big time my god
um all right we talked about capsules a
little bit right
so here's something i do this is some
coconut water in here
wait hold on
talk about the zinc a little bit added
water to the zinc we'll cover that a
little bit i didn't finish talking about
this thing trying to find it
all the labels are backwards here okay
there we go
and i got this ink right there so i take
the zinc every single day i'll take two
dropper fulls three dropper fulls
of zinc every day ask your doctor what's
right for you
what i love about zinc is zinc is this
great thing where you can just take a
little if you wanted to you can just
take a few drops like three drops in
some water
right you can do
and um and the other thing is
um the other thing is with zinc which is
interesting
is i talk about flu cold and flu
protocols and medical mediums and shock
therapy check that out if you get a
chance
right there it's in there which is
incredible
zinc is the kind of thing where we're
missing zinc in our bodies and zinc is
one of those viral fighters it's
pathogen fighters it runs our immune
system
it's critical z therapy works ernesto
amazing it really does it's incredible
what happens with
with that so we did a little zinc so we
got the
and i do zinc separately a lot of times
i just don't put it at all one thing
can you put all these in one one shot
glass yeah of course you can
put all these in one shot glass if you
want so let's go let's move forward a
little bit more
now every single day i try to get the
heavy metal detox smoothie in me if i
can
some days i can't get an image
because the day already went like the
day is just
shot it's it's it's it's gone you know
so we'll go into that a little bit
so what i'll do is i'll put a little
spirulina
right right in coconut water
that's what i'll do that's the energy
spirulina
right there and that's the vimergy
barley grass juice powder
and i put a little barley grass juice
powder in there and i'll mix it up
now later on throughout the day because
i know some of you guys are gonna scold
me
i know it i'm gonna get i'm gonna get
scolded
and i know what it's what's gonna be is
where's the other ingredients
where's the wild blueberries where's the
wild blueberries
where's all the other stuff right if
you're just doing this and i'll also
take like
well blueberry powder right
so that's barley grass juice powder not
barley grass there's a difference you
can't get the metals out with barley
grass so i'll put some
wild blueberry powder in here okay
so you're gonna be like well wait a
minute that's not the heavy metal detox
smoothie where's the cilantro
well i already have the cilantro today
right the other thing is i take wild
blueberry shots
okay that's the other thing so this is
something i do every single day
is i'll take wild blueberry shots that's
the wyman's
um
it's lime as well blueberry juice so
i'll take
shots of this anyway so i take this
throughout the day
i'll do one or two shots three shots a
day that's why blue bridges
that's sure i'm going to spill it on my
yellow shirt right now
so that's what i do every single day
it's at shopwymans.com so shop
wymans.com i'm working with them by the
way
i am working with wyman's
just so you know it's the only company
here i'm working with
because this is this
i'm worried that you know that if i
don't support them we could lose this
product out there in the world and that
would be a shame because this is an
incredible product
okay i mean traditional medicinals i
don't need to work with them
they've been like this for years they
haven't changed anything
for decades and and vimergy is keeping
everything the same so
but these guys here it's hard to make
this stuff so i'm trying to
i'm trying to get the word out so you
know it keeps the stuff
going it's so so critical all right so
we're on to that a little bit so this
this is
my quick heavy metal detox smoothie i'll
put it in coconut water
i'll drink this at my desk right here
so it's a spirulina the barley grass
juice powder
right in the coconut water okay
and um i do the whole wild blueberries
of course when i make the smoothie
and i also do the juice every single day
so that's how i do it
right so that's my quick heavy metal
detox smoothie but keep in mind i also
eat cilantro later i'm
gonna i'm gonna have some adults later
and i already
i'm you know i'm gonna have my wild
blueberry shot
so keep in mind that i'm getting the
heavy metal detox smoothie throughout
the day
i had cilantro earlier today you know
looks yummy
adrenal snack yeah it's great adrenal
snack all right so
what have i not covered when we're
talking about so i take no here okay
let's talk about a night timer
uh routine here's my night time
right here yeah i take celery for us
before bed
celery force does does it's like a
a leveler is what it is it gives you
clarity
right it always gives me clarity i run
on it all day
but i also take it before bed believe it
or not so i'll do both
it doesn't make you sleepy
but it gives you a better sleep that's
what
that's what i discovered so i do the
celery force it doesn't make you sleepy
but it gives you a better sleep that's
what i like right and what i also love
about cellular pores when you take it
the morning or take it during the day
you have clarity and people always say
well how come he does what he does how
come he can do all the things he does
and
whatever and he's got high energy and
stuff like that like i'm trying to keep
it kind of cool and keep the energy cool
right here to show you guys what i take
but people are like why is he high it's
something i take every day it helps it
contributes to my
high energy but i noticed that when i
take it at night
it gives me a better sleep which is
which is great that's gaba right there
that's the bemidji gaba i take
every night before bed and that's the
melatonin i take every night for bed now
dosage of melatonin if you are a
melatonin taker
or you you know want to take melatonin
ask your doctor what's right for you on
a dosage
right and your doctor might like the
dosage on the bottle
what i do before bed is i'll take
about four of these right here is what i
do so i'll take four of these capsules
okay these capsules are five milligram a
piece so i'll take 20 milligrams
before bed sometimes i'll take more
um i don't recommend that for anybody
here you guys ask your doctor what's
right for you
but what i do is i take four capsules
right before bed and melatonin
and then i take
screen's frozen you guys we're getting
frozen out
two capsules of let me see now what i do
also is i'll take six capsules of
vitamin c
or six capsules i'll take that three
times a day
sometimes four times a day that's what
i'll do
yeah i noticed it was frozen out on your
end
it's not frozen on my end that's just
that's that's a censoring thing
yeah pharah says the tick tock's not
freezing
yeah so there's the vitamin c in there i
put a little honey in there too
and i'll crack an orange
so cracking orange
mix it up vitamin c shock therapy i do
that a lot
just you know probably almost every
single day
i'll do that
now that's two capsules in that one all
right
but i told you before that i take
i take six capsules
sometimes three four times a day of
microc
should you guys
hope i'm not boring you guys with what i
do
all right it's vitamin c shock there be
right there now time t
i have every single day so time t
is something i have every single day so
you know
let's go into that
right so time t
is something i do but i do fresh thyme
it's honey in there i put some sprigs of
thyme in there
too right there with fresh honey
i do that every day
i use a lot of honey you guys glucose to
the brain
is is really a good thing i'm going to
talk about a lysine
i'm assuming you guys are frozen out on
facebook
most likely that's where i'm heavily
censored
all right
so i got the glutathione something i
take every single day that's of energy
defined which is incredible does your
regular diet not provide
all of these vitamins and minerals
samantha it works like this
is that regular diet is you can say
regular diet for
thousands of years if you want hundreds
of years
but what has changed what has changed in
the last hundred years
radiation floating through the sky
nuclear waste in
places you wouldn't even believe
chemtrails dropping crap on us every day
mercury and chemicals pathogens and
toxins engineered viruses released into
the environment to actually just
destroy people um epstein bars and
shingles viruses left and right
mutations of different strep bacteria so
is your regular diet was it was your
regular diet prepared for
the onslaught of horribleness that that
is upon us
is your regular diet it's a good
question samantha though is your regular
diet
there to stop fragrances from actually
destroying our brains
perfumes colognes the toxicity levels of
that
fragrances you guys there's no there's
no list of ingredients in fragrance
they won't do that you know perfume you
know you know what the list ingredients
and perfume is
perfume perfume
perfume has dozens and dozens and dozens
of dangerous chemicals in it
but they just put it under perfume
everybody's always like
well i'm looking at my skincare it has
this in it i want to be careful what i
put on my face i want to be careful on
what i do with my skin care
i read all the ingredients the hot
ingredients but how come you don't you
can't read the ingredients on a perfume
or air freshener it's just fragrance
it's under the term fragrance or perfume
right in skincare fragrance is under the
term perfume or fragrance
right you can't you don't know how many
hundreds of chemicals actually
it's in cosmetics perfume and cosmetics
can be a hundred dangerous chemicals
from chemical companies
they can't list them out you would you
would have a coronary if you saw it
i mean you would have you would have a
stroke
if you saw what was in there if you guys
saw what was in your perfume your
cologne
if you saw the list of chemicals from
chemical companies that they won't show
it's hidden so everybody's all into i'm
into really good health i'm into
healthcare
i'm into skin care i'm into like
environment
i'm into all this stuff and yeah i know
i'll put that on me let me spray some
clone and perfume on me
let me and you mean while you're covered
with hundreds of dangerous chemicals are
destroying
like the earth the environment right
and so anyway we weren't our regular
diets aren't prepared for that
our regular diets are prepared for the
next onslaught of chemicals being
you know churned out of a chemical
factory put in perfumes and colognes
put in air fresheners put in scented
candles
you won't see a scented candy you just
see scented candles say fragrance
fragrance beeswax yeah you'll see some
other stuff in there but you won't see
what the 100 chemicals are in the
fragrance
so regular diet doesn't take care of
that i'm sorry
the regular diet doesn't take care of
that
the regular diet does not cover the
onslaught of poisons and chemicals and
everything else you see how it works you
guys so important to know right
yeah sad that people make millions
dollars poisoning people
healthy liz they do they do it's it's
incredible really
so anyway so that's just some
information today that look you guys
lysine is something i take every day too
there's a vegan epa i take right from
vimergy it's the only one i trust i
won't take one
if they actually didn't have this i
would never take an epa dha really
anymore just none of them are up to snub
to compare to this now
and then the curcumin i take every
single day as well so i take that one of
emergency curcumin right
so this is all the stuff i do and what
do i do for dosages of curcumin
every single day i'll take four capsules
four capsules are curcumin every day
that's what i do
look don't like as i said before i gave
you kind of a little disclaimer don't
get overwhelmed at what i
take i'm under immense pressure enormous
enormous stress
i'm putting out probably the the most
comprehensive book i've ever put out
in history in my history and in the
history of natural medicine
and conventional medicine too so you
know i'm getting working on that
and i got a lot of their stuff doing so
i inputs my own personal life stuff
which is you know
stuff that happens in all of our lives
that you know you can't avoid that's
like
just life right so with all of that
meaning like every day you wake up and
you have to do
your chores and everything else right so
the bottom line is
uh don't get overwhelmed at how i take
my supplements how i do it but i do the
lemon shots lemon balm
shots i do enough b12 it's critical
right there i do the golden seal
i do the wild blueberry shots every
single day
shopwymans.com this is all vemorgy.com
the supplements here
you get your you know traditional
medicinals to find them
in the store right but i do a lot of tea
like i said you guys
showed you that so this is this is a big
part of it i do
like i said the heavy metal detox goes
in here a lot of times
you know but i also have the cilantro on
the same day i have the dolson the same
day
and i have the in the wild blueberry
shot so i'm getting that a lot if i
can't make the smoothie one day
there's that and the vitamin c
i take a lot i'll sometimes i'll take 10
capsules
three times a day of the microc
especially if i'm concerned about being
exposed concerned about anything like
that if i feel like i've pushed myself
to a limit
the less sleep i get by working harder
say i'll only give myself three hours of
sleep
like last night i only gave myself three
and a half hours of sleep right
so my three and a half hours of sleep
i'm like i better take more vitamin c so
i took
10 capsules of vitamin c is what i did
the microc the best one there is that's
the best seed there is anyway
guys i'm heading off to ig i think we
covered
a good portion of what i take in a day
and but we're going to be doing another
live on immune system so maybe
in like a couple days or something like
that we'll do an immune system one then
we're gonna do or a baseline one what's
a good baseline because this is
everything i take in a day
but what's a good baseline for someone
you know like
what's the definite baseline for
somebody and they can work from there
so that'll probably be the next
you guys i am heading off to instagram
i'm turning on tick tock back on i'm
turning clubhouse back on
selena says love your lives i'm honored
thank you for being here
yoroshini good to see you by the way
ichoda good to see you guys
she good to see you natasha good to see
you
guys you're amazing yeah
austin glad you're here christine k how
much cilantro do you take anthony i eat
a lot of it
i eat two bunches a day minimum for me
that's what i do is
two whole washed bunches of cilantro a
day
that's what i eat throughout the course
of the day i eat it as leafy green
i've done more than that every day but
some days but yeah i'll do up the two
bunches one bunch for sure
i'll get in me a day so that's really
cool any questions on foods i'll tell
you i need to
tell you anything about that yeah ashley
kevin
monica michelle l on tick tock
farah good to see you glad you guys are
coming on
and checking out the lives all right you
guys i'm i'm gonna head off to ig in a
little while
and um tick tock i'm turning you back on
clubhouse i'm turning you guys back on
love you guys and take care