[Music]
tech problems left and right
we're talking about migraines today um
right out of here the new edition
medical medium talking about migraines
and we're talking about celery juice
juicing celery the power it has how it
can heal people
and it's you have to know that
there's something special about celery
that's not in
other herbs and i said herb
yeah everybody thinks it's a veggie a
vegetable
it's not it's a powerful herb it's
herbal medicine
when you juice it you really do heal
important to know and why do you heal i
want to talk about that a little bit i'm
seeing you guys all come on
yeah okay i'm glad you guys are coming
on i could see you i couldn't see
anybody or anything so i'm glad we're
we're together now this is perfect
um but the information about migraines
is really powerful so if you don't have
migraines you still want to stick around
because it does cover other aspects of
health it's important to know
and i'm going to read a couple of
different little things plus we're going
to use some celery
talk about the power it has so let's
let's do that you know um
i wonder i want to answer questions too
that's why i'm here
celery juice gives me elena celery juice
gives me a horrible
d horrific detox symptoms headaches
um any advice i mean you can do
little amounts you can start out with
two ounces i mean that's what i can do
you know less that i would do like if i
had that kind of something else going on
but what else are you doing what else is
happening
as well so kind of i want you to be your
own detective and i want that for
everybody i want them
to everybody to be their own detective
on something like that
um do you have nutritional yeast in your
diet do you have eggs in your diet and
you probably don't have any of that
right do you have caffeine in your diet
you have vinegar in your diet
um do you have things like that going on
natural flavors in your diet
so those things you got to make sure
aren't happening right there
and um and so another thing too
is celery juice kills off pathogens so
it kills off
bugs that sit inside the liver that's
one thing i'm going to talk about now
how celery juice destroys pathogens
destroys viruses bacteria destroys
destroys yeast mold fungus
and gets another body and some people
they'll have they'll have
all kinds of stuff inside their gut all
kinds of microorganisms that are not
good e coli they'll have staff they'll
have c diff
lily blue says i have no more migraines
after drinking celery juice that's
why i'm juicing celery today not because
i have a migraine but i'm juicing celery
because i'm talking about the migraine
chapter in the new edition medical
medium new edition secrets behind
chronic industry illness and how to
finally healed revised and expanded
i'm gonna read the migraine chapter
so um elena i know you're talking about
how you feel like you get these detox
reactions
one thing you can do is just two ounces
two ounces
and that's something that i would do if
that was happening to me and then i
would work my way back up work my way
back up but i would make sure it wasn't
eating any milk cheese butter
dairy eggs gluten boom all gone
milk cheese butter eggs dairy gluten all
gone
no nutritional yeast no vinegars gone i
would lower my fats down a little bit
gone bring those down
then i would see what's happening now so
that's just that's just something i
would do
um paula no more headaches after celery
juice
i mean what it does for migraines what
it does for headaches has been like a
miracle for people it's been incredible
it helps severe colitis katrina it helps
with severe colitis no caffeine no dairy
no eggs amazing
so i got this amazing celery right now
look at this look at these sticks
incredible sticks right now i mean i'm
so happy when it's like this
big and juicy look at this celery stick
right here so this
is one of the most powerful healing
tools in the world right now i'm gonna
talk about why uh elena
hubert the new edition is so good you
guys full of amazing information the new
edition
is is a powerful book it's so packed
with information and details it's really
exciting
so you know i'll give you a little
rundown on the book if you guys
haven't looked at it okay i got the adhd
the autism that i did the other day the
talk on that i got the chapters in here
the migraine chapter the shingles
chapter like trigeminal neuralgia
sciatic
pain bell's palsy talk about chronic
fatigue syndrome fibromyalgia
talk about multiple sclerosis
epstein-barr lupus
these are just a few things that are in
this book
it's really a powerful book altogether
diabetes hypoglycemia adrenal fatigue
chapter tinnitus vertigo body pain
neurological symptoms of all kinds
um gut health issues candida fruit fear
i mean
seriously it's so packed it's you can't
lose
with this book r.a rheumatoid
arthritis frozen shoulder from shingles
epstein bar so um i'm gonna i'm gonna
choose celery juice and a celery in a
couple of minutes
and i see you want me to do a gardening
book
that would be cool someday wouldn't it
that would be awesome
actually yeah what's the best juicer i
saw the question this is the mm-900
hds it's the best juicer for celery
it's a celery juicer model from
omegajuicers.com
and um lorraine l says i really i rarely
if ever get headaches
uh two these days juicing celery 18
months now incredible i'm so proud of
you really am
so so proud of you um but the mm-900 hds
so it's not just any omega
juicer this is the mm 900 hds i licensed
my name
uh to the company so they can use it i
endorse the company it's such a great
company
and so yeah so uh
great juicer if you guys and i'm going
to show you how it works anyway but i
want to talk about the power celery
juice has
what it's doing i know it's doing so
much for you guys but why
is it helping why is it clearing up
migraines how come it's helping with so
many issues
like what does it do i don't talk about
that so much
i just say hey get your celery juice in
you better get your celery juice in you
um and you know it's not just celery
juice
you know even though celery juice is one
medical medium tool
but why is that tool so powerful just as
i was gonna go into detail about the
power it has and why it's so powerful i
think
it's important to know really because i
i kind of brush by it a lot
and it's easy to kind of just be like oh
my god celery juice okay and i and i
brush by it and i don't talk
about the power it holds and the details
and that
um simply some simple healing
uh i did but then got too much detox
doing that every day so i did 16 ounces
um every other day and worked my way up
so that's to elena that's that's
incredible
that's actually a perfect idea and it
really does work
so great so great just reading the
comments
thanks thanks for being with with me you
guys today
okay i'm in the migraine section on the
new edition
right here i'm going to read a little
bit so let's go
a large part of the global population
suffers from migraines or recurring
headaches of various types so
basically almost everybody gets
headaches
and a lot of people are suffering from
all kinds of migraines
some people experience migraines in the
back of the head if you guys ever
experience it from the back of your head
you know a lot of people get the
migraines and they get it back here they
get
the migraine right here and they get it
right here and it's at the bottom
of the skull and that's really difficult
for so many people that's one place some
people get it
up here in the back of the head right
here some people get it um
you know in all kinds of different spots
um
elena's see
looking at the different so you guys
okay
here's let's keep on going some people
experience migraines in the back of the
head
some on top of the head some at the
temples people get the migraines here on
the temple
get it here and here right
okay and some in the eyes some people
get the migraines in the eyes do you
guys get the migraines in the eyes
right the whole bit you can get them
underneath your eyes you get them above
your forehead
so there's different variations
migraines can also be experienced
as intense pulsing or throbbing focusing
on one side with the pulsing and the
throbbing or a migraine can be felt
like it takes over the person's entire
head and neck
migraine can be the entire head it's
encompassing
top of the head okay front of the head
all of it
um so i just saw somebody say
i get migraines so the comment go up all
in the above
so the majority of migraine sufferers
are women
although anyone can be struck with
migraines at any age even children
migraines can make
life very difficult to navigate right so
let's keep on going you guys i'm in the
migraine section of new edition
glad you guys are here and wellness
island says love celery juice incredible
because i'm juicing some in a little bit
those familia those familiar with
migraines know well
that the pain may be accompanied by
extreme sensitivity to light
you guys get the light sensitivities
with your migraines did you know anybody
even the sinus infections and the light
sensitivity to that
uh gianna says i used to get a ton of
headaches and haven't had one since
drinking celery juice over a year now
you know the celery juice is like the
ultimate
migraine weapon you know it's the
migraine slayer celery juice it's really
it's mind-blowing think about that right
before the whole celery juice thing and
before
um before i reached enough people
out there in the world people just lived
with their headaches uh annealia
i had headaches for years all the time
now i'm on mm protocol since 2019 and i
almost don't have headaches anymore
um anilia you know what happened with so
many people all these years is
the chronic illness i don't know if you
guys i don't know
if you guys are old enough for this but
the chronic illness world was the world
of no one got better
that's it you were chronically sick with
something whether it's migraines aches
and pains fibro
neurological symptoms and you stayed
sick and lyme disease whatever it was
you stayed sick
and what happened was all these years
people who came to me when i was
actually doing the work one-on-one all
those years would get the answers
and everybody would say write a book
write a book write a book they'd get the
answers and they would get better
and everybody would even talk about
including doctors and practitioners
people i knew all through the years that
the world of chronic illness was no one
got better
and that's it that's you just stayed
sick and you tried things and if a
doctor got someone better with the
chronic illness
one person a year was a miracle back
then and so the medical medium
information kind of blew the roof
off of everybody being sick and
this is this great opportunity for
people to heal celery juice was one of
those
powerful tools that moved people forward
and got them better
and so the medical beam community
actually is the community that people
heal in and then the other communities
started taking cues they started taking
little pieces of it like
they take the celery juice and they try
not to talk about it too much because
medical medium
or they because they want their
community to you know shine or whatever
it is and they
and they take the little tidbits that
medical medium was teaching all these
years
third person right there teaching all
these years going back for decades and
decades
and it's really amazing how far we've
come because of mm info
um fact i know everybody's like fact
fact checking yeah fact
fact uh fact that science research
are taking information on adhd and
autism from here and now
uh releasing studies from the post
this published material and including
all kinds of other information
more and more stuff comes out every day
from science and research that
is literally straight taken out of the
medical medium book
out of his book anyway so the medical
medium communities are healing
celery juice is one of these migraines
are a thing of the past for a lot of
people
for a lot of people think of the past
um so those familiar with migraines know
well that the pain may be accompanied by
extreme sensitivity to light sound i
told you guys where sound just can knock
you on your butt
or smell my god smell this fragrances
okay air fresheners
what a migraine trigger air fresheners
scented candles
colognes perfumes the ultimate migraine
trigger is like you go into a store
you're already sensitive with migraines
you're already like on the edge of a
migraine if you live with migraines
and you have to go into like the post
office or something into the store and
you
you open the door and you go in there
and all of a sudden it's air fresheners
or some cologne and you're breathing it
in
and you're standing there and then you
feel the migraine coming on and you feel
it coming on and by the time you're done
in that store or that appointment
or wherever you are dental appointment
whatever it is and you're sick you're
just so saturated with somebody's
cologne
perfume somebody's laundry detergent
that by the time you hop in your car and
you're about to go home you're so sick
with a migraine
your teeth hurt your face hurts your
head hurts and you just gotta get home
can't tell you how many people go
through that and it's terrible really
um blurry vision is something that
happens with migraines flashes of light
look
what i really like about the medical
medium new edition
okay you don't have to have a migraine
or be a migraine sufferer to get
information from this book it's so
packed like
just this is an example right here okay
flashes of light
there's people without migraines with
flashes of light but that's you know
neurological symptoms medical medium
information helps
katrina says had migraines for nearly 40
years whoa
that's really rough after one week of
drinking celery juice i
i have no more migraines oh my god
two and a half years in celery juice now
and feeling great thank you anthony
you're welcome
um spirit of compassion did it not me
i'm just the
messenger that gets the crap being
kicked out of them
for getting too many people better
because you're not
allowed to actually get people better
you can talk
about it getting people better the
communities can talk about it everybody
can stay sick
doctors can talk about but when you
start getting millions better around the
world
it's attention you don't want because
that's against
the rules baby against the rules they
want people sick
they want them to stay sick they don't
want celery juice changing the world
that's why the media wasn't kind to me
over and over and over again with celery
juice
and other stuff okay so look if you got
flashes of light you got nausea you got
vomiting
you know difficult speaking these are
all things that
which is incredible about medical medium
information lightheadedness
fainting spells these are all symptoms
neurological symptoms people get
that have gotten better they've gotten
better
um so anyway a couple hour okay so some
people are
this mystery illness can be debilitating
right we all know that you guys making
it difficult to maintain a job or enjoy
a social
life people with migraines often feel
that they have to schedule their lives
around their headaches did you have to
do that
can i ask you guys a question did you
have to ever do that where you schedule
your life around the migraine like i
don't think i'm going to have one today
but i might have one
today wait a minute i mean is it is the
migraine gonna hit me later
is the migraine gonna be a problem i
can't do anything today or is it gonna
come tomorrow
so whether meetings or appointments or
lunch with friends will be ruined by
migraine
so okay anyway um
you guys i gotta let you in on something
i got a podcast episode coming
and it's this week and it's
a mind blower okay subscribe to medical
medium podcast at apple podcast so you
get notified
um if you want if you listen to the
podcast on another platform
it won't be all of it it'll be censored
so medical mean podcast at apple podcast
is where you want to go
just giving you the 4-1-1 the podcast
episode is coming out
it's coming out there it is right there
it's what it looks like sorry you guys
it's coming out this week okay
that's when it's coming out and it's
about blood draw you know how i've been
talking about blood draw
right you guys know how i've been
talking all about that about how serious
it is
about how it it depletes our immune
system how it removes our immune system
well this is not for the faint of heart
this episode is mind-blowing with
information of how to protect yourself
before you get a blood draw blood test
right how to protect yourself after you
get a blood test
what to do what to look out for what to
ask your doctor
so the episode coming out at medical
media podcast at apple podcast is going
to blow your mind
if you guys know the medical medium
podcast already the 17 recent episodes i
did they're docu series style so this is
a docu-series style episode
it's not coffee talk and then
worthless later okay because that's what
podcast episodes are
most podcast episodes out there they're
coffee talk with a bunch of people
coming on you might grab a little tidbit
you get entertained a little bit
advertisers are on there commercials are
on there and then it's just
a throwaway well medical media podcast
at apple podcast is free
it's a docu-series uh
in the real world in the real world
this episode um it should cost
people money to listen to because it's
literally a docu-series filled with
information
um but i want it for free with no
advertisers okay in your way
no advertisers in your way subscribe so
you don't miss it subscribe to medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast
don't miss the episode coming up and
share the heck out of it
to help others you're not going to help
me sharing it because there's no
advertisers on it so i'm not going to
make a penny
but doesn't matter it's not why i'm
doing it so share the episode
with everybody and any share it with
dogs and cats
you know send it to dogs dogs and cats
send it to your dog
your dog has your dog has his own phone
her own phone right
your cats have their own phone right
because everybody's got phones now
just text a link to your doggy to your
kitty
text a link to your parrot or your
parakeet right they got a phone too
right
text the link to everybody that you know
all right
i didn't have my celery juice yet today
um celery did you stop the bad migraines
of a sick friend
incredible
ellen incredible that's the best news
ever
just saw lou and l she's here too um
michelle ells here wendy burgess gives
me the thumb up
okay guys stop reading about migraines
right now
this is a complex mystery illness
migraines are a mystery illness
it's a mystery to medical research and
science unless you got
a brain tumor if you got a brain tumor
that still might not be causing the
migraine in a lot of cases
people they can walk around with a tumor
in their brain
okay and not have migraines because
people do they walk around with tumors
in their brain with no migraines
migraines are a mystery uh melanie my
migraine started 14 years ago after i
had my two kids
i started mm protocol celery juice etc
about eight months ago
and have not had a migraine since
melanie
incredible that matters
it matters dr faun md
great medical doctor great great if i
had a health condition or a health
problem or a health symptom
if i ever get one down the road god
willing i don't but if i ever get one
down the road
right um i'm calling dr font
uh well first i gotta ask spirit of
compassion and if i need a doctor for
some reason i need him to do something
for me boom it's dr font
uh marion i'll send a link to my pet
cockroach
hey look you know what did you see how
many cockroaches i got on tick tock
these days they're everywhere
everywhere on tick tock um
i've been listening to the fruit fear
podcast again today
nancy really lunch boxes to school are
full of fruit today
lunch boxes to school are filled with
fruit today amazing proud of you
okay all right you guys i'm a little
silly today all right so just bear with
me
valerie said tic toc okay hey
come on i gotta snap out of this i gotta
stop fooling around i'm actually fooling
around today i feel bad
i feel like i'm not taking things
serious um
for you guys the combination of issues
that trigger it
into are different for each person
combination of triggers
triggers for your migraines they range
differently you guys different triggers
different migraines people have
different problems inside their body
different toxins different issues of all
kinds so i'm going to talk about that
for a minute
um doctors try to treat migraines with
drug cocktails try this benzodiazepine
here
that might help try this antidepressant
the present that might help
try this anti-anxiety med that might
help try this
anti-inflammatory that could help
let's try a combination of all of it
let's try this
you know serotonin inhibitor
anyway let's try this biologic
whatever okay people just they get
thrown all these cocktails because the
migraines get so bad so your doctor's
throwing all this stuff
okay if one group of drugs doesn't work
your doctor will put you on another and
another
until you start to experience some
symptom relief if you
do however side effects of the drugs can
create entirely new problems
and they do benzodiazepines you've got a
whole another host of crap going down
all bunch of problems right um
plus they might work only temporarily
in some cases the body can develop
resistance to a drug over time
yet weaning yourself off the medication
can trigger migraines too
weaning off the medication can trigger
migraines too if you guys just came on
here
i got to take things seriously i'm just
i'm clowning around too much today
it's been like that all day sunny valley
a friend of mine got rid of migraines of
mm info
it means everything that's what i do i
go to bed at night i get ready to go to
bed at night i've
tucked myself in already and i think
about
all the happy people that healed got
their lives back
okay got their children's lives back got
their grandparents lives back
you know and they're recovering they're
getting better
and i i fill my my thoughts with all
the beautiful healing stories from
around the world because you guys are
getting your lives back
and i say to myself let's keep on doing
it because that's what i'm here
for you guys i'm live on youtube live on
facebook right now just so you know
claudia draper i had intense migraines
even before i was four years old and for
my whole life until celery started to
bring them down whoa love celery juice
from my tummy too incredible
incredible that's so wonderful really is
um okay let's read a little bit more you
guys
let's go let's go let's do let's do it
migraine triggers okay medical
communities don't know what causes most
migraines
they don't it's a mystery see
medical research and science doesn't
know they'll take the information
from this book though it's coming see
they take the information from this book
that the science research does
right and then all the doctors
practitioners take a little bit of the
information from the books too that's
out there but it's all published here
first
right um gianna
anthony i did your 20-day cleanse uh
but up leveled it by doing three
back-to-back rounds of the advanced 369
whoa i feel incredible
thank you so much healing my acne and
eye floaters slowly
heal those eye floaters they take a
little time because those are
neurotoxins right the eye floaters you
know about that
neurotoxins do that so you're cleaning
it up getting it better
all right medical communities don't know
what causes most migraines that's in
part why they have a haphazard approach
to treating them
haphazard medical communities are
haphazardous so far the big theory is
that a neuropeptide released in the
trigeminal system
cranial nerves results in head pain for
people particularly sensitive to the
compound
that would be great if that theory was
real
but that's a theory and that's all they
got did you hear that you guys that's
all they have
they think it's a theory by the way the
big theory
that's a theory they don't have any
thoughts or answers i mean they don't
have any facts it's a theory no study
shows it
the big theory is that a neuropeptide
released in the trigeminal system
results in a headache that's the theory
they've never seen that neuropeptide
doesn't exist but some brainiac
person from some institute or some
whatever
came up with the thought that that might
be it and
that's all they got billions of dollars
in research that's all they got but i
forgot that's right
they just care about the next matcha tea
study right
they don't care about all the migraine
sufferers and people literally
losing their lives over migraines or
living a life that's just
you know really really hard they just
want that next matcha tea
discovery of an antioxidant that does
nothing
so that people will get more addicted to
caffeine more and more and more
all right the sarcasm is a little
out there right today so far okay we got
that
all right let's keep on going other
theories include that it's all in your
gut
oh my god if i hear that one more time
you guys if i hear that one more time
it's all in your gut
you guys have to hear the medical meme
podcast that i'm putting out this week
you guys
have to listen to that podcast i told
you share with your cats and dogs they
got phones now right
you guys
pet turtles have iphones now i heard
i mean they do they're watching like
youtube's on
on their iphones all right listen and
they're androids
for real i'm telling you right now okay
um you got to hear the episode coming up
this week set your notifications go to
medical me and podcast at apple podcast
please and you will definitely
be mind blown but forewarning for
warning
it's not for the faint of heart i can
promise you that
it's not for the faint of heart so if
you're it's a little spooky ground don't
listen to it
i'm telling you not to listen to the
medical media podcast episode coming out
this week
don't listen if you've got the faint of
heart thing going on
it will scare the chibis out of you but
also help you too
and help save a life and save yours
jacqueline
you can go on his website and to podcast
and to podcast if you don't have an
iphone right
true if you have an iphone search
podcast in your phone and look up
medical medium it's the
zero zero three episode 2020.
okay guys let's get a little bit other
theories
include all in your gut that's all i
hear
all in your gut great one we don't know
why
and you're sick conventional medicine
alternative medicine now but it's all in
your gut
oh it's the microorganism theory first
of all the microorganism thing came from
medical meetings worked for 35 years
and they took it they took it they took
it i lectured about it taught stores
about it like health food stores all
around the country
i taught about lecture circuits i taught
about in churches
i was in church basements in front of
500 700 800
000 people all through the 1990s
and teaching about microorganisms and
everything and then all of a sudden
years later oh
no it's microorganisms it's all in your
gut we don't see those microorganisms
really we don't know what they do we
don't know anything but your migraines
are from your gut
everything's from your gut now like what
what a what what a ridiculous you know
statement really it's not that's not an
answer
it's not an answer because people can
hear that
take all the probiotics and gut health
products they want their migraines to be
killing them you know
flashes in the eyes migraines in the
back of their head
temples killing them can't function
can't even speak or talk but no it's all
in your gut i mean it's not an
answer oh my doctor was injecting botox
into my skull to stop my migraines i
didn't even talk about that
meaning like i know i've seen that out
there sick
right yeah sick right 20 years of
debilitating migraines you have healed
me
so that's what they do they have they
inject botox in the back
of people's skulls the temples it's so
sad i'm proud of you i'll let you know
i'm proud of you
proud of you proud of you for real okay
proud of you really am alright so
all right let's go a little bit more
there's more stuff to go so uh
so and with women they usually just say
it's hormones that's another thing so
i'm reading the book right now medical
medium new edition of just got on here
and they'll just think it's hormones
that's what they'll think it's that's
just everything's hormones that's your
hormones you're sick well that's your
hormones
you're a woman you're it's your hormones
that's why you're sick you don't feel
good
it's your hormones whoa you're you got
depression that's your hormones what you
got anxiety
it's your hormones right because that's
what it is um you got chronic fatigue
syndrome it's your hormones
that's what it is it's like hormones
hormones and hormone playing that blame
that was since 1950 and that that was
really difficult on so many women um
so yeah anyway okay
in fact it's often not just one thing
but a combination of issues that trigger
a migraine it's a combination of issues
for so many people that trigger a
migraine below
i'll lay out the most common triggers
read through the descriptions
and do your best to identify the ones
that apply to you i
might read a couple right here okay i'm
reading out a new edition if you guys
want to know
also be aware that you shouldn't stop
looking after you identify a single
cause migraines often result from a
cluster of causes two
three four collectively act as a trigger
cologne's perfumes air fresheners
scented candles you guys if you guys are
dealing with any problems
beyond migraines those are triggers
major
major triggers keep that in mind
all right if you're not getting enough
sleep that's something
if you're under chronic stress something
but otherwise you're healthy you
probably won't get migraines but if you
also have toxic heavy metal exposure
such as mercury aluminum
and on top of that you're eating eggs
and dairy products
mucous forms because of the epstein-barr
virus and streptococcus bacteria
this can lead to a migraine right there
on its own
okay so i'm just in this a little bit
you guys i'm going to juice a little
celery we're still reading out of the
migraine section
just a little celery just read and talk
about triggers in a second so
let's go guys want to know it's the
mm-900
hds this is the my favorite juicer
did you know what i was using the other
day i didn't put the thing underneath it
now i'm making sure i'm doing it
the link for the book medical medium new
edition is in the description
you'll be mind blown when you read that
book
okay make sure it's the new edition
to revise and expand it i'm gonna juice
a little celery
talk about power of celery for a little
bit why is it getting your migraines
better
why how is it possible that it gets your
migraines better
how's it possible it gets anything
better first of all it's herbal medicine
and you're able to drink a large
quantity of this herbal medicine
that's one benefit all on its own
this herbal medicine doesn't have
alkaloids
that stop you from drinking a lot of it
because herbal medicine
is really a god-given gift if you
believe in god if you believe in the
light it's a light given gift if you
believe in the universe it's a universe
given gift
if you just believe in the rock we're
floating on and you think there's
nothing to believe in then it's the rock
you're floating on given gift
[Music]
pretty incredible celery juice is
life-changing
simply simple healing thank you for
being on here
i'm honored you're here and it really is
life-changing
all right so
[Music]
timmy see different comments here and
brenda's here
candace is here lots of people on today
pretty amazing
[Applause]
you guys did i mentioned the juicer's 50
off right now
it's incredible it's uh megajuicers.com
it's the mm-900 hds the pulp comes out
bone dry i've saved myself
thousands of dollars with this juicer
i'm happy to say
thousands of dollars really because it's
just so much like
it's incredible ashley kibben's here
[Applause]
ashley are you gonna listen to the uh
new podcast episode on blood draw
basically i call it vampirism in the
modern day world of medicine
[Music]
wild greens here celery juice calmer
that calms anxiety
i had it my whole life wila thanks for
being here proud of you i really am
truly
anna fox says ordering the book tomorrow
for sure
you won't be disappointed with that book
don't
get the old one make sure it's the new
edition so let me talk about celery's
for a second
don't add anything to your celery juice
if you want it to work it has to be
straight
celery if you want it to work i'm just
telling you guys
has to be straight celery okay
if you want it to work it's so important
to know
right so important to know gonna get
this stick right these sticks are
crazy big this is the biggest sticks
i've seen in a long time
don't add water don't add ice
dilutes the sodium cluster salt that is
saving everybody's butt because the
sodium cluster salt
actually destroys pathogens so what
everybody does is they have some gluten
and they feed pathogen
they have gluten they feed the pathogens
they have eggs
they feed the pathogens they spray
perfume on themselves which is toxic
heavy metals which feeds the pathogens
and everybody's just feeding their
pathogens and then what happens is when
you do your celery juice you're killing
off your packages
see how that works
ruth moore following mm protocols healed
my hashimoto's
ashimoto's thyroiditis you know what's
really crazy about hashimoto's
all these years all it means is just
inflamed thyroid nobody knows why
science research has a theory that your
body's attacking
your thyroid your body's immune system
is attacking your thyroid
wrong it's just a theory never they
never saw it they never proved it
theory it's not the immune system
attacking the thyroid it's epstein-barr
virus which now
they're they're linking up steam bar
they they took it post medical medium
book this new edition
so they're starting to look at that
rob says i am a naturopath a
nutritionist and a big fan honored
truly honored rob seriously doesn't
matter where the information comes from
it works and i have tried it how many
times do you need to do
a liver cleanse to get better
depends on each person are they viral
are we talking about low-grade viruses
are we talking about i've seen bars
shingles hhv-6
cytomegalovirus do they have cold sores
ask your patient do you had get cold
sores
ask them if they ever had a cold sore
that means they got the simplex one
inside their liver so you got to kind of
say well
how many pathogens bugs are inside the
liver that's one thing
too do they have any symptoms are they
fatigued do they have an aches and pains
any neurological symptoms
um that's something to us to consider of
neurological symptoms
and if they have neurological symptoms
then we're dealing with definitely an
epstein-barr we're dealing with probably
one or
two varieties epstein-barr this is how i
help doctors
and and so those are some things right
there do they have metals
if they're sick with a lot of
neurological symptoms then they'll be
viral with metals so they'll have
viruses with metals that means the
epstein bar the shingles is feeding off
of toxic heavy metals
and then releasing the neurotoxin so if
you get people with fibro you get them
with lupus you get them with multiple
sclerosis you get them with cfs
me you're dealing with viruses with
toxic heavy metals mercury being
predominant so then the viruses are
feeding off of mercury then
releasing the neurotoxin that neurotoxin
inflames the nerves are they getting
vertigo tinnitus are they getting
dizziness are they getting focused
concentration brain fog
then you got more metals you got more
you know stuff and then
what kind of food are they on are they
on nutritional yeast are they on the
number one food group in the world
caffeine okay just got to try to chip
them away off that get them off the cafe
are they on the gluten are they on the
eggs these are all the things checked
onto your patients see what they're
doing
and always know your patient might not
be ready and you know this your seasoned
doctor
you you know that your patient might not
be ready to drop the gluten or your
patient might not be ready to
drop the eggs or
drop the dairy or drop the caffeine so
then you're like whoa we got to make
sure you do more of a liver cleanse or
an additional liver cleanse
so these are the variables right there
these are just some of the variables
you know there's a lot more variables to
actually work with that's just some
and the new edition really talks about
the variables and explains it in
in depth um too so that counts as well
um cleans the heel is a great book as
well so let me pour this right here
still going to talk about celery just a
little bit and the power celery juice
has
okay
just gonna someone said he's using a
metal strainer he's using a metal
strainer i saw that the other day
isn't he worried no i do a heavy metal
detox smoothie every single day you
can't avoid metal you're gonna you're
not it's hard to avoid metal everywhere
in your life it's falling out of the sky
metal is falling
out of the sky you're breathing it in
you have to keep that in mind that
you're breathing your metal
in so you know
that that's what people are doing
they're breathing their metals in
that's just some place that's just one
place hilly says i'm so hungry when
i do the cleanses are you getting enough
calories which cleanse are you doing
you're doing the 369 advance you might
get hungry on that one that one's pretty
strict
and but you can increase some of the
different fruits
maybe add a little bit more smoothie as
you kept more calories you're doing the
mono eating cleanse you can increase
more potato in there
you can get more calories to offset
being so hungry
that's an option right there that's what
i would do that's what i would do that's
all
um so i just juiced this beautiful
celery juice right here
so rano sir anthony
can you explain to us what happens
in the body during a migraine attack
yeah definitely all right so um
i wish i had some nerves and hey i got a
brain
got a brain here somewhere so i got this
additional brain see so well those are
metals right there right i got the
little metal
demo you see them they're shining a
little bit okay so here's one reason why
we get migraine attacks
overheating of the brain so you got this
electricity swimming around your brain
swimming around electrical current right
it's running through synapsis
it's uh it's riding on neurons
electrical currents
and what happens is when you get toxic
heavy metal issues
that's a big one a big one for migraines
and i'll talk about it in the book right
there
your brain overheats because the
electricity is ricocheting off a metal
it's riding on metal
it's it's it's being interfered with so
electricity running through
your neurons neurotransmitters start to
burn out when metals are in there
because you're overheating so it's a
constant overheating in the brain so the
migraines come on easy just thoughts can
bring on migrants just
because if it takes electricity to think
and then if you're under stress
it takes that then you're actually
really pumping that electricity and if
you ever anybody ever gets angry if you
ever get
angry or upset you get hot headed right
get the hot headed
you know when you blow a cork in your
hot headed no there's a tremendous
amount of heat generated
electricity and if you got them if you
got the the metals
you don't even have to get hot-headed
you don't even have to get
angry to get the migraines i mean it can
happen
just from the mercury just from the
aluminum deposits to the mercury
aluminum different parts of the brain
that's just on the midline canal i mean
just putting them in different spots
right here
so you know but yeah perfumes colognes
is a great trigger perfumes and clones
is a toxic it's basically toxic waste
so perfumes and clones after
shaves all of that are triggers
because they're chemical poisons
okay i'm going to read a couple of the
triggers right here that's just i just
given you one
variety one reason another thing is if
you have a viral headache
like the epstein-barr headaches or the
shingles headaches that's the other one
too
so you've got all these cranial nerves
okay
running across the face you got all
these cranial nerves that's another
thing too
so you got these cranial nerves got the
trigeminal nerve right you got the
facial nerve so you've got these cranial
nerves cranial nerves get
lit up by neurotoxin so if you're
somebody that deals with simplex one and
you get a cold sore once a year
that virus sits inside the trigeminal
nerve um
and it sits inside cranial nerves so
you'll end up getting headaches from
that virus you can also have shingles
the neurotoxin from shingles
creates all kinds of head pain
periodically all through somebody's life
in migraines
um epstein-barr can release a lot of
neurotoxins those neurotoxins inflame
nerves too and they inflame cranial
nerves and that's another reason why you
get headaches i'm just giving you as
many
different migraines and i already told
you guys about the simplexes right
right so uh the usual suspects right
are concussion meningitis
stroke those are suspects so it's like
well if you had a stroke
and then you get headaches after a
stroke doctor's gonna be like whoa you
got your headaches because you're
post-stroke
right if you have meningitis in the
moment and you have a headache because
you have meningitis
doctors gonna be like well your
meningitis is actually giving you the
headaches right usual suspects that are
obvious
concussion you bang your head get into
an accident you're riding your bicycle
you fall off your bicycle you bang your
head you bang your head how many people
bang their head
going into their car right like opening
the car door and banging it
on the door jam well i banged my head
enough times on the door jambs of cars
where i
jump in or something and you bang your
head and you're just like oh my god what
did i just do
um renee i listened to the chemtrail
podcast blew my mind
renee renee um
i'm releasing the blood draw podcast
i put it in the category of the
chemtrail podcast
because it is not for the faint of heart
so if your mind was blown
uh and you were okay with the chemtrail
podcast like you're not like you're okay
you're strong you can get through that
podcast episode
then make sure you got your notification
on
this week i'm releasing the blood draw
podcast episode
share it with every single body you know
everybody you know okay
you've got a pet turtle send the link to
your pet turtle's iphone
okay we're in the trigger still um
tia transient ischemic attack ischemic
attacks are actually
you know that could give you a migraine
if you're having that blood
vessel break or that blood vessel
um tiny ischemic stroke right um
brain aneurysm this is these are just
obvious migraine stuff but this is the
obvious stuff right
brain tumor obvious but i told you
people can have brain tumors and not
have uh the migraine brain cyst
microcyst that can do it repeated
cervical nerves okay so here we go
um let's go into a little bit more
there's so many things there's there's
the stress trigger
okay i told you about the overheating
that's one menstrual cycle
trigger so let's read a little bit of
that right there it's going to
many female migraine sufferers notice
that their migraines come on right
before during or after the menstrual
cycle right
i mean that's really common it's like
during the menstrual cycle i got my
migraine coming on i got it coming on
okay this is because when a woman is
menstruating her reproductive system
requires 80
of her body's immune system so here's
how it works when you go into your cycle
of your immune system goes to your
reproductive system 20
is now just what's going on through your
body right to cover the rest of your
body
and when that happens it you you could
be
fending off other things you could be
fending off heavy metal toxicity
epstein-barr strep all these different
things your immune system is now
occupied on menstruation and so
therefore
everything else is fair game now it's
like epstein-barr can creep up and cause
a problem
your strep that causes acne can cause
problems and now you're getting more
acne you get migraines too from all
these things
um and so that's that's this is a this
is the reason for a large
amount a large proportion of women that
are suffering
okay and the book lists all the triggers
this is the medical medium new edition
i'm reading all the triggers right here
i have it i don't know if you guys can
see it see all my post-it notes
all around the triggers okay
so um heavy metals and other
environmental toxic triggers so
perfumes cologne said to candles other
toxins laundry detergents
major trigger right there fabric
softeners
boom major trigger on its own pesticides
herbicides around a building an
apartment building or in
the yard or anything like that that's
another one too
sinus related migraines streptococcus
causes chronic sinusitis
and now you're in this whole thing where
you're getting chronic sinusitis
migraines that's another trigger all in
it so i'm giving you guys
whatever i can here there's so many of
them okay
caffeine caffeine yep
we try to treat our migraines with
caffeine seems to give us some relief
but then that migraine comes back worse
than ever because that's what caffeine
does
it's what goes up must come down what
goes up must come down it's the caffeine
nightmare okay so coffee drinks matcha
tea chocolate cacao and other caffeine
over stimulating and hot and highly
aggressive to the central nervous system
caffeine acts as a neurotoxin that can
trigger migraines
some people claim that chocolate and
other forms of caffeine can help a
migraine because the truth is these
people
are in and out of withdrawal you're in
you're out
got one step and one step out we're
gonna do a little dance
right that's it you're in in you're in
or
and out of withdrawal so you're back and
forth back and forth
that's what's going on there they've
experienced that effect because caffeine
triggers the adrenals to flood the body
with adrenaline which acts as a steroid
for the inflammation that causes
migraine so what you do
you get high in the caffeine and then it
acts as a steroid
because it's triggering your adrenals
your adrenals are flooding all this
epinephrine and now you're getting the
epinephrine effect it's like the bee
stinging treatment right you know the
bee sting treatment
okay that people do that bee stinging
treatment
gives you the ultimate adrenaline high
because you just got stung
by a bee it's not getting you better
it's not going to heal you because the
bee sting treatment can't heal you but
what it does
is it causes your adrenals to flood a
tremendous amount of epinephrine because
you're stung by a bee
that epinephrine is self-steroidal
treatment so you're
treating with self steroids that's what
the bee sting therapy is
it's you're using your own adrenaline to
and that's medical medium information
nobody knows why the bees things work or
band-aid that's the point they don't fix
a disease
condition they band-aid things for the
moment right
and so the bee sting therapy is band-aid
nobody knew why they band-aid
but i've been teaching why they band-aid
for years it's because once you get
stung by the bees so you put the bee in
the cup
you stick don't do this i'm not saying
do this do not do this i'm not
recommending this but you put the b
they put the b in the cup they stick the
beat the cup on their leg
the b kind of swims around in the cup
for a little bit and then it goes down
to the leg and then goes boom and you're
stung
and then your adrenals are flooding
flooding flooding flooding
and now you're being self-treated with
adrenaline
you got a steroid you're being
self-treated see how it works
well same thing with caffeine with
migraines in other conditions
it's self treating that's what you're
doing you're self
treating with adrenaline so i'm gonna
get jacked up and high on caffeine
i'm gonna do it now that everybody keeps
on saying it's good for you i really
feel like i can do it it's freaky
for you know fair game i could do it
free game let's do it
and you're doing all the caffeine and
you're you're feeling like you're
self-treating
and then all that adrenaline is doing
that it's trying to get the inflammation
down and then when that adrenaline wears
off
caffeine wears off boom you're back to
square one
you're in you're out of withdrawal all
right so
a couple of different things there
there's gluten is a trigger eggs are a
trigger
fermented foods are a trigger for
migraines okay book
book covers where to look how to heal
for your protocols what to do for
migraine protocols
all that stuff um anthony charles
hey great name love the name
what helps the personalization and
derealization
i talked about this as toxic heavy
metals sometimes a little bit of
low-grade epstein-barr but mostly toxic
heavy metals
de personalization definitely metals are
in there
honestly if i was dealing with the
depersonalization
i'd be working on getting my metals out
getting my metals out that's what i
would be doing right there
um i would be doing if it was me i'd be
doing the spirulina
the barley grass this is the vimergy
spirulina the vimergy barley grass the
only ones
i trust um and i'm not sponsored
okay that's what i would do ask your
doctor what he would do just
listen to your doctor whatever your
doctor wants to do but this is what i
would do if i had the personalization
i would get the medals out if i had the
personalization
um donna anthony what is
the best way uh for withdrawal from
caffeine
last time i did it my muscles and legs
were screaming at night did you listen
to the podcast coffee matcha tea
chocolate on
medical mean podcasts at apple podcast
donna check it out listen to it okay
ask your doctor if if that's okay for
you the stuff on there
but i i mean if i had the withdrawal
thing going on where i was like whoa i
can't get out of withdrawal
i would i would listen to that podcast
episode take notes
it's an educational docuri style podcast
i try to make it as entertaining as
possible
the podcast episodes there's no
advertisers there's no commercials it's
it's free listening
every time advertisers come my way and
they're saying there's no reason you're
supposed to have advertisers
i say no no no no appetizers for me um
so and and uh celery juice is is is very
helpful all on its own right there it's
one of the healing tools i got the
celery juice right here i just made but
it's there's there's
medical meaning protocols are not just
celery juice just got to know that
medical mean protocols are more than
just celery juice oil this is one of the
healing tools
this is the mm-900 hds 50 off right now
mm-900 hds this is the juicer i use
i told you guys so many times um
so it's it's a powerhouse for making
sure that you're
you're here's what happens right your
pulp comes out dry
and that's what counts when it comes out
dry okay
then you're saving all this money you're
squeezing every last drop out of your
celery that's the mm-900 hds it's the
one i use it's incredible so i just use
the celery with this okay
megajuicers.com it's the celery juicer
it's the only model that does the celery
juice and it does everything else too
yeah that's funny margaret been
educating myself no one
no one putting butter in your coffee
yeah the
butter in your coffee is bad idea it's a
bad idea for so many reasons
i mean look i'm not trying to you know
harp on anybody
out there but i'm just saying that i i
think that that's probably one of the
worst you may as well have the eggs in
the bacon and the toast with it with the
butter and the coffee
and um getting jacked up on caffeine all
on its own is terrible for people just
terrible
anyway not organic celery is okay
so celery that's not organic is okay
so that's what celery that's not organic
is okay
um just try to wash it good the benefits
of non-organic celery
outweighs the bad that's how incredible
it is and you're still going to get
pesticide exposure anyway
you're going to get pesticide herbicide
fungicide exposure all the time
everybody does
they get it on their clothes they get it
on there to get it on their furniture
coming out of the furniture
they get it from you know sprays
floating in the air every day they're
just getting it so
so yeah you want your celery no matter
what okay
and um different farms
you know plus celery i mean they grow
different types of celery different
farms it doesn't always look the same
it's different
the way it grows and everything and it
tastes different so this one happens
tastes really good look at these big
juicy stalks
haven't seen those in a while i've been
stuck with the more the leafy
spindly green kind that's really
astringent still healing
but really astringent so giving you a
little tips on celery on that level
okay they taste different but the leaves
are okay if you don't want to take them
off you don't have to take the leaves
off you can keep them on
so yeah any tips i can give you but but
you guys um
i just want to run one more thing down
about celery juice what it does is it
goes through your intestinal tract right
it starts to clean up old
debris shouldn't be there petrified
proteins attach
the linings rancid fats attach to the
linings of your intestinal walls
it starts to cleanse that stuff out it
goes
up into your liver so i just want to
give you this one quick run down right
here
okay that's your liver right there when
you're drinking your celery
juice okay all right hepatic portal
highway which is your veins going into
your liver
that stem off of your intestinal tract
so here it is so
sending off of your intestinal tract all
right right here so you drink your
celery juice
you know and it's going down going down
now it's going into your intestinal
tract your celery juice okay
it ends up going into these tiny blood
vessels in your
small intestinal tract and it ends up
all connecting to the paddock portal
highway up into your liver
is where it connects up into your liver
and so when it gets up into your liver
that's when the celery juice does its
magic it starts to revitalize the liver
sodium cluster salts start to kill off
epstein-barr shingles other pathogens
streptococcus you name it it starts to
clean it all
up that's one thing it does and guess
what that celery juice
finds itself up boop the duct into the
gallbladder
starts to loosen up some of that sludge
and dissolve it
dissolves gallstones it has a dissolving
gallstone dissolving power that's what
the celery juice has these are just some
of the things it does
and it's killing pathogens as
its happenings pathogens that sit in
people's gallbladders people got strep
in their gallbladders they get strep
infections in there
they get all kinds of other stuff and
it's the
killer of the bugs that's what the
celery juice does
it's the killer of the bugs and that's
why i love it
and it's cleaning up the intestinal
tract getting rid of old debris trapped
in pockets slowly
so when you're on your celery juice year
after year you're really starting to
clean everything out unless you keep on
putting everything bad back in and
that's a whole other story
all right but i talk about in the books
how to work with celery juice all the
different ways guys i'm heading off to
tick tock
and ig i'm gonna make some more celery
juice i'm going to talk about some other
stuff maybe migraines other things too
and medical mean podcast at apple
podcast i'm dropping the bomb
this week it is the blood draw episode
i've been talking about it but the
episode's a whole another game
make sure you subscribe make sure you
hear that medical mean podcast
apple podcast i love you guys i'm going
to tic tac