big news really big news uh
extremely big news i'm excited to
announce the official medical medium
podcast
the first episode is chemtrails the sky
is falling
and it's not for the fan of heart it's
actually
really scary at the same time so
you know i mean if you're i i'm caught
where
i almost don't want you to hear the
episode but yet i want you to hear it so
you can learn and actually spread the
information around
get people to hear the episodes so they
can learn how to protect themselves
but it's really powerful it's a free
resource okay so this medical medium
podcast
on apple podcast that's where you can go
listen to it is on apple podcast
this this official launch of the medical
medium podcast is a free resource
okay no infomercials you're not going to
get infomercial to death
okay it's not going to be like sales
pitch after sales pitch even though i
don't do that anyway
so you know sales pitch after sales
pitch it's not gonna be any of that no
advertising no sponsorships this
this this medical medium podcast is the
real deal
and so i want you guys to check it out
it's on apple podcast that's where you
can find the first
the first episode is chemtrails the sky
is falling
and there's tremendous amounts of
detailed information in there that
no one's ever heard before ever they
haven't heard
it anywhere before it's unique it's
original just like medical medium
information has always been
but if you know something about
chemtrails uh
you're going to find out you really
didn't know hardly anything
at all about it you're going to learn
the truth but here's the thing
it's not like i'm just giving you
regurgitated information
of something that's out there already
that's not it
this is an historical moment i'm
releasing
information no one has ever ever
seen or heard about chemtrails
ever in our history so i tell you about
the story going all the way back how it
works what's really happening
how why our birds are dying in droves
and massive flocks how we're losing all
of our bees
how there's a confusion out there to why
people think we're losing bees they
think we're just losing them all because
of gmo
they think we're losing it all because
of other reasons actually we're losing
our bees
and i talk about why on this chemtrail
episode
you can um you can see the link in the
description
so check it out so you'll see the link
in the description
so you know where to listen to this
podcast it's on it's on apple podcast
that's where you can go and get it
if you don't have like if you don't have
an apple device and you got an android
or a different device
just go to the app store and you know
and get the apple podcast app
that's all that's free just get it you
know get connected to it
and you can hear this this is where the
platform's going to be for this
medical medium official podcast
uncensored
uncensored okay
the episodes to follow are going to be
pretty mind-blowing actually
mind-blowing and it's all unique
advanced
medical health spiritual emotional
information
in each podcast that each episode that's
what it's going to be
so i'll cover a little bit about that
too because medical medium information
has always been about
you know providing information about
pitfalls and about potholes to avoid
so you can protect yourself protect your
family protect your friends
so if you just got on here the first
episode is chemtrails the sky is falling
have you listened to it
have you listened to it yet and i want
to read the comments i got the monitor
with the comments right over here to the
right
um so um but yeah apple podcast is where
it's guaranteed to be
any other platform it might be uploaded
fragmented
you might not have heard the whole
episode but don't know it so keep that
in mind if you're used to listening to
it on a
another platform because it might be
worth
going to where it's really guaranteed to
be apple podcast
and so um so i want to talk a little bit
about this if you've heard this episode
already
so if you heard the episode already let
me know what you think about it
um just you know out you can ask me any
questions about it the whole bit go
ahead
it's perfectly fine and i mean there's
even powerful hidden messages spiritual
messages
inside these episodes on top of it so
you can look out for that
just know that when you listen to this
episode
it's packed with details and information
you might have to listen to it twice
or even more than twice in order to
actually glean and gather
all that information there's so much and
love you guys too patty says love you
anthony love you too
um mm podcasts uh
have been out there no that the mm
podcast in the past that was an old
radio show
so that wasn't the mm official medical
meeting podcast
big difference i'm just letting you know
this is an entirely different situation
if you're used to my old radio shows
those were censored because pretty much
it wasn't my podcast a whole bit
this is the medical medium official
podcast
just tried and true this is it um and
and it's it's exciting the first episode
is chemtrails the sky is falling
um if you're somebody in in your and you
like
being in the world you're in now you
don't want to know about certain things
i would sit that episode out because
that episode chemtrails is just
it's it's scary it's in it's a scary
episode so i'm just
giving you kind of the forewarning a
little kind of forewarning there
um but if you think you can handle it
and handle the truth or handle
the truth but more than that the
information
at you know at its entirety there then
if you feel like you can handle such a
shocker then
a good apple podcast and listen to
medical medium
chemtrails the sky is falling and um
but yeah so so there's so much to talk
about
i'm glad we're here this i'm excited
that we're here you loved it robin says
loved it
with with uh eight explanation points
and um
uh pressing says we love you anthony you
and spirit compassion are amazing
listened to your podcast last night here
in australia
what an eye-opener absolutely loved it
thank you for all that you do and your
amazing enthusiasm to help heal the
world
i'm honored bless your heart truly and
thank you for listening tell other
people
share it tell them where to find it on
apple podcast and share that episode
chemtrails
because thursday i'm releasing another
episode okay
and i'm gonna give you an idea of the
episodes that are coming there's gonna
be episodes on all the different
conditions and symptoms
and it's gonna even be more so than i
ever did on the old radio show
and so with this podcast the medical
medium podcast it's going to be
going to talk about like you know the
eczema psoriasis rosacea vitiligo
hashimoto's thyroiditis lupus ms
diabetes
migraines brain fog anxiety depression
all the different conditions and
symptoms but you guys
check this out check this out i'm also
gonna have episodes
for spiritual emotional growth
soul healing episodes powerful soul
healing episodes really powerful
so that you can heal the soul so you can
heal any ptsd
so you can heal emotional wounds like
old
wounds of betrayal and losses and
you know things that you've gone through
in your life hardships and
so i'm gonna have those powerful
episodes coming up
and you don't want to miss those because
if they're
they're on a level all on their own too
so
medical medium information has always
been about advanced unique original
information it's not like other podcasts
okay
other podcasts they're regurgitating the
same old stuff they're regurgitating
misinformation about health and just
swimming it around swimming
around they have guests come on and it's
all the same stuff unless
they took pieces from medical medium
information for the 35
years of putting out unique information
and then it gets taken not cited back
and then it becomes out
there like that but this is different
medical medium information has always
been about ahead of its time
by decades and even more and what you'll
find
in this podcast is that plus even
more it's going to be to a whole another
level it's going to be unbelievable on
that level
so this episode chemtrails this guy is
falling
really really powerful and it's the
detailed truth in history
about chemtrails not speculation not
theories
the story the legit
real mind-blowing deal okay you're going
to learn why
flocks of birds are dying all over the
planet how they've been dying for
decades however
how no one no one's allowed to tell you
guys this
but they won't tell you that we've lost
half the bird's pot the half birth
half the bird population on the planet
is gone
and they don't let anybody know it's
kind of like
this thing where you you live in it and
you don't know
that it's a fraction of what it was 50
years ago a fraction of what it was 40
years ago people have no idea and where
that's heading
how we're going to lose all our birds
eventually why the bees are leaving
you know the whole bit so it's so
important i talk about why there's
really red tides
i talk about a lot of different powerful
points you really
have to really have to listen to the
episode but at the same time
a little disclaimer meaning if you
you know it's not for the faint of heart
it's not for somebody who's
gets spooked easy um don't listen to
this podcast if that's the case because
it's that
intense it's that scary and but yet
uplifting too
powerfully uplifting and with a powerful
message in it
so and the episodes to follow are always
going to have a powerful spiritual
message in it information like basically
you know a puzzle of information to
glean from and heal from
you know you know please post your
favorite parts so that's the other thing
post your favorite parts on this episode
chemtrails the sky is falling
you know and tag you know at medical
media i mean uh tag at medical medium
medical medium if you're on if you're on
uh instagram
if you're on you know if you're on
facebook then just
you know you know what i mean just um if
you're on youtube
the same thing just do your thing and
it's like it's important to to spread
the information out there
and get that information out there so
people can heal charlotte said thank you
for everything bless your heart
um yeah so the episode i'm launching
thursday's a surprise that's another one
and when you hear about that episode
don't get fooled about the title so much
because when you get into the episode
it's shocking
it's unlike any level i took it to
um justine has said my favorite part is
truth
um you love the entire podcast joanne
your poem at the end was beautiful
so that's from spirit of compassion
joanne i always get i'm always going to
have powerful messages from spirit of
compassion
always in there to help people heal and
and that's going to be subscribe to
medical medium podcast
on apple podcast so that's what you do
to in order to hear the episodes
um that's the platform definitely going
to be on there um
catherine said god bless you in spirit
bless your heart too god bless you too
drinking jackie you're drinking uh
celery juice every single day i'm proud
of you incredible
incredible um so
with this episode i just want to kind of
give you a little quick rundown on this
episode too
is look if there's something in this
episode you really like
and information that you really love or
that's just really
uh shocking and interesting in some way
and you want to share it please share it
share it out there and if you can leave
i don't ask for it
i don't ask for anything i always do
free free free free free
you'll notice on youtube you won't see
advertisements pop on youtube you won't
see that happening
you won't see all those kinds of things
i'm not trying to sit there and
infomercial
you on youtube and and pump all these
things and pump all these things at you
guys
you know like a broken record and all
that i'm always about getting you
information so you can heal but if you
if there's anything you can do for me
i'm not just saying just leave a review
on apple podcast so that people
can find it and then listen so they can
get healing information that can help
their family and their friends and share
it i mean share it that's the bottom
line it's really important
and that would be really helpful i'm not
sponsored i'm
not sponsored by anybody okay so you
know
it's not that the medical meeting
podcast isn't sponsored
i've had people come to me saying wait a
minute you're six time new york times
best number one new york times
best-selling author
okay with uh millions of books around
the planet in
in every country in in in the world
healing people worldwide
you got more people healed with your
information than any other
avenue that's ever happened in medicine
and
um and all of it said and done this
podcast
should be sponsored this podcast should
have big advertisers
this podcast should have all that and no
i said no
maybe someday no not now not now i just
don't want to do that
and i dumped my own money into it okay
and worked hard on it it's really high
quality
and then the information is mind-blowing
i want you guys to have a resource
that you can enjoy but also get
tremendous amounts of powerful
information
so you can heal and uh rc says what's
next
well thursday you'll see thursday you'll
see so make sure you subscribe to the
medical medium podcast on apple podcast
uh please share and sign back
to this podcast cite it back to the
chemtrail episode
so people know where that information
comes from because if you know something
about chemtrails
you'll find out that you don't know
you know yeah you'll know something
about them from the misinformation
and the theories out there but when you
actually hear the truth of what really
happened why these chemtrails are here
what's going on and you learn that
it's a whole different ballpark and that
information will then get saturated out
there it won't get cited back to me
probably eventually
and then it'll be like oh oh the that's
where it comes from out there somewhere
no you'll it originates here like 35
years of medical mean information that
has escaped through
toxic heavy metals talk about that
originates from medical medium
information
lemon water cleansing the body and the
liver cleansing the liver
lemon water that's medical medium
information started 35 years ago
and there's a celery juice same thing
but it's like what it is is
what you'll find in this podcast along
with other stuff
in in you'll find information
decades ahead of what's out there now
and the whole bit so
um charlotte says love the ending you
sound it like an mmm badass that's funny
and um you know it's like it the
the whole thing about this podcast is
i wanted to like this is an uncensored
podcast i told you it's not sponsored
it's uncensored if you want it if you
want it listen to it go to apple podcast
because that's a platform i can ensure
that that's where it's definitely going
to be there upload it it's there
and um the thing about this podcast it's
about empowerment
and i've always been about that that's
what my books are about
that's where all that incredible
information in the book comes from
spirit of compassion in the books like
cleanse the heel that's
saving lives right now by the millions
around the world
and and i just wanted to take it to the
next level for you guys i never
launched my official podcast ever and it
was time it was time the other
the radio shows were the old radio shows
this is the next level
and i will talk about mercury fillings
on a podcast
episode i will i just saw that just now
i will i will i will
so for sure because i think that's
really important
um jennifer be ready to sit on the edge
of your seat it's going to blow you away
awesome thank you for telling people
that so but also
at the same time thank you for warning
them that they're going to be on the
edge of their seat
so i really appreciate that in case
someone doesn't they're they're really
sensitive
and i understand and they might not want
to listen to that because
yeah you know so it could be really
intense on all kinds of levels
so but thank you for thank you for
warning um people with that one i just i
i love you for that and letting them
know too and you just downloaded and
subscribed
gene hey thank you thank you
i appreciate it because then you'll
learn about this you'll be able to
protect yourself tell other people and
all of that you know vivian why do we
keep destroying ourselves the human race
because it's good versus evil and i talk
about that in this podcast and i talk
about that in the other
episodes too in some different ways
because
yeah darkness does want to destroy
people so it's a very horrible thing
it's evil tricking the good
and that's been around for centuries and
centuries and centuries it's been around
since the beginning of the human race
but um but either way it doesn't matter
you'll protect yourself from the whole
bit and we can rise out of the ashes
together and we can heal together
and we can be stronger together valerie
said thank you so much anthony
and the whole bit um you know i'm really
proud of all you guys i know you're
working really hard on everything lemon
water for the win
yeah yeah lemon water
um do you do do you do a podcast about
skin issues that are rare
yes i'm going to i'm going to do
podcasts on skin issues that are rare
a lot of times a lot of skin issues
they're rare
but there is a cause in a sense where
there's a cause of why someone has a
rare skin issue they're just diagnosed
with different names and they don't know
that it's a part of another skin
condition
i'm going to talk about all of that of
course thank you mm
thank you for caring um the books are
free at the library
yeah i mean you can order one too on
amazon uh amazon in the us at 1699
51 off of cleanse the heel book but get
him at the library
give him the library um michelle
michelle
l he has tons of solutions thank you
michelle michelle's out there i
i i always see you out there you're
always fighting for medical medium
information
trying to help people heal and and um
blown away really
and just i can't thank you enough for
the fact that you have so much
compassion and you actually have
patience to tell other people
about medical medium information what
could heal them michelle and
how they can heal and you're always spot
on and
read your comments and stuff just always
spot on it's just like
my god like you know the books um
the whole bit and um you know
alexandra says it's so sad anthony i
worry for my children and grandchildren
so sad what's going to happen in the
future just don't worry about that what
it is
is it you can we can adapt
and i talk about that in the episode we
can adapt i want you to know that
and we can adapt as humans and we can
use foods
as our medicine we can use foods as
tools
and i talk about medical medium
information was never fruits and
vegetables medical medium information
was fruits
leafy greens herbs wild foods
and vegetables and we can use those to
actually adapt
and we can look up at the sky and be
like it's all right if that stuff's
falling down on us
we can still adapt and heal and cleanse
it out of our body so we have tools so
that's the good news
that's the good news um jacqueline says
love the books
yay incredible um have you listened to
the first episode you guys on apple
podcast
uh have you listened to it uh chemtrails
the sky is falling
you don't want to miss that episode or
if you're sensitive
and kind of a little bit of faint of
heart you might want to miss it it's
a little scary and really intense uh
more than a little scary but i but but
either way
um you can listen to it okay and you can
share it with others and the whole bit
if you have
if you don't have an apple device or
something like that and you have a you
know
android or something like that you can
just you know upload the app
go to the apple just go to the um app
store
and just apple podcast app and there you
go boom free
you got it you can make sure you and
then you can subscribe so you're the
first to get notified
so you don't miss an episode because the
episodes are going to come flying out
they are i got one coming out thursday
you don't want to miss it if you
like this chemtrail episode you're going
to like the next one
and just so you know it's going to be a
sprinkle of
all kinds of powerful powerful episodes
it's going to be about symptoms and
conditions
it's going to be about spiritual and
soul rebuilding
okay heal our soul and to heal our heal
our anxiety and depression and
it's going to be about healing from you
know wounds and emotional wounds from
betrayal and losses and hardships
and powerful episodes to help people
through that that's going to be a really
big deal you guys
there's going to be that there and then
there's going to be episodes sprinkled
about
such as like chemtrails and other things
like that it's
going to be controversial medical medium
information has always been
controversial
um powerful information that's coming
out so
and so i'm glad i'm glad you guys yeah
growing inside exactly grow inside
and um but i'm glad you guys are
just you're in it to you know
help others too because you want other
people to heal you want yourself to heal
i know so many of you guys have so much
compassion for others out there so share
share the episode to other people that
you think would like to hear it and
everything and leave a review on apple
podcast
you know and if you can leave a review
there because it is helpful because what
it does
is it helps people know that this is
good
stuff that this is good stuff rhonda
says thank you for the podcast i
listened
that's incredible um so yeah
so if there's if there's you know look
if you listened already to the podcast
you want to ask a question please ask
some questions
i can answer some questions about if you
listen to the chemtrail podcast
and um and
what i talk about in that podcast is
pretty eye-opening
it's it's a shocker if you just got on
here just know it's originally unique
it's not
been out there before so it's a historic
moment right now so when you listen to
that chemtrail disguise following
episode on apple podcast what you'll
notice is
that's historic historic moment that
that information was just released
now so that's really you know a really
exciting moment and
and you'll connect the dots once you're
listening to that episode you'll connect
the dots and you'll be like oh my god
and and it's just it's a whole other
level that's a whole nother level
and i talk about like the polar caps
what's happening with the polar caps
how chemtrails are involved i talk about
that the red tides
how chemtrails involved and i talk about
what are these chemtrails
where is it coming from how is it coming
why is it coming so i talk about all
that too okay
so um kathy said sad we were going to
lose the butterflies
uh yeah it's really a sad situation but
you gotta hear what's happening in that
episode
um yeah and the bottom line is it's
about though empowerment it's about
adapting it's about healing you know i
just know that a lot of you guys want to
know what's happening you don't
you want to know what's going on you
want to know
what is happening around you especially
if you're sick and you're dealing with
chronic illness you're dealing with
symptoms and conditions if you're
dealing with some kind of issue
or some kind of problem or in something
that's impeding your life in some way
and if you are then this is important
because you can protect yourself
you know you can protect yourself and i
talk about how
somebody keeps us busy down here where
we're recycling things and we should
we're recycling our plastic we're
worried about
plastic straws we're worried about all
this stuff plastic bags and all these
things but at the same time we're
looking at the sky and you see all this
crap being dumped on us and i talk all
about that
um ichoda says hey jodah choda's always
like
oh he's doing incredible stuff she's
compassionate she's got patience for
people out there because i see her
commenting
it's such an incredible podcast i
thought i knew about chemtrails
but this filled in the gaps and all of
the details made it to the next level
each other you know it's it's um exactly
because
there just isn't really enough
information or
barely any information on any level out
there in chemtrails and this
this is the eye opener this is this is
this is the package of information that
really is going to set the stage to so
people can
you know go because i think people that
are concerned about chemtrails out there
they want to know more they wish they
knew more well there's here's the chance
now the details it's in the details it's
unlike anything else
so it's in the details so marcy said yes
i want to know always exactly you want
to protect your family
you want to protect your friends you
want to protect your kids you want to
protect everybody absolutely it's always
good to know it's not
it's not it's not something that you
know you you don't want to be in denial
about or not
no or not no so um
you know the link is pinned up on
facebook so you can see the link to
to go and hear the podcast just so you
know
it's in the description so the link is
in the description just once you know
that
and it's in the description of youtube
so at youtube it's in the description of
youtube
so i want you to know that too um
kelly says i have to pray to all
essential angels so you're reading
medical media book one
and that's incredible the angels are
really important
they are important we want to
acknowledge that they're here i'm glad
you believe in angels some people don't
believe in angels and i'm always saying
no
they angels are there and they're doing
things and
i've told a lot of stories that i've
heard from people from
stories they've had encountered and
experienced with angels
i've had one myself a story in my ch and
when i was younger
god bless you too um so
uh anyway if you just got on here i'm
talking about the official launch of the
medical medium podcast it's not the
radio show
it's entirely different than the radio
show
and um it's uncensored it's not
it's not sponsored there's no
advertisements i'm not going to
infomercial you guys to death
nothing like that so and you'll notice
medical medium
doesn't do that i don't do it on youtube
you don't have to go through all these
ads
on youtube i don't sit there trying to
do this and this and have 20 000 links
of all these things
you know i just make sure that you guys
have
options information that's free free
free free free
you know you can get my books at the
library all that so
but but the bottom line is this is
another free resource i dumped money
into it
i've i worked hard on this to make sure
you have guys have this incredible
resource
so you can move your life forward
there's going to be spiritual emotional
soul episodes to help you heal your soul
from emotional wounds there's going to
be symptoms and conditions episodes on
anything from lupus and als and
and ms and just symptoms and
tingles and numbness ringing the ears
floaters in the eyes
alopecia skin conditions pots
uh dysautotonia you know all of them um
so uh what i liked about the podcast is
getting on your body's
team and validating all the hard work
it's doing to try to keep us healthy
incredible incredible um
you know and you know what you that
that's exactly what it is
it's it's a beautiful thing and it's
it's about being you you want to be in
the game with your body
you want to be in the game with your
body your body wants to know you're in
the game
that's free the body wants to know
you're in the game with it
that you know it you know it's working
hard that you know it's fighting for you
your body wants to know
you're in the fight with your body it's
so important and i talk about that in
that episode
it's incredible it's incredible that you
actually you know pick that off because
there's a lot of information in there
and you have to listen to the episode a
couple of times that chemtrails episodes
guys following episode a couple of times
because it's
packed it's jam-packed so glad you
caught that one
um yeah so anyway
the bottom line is that this is a free
resource
to empower you guys give you more tools
to protect yourself and heal
it's highly controversial stuff and a
lot of it's highly controversial it's
really intense
and um and if you're concerned about
someone being in too much shock
listening to this episode you might want
to sit them out
but if you're if you feel like you can
give this share this episode somebody
who's got the skin
because it's it's it's a scary one and
it's really intense
so um but you can listen to the episode
apple podcast and yeah and it's packed
with information just packed about
chemtrails information no one's ever
heard
so anyway um i love you guys i stand
with you
may the angels be by your side when
you're sleeping tonight helping your
body heal
and that's what you do you know when you
go right before you go to bed
tell the angels to be there they'll sit
by your bedside they'll look out for you
and um i stand with you guys and i
believe in you guys you know that
and take one day at a time have
compassion for yourself
know that i care i got your back and
take one day at a time
it can all rise out of the ashes
together and heal and
love you i'll see you next time bye