we're live it's saturday i'm excited you
guys
making a mojito salad
right right there i'm excited about that
it's gonna be fun
i got strawberries right there i got
grapes i got nectarines are you guys
doing nectarines lately oh no
i can't i can't because of oxalic acid
no
you can you can all right because that's
make-believe
we got nectarines we got uh blackberries
raspberries too i'm excited about making
mojito salad right there right out of
the book medical medium new edition
check that out when you get a chance
talking about
b12 deficiencies being depleted
that's an important thing too talking
about immune systems need to be built up
and why
and everybody is on an acid trip
everybody's on acid and they're depleted
we're going to cover that as well
everybody's on acid they're on an acid
trip
big time so we're going to go into that
if you guys want to know
medical medium we're live on facebook
live on youtube live i'm club balls live
on tick tock
glad to be here it's an honor and happy
you guys are in my kitchen
good to see everybody coming on mm-hmm
so let's talk about it a little bit
one of the reasons why i've been doing a
lot of immune system stuff lately is
because people are getting sick left and
right right now
they are getting sick and
the plague is going around and people
are getting sick
it's happening fast so this is kind of
we're heading into
august so we got this whole thing going
on
that people are dealing with right so
we're heading into august pretty soon
and i said it was coming i said it was
coming and in the fall
it's going to be out of control going
into august everybody's getting sick
critical to keep your immune system
strong so as a reminder before i go into
how everybody's on acid and everybody's
taking an acid trip and how everybody's
depleted
what i've been telling friends and
family make sure you
have your zinc i said it before the
plague started
and i'm saying it now so make sure you
have your zinc
and i went over that that's the vimergy
zinc right there
that's the only one i trust
ask your doctor if it's right for you
but i tell my friends and family make
sure you have your golden seal
so i say make sure you have your golden
seal make sure you have your zinc
so i tell my friends and my family
letting you know
right there that's the vimergy stuff
that's the one i take and my friends and
family take
because in victor i m as the mary e r g
y
dot com that's the vimergy the golden
seal
and the zinc make sure you have it
everybody's getting sick in the middle
of the summer
and they're getting sick and it's gonna
get worse
and like i said it's gonna get worse
come to fall
and really bad during the winter um
another great thing to have for the
immune system that's the lemon balm
right there
it's really gentle for people who you
know they even have trouble taking
supplements because like i said to you
guys before
bad supplements give supplements a bad
name
bad supplements give good supplements a
bad name
good to see you guys so that's the lemon
balm yeah whether you're sick or not
have it it's about building up the
immune system really important cold and
flu protocols and cleanse the heal
now i wasn't going to make today about
supps
right i really wasn't going to do that
but people are getting real sick and
they're getting real sick fast right now
out there
just saying you know cleanse the heal
there's a flu flu protocol
cold protocol cold protocol right
and there you go important to know
so another one for keeping the immune
system strong the microc
right there it's what i give friends and
family the microc
so i'm giving everybody a little another
little warning
to make sure and and i know so many
people already chronically sick
chronically ill but when we have these
flus going around so we got the plague
going around right now
and it's been cranking up and cranking
up and cranking up
so what i've been telling friends and
family right
that have been reaching out to me so
what do i do what i do everybody's
getting sick
they're all coughing they're all sick
they're sick where's your microc
where's your zinc right where's your
lemon balm where's your golden seal
we're at least some of the baseline
where are some of the baseline
at least some of them right so that's
important okay
um spirulina is a great one it's a great
defense mechanism keeps the body strong
so if anybody gets hit with that fever
they get hit they get sick right
that's a great one right there okay
magnesium calm the body which is really
important for muscles so they don't
spasm and everything else
so that's another one so basically
good to see you guys coming on here cold
white spring on acid wish
everybody's on acid everybody's on an
acid trip everybody's depleted
okay that's the magnesium glycinate by
the way
that's the beverage glycinate magnesium
glycinate all right you love magnesium
karen churchill
awesome awesome so
i'm kind of just a little reminder about
this stuff because
and there's the be 12. details matter
so when i prepared everybody right over
a year and a half ago
for what was to come you know so people
actually knew
they can protect themselves
it was important because a lot of people
were able to protect themselves
so many testimonials out there medical
medium land
about how it saved them when they got
the
plague and how it knocked it out and all
kinds of other stuff how it how it saved
them from even getting it all kinds of
testimonials and stuff
and the family members and everything
else but it's so important because right
now we are
we are getting that whole beginning
process of what i said what was to come
mimi says need to bring products closer
to camera
so that's the vimorji right there that's
the vimergy's inc
okay them rgb is in victor i am ergy dot
com
that's the bimmer g's inc that's the
bimmer gb12
that's the bemidji golden seal i tell my
friends and family right now
you better have your golden seal
you better have your zinc in case you
have to do zinc shock therapy
when you start coming down with
something everybody's getting whacked
right now
there's your lemon balm okay
and there's the vitamin c there's the
microac
right there so important
so important i mean i can't even tell
you so today we're making a mojito salad
we're talking about why everybody's on
acid we're talking about why everybody's
depleted
important to know and we're also talking
about what we're up against in the very
moment in the present moment right now
so it's not just chronic illness that
everybody's up against
people are getting whacked right now
they're just getting whacked
like boom boom boom boom boom out there
i'm hearing about it every minute i got
people calling me that i've known for
forever
and everybody's getting whacked right
now so
important to know um and then the cat's
claw
that's a great weapon right there
so the bemidji cat's call chrissa
vermeezy vimergy products and your
guidance medical medium has saved my
life thank you
chris i'm honored you're here fantastic
and that's incredible news it is
so i'll speak louder tick-tock you guys
i'm not speaking that loud enough
i thought it was all right
i'll try to jack it up that's what i'll
do
so that's the vimergy cat's claw right
there
so medical medium information is about
chronic illness right
we know that it's about healing people
with chronic illnesses about people
getting recovered it's about people
getting their lives back
right and all that but it's also about
protecting us from what's happening
right now
and i just wanted to give everybody a
full warning about what's happening
right now all right so
the plague is out there it's whacking
people left and right
we're in the middle we're we're in the
we're in late july going right into
august it's happening a little earlier
but i said i forewarned everybody that's
coming
and it's getting becoming a lot worse in
the fall and other things too with other
kinds of sicknesses like chronic illness
and neurological problems like never
before in our
history that's coming in the fall in the
the winter
whether anybody knows or not it's coming
christian if i could only take one or
two supplements what would you recommend
if it was me
i would make sure i had the zinc i would
make sure
i had maybe some b12 it could be this
the zinc can b12
it could be the zinc and micro c i like
that one right there
okay could be the zinc and goldenseal
right you can't go wrong on those as far
as if it was me
or my friends or family that's what i
would say um
so what's happening you know what's
funny is i did a b12
post uh the other day right
i did a b12 post the other day okay
that's the bimmer gb12
i've been talking about b12 for years
i've been publishing information about
b12
right about b12 and and everything about
it saying xylocobalamin is not the one
you want
right and you know why people's b12
b12 level is high and how that doesn't
mean
it's actually working really good even
though you want it high
and how you want it high right and i've
been talking about a lot of things don't
do b12 shots
i've been talking about that too so b12
shots
like hey i'm gonna go get a b12 shot
here you go let me get a b12 shot
just got my b12 right how b12 shots is
something i would never do
okay and how if you take the wrong b12
like stylo
silocobalamin how it doesn't absorb into
your nerves or your nervous system how
you can't absorb it
and so i did a post on b12 just recently
and it was like no one
i mean there's of course some people but
it was like a whole bunch of people came
on salah kabala solikobalamin that's the
best one
hey try this b12 which had natural
flavors in it some bad b12
hey i give my b12 shot hey i get my b12
patches it was like
it was crazy it was literally crazy land
i mean it's like no one read the book no
one read the medical medium books where
i talk all about b12 and how it goes and
how you don't
you don't do the b12 shots and why and
all these things
and and then that's the same people that
also say i tried mmm and it didn't work
i tried on them and it didn't work and
you're like no you didn't try mmm
they're like yeah i did
i did the low fat um i did the heavy
metal smoothie
um i did the celery juice no you didn't
and and oh i did that and they got the
lingo down that's the new thing
right they got the lingo down act like
they did do it meanwhile they're the
same people
that are saying um i do the b12 shot i
do the b12 patch i do psylocke cobalamin
it's like oh
caught you caught you you didn't do mm
at all because you don't even know
anything about the b12 in mm
so anyway it's incredible how i can do
everything i can
to give you the details because the
details matter so you can get your life
back and
i could just do a post on v12 and it's
like everybody doesn't even know they
don't even know what's going on
it's incredible anyway that's the b12
right there that's the memory gv12 it's
important one
glenda aw i began to come down with flu
symptoms
early this week healed overnight
because i took the same supplements in
your lives glenda
that is ripping through and hitting
everybody right now everybody you're
just getting whacked by that
exactly and that's why it's critical
it's
critical i've been telling friends and
family you gotta have
the right zinc you've got to have the
right stuff
the right you know b12 you got to have
the right golden seal
it's not a joke it's not a joke
hospitals are filled with people they're
getting overflowing again they're
actually going to that overflowing state
everybody coming in there with the cough
just
filing in it's not a joke
it's hospitals are getting overrun i i
know because i have nurse
friends that are nurses that contact me
like aw you have no idea how bad it is
i'm like yeah i do
like no you don't i'm like well how bad
is it
well no it's war zones in like half the
hospitals
i'm like whoa
so yeah it's important so that's you
know
so i'm like what can i do what can i do
i can make a mojito salad and i can talk
about all this stuff
kathy why shouldn't you take b12 shot my
doctor prescribes it for me i take one
every month sure if your doctor
prescribes it do what your doctor tells
you but i would never do it
and i'll tell you why it's the wrong b12
that's
that's one reason it's wrong b12 it's
not methylcobalamin
in adenosilcobalamin going to be
it's going to be stylocobalamin it's
going to be some other kind of b12 that
doesn't work or doesn't absorb
it's number one reason why i want
wouldn't do it but do your doctor tell
you but that's
that's that's i wouldn't do it the other
reason is
b12 only works orally it only works
orally
if someone feels better right after a
b12 shot that day
that's the adrenaline high from getting
a shot
because it squirts all your adrenaline
out that's what happens
so when you go out to get your b12 shot
when you go out to get your b12 shot
you're getting an epinephrine high
because when you get stuck with the
needle
your adrenals go
they just epinephrine
goes everywhere that's what happens
where can i buy you those bimmerjee.com
vimergy.com these and victor i m as the
mary ergy
dot com could also go to my supplement
directory
at medicalmedium.com i'm not sponsored
by these guys
but it's just it's just the best there
is on the market in the world right now
and if that changes i won't be
supporting them in
in doing this i'm not paid by them i'm
not sponsored
so what happens is that when you get too
many b12
shots when you get too many b12 shots
right
you get too many you can become allergic
to b12
doctors don't know this right dr stone
this so first of all when you get your
b12 shot the high you feel right off the
running is the high from the shot
that from the b12 shot because your
epinephrine is squirting out of your
adrenal glands
because you just got the b12 injection
so what happens is that
and the other thing is if you have b12
enter the body from the outside of the
body
anywhere on the outside of the body in
the leg in the butt
on the arm you can eventually build an
allergic an allergy to it
an antibody gets produced against b12
you don't want to have that
so i tell friends and family don't get
the b12 shot
do b12 orally
i said i always tell friends and family
ivs are different that's a different
story
intravenous is different story that's
fine
intravenous is different lucy cohn good
to see you
intravenous is in the vein that's in the
vein
right that's in your vein it's my veins
on my hand here
right so that's in the vein so if
if they put a catheter in your vein
that's an iv vitamin nutritional therapy
and they stick a catheter in your vein
that's different you can't build an
allergic reaction to it it's different
it's different when it's a shock
different one is the b12 shot when it's
the b12 shot it's an
entirely different situation when it's a
b12 shot
my doctor told me i was b12 deficient
when i was
a meat eater and she was giving me b12
shots
five years ago i went plant-based and
started the vimergy b12 and i'm no
longer b12 deficient and one of the
reasons why maria
amazing maria donsky
what's amazing is that the i hear that a
lot
that that's the difference with b12 with
the vimergy b12
and i don't hear that from with other
b12s too by the way
and i hear that with the vimergy b12 all
the time
definitely and yeah
another thing too and we're going to
talk about animal products a little bit
today so i hope you guys hang on for
that
dr faun md
let's start making a fruit salad as well
and we got stuff to talk about
this is great this is mint fresh mint
right here by the way
okay so i'm going to move these over a
little bit
these are grapes right there got some
grapes
right hmm good
i got some raspberries
got some nectarines
yeah already did and
got some strawberries
right
some blackberries
you guys okay just moving these over a
little bit
got some limes too because that works in
here
[Music]
lorraine now remember you wrote your
comment and he juggles
and then raw honey got some raw honey
right here
that was actually really fun when i read
that i laughed
okay so um
cindy says doesn't have to be organic no
it doesn't have to be organic no
just wash it good but you have been
washing my produce really good lately
because
of the play going around right now
do you grow your fruit i grow some of it
i have a little tiny berry patch
too much fat fruit is bad for you i
think there's uh
i think you're stopping by
i think you're on your way right the
person who said too much fruit is bad
for you you're coming over right
we give you an invite you're going to be
in the kitchen any second
i'm just waiting for the knock on the
door
the person who said too much fruit is
bad for you is on their way
oh there they are they're knocking at
the door now okay let me go let them in
are you guys okay if i let them in for a
second
okay
well i'm glad i invited you over
dear lord oh my god the noise
too much fruit is bad for you
too much fruit is bad for you um anyway
look
i invite we we gave an invite to the
person on tick tight
tick tock who said too much fruit is bad
for you
so we gotta we did an invite and uh here
we are
okay you're gonna leave okay all right
our guest wants to go
too much fruit is bad for you says who
people that don't know why anybody's
sick uh
fruit's bad for you like fruit's been
around for
everybody's always like thousands of
years people been eating
eaten paleo thousands of years people
been eating animal products
but they didn't eat fruit they didn't
eat fruit
okay so fruit's bad for you animal
products aren't bad for you but fruit is
because i'm not against animal protein
for people if they want to be on an
animal protein diet
but you want to like seven ways to
sunday heart attack just keep on eating
lots of meat
you want you want a heart attack keep on
eating lots of meat
i love when someone's like oh fruit is
bad for you then what are you eating
what are you eating turkey are you
eating turkey all day
cause cause i'll tell you right now you
know
like you keep on eating roasted chicken
you'll get your heart attack you'll have
your heart surgery and then dr nesbitt's
going to have to work on your heart
dr nesbitt's going to have to replace
your heart so
i'm not saying you can still heal eating
animal protein on if
it's done right with medical medium
information
but you can also if you don't do it
right and you're doing all your animal
protein and fruits bad for you
you'll end up with that heart attack
just do roasted chicken all day is that
what you're telling me i should do let
me just do roasted chicken i'm gonna
need my high blood pressure medicine oh
my god
i'm going to need my high blood pressure
medicine if i uh
if i i'm not going to eat fruit anymore
so you know what i'm going to have my
10 my 10 000 uh
roasted chicken i'm gonna take my my
high blood pressure and my cholesterol
medication now
i better take it ahead of time
who even eats fruit anyway who even eats
fruit so why would fruit be bad when no
one even ate fruit they're all sick
anyway
i better take my high cholesterol high
blood pressure medication now
i better get my i better get some more
high blood pressure medication in me
quick
all right my doctor prescribed this i'm
allowed to do this on here
my doctor prescribed it
i just just sent more some high blood
pressure medication down can my doctor
prescribe this is perfectly fine i can
take this on here
my doctor prescribed this medication to
me
how's blood pressure and my cholesterol
medication i'm gonna have my 10
000 roasted chicken now and you know
what i might even have my
my 10 000 you know beef patty let me
just do that now
let me just have my my beef patty right
here okay
you guys don't mind right
karen churchill said fruit got rid of my
diabetes my sisters don't believe it so
they're still diabetic
gave them the book too i think i'm gonna
have another meat patty let me have my
my five sec my five thousandth meat
patty
but i won't eat fruit but i'll have
another meat patty
let me have another meat patty looks so
good let me die of another heart attack
come back come back around you're a baby
and then you grow up let me meet again
go go go get a heart attack die
come back around again another lifetime
but if you believe in that
don't eat some eat more roasted chicken
but i have another heart attack we'll
come around again
don't eat fruit but i'll just eat
another thousand roasted chickens
thumbs up if you guys like this video
and subscribe
right or whatever share the video too
share the live video if you guys can
some of you might hate the video
share it anyway
all right first of all
no one's eaten enough fruit for anyone
to know that that caused a single
problem
with anybody on the planet no one's
eaten enough fruit number one
okay number two you're talking about
everybody being deficient everybody's
deficient
they're deficient they don't eat fruit
right
don't eat fruit but you can have your
caffeine you guys don't eat fruit
don't eat fruit
don't eat fruit but you better believe i
can have another chocolate chip cookie
in another chocolate bar
don't eat fruit though let me get
another let me get a chocolate chip
cookie now
don't
don't eat fruit but i'm gonna dip this
chocolate chip cookie in here
don't ever eat fruit but i bet you the
person that doesn't eat fruit had a
chocolate
chip cookie in the last couple of months
yeah let me dip that chocolate chip
cookie right in here
so good in my coffee
don't eat fruit but let me have another
chocolate chip cookie
i'm going to have more caffeine don't
eat fruit
let me have them work heavy don't eat
fruit though don't eat fruit
let me have another chocolate bar to the
person who who said don't eat fruit
cause it's bad for you
how many chocolate bars did you have
last year chocolate no i'm so good
don't eat fruit
don't eat fruit oh wait there's a cherry
here
wait a minute do i take the cherry off
is that what you want me to do you want
me to take the cherry off
don't eat fruit you gave me good advice
that was amazing advice absolutely
amazing about health with liz is this
the best advice ever
don't don't eat fruit but i'm gonna make
sure oh i better throw this cherry away
i better throw this cherry away this hot
fudge sundae
is see there's plant medicine in this
hot fudge sundae there's lots of
chocolate which is plant medicine who
cares if it destroys my adrenal glands
and ages me fast
let me just oh wait a minute there's the
evil doer right there
there's the demonic piece of fruit
there's the evil demonic piece of fruit
i'd better
take that cherry off because it's going
to kill me and then i'll eat the rest of
my
hot fudge sundae
guys i think i'm getting like a heart
attack feeling
i better take another high blood
pressure medication my doctor prescribed
this so you can't do anything about me
taking this right now
don't be censoring me because i'm taking
my medication it's against the law
because this is my doctor prescribed it
genie what about moderation in all of
these
like meet once a week i am very
interested in your information
but why don't you just stay in the
positive position of eating fruit
sadly i am losing respect for you oh
that's terrible moderation kills people
that's what it is so what i'm going to
do is i'm going to eat this in
moderation are you
okay with that let me here i got
something else in moderation
i'm going to have a pizza in moderation
i got a friend calling too
i got a friend that's calling now but
i'm gonna have
i'm gonna have a pizza in moderation um
the truth what happens a lot of people a
lot of people who say they lose respect
for me just don't like to hear it
they don't like to hear that what
they're doing is is not good i get it
you don't want to hear it i got a phone
call coming in
you don't want to hear it and i
understand
i get it
hello yeah
yeah i know i i i got this great advice
from a registered dietitian and my
nutritionist slash my functional
medicine doctor they said moderation
i could have what i want they said i can
have pizza
twice a week in moderation i've been
having it three times a week because i
still feel like that's moderation
yeah i've been having chocolate fudge
sundae once a week
it's in moderation though yeah
yeah i've been having roasted chicken in
moderation
mm-hmm yeah moderation
well i've been having i just had a slice
of cake the other day and i just bought
a new one i'm saving this one
as long as it's in moderation i just
have to do it in moderation
what you're losing respect for me why
are you losing respect for me
not because i'm doing it in moderation
that's when you should respect me
yeah all right
moderation is such a great idea uh-huh
yeah well i'm just gonna keep on doing
everything in moderation fruit
no don't have fruit in moderation
oh no i have fruit in moderation there
it is right there i have fruit in
moderation
wait a minute here i got this from
moderation right now wait a minute
yeah i got this this is gonna be
moderation too as long as i do this in
moderation does that
not sound really smart it's okay but i
got my hashimoto's still and it got my
hypothyroid
and i got my skin problems i'm gonna
have caffeine daily is that moderation
because i'm having caffeine every single
day
is that moderation
uh-huh yeah i'm having caffeine and
chocolate every single day how about
that
does moderation sound smart what a smart
doctor i have i have the smartest doctor
he said moderation isn't he a smart
doctor
uh-huh let me just do more caffeine in
moderation what a smart nutritionist i
have good thing
hey you know that anthony william guy i
lost all respect for him
because he doesn't appreciate moderation
you know anthony william that that
you know that
that jerk moderation
april on here says moderation april taft
says moderation keeps us all sick
what april now
i don't like that anthony william guy
he's making everybody sick
robinson says moderation is such a myth
you guys are insulting me because i live
by moderation
i'm going to make sure i have my
chocolate my moderation
bar you guys i'm gonna put chocolate on
my pizza is that bad
you guys i'm gonna put it
you guys i asked the pizza place to
crack an egg to put it on top of my
pizza i'm gonna have an egg on here too
because everybody's putting eggs on
their pizza is that moderation
10 000 chickens in 20 years i've eaten
10 000 roasted chickens in 20 years is
that moderation
i've eaten a thousand pigs in moderation
yeah let me just kill another pig let me
have some bacon in moderation let me
just kill another pig
let me slaughter another another
defenseless animal
so i can have bacon in moderation i had
a slice of ham in moderation yesterday
how about that a slice of ham in
moderation does that make sense
what is everybody out there getting sick
in moderation
huh what do you mean everybody's getting
sick in moderation
is that what it is you guys everybody
gets sick in moderation
does everybody get sick in moderation
how about this i'm gonna eat in
moderation and take my high blood
pressure and my
my high blood pressure medication in
moderation
uh-huh let me do that
i'm going to have 30 000 cups of coffee
in the next 10 years
the next five years 30 000 cups of
coffee and then i'm gonna make sure i
eat plenty of chickens in moderation too
does that make a lot of sense oh wait a
minute for the vegans i got something
for the vegans here
i got something for the vegans
yeah the vegans
[Music]
i got something for the vegans the smart
asses
who think they know everything or the
vegans
i'm gonna do i'm gonna do a jar of
peanut butter every two
days as a vegan and i'm gonna do a jar
of nutritional yeast as a vegan every
two
three days that's moderation right
should i do nutritional yeast in
moderation
huh how come it sounds like anthony
williams against vegans and against
animal protein people he's not he's not
against anyone
i love that i love that he's not team
vegan
or team paleo or anything i'm a vegan
i'm gonna eat a jar of peanut butter
every week that's moderation i'll clog
up my heart with peanut butter
oh but it's a healthy fat still will
clog your heart up and i'm gonna have
i'm gonna put nutritional yeast on my
pizza this is a vegan pizza
this is a vegan pizza
okay lots of msg and nutritional yeast
i'm gonna have msg in moderation
nutritional yeast in moderation
it's also got bad b12 in it the bad
stuff
chris your moderation skit shows a lot
about moderation great for us to see
you guys i mean
right did i lose some of you guys
because i know i piss off people because
they don't want to they don't want to
they don't want to be told they're doing
moderation it's just pisses them off
it's death by a thousand cuts here's a
cut
here's a cut right here yeah there's
another cut
there's another cut let's do chocolate
cuts every day
let's do another cut i'm gonna have
another cut that's 5 000 cuts
make sure we get all my my caffeine down
all right come on guys can we get to
work
yes we have to get to work because
medical medium information is about
saving lives it always has been so we
got to get to work
okay look people are already at an
unfair
advantage they're riddled in pathogens
epstein-barr
sediment virus shingles hhv-6 they're
sick with all kinds of different
problems
they get aches and pains and sciatica
nerve pain and trigeminal neuralgia and
plantar fasciitis
skin problems it's vertigo dizziness eye
floaters ringing in the ears
people got enough problems because
they're viral and they're sick so let's
just moderation what
how about moderation sounds real good
viruses were released by classified
medical industries
years ago and our body wasn't set up for
those
so what moderation's gonna fix it
moderation doesn't fix anything
so i'm making a mojito salad
and for some reason i went off track
so here's what i'm making just so you
guys know
someone wait that doesn't look like it
here we go
yeah disaster relief lorraine
everybody's on acid and everybody needs
to get alkaline but in the proper way by
the way that's some keto salad i'm
making which is fruit
antioxidants knocking down those free
radicals right there right
we're talking about keeping the immune
system strong because whether anybody
knows it or not they may not be aware
but there is
a vicious little bug buying around
and people are getting hit with it
really hard left and right
left and right and it's setting a lot of
people back with chronic illness it's
cryptical
to have the zinc so that's the vimergy
zinc it's quick you can use
you can do whatever your doctor tells
you do your doctor tell you but i've
been telling family and friends about
the zinc the golden seal
about the golden seal about the b12
about the cat's claw
how critical this is and the micro stick
not sponsored by those guys but that was
something i just wanna remind any
anybody who just came on now who's like
what's going on all right so we're
making a salad let's do it i'm gonna get
my knife out right now
a couple of things i want to tell
everybody what you look when you look
outside in the world
everybody's really acidic they're really
really acidic
they're filled with acid they're eating
foods that create
acid everyone is on acid they're having
an acid trip
the acids do damage over time it's what
ages people
so what people are being told when
they're told to eat their eggs and
they're told to eat all
their meat i'm not against me
for one reason is because it doesn't
feed a pathogen but it does keep you
really acidic
i'm not against peanut butter for vegans
if they want to eat it wherever the
peanut butter went
if they want to eat it but the problem
is
it still makes you really acidic fat
makes you acidy and more
acidy inside your body fatty acids
fatty acids everybody's fatting
themselves to death
it's all that fat and and that fat makes
you
really really acidic so whether you're
an animal protein dude or gal and you're
doing the animal proteins left and right
where you're a vegan plant-based dude or
gal and you're doing all the nut butters
and the oils you're making yourself
acidic all the time so then when
pathogens come around
like the plague you're more susceptible
because acids also deplete us
of all those minerals of all those
vitamins and nutrients they deplete us
okay sure an avocado's healthy it gives
you some vitamins and nutrients but you
lose
more of them because when you overeat
avocado the fat
causes a depletion all the fatty acid
so when you're saying well you know
sunflower seeds are really you know
really healthy it's a healthy fat
but when we're eating too much of them
while we're eating other fats and we're
eating the nuts the seeds the nut
butters the fats the peanut butters the
chocolate
the chicken the fish the meat we're
always fatted out and then we get
depleted we're running on acid
we're living on acid we're having an
acid trip i'm going to chop up some
strawberries here
and that that's where we that's where it
gets us
right so i'm doing a little strawberry
chopping
okay so i'm cutting these
uh strawberry pieces up i'm gonna throw
i'm gonna mix this bowl of fruit in a
little bit too so i'm putting
strawberries in here i get it there's
fruit fear out there people are afraid
of fruit fruit isn't why people are sick
keep that in mind you guys
so important to know keep that in mind
fruit isn't why
people are sick it's not fruit
it's pathogens it's metals right
and then it's not eating or drinking the
right things to
to help your body assisted in healing
important to know
so i'm making this right here i'm
chopping up some strawberries
what you're gonna find in the health
scene is everybody demonizes
fruit
fruit is not why someone's in a dentist
chair are you kidding me
it's from chocolate all the chocolate
they've been eating all these years
it's from the caffeine dissolving teeth
over time
let me tell you something about caffeine
not only is it tremendously acidic
in the body all right but it depletes
you of
every nutrient that you have that's
available
it depletes it squeezes it right out of
you
vinegar does the same thing it depletes
so we walk around to pleat it right
so i'm chopping up some strawberries
right here okay
leads to bone loss tooth enamel
leeches calcium out of you that's what
it does it leeches all the calcium out
that's what it does what happens is you
end up becoming a buffer for all the
poison you're putting inside of you you
become a buffer
you know what that is you become the
buffer
your bones become the buffer to save
your life
so you want to keep on you you're going
to be on all that acid you're going to
be on the peanut butter you're going to
be on nuts and seeds all the time
healthy fats are okay have a little bit
here and there right
little touch of it here and there but
people are drowning themselves in it is
what's happening
so then we lose our bones we lose our
skeleton frame we lose it we get
osteopenia osteoporosis you don't even
see it your
your bones get porous your teeth get
porous and then they start collapsing
later on
you're fine in your 20s and you're
drinking your coffee and your caffeine
and you're doing your thing and you're
doing your functional medicine stuff and
you're doing your probiotic and you
think you're totally on it you're doing
your little avocado toast
and boom later on your skin age is fast
you got to get botox left in right
because people are getting botox left
and right
your teeth start to fall apart and then
you got to get all the veneers and all
the other stuff and the implants and
stuff people don't realize it
dino says does natural alkaline water
ph 9.5 okay to drink
does that help with the body's acid is
it natural coming out of an
aquifer is it natural coming out of a
spring
so if you have a high ph water coming
out of a spring you can drink it it
wasn't manufactured
that's different that's different you
don't
have to have alkaline water that's
coming out of aquifer or spring
in order to heal and stay alkaline just
need some leafy greens and some celery
juice right
yes from a spring then it's okay from a
spring
then it's okay all right it's not
manufactured
exactly it's very important to know it
wasn't manipulated the water wasn't
manipulated it wasn't manufactured keep
that in mind that's
that's why it's okay sadino that's okay
good to see you dina
i see you leave comments on youtube
every now and then
um so what happens is we're so acidy out
if that even makes sense like a word
we're so
drowning in our own assets because it's
created by all the stuff we're also
eating and then the stress adds to it
from all adrenaline here's what happens
too
when you do your caffeine and you do
your coffee and you do your chocolate
you're on a psychoactive drug which
triggers off your adrenals and now
epinephrine is flooding your system and
epinephrine is acidic
and it starts to burn your nerves and
bones over time
right if anybody's going to talk about
moderation
talk about making sure that you slow
down or
bring to a halt eventually some of those
bad things
nutritional yeast all that msg blows out
your brain
blows out your brain stem msg's so toxic
to your brain you guys it builds up and
it builds up and it builds up
so i talk about all those toxic
supplements that have natural flavorings
and flavor and flavors in it
all that stuff that's all msg elio
how do i get my protein to build muscle
mass if i don't eat chicken turkey or
meat sounds like you've never read one
thing from medical medium
sounds like you know that's a good
question though okay
that that's that's a really good
question okay um i i just have to
i have to plug in my robot just hold on
okay
just hold on okay
protein robot protein robot protein
robot protein robot protein protein
protein
need to build muscle meat protein i
shall kill a pig eat a pig
yellow fish protein my protein protein
robot
trunky robot protein breaking build
muscle make me strong protein make me
strong make me strong
give me strength protein heals me
protein heals me everybody says protein
protein
rub kill the cow
chicken chicken kill the chicken brookie
here's how it works
i don't think that was the best robot
but whatever
okay protein
doesn't kill off a pathogen that's
weakening you right protein
doesn't give you nutrients
minerals antioxidants protein
doesn't even build muscle it doesn't
what builds muscle is glucose and
mineral salts
that's it builds muscle so you gotta
have sugar to build muscle
you know what happens here's i'm gonna
tell you right now okay
when someone's sick with chronic illness
right
when someone's actually sick with
chronic illness and
they're wasting away because they got
me cfs they got chronic fatigue syndrome
they got fibromyalgia so they can't
they can't work out and they're losing
muscle
the worst thing ever for them
is to get caught up in the protein law
that protein law
will kill them i have watched doctors
contact me over the last 35 years
telling me aw i got a patient bed ridden
they're atrophying what are you feeding
them
feeding them lots of protein you're
gonna kill them quick
you're gonna kill the person quick
they're gonna die
what do you mean die they need protein
they have no muscles
they're laying in bed sick you're gonna
kill them
carbohydrates build a muscle if they're
in bed and they're bedridden you better
be giving them bananas you better be
giving them potatoes you better be
giving them some fruit
yeah you better because you in order to
build a muscle you have to have two
components one is
a carbohydrate to go into the muscle
cells
to sustain it so it doesn't atrophy the
other thing is
you got to be able to use your muscle
and when you're chronically ill you
can't use your muscle
so then you better at least have that
carbohydrate available
it's why people have to do that bulk and
cutting thing
they have to bring in the carbs to bulk
up all those weight lifter dudes
even pros that reach out to me that are
on the scene
in their pros they reach out because
you're like what do i do
you're missing the carbs because if you
want to go and try to build your muscle
on just
fat and animal protein you're not going
to sustain those muscles
and so what they do is they bulk up by
adding the carbs in
that's the bulking and cutting the
reason why they're bulking is because
they're adding the carbs in
that's what's making them bulk up that's
the whole point
and then when they drop back the carbs
and they drop
drop back the calories they drop
everything down their portions
they they try to lose a little bit that
excess fat
but they still get fat from the fat
but then they get stuck because they're
losing muscle so then they have to do
the
carbs again they do the bulking and
cutting
what's giving them the bulk in their
muscle is the carb
aspect it's the carb it's not the
protein
because the brain washing is insane
reclaims the heal
it's a great question though okay
re-cleanse the heel
well medical medium book one new
addition cleanse the heel
read that one too how about that read
that one too
okay you guys let's go so we got the
strawberries in here
right
people are afraid of fruit just afraid
of fruit
it's so sad got some blackberries now
you can pop these blackberries whole i
like to do that
can you please explain how people
keller peterson is still alive eating
just beef for years
yeah i could easily explain that okay a
couple of things to understand
you don't know what people eat behind
closed doors do i have to be the fly on
the wall right now
do you have to be the fly in the wall
how many people lie on social media
do many people lie in the industry do
many people lie on instagram
do many people lie on facebook do many
people lie on
youtube you don't know what they're
eating and what you don't know they're
eating
they can sit there and tell you they're
eating beef the whole time and you'll
get you know what this reminds me of the
story
of the famous clinic that was anti-fruit
and anti-sugar
a famous clinic just so you know and
that famous clinic is still
out there and the head of that famous
clinic
was caught by the chef at 12 o'clock at
night
reaching into the refrigerator in the
kitchen when everybody was in bed
on the in the clinic it was a retreat
that
purse that owner of that clinic the head
of that clinic was caught
reaching for a whole bag of dried fruit
a big bag of dried fruit in the
refrigerator at this clinic
and was gobbling down dates and an app
dried
apricot and dried mango but yet telling
everybody
for years that fruit is a curse he
doesn't eat fruit
he's com he's on only animal protein
and the dude the owner of the clinic was
caught by the chef
that knows me personally and knows a
bunch of other people and told a bunch
of people
the dude was in there in the
refrigerator trying to gobble down all
that dried fruit in the middle of the
night was caught at midnight
how about that why is everybody just so
gullible it's just easy to
just fall into the bs
it's not enough truth out there and
there's too much bs
it's just sad this is heartbreaking
really
so i'm going to throw some raspberries
in here
better take more blood pressure medicine
and some cholesterol medicine you can
you can you can live on meat
yeah but eventually if it's just me and
i'm not anti-meat if someone wants to be
on meat i'm just i'm
i want to make sure if someone's animal
protein i'm not against an animal
protein people
i'm not against vegans people think i
hate vegans
and i know vegans hate me because
they're like oh he doesn't know anything
about veganism
okay sure more people healed and chronic
illness ever before in history because
of medical media information but i don't
know nothing
most powerful people in the world
reaching out to me every day
just most powerful people in the world
knocking on my door constantly
will we have to like fend them off
because i got just too much going on
because they've seen the 50 doctors and
the best neurologists and they take
their private jets all around the planet
all around the globe their private jets
doing every therapy possible and they're
knocking on my door
sure i don't know anything about
veganism
and then people steal medical medium
information left and right and they plug
it into everything
so you'll have vegans actually being
saying oh medical medium doesn't know
anything meanwhile they're using medical
medium tools that were given to the
vegan community in the last 35 years
from
me and not from science and research
because science research didn't have the
info so where did the info come from
i'm the only one hearing a voice that
brought in advanced medical medical
information into the world
i've also lectured on the scene for
years teaching people
and even science research skills medical
medium information
all the time put some grapes in here
do not mono eat grapes
okay grapes that they're a medicinal
food
absolutely don't mono eat grapes
don't mono eat blackberries don't just
eat blackberries for weeks and weeks and
weeks and no other food
it's too astringent too cleansing
but you can have grapes every day what
you're looking right here is antivirals
antibacterials
anti pathogens anti
oxidants
so i'm making some fruit salad here
minerals trace minerals
macro minerals right
glucose
so
all right let's keep on going a little
bit
now what people have to understand
something there is sugar in meat
the animal has its own blood sugar the
animal eats grass say you got a cow and
the cow is eating grass right
so say your cow is eating grass okay
right all that sugar from
the grass gets
concentrated into the cow's blood
and then the blood that's in the meat is
sugar so you can
you could live on meat by itself
you could but it's still not enough
glucose you can do it for a while
but you can't do it long term especially
if you're sick and your neurological
system is compromised
if you're some dude and you haven't been
sick yet you've got nothing going on
you get a sniffle once every couple of
years you haven't had pathogens affect
you yet because you haven't gotten the
pathogens
you haven't gotten enough heavy metals
yet you haven't had any of that right
and you haven't been sick yet so say
you're a dude that hasn't been sick yet
you will but you haven't been sick now
yet you're young you're 20 years old
right you're in the gym you're working
out you can be on meat for a little
while and not see a decline
yet but eventually you'll just see a
decline after just six months being just
on need alone you're going to see
decline in your muscles
you'll start losing your muscle mass
start going away be 20 years old say why
am i not building muscles you start
losing your muscle mass
and you start aging fast too your skin
turns to you just start aging fast
that's what's happening though why do
you think the carnivore movement put in
honey did you guys know that
carnivore movement why did you need
honey i'm that's a head scratcher for me
um carnivore movement completely
anti-sugary anti-fruit anti-anything
sweet
scratching my head a little bit on that
why did you guys bring in honey
recently hmm because you guys were
sucking it out
you guys were struggling because you
were noticing too many people could not
handle it and do it they were binging on
carbs
yeah i'm on the carnivore diet let me
just feed on a whole bunch of yeah i'm
on the carnivore diet
but i'm just not going to tell my
carnivore teacher what i'm doing here
yeah i'm on a carnivore time
okay back on the carnivore diet they
needed sugar
so they put honey in the carnivore diet
teresa
how's diabetes happening then too much
bad sugar
bad sugar sugar has nothing to do with
diabetes
besides diabetics need sugar to stay
alive is that interesting
a diabetic needs sugar to stay alive
okay you find you find a type 1 diabetic
on a bus
passed out you better get some orange
juice to the lips as fast as possible or
they're going to go into a coma
why is sugar the problem with diabetes
it's fat
it's fat fat is how you get insulin
resistance fat is what kills the
pancreas it's not sugar
you can't have sugar and fat together
because the fat ruins everything it
stops the sugar from going into your
cells it's not sugar that causes
diabetes you guys it's the fat that
causes diabetes
originally that's all medical medium
information going back years ago now
there's a whole bunch of people
practicing that there's doctors
practicing that there's there's all
kinds of people out there talking about
it
sugar okay gets blocked from the fat so
it can't enter into your cells so then
you can't get the glucose you need and
then as a diabetic
or somebody with hypoglycemia and
hyperglycemia you get just all screwed
up because the sugar is blocked it's not
getting into the cells
it's not getting into the cells it's the
fat in this that gets you you see this
you guys it's the fat inside of this
that gets you
fat is in ice cream it's not the sugar
in ice cream it's fat that's in ice
cream
and guess what back to the back to the
whole
moral of the story or whatever back to
the whole story is
we're acidic we're on acid because we're
doing so much
fat we're we're on so much acid we're
tripping every day on acid
let's finish this up we got strawberries
in here got raspberries in here we got
grapes in here we got blackberries
let's get some nectarines in here
let's do that there's fats in cookies
cakes and donuts that's why you get sick
as a diabetic become a diabetic
eventually
there's fat and pizza pizzas fat plus
sugar
cookies are sugar and fat donuts bagels
and cream cheese
fat and sugar combined makes you sick
with diabetes
no one's eating sugar by themselves i
don't get it are you guys eating the
sugar without the fat and the ice cream
what are you doing like are you eating
the sugar without it like who's eating
this
are you eating just the tomato sauce on
the pizza because i'm confused here i'm
scratching my head right here
are you eating all the cheese and the
goopy fat inside the cheese and the
goopy oil that's on the pizza dough or
the egg inside the pizza
the pizza dough in some pizzas
you guys full moon medical medium
podcast at apple podcast
full moon uh moon meditation
free do some soul healing
heal some wounds so check that out when
you can
leanne says use vimergy totally just a
reminder i see more people came on we
got more people on tick tock and letting
you guys know there is a plague at bay
out there
knocking on people's doors i'm seeing
people get sick and
left and right out there hearing about
it from doctors calling me left and
right right now
so we got that bad ugly flu going around
got the play going around and fall
winter's gonna be far
worse i'm telling friends and family you
better have some zinc
that's the vimergy stuff you can use
whatever your doctor wants but i'm
saying this is
this is what i recommend there's the
microc vimergy
these and victor i m is the mary e r g y
dot com
vimergy that's the stuff i use my
friends and family there's the golden
seal
darcy lee she saw you the comment went
up you love the meditation you guys
the move meditation
[Music]
let's cut up a nectarine
let's do that
how you know you know what happens is
that
so i you know i have friends that are in
health some doctors and they'll say to
me
how do you do it no every day
you try to put out this life-saving
information
and then someone's like
yeah someone's like i'm gonna get my b12
shot
i need some protein sugar's bad
fruit's bad for you you know
um how do you do it and i'm like how do
i do it
it's a lot of people that do hear it do
read the books
lots of people hear it they read the
books medical medium information saves
so many lives how can i how can i
like disrespect that i'm not gonna
i'm not good so important
so i got some nectarines in here i got
strawberries
nectarines were nice and ripe and i got
some blackberries and grapes
let's get a little bit of mint on here
now you can chop up the mint and you can
also put the mint pieces on here
you're the best anthony medical medium
and spirit of compassion
you're my real life superhero david
scott honored
honor you're my hero too man
two weeks two weeks i've been doing
the comments keep on bouncing around you
guys
see if i can find it two weeks i've been
doing uh
doing fruits and veggies my hair was
falling out
it's so much better i have more energy
what will keep on making the hair fall
out is keep on doing the chocolate
caffeine
the vinegar nutritional yeast just all
these things
right too much meat i support animal
protein people i support
plant-based and vegan people i just want
them to have the tools so they can heal
if they want to be either or
if your plant-based stay plant-based
don't leave it don't stop it
if you're animal protein that's what you
want that's where your heart desires
then stay there
we can still work on healing regardless
but we just have to do a couple of
things or a few things depending on
what's happening
too i'm gonna add some um
some mint sprinkle it on top and i'm
gonna add some lime
it's beautiful beautiful i'm gonna take
some mint leaves here and i'm just gonna
do this you guys
and i'm just going to sprinkle a little
bit of the mint on there let me get a
lime going here
we're live on tick-tock right now just
so there's no confusion we're live on
facebook we're live on youtube and we're
live on clubhouse too
and i'm honored to be at your service
just made the mojito salad and i am at
your service
i will do anything to help you guys find
a way to heal
josephine well i haven't had seen
results yet
doing celery juice for two months now
frustrated
so i want you to be your own detective
how much celery juice
what else are you doing if you have the
chocolate the caffeine the vinegars in
there
how much dairy are you doing are you
doing the the eggs
any eggs happening okay all these matter
is your celery juice high pressure
pasteurized because
high pressure pasteurized which is the
bad stuff hpp
does your cellar juice have lemon in it
does it have ice in it does have water
in it these are all bad things is it 32
ounces celery juice or eight ounces of
celery juice
i want you to be your own detective is
anybody out there jumping into new
medical treatments right like you said
no new medical treatments are offered
all the time
sometimes even most of the time new
medical treatments set people back
and then they're doing that at the same
time they're trying to do something good
and they can't see the results yet
because they've already done something
that wasn't good
it happens neurological line like the
medical treatments for neurological lyme
is just
hammering them with antibiotics
antibiotics
antibiotics i can't tell you how many
people they're
they're they get their neurological lyme
diagnosis and then they're at the
doctor's office and they're both
slamming them with antibiotics the worst
kind of antibiotics
and then they're like why isn't my
celery juice helping why isn't my
why isn't my eight ounces of celery
juice helping and how many blood draws i
want everybody to be their own detective
how many blood draws is someone getting
because if you're getting blood draws
you just had another blood test
boom you've just been set back because
they'll take they'll they'll drain you
to death
they'll drain someone to death people
you people get cancer they take blood
from you every week until you did you
literally take everything out of your
whole immune system you didn't even
stand a chance the way they
drain your blood so it's um unbelievable
another thing people get new bugs they
get new bugs happening
and they need to go further to clean up
their strap in their epstein bars
so they don't get much worse also you
may not be recovering from a small
amount of
celery juice yet but is it keeping you
from getting worse
keep that like in the detective hat
right there is it keeping you from
getting worse
and then you just need to go further
meanwhile it's stopping you from getting
worse
right keep that in in the bonnet right
there your detective bonnet
okay really important did you learn the
true cause of why you're sick did you
take your symptoms
did you take your symptoms to the
medical medium library
did you take your symptom to the medical
medium cleanse the heal book
learn why you're sick and then you see
the protocol what supplements you're
using you're using the right kind of
supplements you're using ones with msg
in it using the bad ones you're using
the right ones
are you on the anti-bug cleanse are you
on the mono cleanse are you on 369
cleanse are you doing 369 advanced
multiple times
are you doing the heavy metal detox
movie right are you using the right
spirulina for your heavy metal detox
smoothie to get the metals out
celery juice is just one medical medium
tool
i'm not trying to overwhelm anybody
but there's reason why we're not getting
better and how much chocolate are you
eating
are you doing the moderation thing and
getting blood draws at the same time
from the doctor's office
they'll moderate the crap out of you and
draw the blood out of you until you're
gone
they just rot until you learn how to how
to stop them from taking all your blood
i believe in blood tests but there's a
way to stop them just go listen to my
podcast
i need another high cholesterol pill
right now oh my god
this job is getting too hard i need
another high blood pressure medication
here
i'm allowed to just unprescribe this so
i can do what i want
claudia if you're really sick like me it
takes much longer to heal than you'd
like
but i am healing explanation points use
supplements to move things
this stuff really works
very kind advice by the way thank you
very kind advice
so i already mixed this it's all set i
put some mint on top i put some lime on
top
right now i got to put a little honey on
top too
sorry about that you guys people who
know the medical bean recipes are like
where'd the honey go
oh this is so bad so much sugar on here
oh no it's got fruit in here and honey
in here
this is really bad really bad
that's incredible for you by the way
this is an incredible meal for you
incredible
this was for the there's a recipe in
medical medium new edition by the way
you guys i hope you have the books i
know that a lot of people come on here
and they're like
this medical medium a keto i'm like oh
my god
are eggs okay
it's medical medium like eggs i'm
heading off to ig
so by the way let's recap before i go i
don't want to go yet
i want to recap okay
we're up against some serious sickness
out there we already have people
chronically ill and getting chronically
ill even faster and worse as the next
month's coming like i've been
forewarning
in the fall and winter there's going to
be so many neurological problems people
won't even believe it
neurological symptoms and brain
inflammation and everything else and
cranial inflammation
cranial nerve problems and brain
inflammation all of that okay
it's already on its way i talk about
that all the time it's been happening
for years and
it's it's getting worse the other thing
is right now we have
the bug going around so what are you
doing to protect yourself i tell my
friends and family make sure
you got the vimergy goldenseal make sure
you got the beverages inc
make sure you're made of emergency lemon
balm the vimergy b12
then rg micro see at least
at least what else are you doing you
know lysine's a great one right there
licorice root incredible cat's claw
another one
bemergie.com right i'm not sponsored but
um
but we got to have some things that
actually help protect us
it's how i feel it's what i tell my
family and friends okay
and how are you eating are you cranking
the chocolate back it down
your adrenals are just going to get
eventually wasted someday by it
you know are you are you cranking the
nutritional yeast and the apple cider
vinegar are we making ourselves really
acid or
acidy are we doing too much coffee what
are we doing back it down
if you're an animal protein person lower
the animal proteins the fats
bring in more medical medium recipes
if you're a plant person lower the fats
you're gonna nut butter yourself to
death
it'll happen down the road you'll quit
being a vegan because you're just gonna
get sick
and you'll think it was the veganism
that got you sick and you'll end up
going to eat animal protein down the
road later and getting yourself sick too
that way
learn how to eat like a plant-based
person should learn how to eat like an
animal protein person learn the tools
and why we're sick
and do the moon meditation magazine
podcast at apple podcast i love you guys
and if you want to know what those acids
do
those bad acids they dissolve the bones
dissolve the teeth
wreak havoc lower the immune system and
deplete us
what more can i say or do but
guys i am at your surface heading off to
instagram
are you coming instagram coming over
there stacy
this is the best live thank you hey i'm
honored
can't believe it tick tock you guys on
tick tock i'm turning you guys back on
i'm turning clubhouse back on in a
little while michelle l good to see you
on tick tock um
i'm turning you guys back on you guys on
facebook and youtube
i'm heading over to instagram now listen
little
little disclaimer for instagram there
when they kick you off
because that's what instagram does
facebook does too by the way when they
kick you off
instagram go to tick tock
maybe listen on clubhouse or something
okay they also remove the sound on
instagram
they remove the sound they kick you off
you go back on they kick you off again
anyway i'm just giving you the four
warnings so you can go on tick-tock
watch me there if you need to i love you
guys so much
seriously take care i'll see