how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William hey everybody we're talking
about
Chemtrails you might want to brace
yourself for what's coming in this
episode it's a powerful episode that you
really should be informed wared about
it's always about protecting our health
in every way possible and chemtrails
that's an area we have to cover I have
to give you guys a little warning though
after you hear this you may never see
the sky the same
again this is all information from
Spirit of compassion since I was a child
naysayers they can believe it or not
that's fine maybe somebody can call it a
Theory look we can call it a spooky
Campfire story if it makes people feel
good we can do that too that's fine but
hey when you hear what I have to say
just get ready bottom line you've
probably done your research with
Chemtrails somebody has somebody must
have because there's people out there
they're like Chemtrails I know about
those and I've heard about those and
there's some information out there and
yeah some of it's accurate one of the
accurate parts of chemtrails is that
they there are chemtrails that there
actually are chemtrails so I'm going to
tell you guys what information isn't out
there and it's a lot What Spirit of
compassion has told me the Deep secrets
of the chemtrail game yeah did you hear
that I said game yeah a sick game my
first experience with Chemtrails was as
a child and a friend of mine pointing
out a contrail on the horizon and my
friend asking what does your spirit say
about this
contrail and that's what he said I said
well let me ask Spirit of compassion
what is a
contrail and spirit of compassion said
there are
contrails and there are man-made poison
Trails where man is poisoning man these
are two entirely different
things ever since then I was intrigued
in fact I was obsessed about doubted why
on Earth would man be poisoning man that
right there when I was young I I I it
was overload it was
overload why on Earth would man be
dumping poison on man that was hard for
me to receive as a child because that
one right there just it didn't make
sense and even though Spirit of
compassion delivered me the harsh
reality of chronic illness already as a
young child teaching me so many of the
things things that that I've lectured
about over the years that people know
about now that has been passed around
because the health scene was so small
for years ago and all the information
that got out there that was so like
harsh reality of why women are sick and
why men are sick this was a hard one for
me it was a hard one when I receiv
received this as a child I mean I knew
about rat poison I knew about rat poison
that kills rats right rat poison I was
afraid of of it I was afraid of rat
poison you just don't want to play with
that stuff I knew about insect poisoning
too my neighbors they sprayed out of a
can so this prompted me to constantly
ask Spirit of compassion what's that
Mark in the Sky What's that plane what
is that streak in the sky what is what
is this and spirit would say that's a
passenger plane that's what that is
that's a passenger plane and that's a
cargo plane there i' be like oh what's
that plane you know a couple hours later
what is that one you know well that's a
third type of plane you got your
passenger planes where people are on
them you got your cargo planes where
they're delivering packages and
everything else right and all that and
there's other little tiny planes you
know that fly around or private planes
little ones and all that but big planes
I'm talking about big ones and there
then there was this third plane
and we'll get to that in a little bit
about that third plane now there is a
big difference between a contrail and
what people have named now a
chemrail so hey I learned it as manmade
poison Trails that's what Spirit of
compassion said and now I guess they're
called Chemtrails and it's a good name
for them too I like that name I do
contrails contrails are fuel burning and
heat exchanging from a plane it's this
heat coming out of engines okay so when
you're entering a higher altitude and
you got that fuel burning emitting all
of that different vapor and that air is
cool as that plane is rising and you you
can see these contrails out there yeah
there's this little tiny streak and you
see mostly contrails in the fall
contrails in the winter on the horizon
of the night sky right on the other hand
a chemtrail is something sinister
something dark something dark in a
Despicable way that's even
unimaginable really is it was for me as
a child and before I tell you what
Spirit of compassion has told me about
the
Chemtrails I got to bring you back into
history a little bit to World War I
1914 okay and the world was at war and a
few years before the world was at War a
few years in the early 1900s the
chemical industry was
birthing it was birthing they were
experimenting with chemical
concoctions it was a brand new industry
and fierce at that for industrial use
World War I was the money and the fuel
for the chemical industry to become
larger to ignite to propel it was like
the it was like the gasoline on the fire
that war for the for the chemical
industry so it became larger because the
chemical industry was contracted to feed
the War Industry the global War Industry
they were hired to produce chemicals for
chemical warfare and all kinds of other
Industries about war and this was all
around the world and a surplus of these
chemicals were stockpiled storage bins
of these chemicals the chemical industry
loves War they love insects too now they
love rodents they love machines they
love anything and they loved all that
back then and everything that they
believe needs a chemical you might be
wondering like why is he talking about
World War I yeah yeah I got a real
reason and it's a powerful reason to
just hang on and when I tell you guys
fasten your seat belts like I have in
the past you're going to want to fasten
your seat bels for this one I mean you
really are I I would be sitting down for
this show but the war ended early with
the help of the Spanish flu right you
guys probably know that information
there the flu kind of knocked that war
down but hey that disappointed the
chemical Industries they were hoping the
war would last forever but you didn't
need a war lasting forever for them this
was the true birth of the chemical
Industries and it spawned on the birth
of all chemicals used in all industri it
led to constant production of industrial
chemicals all the way to World War II
Not only was the chemical industry
producing for World War II now but they
were producing on a much larger scale
for almost all Industries around the
world everywhere at that point because
of this there was so much overflow of
byproduct the industries had to dump
some of the chemicals into rivers lakes
in the ocean and I'm going to talk about
byproduct in a minute what that means
byproduct coming off of creating a
chemical not just the chemical
itself the industries they just dumped
it right into rivers they dumped them
into lakes they dumped them into the
ocean they dumped them everywhere they
were they were already doing that since
the early 1900s they were already
dumping all this stuff everywhere but it
was increasing greatly and with more
dangerous
concoctions the chemical Industries knew
if it persisted
our lakes and rivers would
die they would die and they would die
globally and they knew this just like
Lake Erie almost was pronounced
dead almost pronounced completely dead
and when it gets to that point when a
lake actually completely dies you can't
bring it back so The Dumping of these
chemicals slowed down in the 1960s and
storage bins and storage bins started to
accumulate more and more and more around
the world storage bins of chemicals you
have to understand something this is
important the process of making
chemicals is a wasteful process in order
to make a chemical for a use there's
trial and error they experiment over and
over and over again and create bad
batches they create mistakes nonstop
it's practice is what it is it's
practiced mistakes
that have to be discarded where does all
that practiced mistake go millions and
millions and billions of botch jobed
gallons have to go somewhere of chemical
so not only do you have the mistakes
made as they try to discover a chemical
for use but the byproduct produced is a
whole other level of waste which can
lead to millions of gallons on its own
hey this might be boring when you think
about it to somebody they're like I
don't want to hear about chemicals oh
yeah you don't you don't okay you don't
want to hear about them okay all right
okay you okay you live in that world but
you know
what you want to know you want to know
what's happening because it involves you
it involves everybody this isn't just a
story about some chemicals or something
this this is critical information so you
can protect your family so you can
protect your loved ones and protect
yourself the byproduct I'm talking about
produced that's a whole another level of
waste it's not just the chemical that's
being produced but the byproduct which
can lead to once again millions and
millions and billions of gallons on its
own per one
chemical now per one chemical they try
to deem useful this can mean up to a
thousand times the byproduct per
chemical produced it could up to that
this translates to trillions and
trillions of gallons of byproduct over
the years what's byproduct deadly waste
chemicals you know from a chemical when
they're trying to make it that was a
method of disposing of the toxic waste
the method was throw it in Rivers throw
it in Lakes let it drain into lakes let
it drain in the ocean but where's it
going to go you know in the end with all
of that trillions of gallons where is
the industry going to store all of those
toxic gallons because they back down on
dumping it in any streams rivers and
lakes and and the ocean back in the 60s
it was back down and where do you store
all that because it's going to take up
so much land in the world so much land
in the world massive amounts the old
method was to dump it like I said in our
rivers and lakes and the other old
method was to dump in landfills and
toxic dump sites where then the rain
would come and the rain would slowly
wash small amounts of it back into the
ocean back into the rivers and back into
the Lakes this has been ongoing since
the early 1900s it was the older method
I'm talking about to discard it and get
rid of it but you'll see why I'm talking
about this as we move along the global
chemic you know chemical Industries had
a problem on their hands they couldn't
dump it all in the rivers oceans and
lakes not all of it and there was
nowhere to store the mass amounts
anymore there wasn't enough land
available to store the surplus of
chemicals and the excess byproduct it
would take over planet Earth we're
talking about levels that are so huge
and so massive Unthinkable levels and
amounts and different kinds of chemicals
thousands of different kinds of
chemicals and their byproducts before we
go further though we will talk about
those planes we see in the air so now
there's airliners right hey they have
passengers you guys have been on those
planes before they got passengers you're
flying all flying up there and then
there's cargo planes and they might have
a couple of P passengers on there but
they have you know packages and
shipments and carrying packages all
around the globe
but there's another kind of large plane
up there Spirit of compassion told me
about it it's separate from the other
two kinds of planes I just mentioned
these are older
airliners they're older airliners these
airliners are from the late 50s and the
60s and the 70s and the 80s and the '90s
these different kind of planes people
used to travel in them yeah airliners is
what they were but not anymore they fly
with no passengers on there anymore
those days are over they travel on their
own flight patterns and they land in
private airports their own private
airports these private airports aren't
military they have nothing to do with
any world
military and you know what's really
weird they have nothing to do with any
world
governments it's a whole other
organization
built for the chemical
Industries
and I should have my flashl shining on
my face right now as we sit around the
campfire you know get ready for the
information though and a whole other
organization of private contractors
built this for the chemical
Industries I always tell you guys about
the private deals that Spirit of
compassion has told me about all through
the years I tell you about the private
deals going on here's just another one
to add to the list right a private deal
that was put in place in the
1960s made without anybody's say or
input no Town Hall meetings like always
say it's kind of reminds me of the just
like just like the protein law hey if
you're new to Medical medium information
you be like what's the protein law well
the protein law is something you've been
brainwashed with okay just so you know
all right back in the early
1930s the the whole thing about protein
was purposely done and it was in it was
put into schools and all of this
information about I can give you that
another day you're going to hear about
the protein law and you'll know why
you've been brainwashed by the protein
law but and then there's the autoimmune
law too where we've been trained that
our bodies attack themselves that we're
taught that our body turns against our
glands and organs and our body's immune
system destroys itself right the
autoimmune law that started in the 1950s
that private deal that was made that
everybody's brainwashed about to
alternative medicine and conventional
medicine well we'll talk about those in
future episodes but this was another
private deal that was made these old
planes were hollowed out tanks were put
inside of them and not the tanks that
are theorized now not the tanks they cuz
you know people talk about there must be
tanks in these planes right but these
tanks are large tanks not little tiny
ones they're large tanks and the these
planes are gutted and these large
plastic tanks are installed the tanks
were filled with old chemicals and their
byproducts that's what happens so the
plane is sitting there a truck comes by
and then fills the plane up with these
toxic waste
chemicals that's how the system works
the planes land once they empty the
chemicals they land they're in the
airport trucks come by they fill up the
tanks planes take off it's and they they
go out and they're just they're up in
the air again so the global chemical
industry was was harboring for over 50
years since before the 1960s all these
toxic chemicals that that they've been
holding on to because if they dumped
everything in the rivers and the lakes
and the ocean at once and in landfills
throughout the throughout the whole
1900s and early 1900s it would have been
epic disaster an epic disaster so many
of the chemicals were held on to and
kept in store Vats the plan was to fill
these planes with these chemicals and
release them when the planes are up in
the sky you know is that a nice thing to
do I don't think so the planes go high
in the sky and they release these toxic
chemicals so it would slowly thin out
over time as these chemicals
dissipated this isn't in just one
country okay okay so if you're thinking
that in your mind you're like whoa what
country he's talking about no no a
global
phenomenon a global deal the planes are
flying all over the entire planet
dropping down these chemicals and
chemical
byproduct these old storage Vats of
chemicals that all these chemical
Industries had sitting around too too
long something happens to these
chemicals when they sit around too too
long on another note things grow inside
of them strange forms of bacteria
strange forms of mold fungus toxic algae
and that's something you got to remember
as we go through the show toxic algae
interesting you know like red tide kind
of stuff we're going to keep on moving
along new allergens we never even
experience grow in these
tanks this is why the oceans get those
algae blooms that actually cause the red
tide by the way these red tides are a
sign of the coming times down down down
the road okay and you know long after
we're here but these coming times where
the oceans die and turn completely red
you know the chemicals are
producing the over production of the
toxic algae that's what happens the
chemicals that are being dropped out of
the sky are igniting and proliferating
toxic
algae because that's where the toxic
algae are coming from see we kind of
play stupid down here we're like testing
water we're testing red tide certain
times of the Season hey it's dangerous
to go in the water don't go in that
water right now you might get sick you
know we're doing little tests on it but
that toxic algae comes from someplace it
didn't come come from down here that
toxic algae came from up there and
rained
down that's how it works see you get
microorganisms they have to survive they
need to survive and when they sit in
these chemical soups in Vats and storage
bins for years and decades they adapt
the more microorganisms then breed life
in there and then they have to adapt to
survive and that's going to be a whole
story for another day on know how that
works but let's just keep
going but what you see is not what you
get up there in the sky when you look at
the Chemtrails in the sky you might be
thinking oh wow that chemtrail now he's
talking about that chem trol is going to
fall on me I see that one right up there
that one's going to fall on me hey look
there's another one right there hey look
there's 10 over there those guy those
chem trolls are going to hit me now no
this is a good piece of information to
know know the Chemtrails you see are not
coming down on you they're not if you
can see it it's not coming down on you
they're coming down on somebody else
miles away the chemtrail that comes down
in you you can't see it's already come
down it's already been heading down and
comes down they float through the sky
and they dissipate and they drop miles
after miles after miles and they fall
down on somebody else the ones you see
in the sky anyway so the planes they
drop these chemical soups all day all
night non-stop but non-stop all night
all day all night all day chemical
byproducts are forever being produced by
the chemical industry if you're
wondering what byproduct I'm talking
about it's endless really I mean it's
endless so many things that are man-made
out there they prod everything man-made
produces chemical
byproduct from many Industries including
the petrochemical Industries throughout
the world the entire world the byproduct
is highly toxic and it can't be dumped
in the ocean like I said in one shot you
dump all this in the ocean in one shot
shot you guys and the ocean's dead
that's it every the whales die
everything dies that would happen you
dump all this stuff if all the if the
chemical industry opened up the
floodgates and let everything roll into
the ocean at once all their backlog
their trillions of gallons the ocean
would die and one shot and turn deep red
blood red and every single dolphin would
die you know a fraction of this
byproduct just a fraction of this
byproduct I'm talking about sent down a
major river would kill the entire River
and all the foliage and plant life
within the river and around
it it has to be dropped
strategically the chemicals have to be
dropped
strategically out of ples in our
atmosphere to thin out and spaced out
enough so it doesn't show the immediate
harm on our environment and
nature Spirit of compassion says to me
and always has the plan is as you drop
it slowly Spirit of compassion told me
as you drop it slowly out of the sky it
gives our oceans rivers and lakes and
forests time to
adapt I always that always blew my mind
Spirit of compassion would say it
lessens the shock on the environment it
gives everything a chance to
adapt and that was wild to me that was
wild the other plan was for some of it
to stay in the clouds intermix with
precipitation and becom somewhat
diffused by The Living Water that's rain
rain's rain's electric it's electric
that's what rain is it's got a charge to
it and that living water that charge
that was that was part of the plan that
it could diffuse some of it so the plan
was hopefully it stays in a lot of
clouds you've heard about acid rain
right acid rain H you know the thing
that everybody says smog is the culprit
for but there's much more than that it's
much more than just
smog it's it's a lot to do with the
Chemtrails because the Chemtrails a lot
of it a decent amount of it does stay up
there and it eventually comes down in
the
rain I talked about rain being toxic and
you don't want if you're somebody that's
sick and you got symptoms and you're
hypers sensitive you don't want to be
drenched by the rain all the time
because he might feel a little sick and
a little sicker along the way you know
look
Chemtrails is why our skies aren't blue
anymore okay and they're hazy blue the
chemicals that stay in the air and hover
before they even drop change the color
color of our Sky look you might be
somebody that's young and when you're
young you just think this guy is as blue
as it is and that's it but when you talk
to older people like older people
they're like they know what a deep blue
sky looks like
you know photographs from our skies you
guys in the 1940s and the 1950s and
early 1960s are vastly different than
are photographs today of a sky unless
you put filters on them and photoshoop
them and change the colors with your
computer right what a game that is
unbelievable hiding the sky we mostly
have Misty baby blue skies now not rich
Clear Blue Skies we have become the frog
in a pot of boiling water in some
respects each new generation doesn't
know how rich and clear and blue the sky
was in the past you are born and raised
with the new Sky we have which is all
you know just like the frog doesn't know
the temperature of the water is getting
hot until it's too late we don't know
the skies are becoming less
blue when the chemtrails accumulate they
Shadow areas of the world wreaking havoc
on Epic levels because of the drowning
out of our
sun it changes the weather it does
interesting it changes the weather our
weather has changed our climate has
changed because of chem
trails and I'm not talking about the
cloud seeding trail that is known or the
cloud seeding technique that is known
where they use barium and other
substances to manipulate
precipitation Chemtrails is a whole
other thing going on it's separate from
cloud
seeding that's a whole another point to
know the Chemtrails they cause droughts
in places that shouldn't have droughts
they can cause more rain in areas it
shouldn't Chemtrails interferes with
weather patterns because the chemicals
Harbor metals and metals interfere with
electrical activities of our skies
because our skies are electrical it
creates storms where storms shouldn't be
created it even manipulates hurricanes
Cyclones and tornadoes but even worse
our polar caps are melting because of
chemtrails I don't think you guys saw
that one coming right because I know
there's a lot of polar cap people that
are worried and you're just like oh my
God the polar caps are melting there's a
lot of people out there like I can ask
that I get asked all kinds of questions
I got friends that ask me questions all
through the years I mean you wouldn't
believe what people ask me when when
they know me they'll be like look tell
me tell me the hard truth about
something I'll be like what
what and the polar caps yeah and it
causes the waters to rise yeah is the
waters Rising yeah they're Rising ever
so slow slowly but they're Rising but
the Chemtrails are the true reason why
the waters are rising at all not the
fake reason which is just smug and
animal pollution and people pollution
those are bad don't get me wrong smog is
terrible pollution's bad but they're
nothing like chemtrails
here's the the strange thing about
Chemtrails governments have nothing to
do with Chemtrails World governments all
around all around the planet have
nothing to do with the Chemtrails how
weird is that and they have no power to
stop them either or even understand them
it's a private
club and the power behind this club is
like no other governments have to
pretend it's not happening like they
just whistle
like no that's not happening nope nope I
don't see you know I don't see any
trails in this guy I don't know what
that is they got to pretend it doesn't
exist you know what's funny too is it
makes the pharmaceutical industry look
like friendly happy and
safe makes big Pharma look like awesome
just like they've never done wrong they
can't do wrong big farm is like
incredible they can't do no wrong ever
with anything you know how do you solve
a problem that no one really knows about
how do you solve a problem that is above
all
laws how do you solve a problem that's
Global I can't solve the problem I can't
get people off of
eggs I can't get people off of eggs eggs
that are feeding the viruses that are
responsible for chronic fatigue and all
their other symptoms and conditions you
know eggs being one of the things that
actually feed bugs and then the bugs are
responsible these viruses are
responsible so I can't get people off of
eggs I can't can't get people off of
nutritional yeast all that MSG they
don't know they're eating so I know I
can't solve this problem I can't Spirit
of compassion told me when I was young
that the man poison
Club is an evil
machine from what I learned from Spirit
of compassion you don't stop it and you
don't fight it cuz you'll never
win at least not that
way you have to accept it and then you
rise above it Spirit of compassion told
me you rise above it why am I talking
about this now you know and I waited for
years well you know I'm always focused
on you guys with chronic illness and all
the symptoms and conditions and hundreds
of symptoms and conditions that medical
medium information has reversed and
saved lives for so many years and then
the Advanced Medical information
Alternative Health that that that Spirit
of compassion put out there for years A
lot of it that goes right back to me
some of it that got lost in the wood
work out there and people use little
tidbits from Spirit of compassion and
don't even know where it comes from but
out of all that you know I'm always
focused on getting you guys better and
well I waited for years for somebody
else to discover what was really going
on and it's kind of that thing where I
bring out all those hard truths about
the caffeine industry and I bring out
the truth about autoimmune and I bring
out the truth about how to heal in the
viruses and what viruses and how they
been have how they've been let out in
our environment all these decades and
why people are sick with chronic
symptoms and conditions I bring out all
these truths that no one brings out in
alternative movement on any
level or conventional movement on any
level I'm busy with all that so I just
kind of sat back and I'm like you know
what I mean someone's got to figure this
out I I can't do it
all I can't do it all I can't just I
mean I have so much on my plate to
deliver out there so you would think by
now someone could have had figured it
out or what's really going on but it's
above anything we understand so I
understand why they have haven't I mean
look I have to get the information from
Spirit of
compassion and look if you're an asay or
somebody call it a theory if you want if
that makes you feel good if somebody
else call it make believe if you want if
it makes you feel good whatever whatever
works but here's the
problem it's going to get worse and
worse and worse over time the amount of
planes that have been increased just in
the last 30 years is
remarkable remarkable The Fleets are
Mass and growing larger and they run all
day and all night and they never stop
that's how much
chemical is being poured on
everyone in the future you won't really
see a video on any reality TV show or a
video or photograph on someone's social
media page with a sky free of
chemtrails contrails don't leave a Long
Trail they dissipate fast and it only
extends the small distance from the jet
engines Chemtrails go for a long long
way they can go for miles and miles as
the planes are flying the pilot slips a
he flips a
switch so that's what happens there's
this pilot on the plane he's got a
switch to his side and he clicks the
button he just he's he flips the switch
and then the pump goes on so there's a
pump going to the tanks and so the pump
turns on and it pumps the stuff out of
the tanks the chemicals out of the tanks
while the plane is flying and then
spouts on the side of the plane that are
bolted to the sides of the plane because
they're fabricated and built that way
and these these these jets these spout
Jets on the side of the plane release
the chemical as the pump is pumping it
out of the big tanks and
then and then the chemical comes
shooting out of the spouts attached to
the plane sometimes you'll see a trail
go on for Miles right and and then it'll
stop 10 Mi later you'll see the It Go On
Again meaning you'll see the trail start
again the pilot is actually switching a
switch on and
off at the Pilot's own discretion some
Pilots go 20 miles before they switch it
on and off no Rhyme or Reason in many
cases it depends on what mood the
Pilot's in or maybe the Pilot's new to
it all it's first time on the job and he
releases it all at once and then lands
empty the the Pilot's job is to spread
it on and off through the whole duration
of that flight people who are aware of
chemrail think that it comes out of the
engines like they think that's must be
where the trail is coming from it
doesn't come out of the engines that's
not the fuel burning that's not what
that is Spirit of compassion fills me in
on these techniques and look you can
witness some of this yourself if if you
pay attention and you look up at the sky
but I know a lot of people they're
they're a little too busy and they're
not looking at the sky at all what's
interesting about Chemtrails is that the
activity of chemtrails is heightened in
areas where people will be outside more
you know during holidays and Gatherings
and vacation times of the year or when
people are just outside more when the
weather's really good and that's when
more activities happening not because
people are there and they're seeing it
not at all and that's not it but way
more activity more Chemtrails are being
dropped everywhere covering Skies when
people are out
more it's gone beyond the process of
getting rid of just chemicals and
byproduct um spirit and compassion
filled me in that there might have been
maybe the first intention originally
which is get rid of the byproduct get
rid of the
chemicals that was the safest way
someone thought the problem could be
dealt with and you know what maybe there
was a little bit of Innocence originally
with the problem maybe at the very
beginning in the 60s someone was worried
about dumping everything directly in the
Lakes because the demand the chemical
industry was so you know strong and they
were thinking maybe this was the best
idea as you put it up in planes and you
slowly drop it out and maybe they had a
good think tank with it too a lot of big
thinkers but I think there could be a
second intention you know the fact that
they drop more of it when everybody's
around Spirit of compassion told me that
it's possible that yeah there's a second
intention that developed because
whenever the weather is nice like I said
holidays around the world and so forth
it act the activity increases
greatly areas are strategically mapped
out all around the world there is a
method to this madness you guys there's
a method to this madness it's the
ultimate trick played upon us so you're
taking your selfie you have the sky
behind you and there's a streak going
across the
sky it's something I've learned to
accept throughout the decades in my life
as I look up and I see them all that
there's no fixing it it's one example of
how we have a spiritual war happening
you you might have heard me mention
spiritual war recently I'm going to be
talking about that more and more and
more more what's happening it's good
versus evil oh wait wait you might be
somebody that doesn't think there's
anything bad going on you might be
somebody that doesn't think there's evil
on any level and you think maybe
everybody has a good heart you know or
everybody's just kind of misdirected but
they're really good inside and they do
bad things and no there's there's
Darkness there is there is you know to
be more
precise hey evil tricking the good how
about that instead of good versus evil
evil tricking the good so the good
doesn't even know there is a fight one
of the examples of how we have evil
people in the world using their Free
Will well this is definitely one of
those examples of people doing evil
things it's a prime example of how
things aren't what they seem to be and
we stay distracted on other
environmental projects and I wonder if
you're thinking about that a little bit
while this thing that I'm talking about
here the chemtrail Saga the chemtrail
game well this one is completely ignored
organizations that are formed to protect
the environment right many that you know
they're aware of these Chemtrails but
they just ignore them too cuz they got
to they know they have to there's no way
of addressing it it look they're not
aware of the complexities maybe of these
Chemtrails at all who is nobody really
is nobody is but nevertheless they're
aware of something happening up there
these Chemtrails are responsible for the
flocks of birds that mysteriously die
did you guys ever hear about that have
you ever seen that where out of nowhere
a thousand Birds die and they're all
over the streets and all over a village
and all over a town or they're all over
a a a baseball diamond somewhere or they
all over a field somewhere and someone
you know stumbles across them all these
flocks of birds dying everywhere around
the planet at once the birds that swarm
and migrate just die and they hit the
ground and they rain it's raining birds
why is that happening the birds are
hitting pockets of these Chemtrails up
in the sky cuz the Chemtrails vary from
super super toxic sometimes deadly toxic
sometimes partially toxic somewhat
dangerous and because it's different
batches of old poisonous toxins you know
and stockpiles from any decade that
could be loaded up into the plane and
dropped over in the present moment right
now that's been in storage forever so
these birds hit these pockets of
dangerous chemicals up in the
sky and birds that are migrating in
massive swarms and SW and and swarms and
flocks occasionally they run into this
thick
Vaper and then dead birds rain on the
towns and here's the sad part that's
just when we see the birds what about in
all the places the birds fly the
Wilderness the forests and you don't see
them fall and die in there you know like
if a tree falls in the
woods you know if you don't hear it did
it really fall or whatever you know that
whole saying you guys could probably you
guys could say that better than I could
right now I'm sure but well hey if a
thousand birds at a clip fall into the
forest and no one hears it no one sees
it did it really happen yeah it did it
did happen it
did because birds fly in these swarms
and flocks over vast amounts of land
that are not populated by humans
Chemtrails will be the end of our birds
in the coming years way down the road
Birds won't be
chirping there are less Birds now than
ever before in our history and then hey
I got to drop this one on you right now
just you know did you did you do you
have your tea your herbal tea are you
relaxing are you sitting down what about
the bees you you guys care about the
bees right I know I do I have a bee
meditation in the medical medium book
one along with other powerful
meditations that have have helped people
heal well you guys care about the bees
there are theories that maybe it's the
GMO food killing the bees oh I could see
it now someone just got upset they're
saying wait a minute he's Pro GMO no I'm
not anybody who knows me knows that's
the last thing if you read my books I'm
not pro GMO okay and I tell you things
about GMO people don't know about in the
GMO industry but with the but from
Spirit of compassion of course it's
where I get my unique original
information but here's the thing you
know yeah GMO food is not helping out
the bees it's true for for a mult
multitude of reasons and I know that but
there's a more predominant problem the
Chemtrails the Chemtrails are killing
the
bees yes huh the Chemtrails Rain On The
Beekeeper
and the bees it's crazy how that works
right isn't that bizarre you know how
the beekeeper is smoking out the bees to
get the
honey a little smoke smoke
canister well the Chemtrails are smoking
out The Beekeeper as he's doing that and
the
bees what's the irony to that one it's
so it's so crazy you know when the bees
are docile and they're crawling around
on the ground and they're just dying a
slow death have you ever seen a honeybee
just crawling around and you're like
honeybee I want to help you I want to
help you get to a flower I want to get
you to a flower get a little twig get a
leaf and get the honeybee as he's
crawling he must just need to go back on
his flower and get some nectar maybe
he's unhappy what's wrong with him and
how many times have you heard that I
mean I've not only heard that but I've
seen that myself I've seen it I've seen
people talk to me about it like oh my
God you wouldn't believe these bees are
crawling on the ground and somebody be
like well it's the Time of the Season
well did the bees sting you and then the
Stinger's gone and that's why the bees
crawling on the ground no no that's not
why the bee's crawling on the
ground you know when those bees are
docile like that and crawling on the
ground like that they're dying a slow
death because of chemtrails birds and
bees are canaries in the coal mine they
go first before us and guess what goes
next the dragon flies they're dying
they're the other Canary they're getting
sicker and sicker and sicker and slower
and slower than ever and we need those
dragon flies we need those
desperately
butterflies bye-bye butterflies for the
future because butterflies are going to
take a big hit big hit from the
Chemtrails and they already are and then
we have the schools of fish wait a
minute you know the schools of fish that
die by the hundreds of thousands in our
oceans they wash up on the shore and
everybody's smelling dead fish and
freaking out environmentalists are
testing the water and freaking out and
nobody knows what happened at all it's
just nobody knows what happened and all
these fish are just sharks too sharks
everything is just coming up swordfish
everything any kind of fish is just you
know seab bass everything's just washing
up dead it it's unbelievable it's
unbelievable as it's sitting on the
beach rotting and then you hear well
wait a minute wait a minute maybe it was
the algae bloom and algae Bloom okay
yeah okay yeah sure of course where'
that algae bloom come from how does that
work that's why you see from time to
time the stories out there are
devastating about you know the amount of
dead fish and other sea life what about
other sea life not even fish just on the
shore rotting and what about all the
kill offs that aren't being talked about
or seen that's just the ones that are
seen you know Spirit of compassion you
know tells me about these chemical soups
that drop out of the PLS and what they
do they
pull you know they pull in areas of the
ocean that are more stagnant because of
different currents so the chemical soups
that have this mutated toxic algae
that's 50 60 years old sometimes that
just came out of an old tank and was
just recently stuck into a plane and
then dumped on us that algae okay that
dangerous toxic stuff it ends up
proliferating and thriving in more
stagnant areas naturally stagnant
because of just the current of you know
edies and oceans and and and movement
and all that and then fish swimming
along they're trying to get food whoa
schools of fish are like Whoa We got
some good stuff to eat we're going we're
going and they hit these poles of
chemicals and toxic mutated
microorganisms and algaes and they die
fast just like birds
instantly they just die and it's
immediately f for the fish and the birds
welcome to the Chemtrails welcome to the
Chemtrails in 20 years from now the
plane fleets will be increased greatly
the goal is the to have a vast Fleet the
chemtrail planes already take up a large
percentage of the sky as far as with the
flight patterns and everything and you
know what's crazy is the flight Towers
they just have to ignore it I mean
forget the radar well what are all these
planes oh they're not passenger planes
and what are they everybody has to
ignore it that's that is really
interesting right I know everybody's
worried about 5G right now and I'm going
to talk about 5G eventually and go into
that and if it affects her health or if
not or however I'm going to go into that
whole thing we're going to cover it and
we're going to get there don't worry and
spirit and compassion will have powerful
information nobody knows about it
meanwhile no one's worried about the
chemtrail game and yeah it's a game it's
a sick game I call it a game because
Spirit of compassion tells me it's
become one it has you know Spirit of
compassion tells me that the industry
the chemical Industries worldwide they
want us focused on other targets you
know they want us focused on 5G they
want us focused on anything else that's
bad they just don't want it focused on
those Chemtrails that's bad I call it a
game like I said cuz it's become one and
look they want us focused on this they
want us focused on plastic bags which is
it's good focus it is they want us to
focus on cups and straws and toilet
paper rolls you know like empty toilet
paper
rolls cans and bottles uh they want us
focus on creating less trash I think
it's all important I stand behind all of
that that that is important it CU it is
right but you know yeah it's like when
I'm taking the bottles you know and I'm
taking whatever like the recyclables to
the garbage and I look up and I see the
Chemtrails up there uh I I mean yeah I'm
looking at all the Chemtrails in the sky
while I'm trying to recycle stuff it's
it's it's a tough one to swallow right I
don't know it's it's hard for me because
I'm like maybe what cuz I know so much
about this stuff and you're just like
you're looking up at the sky and you see
10 Chemtrails and you're like what Brew
is that is that from 20 years ago is
that from 60 years ago what kind of
toxic crap is that coming down is it
pesticide you know byproduct is it an
herbicide byproduct what could what
could it be and you know you sit there
and then you put your recyclables in the
bin and look I mean you can look in this
guy many times and you'll see 30 40
Chemtrails just drifting along they
drift along
forever but I get it we have to do our
part and we have to be mindful about the
environment which I stand behind 100%
we're being Mindful and they're playing
a sick joke on us and look maybe you
don't see it that way I kind of do a
little bit the Chemtrails they settle in
the early morning de so check this out
this is an important piece of
information the Chemtrails they're
falling all night long and they fall
during the day too but there's a
difference in the morning right around
Dawn there's this moisture that occurs
and that moisture ends up on your car
windshield that moisture ends up on the
grass in the summertime where it's wet
in the morning and you'll find that
happening a lot and when you're walking
along you can even get soak and wet in
the grass if you're walking on a lawn
you know first thing in the morning
early that moisture holds in the air in
the morning and it holds on and suspends
all that chemtrail that's been dropped
down and it tends to Harbor underneath
the tree line so when people are jogging
and they're jogging they're running in
the morning out they're out in the
streets jogging running wherever they
are or they're walking on Trails or
whatever it is they're inhaling more
they're inhaling more the Chemtrails at
that time in the morning it hasn't kind
of lifted and blown away yet it hasn't
kind of moved and shaken out of it so
when we're doing our workouts and we're
doing that we're breathing in and
inhaling more chemtrail and we're
sweating and we're absorbing it into our
pores that's what happens and you know
that's why look we'll talk about some
tips and some things to just think about
protect ourselves and everything and all
that coming up but check this out our
skies are supposed to be sacred right I
mean do you think our skies are sacred
do they mean something to you when you
look up into the sky I mean you look up
there do you ever lay on your back on
the ground and you're looking at the
clouds as they're changing shape and you
see different shapes in the clouds and
we look up look at them in awe and we
think about the things hey there's a
horse up there look that cloud looks
like a horse hey that cloud looks like
something else and what about the fact
that we pray too so many people pray and
the sky means everything what about
meditation we meditate with a sensation
of something above us don't we like when
you meditate are you thinking or feeling
something above you when you're
meditating like the sky or the universe
that feeling above us and you know
children fly kites right in the sky you
look at the sky and you're flying a kite
on a windy day we feel the Sunshine on
our faces and we look at the falling
stars at night have you ever looked for
falling stars and you dream and we look
at the
constellations meanwhile what's going on
here on our planet yeah is sad and
corrupt this is one of the many reasons
why I get disappointed when people in
the health movement don't think we need
to cleanse and I'm going to repeat that
for a second people in the health
movement yeah there's many of them that
don't think we need to cleanse and if
they do think we need a cleanse it's a
cleanse that doesn't get any cleansing
done but
and if you're new to Medical medium
information you can learn about
cleansing everything sure and all that
and making sure you're doing it in a
really good way healthy way and you know
health professionals and hobbyists hacks
and health influencers and influencers
don't know what's causing our illness um
they don't know why everybody has
chronic fatigue syndrome and all the
different autoimmune varieties and and
rheumatoid arthritis and Hashim modus
thyroiditis and fatigue anxiety and and
you know everything else all the tingles
and numbness and aches and pains and
depression people don't know why chronic
illness is still just completely not
understood and
misunderstood unless they've gotten
tidbits from medical medium information
throughout the years you know like
celery juice therapeutically 16 o or 32
o or 64 ounces on an empty stomach and
how to use it making sure you don't mix
anything with it the world wasn't
drinking celery juice before Spirit of
compassion put it out there and in the
way therapeutically like you know he has
but everybody's a health expert these
days but what's interesting about
everybody being a health expert these
days they don't have a clue about why
we're even sick or what we're even up
against and this is just one reason why
we have to take care of ourselves is
because of this very reason here the
same reason why nobody knew what was
happening with these Chemtrails people
who believe Chemtrails exist don't know
how it works and everything else and I'm
giving you the I'm giving you the
information right now but hey that's
what I mean there's even more things
than that there's so much more and look
what's in the medical medium books about
why we're sick there's a reason why we
have to take care of ourselves we need
extra help but we need the right tools
your body needs to be
validated it needs to know you
understand its fight like you understand
what it's up against your body needs to
not only have like the right tools that
you possess to offer your body but it
needs to know you're in the game that
you're in it with it and that's the
whole thing because our bodies are on
their own and then we're all playing
guessing games that's how it works out
there you know it's like people they'd
rather just think that maybe you know
their health problem is a little bit
their gut their microbiomes off or
something their gut floor is off and
that's why everything like it's all in
their gut and that's why they're sick
and that's why they have eczema or acne
or any kind of other condition or
fatigue maybe they think it's genetics
too or it's hormones or they need to be
rewired and it's all in their head like
their train of thought isn't good and
it's time to rewire their mind or get
their meditations right and you know and
maybe it's okay if it's autoimmune and
your body's attacking itself kind of
thought but people they just don't
really give their bodies the
understanding their body needs and
that's a problem out there and I know a
lot of people they believe they're
Health experts or they want to become
Health experts and they don't know what
we're really up against or what causes
Hashimoto thyroiditis or what causes
rheumatoid arthritis or what causes
chronic fatigue or eczema and psoriasis
and anxiety and tingles and numbness and
AES and pains and vertigo and if you
don't know what causes all that and then
you don't know what contributes to all
of that and your body's like hey help me
um no it's it's not leaky gut nope um
it's no apple cider vinegar isn't the
answer it never got anybody with lupus
healed um uh Apple CER vinegar never uh
got somebody better with multiple
sclerosis uh please uh I need the
answers here I need help I need you to
believe in me and know what's wrong
there's toxic heavy metals and there's
Chemtrails falling out of the sky and
there's pathogens and bacteria viruses
and there's the Epstein bar and all in
petrochemicals in our system and
everything else and I need you to work
with me here and that's what our bodies
are like wanting but we get thrown off
track and and it happens every day I see
it out there people are worried about
collagen and you know I get it but
they're doing that while they're
guzzling down coffee and burning out
their adrenals I think look the bottom
line is it's about like are you going to
work with your body because it's not
hopeless it's not and I still got to I
got a cover more on chem trols I'm still
heading in there we got more information
about chem trols that I have to talk
about but it's not hopeless when you
work with your body and you look out for
it and you understand it and it
understands you and we just we work
together as the Chemtrails fall out of
the sky they have to land somewhere and
you might be somebody that's like hey I
eat really good food I eat grass-fed
beef but the chem Trails they got to
land on the
fields and the rain washes them into the
Earth too and if you maybe you're maybe
you don't eat animal products maybe
you're vegan maybe you're plant-based
and all the Chemtrails just on all our
vegetables it's on everything we eat and
the soil gets disrupted because it gets
depleted of zinc nobody knows about this
information I've talked about that
Metals fall from the sky that's the
Chemtrails I've been talking about all
these years you guys Metals fall from
the skies they soak into the store they
soak into the
soil and they destroy microorganisms the
soil born microorganisms in the soil
they kill the soil and they deplete it
of zinc and our soil becomes immune
deficient that's what happens from
Chemtrails now look we still need to eat
our Foods we still need to eat you know
our organic foods we can't get organic
we get you know conventional but the
point is is that we need to take care of
our body
while we're eating and living here we
have to adapt and then if you're doing
the animal proteins well I do I do
grass-fed beef somebody might say I got
it down I'll do a little grass fed beef
I do Freer range chicken or whatever and
animals or I do lamb or something
animals graze any kind of animals that
graze and they're eating grass or
they're eating meal of some kind that
was raised either way with chems falling
on it it was grown with chems falling on
it either way animals that graze in the
ground grass that grass is loaded with
Chemtrails and it builds up in
concentrations inside the animals so
that grassfed beef or grass-fed butter
will still have concentrations of
chemical soup that won't even be tested
because they don't they're not testing
for that they're not finding what's in
Chemtrails in our food that builds up in
our bodies when you eat it they're not
looking cuz they don't even know what to
look for guess what because 90% of the
chemicals falling out of the sky
from these Chemtrails are
unidentified they're privatized
chemicals they're secret soups and
recipes made by the chemical industry
that don't even they have their own that
don't even have patents never mind the
ones that are patented they're still
their own recipe no one knows what's in
most of the stuff especially their
mistakes and their test ones they're
test runs nobody knows what's in this
stuff so it's not even anybody's even
testing this stuff stuff in our food
that's how sad it is and if you don't
know how to assist your body in getting
this stuff out of you well it leads to
problems down the road and you might be
somebody that's like I don't want to
know about it I don't want to know I got
a friend that's like that just doesn't
want to know doesn't want to know what's
being dropped on them rather just you
know I want a glass of wine and just
leave me alone and I kind of want to do
my thing sure okay fine fine when you're
sick down the road whatever and but the
thing is that zinc deficiencies we all
have you know that's because the soil is
getting depleted by Chemtrails is being
a big part of it and when we have no
zinc in us or very little zinc in us
it's why we get sick from
viruses any kind of virus virus that's
going around whatever any kind of virus
the Epstein bars that people are passing
around the shingles viruses the hhv 6es
the hhv 7s the simplex 1 and Simplex 2
just because you had a cold sore years
ago doesn't mean that simplex virus
isn't living inside of our livers and
our bodies and wreaking havoc and giving
us other symptoms see nobody knows all
this information they just don't
understand that but you know in order to
adapt in order to take care of ourselves
we have to
adapt and that's a big part of it and
you know what's funny all the
information Spirit of compassion gives
me in the volumes I put out there and
the frontier head of Frontier
groundbreaking information in
alternative medicine conventional
medicine that that I've put out over the
years and with all of that you'll hear
out there lymphatic system Anthony
doesn't know about the lymphatic system
he doesn't know he doesn't know anything
about the lymphatic system it's
like are you kidding me my god do you
know anything about the
Chemtrails you know never mind that and
it's interesting you'll hear from people
like he doesn't know about the lymphatic
system you'll hear that from people that
don't know why anyone's sick they don't
know why people have viruses or what
kind of viruses or why people are sick
with anything or where toxic heavy
metals sit in the liver in the brain or
any of that stuff and if they did get a
tidbit of that somewhere so 35 years of
work of putting it out there Spirit of
compassion's work all these years you
know the health movement it was a small
small world it still is now but it was a
small world back 35 years ago really
really small and so that information I
just put it out there and put it out
there and put it out there you know but
what's interesting about the lymphatic
system is people be like hey doesn't
know about the lymphatic system you
kidding I've written about it in the
books but that's coming from people who
don't even know why anybody's sick like
I said before and really you got to go
deeper past the lymphatic system that's
where you have to go you have to go
where real problems are inside the body
like bigger problems much bigger
problems like deep in the liver because
that's what I've been talking about all
all these years and all these years
lymphatic system cleanses out its Poison
by default on its own it's doing that as
you live and breathe and and live your
life but if your liver's clogged up and
stagnant and sluggish and you got
low-grade viruses nobody wants to know
about because the lymphatic system isn't
why you have Lupus your lymphatic like
the lymphatic system isn't causing that
your lymphatic system is not causing
neurological symptoms it's not causing
tingles and numbness and aches and pains
and ticks and spasms and burning skin
and floaters in the eyes and severe
fatigue your lymphatic system doesn't do
that it doesn't create it's not causing
your edema it's coming from a deeper
Source it's coming from pathogens your
lymphatic system doesn't cause lupus it
doesn't cause Hashimoto it doesn't cause
lime it doesn't c yeah that's what's so
funny it's like oh it's the lymphatic
system that's really interesting but you
know your lymphatic system's health
happens to be a direct result of your
liver's Health it's a direct result of
if you have pathogens and that's what
people all have and they're all passing
around and if you're just focused on the
lymphatic system but not the real
problem it's like cleaning your house
you know you're cleaning your house
you're cleaning your bedroom you're
cleaning your rooms you're cleaning your
bathroom you're cleaning your kitchen
spotless you're scrubbing your kitchen
sink you know you're trying you're
cleaning it all that's your lymphatic
system you know you're cleaning
everything Meanwhile your basement has
rats fering in it mice festering and it
roaches ants and termites and they live
in your basement and they're breeding
and nesting and devouring the very
Foundation of your house but you're
worried about your lymphatic system and
you're cleaning the up upstairs there
and you're cleaning the upstairs and
you're not even you're you know that's
the thing so people pretending the
lymphatic system is why we're sick is
really a joke I mean that's a joke I
mean that's
101 um let's see beginners back I don't
know uh years ago when nobody knew what
why anybody's sick and once again well
is it candida uh is it lymphatic system
is it gut is it what is it it's back to
that game so it's kind of sad and when I
see that out there it's kind of sad
meanwhile yeah you drink your celery
juice and you're going to go for the
deeper problems therapeutically you do
your heavy metal detox smoothie you go
for the deeper problems therapeutically
go with 32 o of lemon water you go to
the deeper root like deeper and then
that's just the start of some of the
medical medium tools that got around
over the last 35 plus years and so when
you talk about the lymphatic system you
missed the point of allog together about
everything else the
pathogens everything we're dealing with
all the toxins like from the Chemtrails
we inhale daily that have to go into the
liver cuz that's where they go they go
into the liver and all these other
toxins they just go and they they make
our liver sick and stagnant and that has
to get sick and stagnant first for your
lymphatic system to even have any issues
you have there has to be a sicker deeper
problem you I'll be talking about the
lymphatic system in the future we're
going to do a whole podcast inside and
out about the lymphatic system but why
do I want you to do lemon water in the
morning more than 8 O much more than 8 O
why do I want you to do lemon water 16
to 32 o because it's purifying more than
just your lymphatic system I'm trying to
go for the deeper stuff I'm trying to go
for the deeper stuff not the surface
stuff I'm not trying to go for the
surface stuff the lymphatic system isn't
why somebody's bedridden and they got
like the worst hives and lupus and
migraines and trigeminal neuralgia and
their back is killing them and they
could barely walk and they're feet hurt
that's not the lymphatic system I mean
it's so embarrassing when I think about
it it's so beginner stupid I mean I'm
sorry I'm sorry it's just look
anyway the lemon water is critical for
flushing to get to the Deep rooted
things the cell juice is critical for
using it therapeutically to destroy
pathogens that are deep inside the liver
deep ins seter organs that are in their
bloodstream and so forth you know and
the celer juice is disarming these
toxins that fall from the sky and all
that stuff see the tools are all here
I've always had you in mind for what we
face and what you don't know you face
out
there Chemtrails are part of the
spiritual war that's going on around us
and above us Mercury is part of that
spiritual war that's going around us the
caffeine industry is part of that
spiritual war that's going on around us
so many pieces of the puzzle that show
us there's good versus evil and how evil
looks for ways to control people and
then keeps them controlled and then gets
them sick and has The Thirst to keep
them sick forever if possible and then
wants them relying on everything they
just don't really need Darkness never
wants her eyes open and see what's in
the sky and above the trees it would
rather have us unknowing its time and
then bring us to our knees they keep us
busy down here distracted some are bored
they want us to lose ourselves in our
minds while all the bad around us keeps
getting ignored there is hope when
you're empowered though you have the
truth on your side and the knowledge and
you support your body with what it needs
and you understand your body as it cries
for help and asks you please when you're
on the same page with your body then
you're in the
game see that's what matters in order to
let the good things in life remain when
you have the tools and you apply them
right you are unstoppable against evil
and you're gaining all the Insight
because as they drop that stuff down on
us you can laugh at it as it's coming on
on down it's not going to get in your
way because you're taking care of
yourself now you can say I'm in control
of my life I got the wisdom I got the
Deep spiritual Insight I have control
over my well-being you're not going to
take control over me see I can live my
life the way I want to be and keep from
getting sick and recover if I've been
sickened if need be I'm not blind when I
look at the sky the Wall's not over my
eyes anymore I can see past the Horizon
I could see past the madness I can see
past the smoke and see past the fog I
can use my own free will to determine
where life is going to go for me I can
fight to be free and heal my body and
see the path where it's going for me
remember this your body has the power to
heal and can override through thick and
thin and our bodies fight for us as we
acknowledge and validate our B's fight
along the way then nothing can get in
the way see I believe in you and I know
you can
heal as you guys know I'm not a doctor
any information you learned here feel
free to take to your doctor or
healthcare provider if you found this
show helpful and informative feel free
to share it with someone in need of the
information if you like this show Please
Subscribe and leave a review on Apple
podcasts you can also find me on YouTube
Facebook and Instagram at Medical medium
and for more information on healing
please visit medical
medium.com thank you so much for
listening
oh