how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William let's talk about fruit fear and
how dangerous fruit fear has become they
lied to you and they lie straight to
your face so that you do the dirty work
for them and spread their lies and
disinformation far and wide over time
they rob and steal any chance for you to
heal they keep you lost and scared and
keep you in fear fruit is bad fruit can
harm you fruit can kill you avoid fruit
they say there's some realities you must
know about the war on fruit did you hear
that I said the war on fruit
yeah and where it's leading us in our
coming days the results of what happens
when fruit fear in the health movement
completely gets its way and no one wants
to eat any fruit because they're totally
afraid and scared so let me give you a
picture of what will take place not too
far off in the distant future and so let
me tell you a story so let's go into it
now the demand for fruit grows smaller
and smaller as as the years go by
grocery stores worldwide are throwing
away more and more fruit because people
aren't buying it this leads us to the
health food stores and grocery stores
ordering less and less fruit fruit
juices such as apple juice and other
organic Whole Food pure juices just sit
on the store shelves and collect dust
and no more is restocked and ordered
because of the fear spread by the fruit
demonizer that 100% pure organic juices
are dangerous for your health and can
even kill you more and more anti fruit
propaganda keeps on being promoted
nonstop without any science and research
showing us evidence that fruit is bad
for us Fruit Farms Orchards orange
groves Bramble Farms watermelon patches
melon patches banana Farms pineapple
Farms are not making enough money to
keep equipment running and Manpower they
just shut down land that's owned by
these fruit farmers both small farms and
big farms have to burn their Orchards
and Groves down in order to clear the
land to try to reestablish a new way of
living fruit farm land that is least
they build housing on and also burn all
the Orchards down the amount of burning
worldwide of these fruit trees and
brambles will be
catastrophic this will admit tremendous
amounts of smoke and Ash into the
atmosphere hindering Wildlife
globally and because there's that much
ancient fruit land and Farms that have
been here feeding the populations for
hundreds of years and when it goes up in
flames it's
disastrous every season as the fruit
naturally drops and sits on the ground
in The Orchards it feeds animals and
Wildlife like deer and moose bear Fox
birds and other Wildlife before winter
comes it keeps them alive and gives them
a fighting chance to survive the Year
this disappears and so does a large
portion of wildlife that has been
feeding on Fallen fruit for hundreds of
years bees already are losing the
ability to thrive in the future they're
lack last chance of survival will end
with the loss of the blossoms from the
cherry blossoms apple blossoms pear
blossoms Peach blossoms nectarine
blossoms and Plum blossoms and
watermelon blossoms and virtually every
other
fruit bees rely on fruit trees and their
fruit blossoms worldwide to sustain and
survive and because there aren't enough
wild flowers to feed them already never
mind in the future they're going to
suffer greatly
experts in the health field are unaware
of this environmental change that's on
its way and the ecosystem shift that
will occur fruit is one of the most
important parts of our ecosystem without
its balanced it will be thrown off and
it will trigger famine and loss of life
and the slow destruction of our
environment on an inner way and every
way meat butter milk cheese yogurt has
become scarce and hard to find without
the pollinators it will affect
livestock grass-fed beef from grass-fed
cows don't eat grass only they are in
the fields eating wild flowers from
herbs that prevent the cows from getting
disease with the loss of the pollinators
Bine viruses and bacteria will dominate
and livestock will have to be put down
in the masses because the bees spread
immune system building properties to
each Wildflower for the cow to consume
and now that the bees are gone the cows
at graze are not getting their
medicine phytochemical compounds pass
from flower to Flower by the bees in the
fields the livestock grze in support
their immune system meanwhile Health
influencers on social media will Echo
the no fruit propaganda more than ever
before while they are battling their new
found symptoms and conditions not
realizing how important fruit was and is
for the world or their own healing
process the largest percent of the food
supply for the bees are fruit trees and
fruit blossoms now that these are gone
there will be pockets of be famine in
areas all around the world where they
just disappear quickly until they're
finally finished and when the bees are
gone the butterfly flies follow and
these Godly pollinators are a big part
of how our whole food chain survives
honey which is a medicine that will be
needed in the future because of our
broken immune systems and the viral
plagues to come will be rare and too
pricey for almost anyone to purchase
propolis will be a critical Hidden Gem
that is sparse and needed and finally
disappears hummingbirds that migrate in
the spring rely on fruit blossoms to
survive because there's not enough wild
flowers in Blossom during the spring so
large portions of the hummingbirds will
disappear and die because they can't
make their Journey without the fruit
blossoms then there's the industries
that will capitalize on The
Disappearance of fruit fruit flavorings
will explode in the marketplace
synthetic fruit flavorings that will be
deemed safe by paid for science and
research will be in high demand because
of the loss of the real fruit in the
world and people will long for Fruity
sweet flavoring of raspberry strawberry
and
watermelon the chemical industry will go
into production and the amount of
chemical byproduct produced will be
destroying the ecosystem even more
children will never get to experience
eating a piece of fruit in their
childhood and won't receive bioavailable
vitamin C and other antiviral compounds
from fresh fruit during a critical time
their immune system is in development
infertility will be on the rise more
than ever before women's reproductive
system diseases will worsen and be at a
level we have never even dreamed of
women's diets will be lacking fruit more
so than ever before it will be rare a
woman has one piece of of fruit a year
which will worsen infertility and this
will threaten the existence of the human
race how did we get to this place at
this point in time in the future no one
realized that they were being used and
lied to about fruit so let's talk about
today you guys did you ever think about
what could happen like if fruit is just
done like gone there's a Tipping Point
where stuff just goes wrong just like
when someone's sick and they get sicker
and sicker and sicker there's a Tipping
Point there too that you never want to
be in or never want to go to so in the
present moment right now women's
infertility is on the rise you know
fibroids endometriosis PCOS reproductive
cysts reproductive cancers because women
aren't eating enough fruit that's
actually a part of it I mean there's a
lot of part of it but that's a part of
it there a lot of pieces instead women
are told to eat eggs eggs that's what
they're told to do it's like replace
fruit something that's been around
forever and just no just eggs replace
everything I guess because that's what
it is is everybody's told to eat eggs
which ironically eggs worse in
reproductive system conditions by
feeding the very viruses that cause
women's reproductive system diseases and
symptoms and conditions right and so
I've talked about that for eggs feed
viruses viruses that are in the
reproductive system creating fibroids
cysts PCOS infertility you know fruit is
antiviral and it's being taken away and
you're like what no way it's not being
taken away how's that possible you know
people can make choices they can have
fruit or not yeah well everybody's being
told not to eat fruit these days fear
fruit fear big time and it's
infectious it really is infectious it's
easy to get tricked I mean you haven't
yet maybe you're maybe you're like a
lucky one that's like didn't even know
about it or something but it's so
infectious where it's like instantly
like what fruit's bad well it's going to
feed mold it's going to feed something
what is it going to do create candida
it's going to make me sick is it what
and that's what everybody's doing now
and look fruit is critical in keeping
our immune system strong
I'm just scratching the surface right
here of the
sabotage that a small group of health
authori started more than 10 years ago
did you hear
that because I hope you heard that
Sabotage by a small group of Health
authorities over 10 years ago that had a
master plan and we just buying into it
yes there were certain individuals who
started fruit fear yeah get that message
get that memo now because it's a big
deal and and they were purposely planted
into the health world to spread one of
the largest greatest deceptions in lies
of our day that fruit is bad fruit is
harmful fruit's dangerous I'll spell it
out for you okay I'll just spell it
right out just straight out people were
planted by IND Industries to purposely
spread disinformation about fruit in the
holistic health movement to stop people
from eating fruit and it's
ingenious ingenious because it's
working it's actually brilliant because
it's working that's how good at it they
are and it convince good-hearted
professionals and health like look
you're probably thinking no no my
practitioner is a great person of course
of course your practitioner is a great
person of course your doctor's a great
person of course your health coach is a
great person they got Pure
intentions absolutely but they get
convinced that fruit needs to be avoided
you see especially the sweeter fruits
have you heard that one like oh yeah
stay away from sweet fruits stay away
from sweet fruits hard to believe
whether you believe it or you don't it's
reality see I know there is something
you guys know a lot of people in health
know okay and it's that there are
certain industries in the conventional
medicine world that love us being sick
they love it they love us being sick
with chronic illness right you know
about this you guys know about this to
sell drugs and everything you you know
the whole story that's been out there
that part anyway if we get healthy and
you get you start living longer and you
get healthier we're less dependent on
what they're selling to try to Keep Us
Alive you know all the stuff they try to
Keep Us Alive with like drugs and stuff
or you can look at it this way to keep
us sick however you want to look at it
they go broke if we stay healthy or
we're just not really that sick at all
sickness is the money making machine duh
duh and you guys know this totally right
but there's something you don't know I'm
going to drop a whole bunch of more
stuff you guys don't know and it's this
it infected a part of the alternative
medicine world
Jeepers it got to the herbalist who once
knew fruit was good for us many years
ago it got to the Cairo in the village
the chiropractor in the village who
never had a problem with bananas until
now forget it chiropractor is not going
to recommend bananas anymore very few
have ever unless they got reignited by
fruit information that's been spreading
around from medical medium information
all these years to fight this battle and
and this information even you know this
misinformation fruit fear got to the
Healer in the next town that loved
giving people apples to help them heal
recommended them but now no more no way
stay away from those sweet apples the
strategy was to put out the word that
fruit causes multiple problems right you
heard it diabetes oh stay away from
fruit with diabetes you know
pre-diabetes stay away from fruit right
hypoglycemia stay away from fruit gut
problems stay away from fruit you got
any gut problems go God forbid anybody
with sibo or anything like that just
don't eat fruit uh it feeds
candida if you got candida or it's going
to give you candida causes it or you got
lime disease stay away from fruit and
causes cancer don't eat a piece of fruit
oh don't eat don't eat that cherry it's
going to cause cancer oh wait don't have
any fruit because it's going to rot your
teeth or causes UTI you guys might have
heard that before right yeah yeah it's
unbelievable and any other condition you
can think of so fruit was weaponized oh
man how can like something that like
simple something that pure something
that natural be weaponizing like
weaponized like what is he talking about
right you're probably like thinking it
was weaponized it was weaponized
purposely against the chronically ill
the underdog it was weaponized against
the underdog slowly against the
chronically ill not all at once though
this is a slow progression and it's
kicking in gear more and more and here's
the thing you guys partly why it's slow
is because people's Common Sense
understands that fruit probably isn't
bad that's what's funny everybody's
Common Sense knows somewhere in the back
of their mind somewhere in the back of
their skull somewhere in there that
fruit is actually good or fruit can't be
bad it's in all of us it's in our heads
okay all of us it can't be bad how can
it be and that's what made this whole
fruit take down this weaponizing the war
on fruit take longer because people are
like not totally getting tricked they're
just like what and so people still eat a
little bit of fruit in places so the
industries planted fruit demonizes in
health movement and this is the next
part I'm going to talk about the
industries planted fruit haters fruit
fear creators okay demonizes to inspire
good intentioned health experts good
intentioned health
authorities that fruit was bad and then
have that shrinkle down to local Hol
holistic health experts like in your
town like in your village on social
media cool people doing their thing you
know like health health coaches and you
know and trainers and all kinds of
people have incredible intentions that
actually want their people better and
stronger but they get totally
confused and that's how it worked they
became convinced that fruit is harmful
for anyone so they attack Fruit on
social media in the doctor's offices
this doesn't mean that everyone who fell
sucker into this attack on fruit is
involved so I don't want you thinking if
someone is ripping down fruit ripping it
apart right you're like oh my God they
must be one of those planted people in
the industry that you know no that's not
it it I'll talk about who those might be
in a minute but it's spreading like
wildfire by good people not purposely
but it got to all the good people and so
all the good people with good intentions
doing good stuff in health they're like
no fruit's bad stay away from it watch
out no sweet fruit fruits don't eat that
don't eat this okay but there are
certain individuals that played a role
in starting this fruit fear in the
beginning they started the war on fruit
and started the lie that fruit causes
harm it was a bad seed man planted in a
dark way to bring us where we are today
with no merit no science no evidence no
proof in any way way that fruit causes
anything or is bad for you no proof and
even the most basic lie of all at the
start that fruit feeds candida or fruit
causes
candida you know an apple doesn't feed
candida you guys but chocolate cake will
you know vegan or animal-based chocolate
cake so let's talk about what what's in
Fruit let's go into that a little bit
cuz I think that's important right there
trace minerals did is that something you
don't want in you trace minerals is that
bad uh phytochemical compounds that are
critical for healing like anti-cancerous
compounds wait a minute fruits loaded up
with anti-cancerous compounds uh you
don't want that in you um vitamin C you
don't want that in you either right no
that's bad vitamin C uh anti-cancerous
compounds antiviral compounds are in
Fruit oh you don't want that in you
especially right now with what's going
down especially every
scared crapless right now just you know
and locked in their homes okay so you
don't you don't want antiviral compounds
that's in Fruit antibacterial compounds
antifungal compounds nutrients totally
packed with nutrients all kinds
undiscovered also antioxidants Living
Water critical glucose no everybody
would rather not have any fruit but
drink some maybe coffee from a coffee
shop that has straight tap water right
from City tap water and but stay away
from a piece of fruit with living water
in it that's pure and you know what else
fruit has fruit has worm expelling
properties so everybody's freaking out
about worms are looking in the toilet
you know and they're looking in the
toilet they're looking for a worm that's
5 in long that's really just some food
all like interwined and wrapped around
itself and or maybe you know I always
tell people the matter what if you're
going to see a worm go in the toilet it
better be moving and it better be
swimming then you can guarantee that was
a worm and but I'll tell you right now
fruit has worm expelling
properties what's in Fruit they say that
they say okay the demonizer say sugar
and sugar is bad so hey you you know
that right sugar is bad you hear it all
the time that's what you hear fruit
sugar sugar bad what huh did you know
with without sugar you die interesting
so without sugar you die uh that's a
funny one did you know every single
movement you make task you do thought
you think uh words you speak hello is
because of glucose that's
glucose and there are sugar in the foods
you think have no sugar check this out
all right let's go into it a little bit
there is sugar in Foods you think ain't
got no sugar all right meat for example
I can't have sugar in it meat are you
kidding caramelized sugar when you cook
meat it's caramelized sugar in there
where' it come from well no one talks
about it because I guess nobody knows or
something let me tell you where it comes
from it comes from the blood of the
animal which was loaded with sugar
glucose the animal can only survive say
like a cow eating grass which is sweet
believe it or not right down to the root
there's a lot of Sweetness in there all
that Sugar from that grass all right
that gets munched up and munched up and
and basically Juiced in that cow's mouth
and that sugar right there is their
glucose for grassfed beef and and the
animal's blood sugar so it could survive
and stay strong and
Thrive so when you cook a piece of meat
which I'm Pro meat I'm Pro plant-based
too you know but when you cook a piece
of meat because that's what you like if
that's what you like when you're cooking
it there's sugar in it and then when
you're cooking it it
caramelizes that's what happens with
sugar the minute you put heat to it the
minute you cook with it it caramelizes
so that's that's the the blood sugar and
it's never measured it's not measured on
any scale science and research doesn't
care about it no I just care about
protein they don't care about the sugar
and meat you know they never dial it in
they will never tell you how much sugar
is in a piece of meat or Animal product
and this isn't an anti-animal product
campaign I don't have a diet belief
system anybody who's know knows medical
medium information is whatever diet
belief system you have I'm about
plugging in powerful tools so you can
make it work work for your belief so you
can heal so I'm Pro meat I'm Pro
plant-based but listen without sugar you
hit the floor you lay down and you
slowly die and there is sugar in the
foods that you love that are fat-based
so you're thinking that's ridiculous I
don't die when I eat all my fatty foods
I'm not dying yeah because avocado has
sugar in it avocado has plenty of sugar
in it by the way hey you know remember
that story I told you at the beginning
in this podcast avocados won't be around
either in the future cuz they're going
to need to be pollinated by a lot of
bees in order to keep the supply of
avocados going and avocados hey if you
love them and they're part of our trendy
diet now they won't be here in the
future cuz the bees will be gone if the
war on fruit continues there won't be
any more bees there won't be enough
avocado trees or bees this is say people
who love them you know byebye avocado
toast it's gone it's
toast which is kind of funny because
toast anyway which is sugar even though
it's gluten-free it's still sugar but
you didn't think you eat really any
sugar right because a lot of people say
I don't eat any sugar really and they're
like hey I'm really enjoying my avocado
toast which is great because avocados
are the healthiest one of the healthiest
fats right if you're going to have fats
it's one of them but think about that
there's plenty of sugar in the avocado
cuz that's what keeps you functioning
it's that sugar and in that gluten-free
toast it's sugar but don't eat a piece
of fruit have that but never touch fruit
oh it's bad because it's sugar fruit's
sugar now and so don't touch a piece of
fruit but have avocado toast which the
toast is sugar basically straight sugar
it's all sugar and then avocado which
has sugar in it there is sugar in nuts
and seeds too you guys your nut Butters
peanut butter almond butter
that sugar is what allows you to
function it's not the fat allowing you
to function and keeping your brain
functioning but that's what someone
wants you to believe that was planted
quite a few years back you know one of
the moles the plants the fruit demonizes
paid for to actually distract people
scare them out of fruit creating fruit
fear along the way they were there for a
reason to try to sabotage fruit this is
the waron fruit the milk cheese butter
yogurt kefir people eat it's all got
sugar in it did you know that it's the
lactose so here you are you're having
your cheese you're having your milk
you're having your butter you know
Butter's got a sweet Edge to it it's all
got sugar in it nut milks have sugar in
it oat milk is sweet and they even add
some sugar in it too so I see people
they're like no I don't do fruit I won't
touch any fruit and they're pouring
their oatmeal milk you know from a
container on their food and in the
container it even says added sugar it's
got like cane sugar in there added to
their oat milk it's got like agave
nectar added to the oat milk it's got
like coconut sugar added like all kinds
of things natural flavoring which is
sugar too they put a little sugar in
natural flavoring they're allowed to do
that and and not say it so so it's like
okay let's just pour sugar on top of my
sugar and does that make any sense but
never touch a piece of fruit because
we're we're afraid of fruit We Exist
because of sugar but most of those Foods
I mentioned earlier don't even have
enough of it or any antiviral compounds
like I said antibacterial compounds
antimicrobial compounds phytochemical
compounds critical an
antioxidants and immune building
properties but fruit does what's
interesting is we're being told not to
eat fruit by people who don't know why
we are sick so you walk around with a
symptom you walk around with a condition
and nobody knows why you're sick because
research and science doesn't know and
there's no answers to why you have a
condition they just tag it as autoimmune
or something but not give you any
answers cause unknown that's the saddest
part chronic illness is on the rise and
it's not from the one banana someone
eats a month or the one apple they eat
every 3 months no one even eats fruit I
mean I bet you guys like plenty of you
out there listening right now don't even
eat any fruit right I mean it's not on
your radar and some people do and if
they do they don't eat much at all and
by the way the world is sitting in the
dentist office chair
right now getting their teeth drilled I
mean that's the thing like our world
that we live in now people by the Yeah
billions are in you know they're in the
dentist office and they're getting their
teeth drilled and it's not because of
fruit we could even argue it's because
they are not eating enough fruit you
know you might have had some fruit a
moment in your life a little bit and
then a dentist blamed a cavity on it but
billions of people are not touching
fruit and getting root canals implants
teeth drilled Bridges all day long no
matter what but fruit gets the blame the
irony is is it gets the blame more than
junkie sweets do right now like right
now at this time we're in Fruit gets
more blame for problems than junky
sweets right now and chocolate Delights
and cane sugar
you guys eating chocolate but you're
afraid of fruit I'm just wondering right
there there's a lot of people I've seen
out there and I talk to and stuff and
people come to me are like hey I can't
eat a piece of fruit but no no I'm doing
my chocolate it's medicinal right I'm
doing my chocolate you can still eat
your healthy chocolate bar with Organic
cane sugar or coconut sugar and do your
Healthy organic cheat meals and
self-care meals with coconut sugar cane
sugar gluten-free grains and those
sugars and chocolates won't get the
blame ever they'll never get the blame
now no way not with the war on fruit
going on but fruit will H it's
interesting right chewing that for a
minute think about it you guys check
this out the same people who sabotage
fruit in the health industry back over a
decade ago also
simultaneously started pushing
disinformation that are brain runs on
fat not sugar it happened at the same
time okay the same time same time the
sabotage happened all right the
propagandists and fruit demonizes the
paid for people involved the moles and
plants they did a
Switcheroo fruit is bad but your brain
runs on fat now the new rule no signs
behind it just runs on fat now and and
if we eat sugar we gain fat and fruit
makes you gain fat is what they say
interesting the same early crew that was
planted by a dark industry and put
people into Fruit fear also push the
high fat Trend that defies Common Sense
saying sugar from fruit makes you gain
weight but all the fat you eat doesn't
and you know what this add part is about
that think about it other health
professionals buy into it and then
spread it around first of all people
don't eat enough fruit that's not why
they're gaining weight look come on
let's be straight you've been tricked
bottom line fat makes you gain fat in
the end not fructose natural sugar
that's in an apple a pear a watermelon a
kiwi doesn't make you fat Okay a kiwi
okay okay a kiwi is not going to make
you fat but will what will make you gain
weight is fatty
meals you see right there so what will
make you gain weight is the fatty meals
that causes a stagnant sluggish liver
medical medium information that put it
out there okay quite a while is way back
so it causes a stagnant sluggish liver
when you're eating all those fatty meals
that's all and your then your liver is
already filled with Metals toxic heavy
metals bugs fats from a lifetime of
eating fatty foods of all kinds healthy
or not healthy or not fats healthy fats
or not and in each person the weight
comes on at different times in their
life because your liver has a tipping
scale too that does before it gets sick
and all of a sudden gets stagnant and
sluggish depending on each person and
get guess what all right come on let's
be honest let's be honest with ourselves
let's not me a denial about this fruit
isn't doing it no one even eats fruit
really and the amount of fruit they eat
is really so small it's
ridiculous it wasn't the sugar in a
chocolate chip cookie or the blueberry
in the blueberry muffin gluten-free or
not that made you gain weight it was the
fat in the food the oils in the cookie
or muffin the fat in the eggs the fat in
the chocolate yeah the fat in the
chocolate the fat in the milk the fat in
the butter the canola oil think about it
you better work out in the gym two hours
a day while you're young still young and
feeling strong whatever and you just
better be in the gym three hours a day
so you can eat all that fat and you know
and not touch fruit until finally it
catches up to you and you know no matter
how hard you work off you're just
working out you're like what is this why
am I gaining weight
think about it any snack treat Delight
gluten-free or not you have had has fat
and sugar combined and no one is talking
about that fact that it has fat and
sugar combined they're acting like all
is great all is great but don't eat that
piece of fruit cuz it's sugar see where
you're tricked out you see where you're
tricked out you know I'm just being
straight out honest because that you
know yeah and each new generation of
young adults whose parents made them
scrambled eggs lovingly in the morning
and then they went out for pizzas at
night end up getting their first
symptoms maybe some bloating maybe some
acne maybe some eczema maybe some brain
fog fatigue or a little weight gain
listen to some health podcast out there
and instantly get scared to death of
fruit that's how it works so it's not
doing the younger generation's Justice
for sure cuz they just getting fed total
misinformation and then they end up
believing every ridiculous unfounded
logic defying deception about fruit and
then they Echo it that's how it's done
and yes yeah they get taught to eat
healthier sure right younger Generations
now it's pretty amazing you get a
symptom and you get taught to eat
healthier like Whole Foods no gluten no
processed food maybe balanced
diet and now they're eating more eggs on
their salads they're trying to do some
food combining twists and turns and
they're doing some fermented foods
healthier oils cuz wow I heard this oil
is healthy and avocado toast uh
gluten-free toast protein shakes and
sure it's an upgrade until they get
sicker later or sick again later and
they're still not eating
fruit while there's while they're
looking for the next diet belief system
like where do I go what do I do I got a
symptom I got another symptom I was
doing good pretty good being off
processed foods now where do I go I'll
go plant-based no wait I'll go animal
based which one do I jump into you know
what's funny fruit is so
demonized that you're encouraged to eat
cacao with caffeine in it which tastes
awful on its own and add sugar to it to
sweeten it and it's heralded as God so
cacao
right take sugar put it into it and no
one talks about the added sugar
everybody talks about fruit being crap
fruit's crap it's sugar it's bad for you
but Cacao is heralded as God see how
Darkness works I'm not saying you can't
have your chocolate I'm just saying the
caffeine industry is even part of this
whole gig all right but you're not
allowed to pick a piece of fruit off a
fruit tree and eat it God forbid or peel
a nav Orange in front of someone you're
going to be ostracized for that you're
going to be totally ripped apart for
that God forbid hypocrisy is off the
charts man it is think about that look
you guys check this out okay our brain
runs on Sugar by the way if you eat
brain which maybe some of you have tried
Brain before because it's you could if
you eat brain you'll notice it's sweet
creamy sweet and a little
salty interesting a little salty too
it's hardened glycogen that is a
carbohydrate your brain is a hardened
carbohydrate kind of like a sweet potato
with some with some mineral salts in
there it's hardened carbohydrates still
kind of soft and to some degree but
hardened and it takes like a it tastes
like banana and a celery stick together
the brain tastes like a banana and
celery stick together like why would I
know that I've talked to people who have
eaten brain okay and I've talked to a
lot of people over the years that have
eaten brain and they're like well I kind
of like it it's a delicacy because I've
talked to people all over the world for
years and years and years thousands upon
thousands over the years and I would say
well and they would ask me well how can
I simulate this brain flavor since it's
not a good idea that I'm eating
brains of different animals and I'd say
well put celery sticks and you know make
a banana salad celeries celery sticks
and bananas together kind of mix it
together and see what you think and the
consensus was always it's so close to
brain so close to The Taste there's a
reason because a banana has tiny amounts
of
Omega-3 right and lots of sugar okay and
then the celery has got those mineral
salts and that is the
combination your brain is made out of
mostly sugar that's glycogen stored
glycogen tiny amounts of Omega-3 and
lots of mineral salts okay and those
mineral salts help feed your
neurotransmitters some varieties of of
Omega-3 that our body even produces
itself from a healthy liver will be in
your brain but that's only a tiny bit
compared to the glycogen level I'm
talking about the stored
carbohydrate our brains heat up when we
think are you thinking now like are you
thinking like hey should I eat a piece
of fruit like should I think about it is
what should I do well electricity is
spinning around right now electrical
impulses are going around in your brain
right now and our brain needs a vast
amount of sugar which is glucose in
order to keep it cool you get a breakup
in a relationship your boyfriend you
know cheats or your girlfriend doesn't
want to be with you anymore or something
happens you go into a shock your brain
goes in the shock and or you you have a
you have a relationship issue of any
kind or any kind of trauma that's what
happens and you need those electrical
impulses to be working electricity off
sudden fires up and goes crazy when that
happens and our our brain needs a vast
amount of sugar which is glucose in
order to keep it cool kind of like
antifreeze to a car engine antifreeze is
Sy synthetically sweet it cools the
engine down
don't ever drink it God forbid but the
sugar cools heat see how it works sugar
cools heat not fat fat creates more heat
sugar cools heat fat creates more heat
so if your brain was all about fat it
lives all fat whatever you know it's all
made out of fat however it goes it's
going to overheat overheat and and what
happens is this is why instinctively
when you have a stressful event I was
mentioning before like a breakup or any
kind of trauma you crave something sweet
afterwards like ice cream that's one
thing right there after a breakup
relationship breakup that's a big one
all in its own I've heard it a thousand
times I need my ice cream like every day
you know the reason is glucose sugar
stops your brain from
overheating and burning up and getting
damaged and even mild tiny Strokes that
are undetectable from being that upset
after your brain goes into a electrical
storm of trauma when you see that
breakup message on your phone you're
like oh my God what is this I can't
believe this right or you get that news
like you're getting a divorce boom those
neurotransmitters they're like firing up
they're like burning up they're like
just falling apart left and right those
neurotransmitters just just like going
left and right and you don't have enough
glucose your blood sugar isn't
stabilized for that you don't have that
storage been in the brain I mean you
could suffer greatly with all kinds of
afterwards PTSD trauma injury you know
look you'll hear okay check this out
right now this is a whole another thing
you'll hear people say I never crave
sugar I call BS on that one okay so you
don't eat cheeseburgers the bun which is
sugar the cheese that's sugar the meat
with caramelized blood in it like I told
you before that's sugar the ketchup
that's sugar the mayonnaise all have
sugar in them um okay so you don't have
the cheeseburgers you don't crave pizza
ever like you don't eat pizza or crave
it the cheese that's sugar straight
sugar basically the sauce the crust all
have sugar in it lots of sugar you don't
crave tacos maybe you're one that does
or doesn't but a lot of people crave
them the corn tortilla the flour
tortilla sugar cheese once again sugar
sour cream Tomatoes salsa sugar sugar
meat NOP there goes the blood sugar
again the meat sugar they all have sugar
in them you don't crave a sandwich
gluten-free or not because the bread
sugar the meat the cheese the
spread the Tomatoes The Nut Butter the
avocado whatever you have in your
sandwich it's all sugar it all has sugar
in it
you don't crave pasta the pasta grain or
Bean pasta has sugar it's all it's made
out of it the sauce sugar the dairy that
you might put on it's all sugar and
people put butter on their pasta sugar
on top of sugar you don't crave chips
and chips like corn chips potato chips
they have sugar in them with with you
know with oil and salt you don't crave
hummus right beans that's the
carbohydrate the sugar and what do you
eat hummus with chips or carrots carrot
sticks or a sandwich a hummus sandwich
all have sugar all meat all Dairy all
bread all nuts and seeds all beans all
avocados all sauces have sugar in them
right mindblowing you crave Savory and
sweet together all the time you guys
that's what everybody's doing you're
craving Savory and sweet all together
all the time
the sugar aspect is what allows you to
function out of all those Foods I just
mentioned you crave or that you want to
eat but God forbid you touch a piece of
fruit I mean for real and then you top
it off all that food you top it off with
what you believe might be a sweet that's
kind of on the edge and a little off the
chart like some ice cream or chocolate
in your diet okay so do you drink coffee
you put your oat milk or dairy or soy
cream steamer or nutmilk in your coffee
that's all sugar but you won't eat a
piece of fruit in the morning cuz you're
scared all these milks have sugar in
them so think about this next time you
hear someone say you don't crave sugar
like you what's funny next time you know
you tell somebody out there I don't
crave sugar just think about that a
little bit and next time you hear
somebody tell you that like I don't
crave sugar like the if they're out
there or you watch somebody's YouTube I
don't crave sugar okay sure and if you
believe that you've been stupified
tricked by not smart
information and then you know it's
everybody's smart I mean it's not about
that it's about the information being
not smart that's you have to see it
because that's what it is and people get
stupified all along I mean all around
it's like all you hear out there I don't
crave sweets I don't crave sweets oh man
meanwhile everything they're eating is
packed with sugar and it could be a slow
burn like oats sure Slow Burn
carbohydrate still sugar that's what
you're living off of or a faster burn
it's still sugar it's all the same in
many ways actually in every way when it
enters your cells and fat doesn't enter
your cells from your blood and become
energy that's a farce do they call it
blood fat are they measuring that every
time you go into the the doctor's office
well we better check your blood fat we
better make sure no because that's not
what keeps you alive they're not
measuring your blood fat it's your blood
sugar they're measuring we need sugar to
survive it's what our cells run on sugar
has to attach itself to insulin to get
into our cells to Keep Us Alive the fat
doesn't attach itself to insulin and go
into our cells where the heck does it go
then that's what I'm trying to say the
fat actually doesn't enter your cells
interesting it's not its job it's not
attaching to insulin so they're not like
you go to doctor's office let me check
your uh blood fat oh where is it at hm
too fat too too high too low um what's
going on nothing it's not even on
anybody's radar but fat gets in the way
of sugar entering your cell so it gets
in the way it's a menace I'm not saying
you can't eat any healthy fats it's not
it at all I'm just saying are you ever
going to eat a piece of fruit or are you
just going to stay scared scared scared
stay sick sick sick misinformation
disinformation never touch a piece of
fruit and just get you know exactly so
insulin resistance occurs from the fat
and the sugar combined right but fruit
does not cause insulin
resistance you have been taught that
your oatmeal is a slow burn okay you
probably heard that like no it's a slow
burn it's it's you know it makes it it
last it sustains you and you've
experienced that yourself it's like and
oh oats are okay I'm not anti oats but
you've experienced it yourself it
sustains you for many hours when maybe
you tried one or two pieces of fruit on
its own and you got hungry fast and felt
like it wasn't getting you through the
day or getting you through the morning
because you didn't eat enough fruit
because it's not that high in calorie in
fact it's not even high in calories and
that's one of the mistakes there's not
even a lot of sugar in fruit that's the
irony and you know and what you're not
realizing is that when you eat your
oatmeal you probably added fat to it
which also increases your calories you
threw the nut Butters in there you threw
the avocado I see people throw avocado
in their in their oatmeal you stick milk
in there nut milks nuts nut Butters
coconut cacao almonds soy you add that
to your oatmeal so now you have this
really high dense dense caloric meal
with a ton of fat on top of it mixed
with sugar and you think you found the
perfect meal when you're you know hey if
you're not really sick or you don't have
a lot of symptoms you got nothing going
on yeah it feels like a perfect meal but
now you have a problem you don't know
about though that's going to bite you
over time and it's insulin resistance
that sits there and goes long sustaining
so you have this long sustaining insulin
resistance that catches up to you over
time and eventually you have to then
learn how to intermittent fast so now
you're 25 years old and is like well I'm
intermittent fasting now I have to not
eat at all all morning all afternoon and
try to exercise and stimulate on coffee
drinks I got to I I have to intermittent
fast now because you're putting the
weight on you're seeing like a pound
come on you're like oh my God that's my
first pound that's my first pound I've
ever seen why am I getting a couple of
pounds on me I exercise um I'm eating
healthy meals I'm doing my peanut butter
butter smoothie bowls and oatmeal with
nut Butters and I'm doing all that
having avocado toast in the morning
maybe I should intermittent fast and and
and that's what people do so now they're
doing that and maybe you get a little
bit of low energy or a little bit of
brain fog and if you're putting on a
little weight and you're like okay
intermittent fasting time and guess what
all these things going wrong putting on
a little bit of weight a couple extra
pounds getting a little brain fog little
acne starts kicking in or anything like
that low energy it's not because of the
fruit it's not because of a few few
berries you might have thrown on one of
your oatmeal
bowls or you know or maybe a piece of
banana or a half a banana you threw on
an oatmeal Bowl it's not going to be
that the underlying insulin resistance
and stagnant sluggish liver caught up to
you so you stop your oatmeal Bowls in
the morning you stop your avocado toast
in the morning you stop your eggs in the
morning yeah you stop your eggs in in
the morning and then everybody has to
eventually intermittent fast and the
only reason it seems to help is because
you gave your body a break from eating
fats for most of the day you went fat
free by default without realizing it by
accident without anybody knowing or
realizing it it has nothing to do with
fruit and that's just one thing that has
nothing to to do with fruit everything
has nothing to do with fruit that goes
wrong and eventually your intermittent
fasting doesn't seem to work anymore
either later on because you get these
cravings and you still have insulin
resistance because you're still eating
fats at the end of the day and you never
know how to escape it and you don't know
you even have it the insulin resistance
and still you stay away from fruit
unbelievable but you still cheat on
pizza ice cream whether it's plant-based
or animal-based so you swing from
craving to craving and then holistic
doctor to doctor and guess what you get
told there when you go to your holistic
doctor you know God bless them but you
get told get off of fruit just don't as
if you eat fruit all day like you get
told to get off of fruit happens every
day people aren't even eating fruit but
they remember eating a piece of Apple
like or they remember eating half an
Apple 4 days ago and they're at the
doctor's office and their holistic
doctor's like stay off of fruit that's
number one that's your problem here oh
whoa as if you're eating fruit all day
long but what's crazy is everyone who
gets sick for the first time never
really ate
fruit how much fruit did you guys eat
before you first got sick and if you did
eat a lot of fruit you're a rarity I'm
talking like a RAR
think about it when someone first gets
sick and they start to clean up their
diet and try fruit more they instantly
get told to stop either through
something they see either through you
know a podcast they heard you know from
a professional being on a podcast
telling you stay away from fruit do low
glycemic or don't do none at all
claiming it's going to make you sicker
when the person already got sick before
eating the fruit and now the person is
afraid of fruit because of anti-f fruit
propaganda and misinformation without
anybody realizing it the very thing they
never ate the fruit was medicine so
without realizing it you guys the very
thing no one ever even ate was their
medicinals was their
medicine they just didn't know how to
use it as a healing
tool you must learn how to use it
properly so when you try the medicine a
piece of fruit it scares them because
you don't know how to use it and that's
what happens you know it's like a lot of
things it's like anything if you don't
know how to do something or you don't
know how to use something and understand
its power or what it holds or what it
does it scares you you don't use it
right no one teaches you and right now
in this world no one wants to teach you
how to use a piece of fruit no way they
want the opposite they want to scare you
scare you out of it and that's the whole
thing they are they they are told the
fructose is bad for them that's what
everybody gets told by Health experts
it's like fructose it's a scary word Now
by Health experts who don't know why
they're sick to begin with meanwhile the
fruit is medicine when you are eating
cleansing fruits and they are dropping
into a dirty environment your
body that's the dirty environment stuff
starts flying crap hits the fan the
fruit is house cleaning it's cleaning
your toilet the fruit is cleaning your
toilet bottom line it's cleaning the bad
inside of you all the sludge that's
built up in your gallbladder the fruit
is sweeping out bugs that colonized in
your gut and liver for years that's what
the fruit is sweeping out the bacteria
in your small intestinal tract it's
helping to dis olve rancid fats and
rotting proteins in the lining of the
intestinal tract and colon and
dadum it's helping to detox your liver
of all the poisons and helping to starve
viruses and then if you're still dumping
in eggs dairy too many nut Butters lots
of chicken right down the pike and then
throwing fruit on top of it that fruit
you're dropping down is going to be like
oh my God this is a serious mess right
right here and there's going to be a
large conflict going on in here a larger
conflict of interest because the fruit
is going to have to try to clean up a
mess on top of a new mess it wants to
digest fast and push out all the bad and
then it gets misconstrued as fruit being
the problem instead of your dirty system
that's a mess so the messenger gets shot
you got a mess inside of you there's a
whole bunch of dirty going on inside
there like a whole bunch of sludge all
kinds of bugs all kinds of troublemakers
and you drop fruit in there to clean
that mess and the messenger gets shot
it's fruit and it's that you know it's
the Apple the banana the mango the
orange the peach one time a year and the
melon that didn't do any harm and it
didn't do any wrong it's only there to
help you and you shoot it in the back
you shoot the messenger in the back you
don't even give it a blindfold or its
last cigarette meanwhile these fruit
haters and fruit demonizes don't know
how to even eat fruit and I know because
I actually talked to one many years ago
that was also onto the bandwagon of
trying to destroy fruit create the war
on fruit and I said do you even know how
to use fruit or eat fruit and they just
knew that you cut a grapefruit in half
and you try to cut the little squares
out the triangles out that was the most
they knew and from what I heard talking
to this one person this professional
they were putting sugar on top of their
great fruit on top of it and fruit they
didn't even know how to eat it or didn't
even know what kind of fruits were out
there but fruits evil totally evil it's
unbelievable so look and there's
therapeutic nature to these fruits and
that's the power that's within him so
that he healing happens all around
inside our bodies fruit can be used
therapeutically you know and when you
align other therapeutic foods with fruit
extra healing occurs so then there's a
crowd that's sick for the first time you
guys hear this all the time maybe out
there you get the crowd that's sick for
the first time maybe they got a little
bloating maybe a little weight gain
maybe some acne a little eczema and they
never really eat fruit and don't start
eating it either sure they get rid of
their processed foods you know they're
eating healthier fats which is which is
good they're eating vegetables they may
see an improvement in their symptoms
maybe they throw in a few berries some
assai told to stay off sugar but still
eat sugar bad sugar and Grains
especially on their cheat days or
self-care days but they don't eat fruit
or ever enough fruit and they hate on
fruit and spread that hatred around like
they just hate it they they'll just
comment about it they'll talk about it
they'll post about it they hate fruit
even if it's done in a nice way like
even if they it's done in a really nice
thoughtful way like what seems to be
kind of like a kind manner of what their
experience is like someone will say
everybody's different I'm different you
know you it might work for you but it
didn't work for me I tried fruit because
of what what they learned from the
health podcast out there the Talking
Heads of health or that piece of fruit
bothered my stomach and didn't make me
feel right or something meanwhile that
piece of fruit just dropped into a dirty
environment and it's trying to clean up
the mess and no one understands cuz when
like I said they listen to maybe a
health podcast or something like that
that fruit is bad they instantly just
all of a sudden go with it they get
suckered into it and they listen to the
talking heads out there that just want
to climb the ego ladder in health rip
rip down fruit on social media Health
experts spreading the same tricks and
game that was originally planted by the
industries to start the war on fruit and
we get suckered into it and we lose
something that was really going to help
us but we didn't understand it we just
didn't understand it and it was actually
going to be a Saving Grace for the
future if you get sicker down the road
you know you'll hear things like like
some low glycemic fruit is okay but
overall fruit is bad you know it's too
sweet and then there's the people who
never even ate fruit got sick tried a
piece of fruit and they're still sick
because they don't know the cause of
their symptoms and how they got sick and
why they're still sick they blame it on
fruit though okay and maybe saying it
made me sick when I tried it it gave me
that tummy ache fruit always gets the
blame aren't you glad you're not a piece
of fruit shunned alienated
underappreciated undervalued shot in the
back maybe some of you guys can relate
and with other things in your life or
something you know chronic illness is on
the rise like never before and no one
eats fruit pretty much no one eats fruit
and fruit gets the blame neurological
symptoms are on the rise like never
before in history anxiety do you have
anxiety depression Lyme disease vertigo
tunitis I'm all I'm going to do future
shows on all those so I hope you listen
neuropathy focus in concentration brain
fog migraines head pain neck pain back
pain joint pain that's
mysterious which we'll cover you know in
upcoming episodes these are all nervous
symptom conditions nervous system
conditions and symptoms and people with
these symptoms didn't get sick because
of eating fruit they didn't eat any
fruit practically nobody does but what
you need to know is an important part of
recovery from these neurological
symptoms that I just mentioned requires
consistent
uninterrupted levels of glucose sugar
from a natural source sugar from
fruit because your nervous system is
made up of nerve cells you guys nerve
cells exist on sugar whether anybody
likes it or not I should say it again
all those nervous system conditions your
Vagas nerve causing all these different
problems people don't even know about
like medical medum information of what
what causes what in your your Vegas
nerve it needs sugar to exist that's
what the nerve cells are made up of they
draw it in they need it
desperately meanwhile fruit is a way for
these people with neurological symptoms
to recover and heal and it's kept from
them on purpose by the industries and by
accident by well-meaning practitioners
and influencers who are you know who are
well-meaning and doing cool things but
don't know why they have stomach pain
and bloating and gastritis
hypoglycemia acne fatigue eczema weight
gain anxiety and don't know how to use
fruit as a healing tool then check this
out check this out then we have the
anti-aging Pros the anti-aging Pros you
know it's all about anti-aging and the
pros out there in the circuit and
everything it's all about anti-aging
anti-aging as if that's an answer for
why a 20-year-old can't get out of bed
and has severe neurological fatigue and
can't function and go to school or you
know the 30-year-old who's on
anti-anxiety meds because they can't
even function the worst brain fog and
depression ever or why
20-year-old has autoimmune or Hashimoto
or any kind of aches and pains what a
farce that is okay anti-aging is the
Panacea like anti-aging is the answer
like everybody's on the circuit don't
eat fruit well let's talk about
anti-aging and living longer and there's
all these 20y olds and 30y olds laying
in their bed on mattress Island
suffering you know if you claim to be an
anti-aging expert and you're not pro-
fruit all fruit not just berries then
you're so far off the Mark it's
embarrassing and the sad part is
anti-aging experts don't even know why
anybody is sick they don't know why the
25-year-old like can't do anything
function laying in bed fatigue headaches
migraines floaters in the eyes and
they're anti-aging experts and they're
on the circuit like they have all the
answers you know that's bad enough to
begin with as it is all of it aging
means we're oxidizing oxidizing means
our cells die the question is how fast
are we oxidizing and what causes the
oxidizing I'll give you a hint we have
toxins pathogens in us more than every
before in a history I've been talking
about it for 35 years I call them
troublemakers take for and think about
this toxic stuff right here take for
example air fresheners plug-in air
fresheners colog perfumes conventional
scented candles conventional cleaning
supplies gasoline petrochemicals
pesticides herbicides fungicides
pathogens like Epstein bar shingles
herpes simplex strep cyeg virus hhvs of
all kinds and all their mutations and
varieties and more and guess what you
age fast with all of that and everybody
is peppered with it all men and women
are saturated with colog perfumes sended
candles air fresheners and living with
bugs pathogens inside of them and
meanwhile they won't even touch a piece
of fruit they get told don't touch a
piece of fruit the very thing that's
anti-aging one of the most powerful
anti-aging tools and healing tools to
get those aging troublemakers out of the
body and prevent premature aging and the
anti-aging clowns on the circuit they're
all against fruit except maybe few
berries or something or a green banana
and or a green apple you know fruit has
undiscovered antioxidants that are
critical to our survival in today's
world especially the stress all that
stress and it's the largest array of
antioxidants that is non-toxic in any
way meaning you can get large amounts of
undiscovered antioxid and a few
discovered ones but large amounts of it
without having to deal with toxic things
involved in other Foods or other places
you can find an antioxidant in caffeine
right in a caffeine beverage but it
comes with a price so there'll be all
the science of research to protect the
caffeine indust rate right and it'll be
like let's find an antioxidant and in
coffeee let's find it in some kind of
caffeinated beverage let's find it in
MCH tea let's find it in black tea let's
find it in chocolate so all the science
will be paid for for that to try to find
that one antioxidant that two
antioxidants and then they Herald that
antioxidant like God like that's going
to be your savior but no matter how much
caffeinated beverage or cacao you eat
one blueberry or one bite of an apple
will give you more
antioxidants than pound of chocolate
cacao can ever offer see sence doesn't
look at antioxidants and fruit anymore
they don't because it would spur on a
massive upsurge of fruit intake and
fruit production and anti-aging experts
they don't Echo the power of fruit and
all the antioxidants they don't they
just look for these obscure items and be
like oh that's good for long lasting
Health that's good so you can live
forever oh that's good too and this is
they they don't even they ignore fruit
there was you know look there was some
food science done on some fruits at one
point like 20 years ago and it spawned
on interest in Fruit being good and it
was instantly crushed and discredited
you can guess all the reasons why you
know you can know you can guess right
because Corruption of course corruption
everywhere instead science
scrambles as it's being paid off by the
caffeine industry to search for one or
two types of antioxidants in a coffee
bean cacao matcha tea or caffeinated tea
meanwhile caffeine blows out and
destroys years worth of
antioxidants so you know what I mean
it's like okay let's have our caffeine
beverage get those two antioxidants in a
small dosage of it and then let's just
blow out with all that caffeine
killing off your adrenals and everything
else because it it Spurs on corrosive
adrenaline you get an adrenaline Spike
from caffeine and that adrenaline ages
you quickly it's
corrosive it actually injures cells and
nerves over time when it's every day
every day and then your hair starts
falling out when you get older and now
you're 38 years old and my hair's
thinning what's going on let me go buy a
supplement that's Hair Skin and Nails
let me go to a natural doctor and look
for some collagen let me go do something
and your hair is falling out and your
skin is getting all dry and crazy and
you're like you're aging at 38 39 when
you're not supposed to you're aging at
30 and here you are thinking you're
getting your antioxidants because paid
for science is just totally tricking you
out and everybody's keeping you away
from fruit and you need fruit to counter
your habit that whole thing your
addiction cuz when you get on that
Addiction on that caffeine and your
adrenaline is running fight or flight
every day because of that caffeine and
you're aging yourself quickly you better
be eating a lot of fruit in the mix to
battle it and counter it with its
antioxidants to stop you from aging so
you can so you can keep your habit going
so all right you guys let's cover some
of the fruit the fruit hater talking
points in the health movement and these
are a couple of my personal favorites
okay the fruit hater talking points you
might be ready for this if you're into
fruit or not or hating fruit they say
that fruit is hybridized extra sweet
because it's manipulated by man first of
all they trick people out with that one
by confusing them by saying fruit is
hybridized most people think GMO is what
it is then they hear hybridize so saying
oh GMO it's not GMO so hybridize does
doesn't mean GMO one thing fruit haters
don't know is we have been hybridizing
grafting and coveting fruit in different
ways for thousands of years all around
the globe this is how the human race
adapts and
survives fruit haters and fruit
demonizes will tell us that we make the
fruit too sweet now and fruits were not
sweet a thousand years ago you know
that's kind of funny because that's
funny how does they know what fruit
tasted like thousands of years ago think
about that one for a minute you guys
wild blueberries are way more sweeter
than regular cultivated blueberries did
you hear that wild blueberries wild are
way more sweeter than any regular
cultivated blueberry that instantly
debunks it I guess we debunked it then
okay there you go that's a wild food
that's been around for thousands of
years wild blueberries
thousands of years growing here and it's
sweeter than a cultivated blueberry
instantly debunked it's the opposite
fruits aren't sweet enough today fruit
haters don't realize that fruit was
sweeter in the past it's not even sweet
enough today that's that's why you know
what that's a lot of reasons why people
hate it right there it's not sweet
enough they cut open to a mango and it's
not sweet enough they're like uh what is
is this they cut they cut open a papaya
and it's not sweet enough and they're
like gross what is this this the problem
is bananas aren't even sweet you peel a
banana and you eat it you can't even
taste the sugar sometimes on any level
in there and so people don't even like
fruit because it's not even sweet enough
if it was that sweet and tast it that
that good and sweet people would be like
I want that I want that all right the
bottom one many of the people that I
know the reason why they hate fruit
because it doesn't taste sweet that's
why they actually hate it they'll taste
some berries they're like tart there's
really no sugar in them they'll taste
you know an apple it's just boring it's
not really that sweet apple pie it's a
different story I have a friend that
would be like well I would love this
apple and an apple pie with sugar table
sugar added to it okay unless someone
runs into the sweetest watermelon
they've ever had like once in a blue
moon in their life or the only other way
they actually like fruit is when they
stop eating all the other sugar in their
diet all the other sugar that I
mentioned like get rid of all that cane
sugar all the nut milks all everything
that has sugar in it that's sweet all
the things all the pizza with the pizza
crust and the cheese and the sauce and
once they get rid of all that for a
little while and they eat a piece of
fruit they're like oh my God this is the
best thing I've ever tasted in my life
it's because they basically went without
all the bad sugar and then finally had a
PE piece of fruit which isn't even that
sweet but thought it was the best thing
ever okay here's a talking point with
fruit haters heirloom foods that have
seeds is what counts and that counts
only well first of all yeah that counts
true you know and these fruit haters say
fruit that isn't heirloom and doesn't
have seeds is bad for us this isn't
accurate they say it with no evidence at
all the truth is a Loom heirloom fruits
heirloom foods are just older varieties
with seeds or No Seeds there are
heirloom varieties of fruit with little
to no seeds and there are heirloom
varieties with lots of seeds nutrient
density in phytochemical compounds don't
discriminate on how many seeds are in a
fruit so it's like that's another psych
out they throw at you right there okay
nutrient density phytochemical IAL
compounds antioxidants minerals and
trace minerals have nothing to do with
if a fruit has a ton of seeds in it or
very few seeds in it so there you go
bottom line people harp on non GMO fruit
and the funny thing is get this point
right here the people that are harping
on non GMO fruit meaning fruit that's
not GMO on any level okay whether it's
hybridized or air Loom or just
cultivated or graft it just natural
things we've done for hundreds of years
all right to sustain ourselves here on
planet Earth when people harp on all
that you know what the funny thing is
these fruit demonizes are most likely
consuming GMO soy GMO corn GMO beets the
anti-aging experts on the circuit with
podcast they're eating GMO corn GMO
beets animal products raised on GMO
grains in restaurants as they're
traveling periodically in their diet
unpurified water in restaurants and
coffee shops GMO canola oil natural
flavors with MSG nutritional yeast which
is natural occurring MSG caffeinated
beverages with GMO soy in it
occasionally gluten in some way while
ripping down fruit all day long it's
sitting there and ripping apart fruit
and ripping down fruit and they're
sitting there too on their po podcast on
their platforms talking about how bad
fruit is and they're getting GMO stuff
in their diet left in right is what
they're doing another difficult part of
fruit fear and fruit hatred is is the
very early disinformation that's
misinformation purposely put out there
that was strategically placed in the
health Movement by these paid for moles
and plants that spark the lies about
fruit having something to do with poor
health or causing sickness and not
helping in any way in someone's healing
or recovery these moles and plants these
fruit demonizer I'm talking about that
did that are still out there now yeah
yeah they're still out there now you
better believe
it they're spouting out and here's the
funny thing too they're still out there
now spouting out encrypted biological
theoretical terminology about anti-aging
anti-aging DNA DNA telr telr genetic
codes molecular mimicry genetic
mutations a leaky gut bofilm
microflora microbiome and more it makes
the person who is sick and has already
been to plenty of doctors believe that
there is this rainbow of Glorious
alternative medicine research and
science that the person with symptoms
and is sick just doesn't doesn't
understand or has to tap into it or
haven't tapped into it yet like like the
information's out there the message is
out there these guys are echoing it
these anti-aging experts with encrypted
terminology
telr okay it's interesting when a
person's laying in bed and they've been
to their 10th specialist 10th
neurologist and they're they're 28 years
old 35 years old they can't even get
into a car they've got crippling anxiety
suffering with fatigue and everything
everything I don't think teles is going
to help I don't think DNA is going to
help them and I don't think talk of
these things really helps and that's the
irony to it all but these plants and
moles these these beginners of the fruit
war on fruit movement from the start
going back years ago that are still
around make it seem like there's these
mysterious options to get everybody
better and meanwhile everybody's getting
sicker like ever before you know and it
makes that sick person feel like they
just need to find a genius or someone
who understands anti-aging or someone
who understands the gut in some way and
everything else that these moles and
plants put out there by the industries
are spouting out in hopes to be healed
or if a person who is not so sick and
they haven't suffered or been to five
doctors they will think these anti-
fruit moles and plants are on to
something so if you're not so sick and
you're not really suffering that much
you got a little acne got some little
bumps on your skin you got a little
tummy thing digestion thing once in a
while you got a little energy loss and
you watch one of these Geniuses that are
on podcasts and other platforms and
other places that tear down fruit in
some way and you hear them talk about
telm and mimicry and and you know
microflora and you're like oh my God
these Geniuses and whoa and they got
answers and they must be working with
today's science it's a great
distraction you know while laying around
with a few symptoms listening to
podcasts and watching YouTubes and
hearing about telr and then getting out
of bed walking to your kitchen wondering
what to eat and they don't care as they
spout these theories out and you're like
well I'm not going to eat a piece of
fruit today and they kick fruit down as
if it's crap meanwhile all that
encrypted genetic anti-aging
inflammation talk and gut health
rhetoric doesn't get someone's tenius
better I'm sorry it doesn't you can
listen to all those podcasts you want
and your tenius is going to ring ring
ring until you learn the true cause
until you learn the true cause of your
eye floaters until you learn the true
cause of your mysterious jaw pain so all
that Health Ric out there and anti-aging
and encrypted genetic talk and Tome
mirors isn't going to get your twitches
and spasms better and ain't going to get
your burning skin better and your jaw
pain and ain't going to get your
migraines better your fatigue your
insomnia your brain fog that's crippling
your
vertigo that talk that DNA talk is not
going to get your vertigo better it's
entertaining I guess because you sit
there and be like whoa Geniuses that got
all the answers on the podcast or on the
YouTube they're so smart they must be
tied into science and all the key parts
of healing it's not going to get your
eczema better you can hear that stuff
all you
want but it does lead you to think there
is this pain fantasy of information that
these guys know and you just need to
learn it that anti fruit rhetoric makes
sense fruit is bad and it will not help
you heal I'm not saying everyone talking
this way is an anti-f fruit Moler plant
or a bad person they just follow all the
lead and they'll just they'll also speak
this you know leaky gut tmrs DNA
anti-aging whatever it is it doesn't
mean everybody's bad that's not it I'm
just saying they're The Originals that
are still out there now setting
everybody up and they're fed the
information to set them up and still
bring down fruit at the same time that's
what that is and they you know but the
but there's people out there that just
take their lead that fruit is bad
because they don't like fruit anyway cuz
exactly it's not even
sweet so it's an easy
knockdown you know anti- fruit
propagandists don't want anyone to know
someone has healed while having fruit in
their diet check that out I'm just
saying it like it is they don't want
anybody knowing someone healed by having
fruit in their diet they ignore the
healing Stories the healing recoveries
that fruit played a role in spirit of
compassion has always told me you can
heal with meat in your diet did you hear
that one Spirit of compassion always
told me you can still heal with meat in
your diet depending on your condition
meat but Spirit of compassion has also
always told me that you can heal with
fruit in your diet too and it's critical
to have it in everyone's diet but the
fruit haters and the fruit fear creators
put a blind eye to this very truth the
truth that so many people have healed
already using fruit critical recoveries
life-saving recoveries I'm not biased
towards meat everybody knows that about
me
it's in medical medium books starting
with medical medium book one but they
are biased towards fruit interesting the
this this disinformation they put out
there purposely about fruit has worked
its way into the plant-based movement so
that people trying to heal in that
movement don't have a shot in hell if
they're really sick so people who go
plant-based they don't have a shot in
hell if they're really sick or keep on
getting sicker that that's what happens
and just being gluten-free isn't enough
and Animal product free isn't enough for
a lot of people who go plant-based and
they become afraid of fruit scared to
death of fruit so they live off of fats
and then they try to go keto plant-based
and then their symptoms worsen and then
another one bites the dust and a plant-
baser then runs for the hills to eat
salmon and eggs to start with and
becomes an animal baser again and starts
eating animal protein and leaves the
plant-based movement and if they ate one
piece of fruit their symptoms will be
blamed on that seen that 100 times out
there fruit has become a scapegoat it's
so you don't have to look at the real
problems and issues that are causing
symptoms it protects the industries it's
above everybody the sabotage the war on
fruit is above everybody which really is
the war on people staying healthy what's
funny is the industries that want to
keep a sick choose professionals who
haven't suffered from chronic illness
yet in their life to spread the fruit
fear these professionals are easy to
convince because they don't know what
it's like to suffer and not get answers
at least yet in their life even though
it comes to them too where they get sick
and they look for answers eventually so
they don't know what it's like to be so
sick and to have tried
everything and they're at that tipping
scale on the edge with their symptoms
and illness where they know the
difference where fruit is really keeping
them alive they've never experienced
that where it's keeping them from
falling more ill having beautiful fruit
and how important it is to find fruit as
well they don't know about
this and they don't know how to use
fruit as has this healing tool I'm not
talking about only eating fruit and
fruit only and nothing else at all
nothing I'm talking about using it
specifically in ways as a healing tool I
have seen so many people with colitis
and Crohns there are millions of them in
the world that if they knew how to use
fruit it could have saved them from
years of Agony same with people with
gastroparesis Celiac IBS gastric spasms
and so many more because yes the ones
that learn how to use fruit realize fast
how much it
matters and these anti- fruit
professionals that haven't suffered you
guys that take their queue from
disinformation spread by moles and
plants believe they have it all figured
out and they think they're smarter and
Superior in health because they haven't
fallen ill yet but they also take that
little humble nature to they play that
games there's a little humbleness going
on so you're thinking huh you know and
then you end up thinking maybe they're
just eating all the right things when
they are just lucky they can still eat
pizza drink wine on the
weekends and here's the thing they teach
younger people who haven't been sick or
suffered yet in the health movement who
also can still eat pretty much what they
want you know who you know some people
right you know probably who they are you
probably see people and they're like
whoa they can still eat what they want
they teach them that fruit is bad so
these younger people naturally spread
disinformation about fruit other places
and other things around too and being
that they know nothing about what causes
illness even if they're a health
professional they still have influence
to take a powerful healing tool like
fruit and toss it away away from someone
who could have used it to save their
life or get a better life or better
their life I hear it every day check
this out I hear healing stories of
people who say they were kept away from
fruit by all of the propaganda and all
the different people talking about it
out there and they were told it was
going to hurt them maybe even do worse
than hurt them it would cause their gut
health problems make them worse cause
candid or leaky gut but they had nothing
to lose because they weren't getting
better any other way because they got
that sick they got too sick so they took
the plunge and learned how to use fruit
as a healing tool properly and it blew
their minds as they healed fruit
demonizes don't know how to use fruit
health professionals who are anti fruit
don't know how to use fruit health
professionals that like fruit and are
Pro Fruit still don't know how to use
fruit either but it's important to know
that fruit demonizes especially not only
don't know how to use fruit but let
their ego control them so they don't
even stay open to the possibility that
fruit heals and they just stay
misinformed and they are making a
mistake a mistake that leaves countless
people chronically ill who are eager to
learn a way to heal occasionally fruit
demonizer will say some berries are fine
green Apple's fine green banana even
they do that to appease levelheaded
sensible people that don't fall for the
anti Fruit game so it's a trick to make
it look like they're still Pro Fruit but
they're doing it sensibly you know like
no just a little this little that but
who cares if you're sick and you're kept
from an answer one of the real answers
one of the real healing tools and one of
the answers that fruit is good see how
there's Darkness behind everything when
you scratch the surface people suffer
when there's healing tools available you
know does the word Darkness like bother
you I look at it this way if innocent
good people are suffering from chronic
illness and answers are kept from them
for devious reasons of any kind and
someone's laying in bed with no answers
and one of the things that can be
helpful is kept from them it's
darkness and just because professional
fruit haters don't know how to use fruit
as a
tool they would rather throw it under
the bus along on with the people who are
sick the spiritual war we are facing
both here around us and above us can
only be one if we know the game Darkness
plays and darkness is uncaring of anyone
and it holds no compassion and it
despises the
light the fruit trees and the brambles
and the fruit
Vines have given us love life throughout
the centuries because they are of the
light but like anything and everything
Darkness trains us to take it all for
granted and why was fruit mentioned over
300 times in the Bible because it
mattered to someone and there's a deep
connection because fruit is a
lifegiver not a
lifetaker fruit signifies renewal of
life
as the darkness shuns the fruit and the
evildoers kill the fruit trees over time
the Angels
Cry as the fruit trees
die ignorance and greed is a great part
of why we are sick the ones that are
supposed to protect us here on Earth
only Mastermind how to harm
us and hold us back from what's
rightfully ours as we are led the wrong
way regardless of who who we
are fruit hatred gives us Insight that
the spiritual war is real you can see
the signs everyone knows there's
corruption in all the industries and
they're seeing it more than ever before
but oddly enough no one thinks there's
corruption in alternative holistic
medicine and the Alternative Health
Information that goes around we think if
it's holistic it's pure and holy
no ill intentions at all and for some
reason the conventional medicine World
released a magical fairy that has
allowed the Alternative Health movement
to be creative and do as it pleases but
that's
impossible there are facets of it we
don't realize ruled by the hierarchy
over time as they work on breaking our
thoughts and breaking our minds so what
I leave to you is the tools to EXP
explore so you have every opportunity to
heal it's everyone's god-given right to
have every chance to give their body
what it needs so you can move forward
and Conquer illness and rise out of the
ashes see I believe in you and I know
you can
heal
as you guys know I'm not a doctor any
information you learned here feel free
to take to your doctor or healthcare
provider if you found this show helpful
and informative feel free to share it
with someone in need of the information
if you like this show Please Subscribe
and leave a review on Apple podcast you
can also find me on YouTube Facebook and
Instagram at medal medium and for more
information on healing please visit
medicalmedium.com
thank you so much for
listening