how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William hey everybody today we're doing
a powerful brain meditation for letting
go of fear and riding fear from our soul
spirit and heart fear is something that
becomes a part of of our soul and it
gets in the way of who we truly are and
it can end up taking away a piece of who
we are and shadowing who we aspire to
be as we go through life and live
through hardships betrayal broken trust
losses broken friendships relationships
or emotional struggles of any kind we
have small outof body experiences where
our soul lead Lees our brain and body
and a disconnect happens and there
becomes an empty space between our soul
and brain a distance and fear fills the
Gap this meditation is about taking
control over your life not letting fear
run you or own you in any way this will
allow your neurons that are in the
emotional Center of your brain to
reconnect to your soul and redirect
their messaging away from Fear pushing
it away now let's begin the
meditation find yourself a safe
comfortable place to lie
down if you need to do this meditation
while sitting up that will work
fine once you are in a relaxing position
close your eyes
now take a deep breath
in and
release now on the count of three take
another deep breath in
1 2
3 deep breath
in and
release now Envision yourself walking
down a
road and you see a bridge in the
distance
it can be whatever type of bridge you
like it can be a wooden
bridge a swinging bridge suspended over
a canyon or
Ravine it can be a larger Bridge
Crossing a wide
river
once you envision your
bridge take a deep breath
in and
release you are
alone you are standing on the
road exactly where the bridge starts
don't walk across the bridge
yet first get a clear image of what's
before
you it's a bridge that's in
disarray it seems to be under
construction in desperate need of
repair it has chunks of bridge
missing piles of wood scrap metal and
trash everywhere on the
bridge but the bridge is still
standing you see a beat up sign it says
warning out of commission
use at your own
risk as you stand there looking at the
debris and Rubble that's on the bridge
in front of you you notice someone is in
the far distance on the other side of
the
bridge they are waving and yelling in
your
direction you hear them Shout
I need
help listen to them Shout
again I need
help don't
worry the bridge is
safe you can't see who this person
is they are too far
away and there seems to be a light fog
in the
air and you don't trust this mysterious
person with your
life it's obvious to you the bridge is
far from
safe you hear them Shout
again I need
you I need
help please come
fast you
holler is the bridge really safe
the person
answers it's
safe I promise it's
safe you instantly think that's the
wrong
answer I promise doesn't work for
you you've heard that before in your
life and you've been let
down then you hear
again please please come
here it's
safe now take a deep breath
in and now
release on the count of three take
another deep breath in
one 2
three take a deep breath
in and now
release you can't trust this
person but something inside of you is
pulling you in their
Direction onto the
bridge something you can't
explain something that feels
familiar you slowly take your first step
onto the
bridge and see for yourself if it is
safe to the left of you you see old car
tires ahead of you you see piles of
rubble
metal and what looks like a disaster
area you take one more
step and to the right of
you there's a lemonade
stand it appears before
you there is a
child and
mother selling lemonade
it makes no
sense you didn't notice them
before and why would they be on such a
dangerous
bridge you ask
them are you
okay no
response they're sitting there
safely on this little spot on the bridge
that's
clean and
clear the person on the other side of
the bridge calls
out didn't I tell you it's
safe the person
says
please come
here come here soon
you look ahead it's a disaster
Zone you still don't trust this
bridge the
bridge is in total
[Music]
shambles but where your feet are
touching on the
bridge it is
secure now take a deep breath
in and
release you take a step
forward away from the lemonade
stand and it's
gone it disappears in the
fog
you look to the right of
you and there is a broken down
car you look ahead of
you and it's a waste
land concrete
blocks metal
barrels and holes everywhere in the
bridge you look to the left of
you and you notice what looks like two
parents and their
children with fishing
poles they're casting their lines off
the side of the
bridge it makes no
sense the bridge is a
disaster you did not see them
before
when you look around
you there's barely any Bridge left to
support
anyone but in their space as they're
fishing they are
fine they have a solid
railing supporting them as they're
fishing keep
going the voice says from the other side
of the
bridge I told you it's
safe come
quick now take another deep breath
in now
release you take another step forward
onto the
bridge and a friendly puppy comes
bounding up to
you it startles
you how did this puppy cross over the
holes in the
bridge it looks like a golden
retriever the puppy begins to lick your
hand
the tongue is
grippy it doesn't make
sense how did it get here from the other
side behind the puppy is a hole in the
bridge and behind that hole is debris
everywhere you hear the voice
again the person from the other side of
the
bridge I'm over
here come
here hurry
up I need
you but you see everything wrong around
you the bridge is falling
apart it's a disaster
Zone but where you are standing has
repaired
itself underneath your
feet has gotten strong and repaired
itself and you and the puppy are
safe all of a
sudden a leash appears attached to the
puppy and at the other end of the leash
is a
person who offers a delightful
smile you think how is this
possible as they walk by
you you turn around to look at them and
they disappear in the fog and are
gone but you are gaining a little bit of
trust step by step on this
bridge as you discover pieces of the
bridge are
safe but now all that's left before you
is a giant hole in the
bridge and you are not sure that trust
and confidence will be enough to carry
you across this
hole do you see the hole in the
bridge look you can see
it
the person in the distance
yells I need
you keep
walking don't slow
down you think if you take this next
step you can fall through that hole and
become injured or even
die you turn around and say
say I
can't I'm not going to die for
you I refuse to die for
you I don't trust
you it's not worth
it the voice says hurry
up I need your help you can't let me
down step
forward I promise it's
safe there's that word promise
again you've heard that word
before as you look back in the other
direction behind you to where you
started because you're thinking you
better head
back but then you realize it's too
late the bridge behind you is worse than
it ever was
before and the
people have all
disappeared and you realize it's
possible you've been
tricked taken advantage of and
misled The Voice yells out
listen to me you will be safe the bridge
is
safe time is running out the voice
says please
come you take a deep breath
in and
release
take another deep breath
in and then
release as you're standing there on the
bridge looking at that great big
hole you decide to close your
eyes
now take the next step forward Over the
Hole your foot hits Solid
ground and you don't fall through the
bridge you're
standing you open your eyes while you're
standing there on the
bridge and you see underneath you the
whole in the bridge is
fixed take another step
forward as you're
walking you see the bridge is starting
to
mend the bridge is repairing
itself with each step you
take as you are stepping across the
bridge
you start seeing people on this
bridge and
realize you have met them before in your
life you start seeing family
members
friends familiar animals walking
by all of them are happy
everyone on this bridge you have known
at one point in your
life you hear the person
again at the end of the
bridge I'm
here keep
walking you are almost at the end of the
bridge now
and the bridge is
beautiful it's
safe it's
peaceful you can feel the warm sun on
your
face as you're walking on this
bridge and the mild fog around you is
lifting you are almost at the end of the
bridge
now you get to the last step of the
bridge and you're standing
there and the person who's been calling
you all along from the other side is
standing there as
well right in front of you waiting for
you and it becomes
clear this person
was
you this whole
time your soul was
waiting at the other end of the
bridge and the fear that was keeping you
apart is now
gone
now take a deep breath
in and
release you can now open your
eyes we don't realize that when we go
through life our soul becomes in injured
from betrayal and broken trust and this
creates fear within us this hinders the
bridge between our soul and our physical
brain and this bridge is the connection
that allows us to feel safe and to trust
again and not live in
fear you have now completed the
meditation that Bridges your soul to
your physical neurons in the emotional
Center of your brain so that the
connection between them grows strong and
fear and broken trust won't hold you
back feel free to repeat this meditation
daily every other day or a couple times
a week because each time it only becomes
more powerful in its ability to mend the
bridge between your soul and your
body I believe in you and I know you can
heal
[Music]