how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William hey everybody we're talking
about eggs and why eaters lose all and
don't win anything I got nothing against
eggs that's not what it is I'm just the
messenger of something no one wants to
believe the truth on how eggs were
weaponized and used against us and when
you hear how you will never look at eggs
the same
again the one question all these years
everyone who knows me personally has
asked me is what do I know and how much
do I know give me the SK scary stuff aw
so you guys are my friends I'm going to
fill you in on what I know on what
Spirit of compassion told me many years
ago when I was younger about guess what
eggs like so many secrets of the health
industry you won't find this information
out there anywhere else so let me take
you back to the 1920s to when pathology
was expanding the search for what causes
disease truly began and even though
medicine was in its infancy there was a
private group in the pharmaceutical and
medical world that no one was aware of
it involved investors and interests and
a think tank and they were focused on
something that would lead us to how sick
we are
today and why we are getting sicker than
ever before this mysterious group of
people were learning about bugs not the
ones that fly around
like and you know and other little
insect sounds and everything else not
the mosquitoes not those kind of bugs
they were focused on other bugs
pathogens and realizing how dangerous
they can be catching them harboring them
holding them hostage these little
pathogens and what pathogens am I
talking about virus uses and
bacteria and they're realizing that they
may be able to use these bugs but in
order to make more pathogens more bugs
cuz how can you use them if you can't
keep on recreating them the Private
Industry needed to figure out how to
grow them it's like anything you grow
it's like if you want to grow something
you just got to learn how to grow it
right you want to grow a garden you want
grow some tomato plants you want to grow
more Tomatoes got to figure out how to
do it well they had to figure out how to
farm these bugs so it was bug farming
and even then they knew viruses and
bacteria needed something to sustain
itself needed a food you know how like
you're hungry are you hungry right now
and we need food to sustain ourselves
well they knew something with these bugs
that they needed something like we
needed something cuz they were like well
bugs need something well we need
something everybody needs something the
Private Industry also knew that all
viruses and bacteria were alive The
Details Matter here the Private Industry
knew viruses and bacteria were alive not
the public one because everybody has
been told all these years and now the
viruses are not really alive and all
viruses and bacteria don't eat food they
just don't eat that's what we're told
too all these years like why would a
virus or bacteria actually eat
like like why would it eat and spirit of
compassion has been the only source
saying for decades now that bugs eat to
stay alive
because the truth is the Private
Industry has always known this you have
to understand something everything you
know about science and research in
health is controlled or they only let
certain information out of the gate
there's so much classified classified
research and science see the difference
all the medical information and research
and Science in the health industry both
conventional and Alterna ative even
today is controlled and someone doesn't
want you to know that bugs like viruses
and bacteria eat food to stay alive
because someone's going to get in
trouble down the road if that just keeps
on going and going yes they are alive
and yes they eat so the industry needed
to find a food like we need a food how
are we going to keep these bugs alive
what are we going to do they need a fuel
source something that bugs would feed on
pathogens would feed on the goal was to
keep bugs alive outside of the human
body and allow them to grow in the lab
Farm them you know like farm- raised
fish you got them wild in the ocean you
know like wild caught fish wild fish
right and you got them wild in the
streams but they Farm the fish so they
Farm the salmon you know how do you farm
them and keep them growing and then just
feed them and find a food they like well
the industry needed a perfect
environment and tried everything they
tried sugar to feed bugs and pathogens
and guess what it didn't work because
viruses and bacteria don't eat sugar
they found sugar did the opposite how
weird is that Sugar inhibited the growth
of these pathogens they couldn't go
anywhere or develop or proliferate with
sugar so then the industry tried various
animal products they tried meat think
about that one for a second did that
work see that wasn't the winning ticket
either it didn't work animal meat would
not feed the bugs cuz I'm sure some of
you plant basers out there like yeah
that's what's doing it probably that's
what's doing it you know they
systematically went through every food
and stumbl across just one how weird is
this just one what they learned was that
when they examined an egg a fresh egg
they noticed that on the outside of the
shell bacteria was capable of living the
bacteria could live and survive on the
outside of an egg you ever hear of like
salmonella being on like the outside of
eggs you know over the years like whoa
there's a recall from 10 Farms out there
and we need all the eggs all destroyed
that are in the grocery stores because
there's a salmonella outbreak break and
it's on the eggs it's on the eggshells
like well why is the salmonella still
alive why is it still alive the eggs
well it's been days and days and days
later they've been packed they've been
shipped they've been on trucks tractor
trailers they've been on highways for
three straight days then they get into a
store they're not even packed out yet
they're sitting in the back of the the
you know the refrigerator section of the
grocery store and then a produce manager
or a dairy manager comes out he like
okay let's get these eggs on the Shelf
this is like 10 days later how is
Salmonella capable of living on that egg
all this time later but check this out
okay I talked to an egg farmer and he
said well the process is kind of like
this Anthony you got to collect the eggs
they got to go in the cartons they got
to get on a truck they got to be at a
waiting area a transition place a
station then they're back on another
truck then they're driving across the
country then they get to the store and
now they're in the cold section of the
store in the back in the warehouse of
the store and then all the Egg Farmers
have to call all the stores and yell at
them and say can you hurry up and get
the eggs on the shelf and then all the
stores say we haven't sold our other
eggs yet and it's still in the shelf
life date the freshness date is still
good and we want to sell those out
and the Farms are like wait a minute
here just hurry up and get them out and
so now it's another week in the back of
the store and then finally when they
sell all the eggs they get the other
eggs out they put them on the Shelf
we're talking two weeks sometimes we're
talking three weeks so Egg Farmers they
actually have to put a longer shelf life
date on the carton and then here's the
funny part then you go to the
store oo I like these eggs oh I like
these eggs too let me get those okay I'm
at the checkout I'm getting my eggs let
me go home putting them in the fridge
they're nice and fresh there's a good
date on them but you don't eat them that
day not all of them sometimes people
leave eggs in the fridge they're like
there in the fridge for like a week
that's another week and maybe even more
and guess what when there's a salmonella
breakout they're like throw out your
eggs everybody throw out your eggs
meanwhile those eggs are already a month
away from when they were hatched I mean
laid you guys know what I mean so now
before this discovery that bacteria can
stay alive on the outside of an egg they
kept bugs alive in human blood now this
Private Industry many many years ago
they tried animal blood and noticed
pathogens bugs could not live or Thrive
longterm viruses and bacteria they
couldn't proliferate or colonize in
animal blood easy now remember animal
blood on its own I'm talking about human
blood on its own not inside the host
they found human blood was the only
blood that would sustain these bugs and
keep the pathogens alive enough so they
kept these early pathogens alive using
human blood keeping the temperature
adequate so it's like let's get a
patient in here let's steal some blood
let's keep that blood in the
refrigerator let's make sure we take
some out then let's keep the temperature
adequate let's keep the bugs in there
let's see how long they can live let's
let's analyze them let's see if we can
keep them growing enough to stay alive
but they won't proliferate and they were
in this Jam like how are we going to
farm this stuff like how are we going to
make these pathogens live longer and
isn't that funny because shouldn't you
want pathogen not to live like hm we got
a plague right now right do we want that
virus that's going around right now
scaring everybody do we want it to live
like do we want all these bugs to live
well that's the deal this private
industry was about growing and farming
bugs and it's going to take us to some
other talk later but because they
realize humans had a percentage of
something inside their blood already
that was keeping these bugs at least in
a
hypnotic state so what was that a
percentage of mercury people patients
had a percentage of mercury inside their
blood and that mercury was keeping the
bugs in this hypnotic living state so
they can analyze them study them try to
keep them alive preserve them sustain
them them Mercury was used in almost
every aspect of medicine back in the
1920s and a little bit before that too
they wanted more they wanted more bugs
they needed them to thrive they needed
them to grow and colonize and Mercury
was preserving them and keeping them
alive and sustaining them in that
hypnotic State and even partially
feeding them but it wasn't enough and
they didn't know how like how can we
grow more bugs until one patient's blood
not only kept the bugs alive it exploded
them it exploded them they noticed quick
colonizations they were able to watch
viruses reproduce
rapidly they were able to analyze
pathogens recreating themselves in large
numbers oh my God it was that kind of
moment they're like what was in this
person's blood what was in it that did
this so they analyzed what the patient
was eating so sir um we got to talk to
you about what you were eating and what
you're eating and stuff why well we just
need that information we need to know
well okay here's my diet I eat eggs in
the morning and um I eat eggs for lunch
in the
afternoon and I eat eggs for dinner
and before I go to bed I eat another
egg and they noticed that this patient
their diet was
95% eggs and this patient had a lot of
their own Chicken cops so a lot of
Chicken Shacks on their property and
they ate eggs and this is right around
the 1920s early 1920s so they were like
wait a minute here so they noticed when
another other patients blood wasn't
allowing pathogens to survive at all
their diet comprised of no eggs so now
they're like okay we got something here
this patient eats no eggs their blood
isn't helping at all like the pathogens
are just staying hypnotic with the
Mercury for a little while inside the
blood but then they just die off
eventually but this guy's blood is
allowing pathogens to thrive right in
front of them as if it was a magical
magical experience like a miracle was
happening and that's what they noticed
so but there was the potential for mild
growth if someone ate some eggs so then
they brought people in were like listen
we want you to eat eggs for breakfast
only every day s days a week and let's
take your blood so then they take their
blood and they noticed the pathogens
were alive and doing a little bit better
and even growing a little bit so then
they would tell a patient well we want
you to eat eggs for morning and eggs for
afternoon but don't eat them for dinner
and they took blood and they noticed the
pathogens were colonizing even more and
then they went back to that other guy
and they said we need some more blood
and that guy was like sure and they
noticed oh my God this is exploding so
then they requested all their patients
to be eating eggs three times a day and
they were even more than that they'd say
eat them as much as you like can you
imagine some patients were like I'm
getting sick of eggs here I'm getting
sick of eggs right here they said well
you can eat some other things in between
you could still eat some other foods but
eat eggs three times a day and the goal
was two eggs three times a day that was
the amount they wanted now this is
interesting because a lot of people they
would eat two eggs three times a day but
some people would eat less eggs some
people would eat a little more but what
they noticed out of everything that no
matter what if eggs were a big part of
the person's diet the bugs would grow
quicker no matter what so this led to
the discovery of a food that was going
to change history in chronic illness
you're probably thinking wait in a good
way or a bad way well let's just say
hang in there cuz you're going to know
we're going to talk about it instead of
using a patient's blood they went for
the egg itself and that's when they
realized that when they took a virus or
bacteria that was in a patient's blood
and now placed it on the outside of an
eggshell the virus and bacteria was able
to survive they started connect Con in
the dots so what's the next phase what
is it it was to cut the top of the egg
off the
eggshell and cut the top of an eggshell
that was fresh from a fresh egg keep the
temperature of the egg at the right
level and then insert the bacteria and
viruses into the egg and of course add a
little nutmeg and cinnamon actually
no add a tiny bit of mercury what else
would the medical industry be adding and
that's what they did they put a little
bit of mercury inside the egg with the
virus and bacteria it's a brilliant
brilliant Discovery and and scheme and
then what would happen they reproduced
and colonized rapidly viruses bacteria
the farm raising happened boom they got
it does this remind you guys of
something why are we told to not leave
that egg salad with the Mayo
unrefrigerated in the sun too long at a
picnic or a party right like why are we
told well because bacteria will find it
and colonized on the eggs and in the
Mayo which contains eggs in the egg
salad and then food poisoning commences
here we come so let me spell this out
for you the classified industry took
your favorite food used it in labs to
breed viruses and bacteria farming Farm
raising them creating many different
strains and mutations that weren't out
yet in human nature and somehow somehow
these pathogens got out of the labs and
into people I don't know how that
happened um that they just walked out of
the lab you know the virus is just got
off the they got out of the pre petri
dish they got out of the egg they
crawled out and they just walked drawn
out hey I'm putting on my shoes got my
coat got my umbrella we're all heading
out of the
labs yeah how do they get out okay and
this led to the early explosion of
chronic illness in the 1940s and 1950s
when women were filing in to their
doctor's offices with symptoms never
seen before in our history by 1950 this
was happening what does this have to do
with you who cares this is boring who
cares it's why you're sick now you got a
symptom it's why you're sick now you got
eczema it's why you're sick what does
this have to do with your acne a lot
that miserable acne that people have
where they're so upset and they're so I
mean traumatized by it and it can really
affect somebody's life on a deep level
emotionally mentally physically and that
acne wouldn't be there if it wasn't for
this this is why you have struggled with
acne this is the classified private
industry's fault going all the way back
it's why you're suffering today it's why
your bloating is happening because of
this it's why your endometriosis is
happening your body pain your fatigue
and every other condition you can think
of everything now hm get ready for this
one the industry wanted us sick the bugs
just didn't walk on out no they needed
us sick it was important they created
illnesses by using bugs now the public
industry public medical industry public
research and science public industries
of all
they don't know this people work for
them everything's happy good you go to
the office whatever you go to the lab
they don't know this is going on they
didn't know that this is where it
started this is the classified stuff
going all the way back you're not
supposed to know this so that's what fed
the industry it kept them fat and happy
people being sick was the bread and
butter and bacon and we were fried in a
pan and our favorite food the egg
an old survival food that helped Keep Us
Alive during hard times was used against
us was used against you was used against
your children was used against everybody
you know and it's still being used
against us unknowingly today we eat the
egg we feed our bugs we eventually get
sick if we collect more bugs we feed
those bugs and we get sicker the
industry keeps on raising bugs new ones
and old ones they catalog them secretly
classifying them they categorize them
in different strains different
categories different
mutations and then they feed them eggs
while they're doing it they feed them
eggs while they're doing it and then
they let them out of the game
meaning they release them to the public
mhm they do and we get more bugs because
of it and then we eat eggs and we keep
the bugs alive and then we get
sicker and if you are lucky and you're
someone with very few bugs or not the
aggressive strains or aggressive
mutations you can eat a lot of eggs and
get away with it for quite a while
especially if you're eating other good
foods or taking care of yourself you can
kind of keep that balance but if you're
somebody with lime disease neurological
lime brain fog Hashimoto thyroiditis
rheumatoid arthritis do you have that
eczema psoriasis endometriosis fibroids
cysts lupus Ms ey floaters are you
somebody with eye floaters so many
people have so many different kinds of
ey floaters right eczema psoriasis I
said that before Vitiligo depression
crippling anxiety so many people are
suffering from just debilitating anxiety
body pain neck pain back pain
fibromyalgia burning skin Tinkles and
numbness hives how many people have
hives out there mystery rashes
dermatitis Scleroderma rosacea Crohn's
citis cold sores yeah cold sores
H guess where those cold sores came from
from they were raised in eggs going all
the way back a 100 years and they were
let out of the gate so your misery with
cold sores which is herpes simplex one
lives on and lives on and then we pass
it on to somebody else and it lives on
they did this and they used the egg to
do it it was the only way it could be
done and then there's sibo and Celiac
migraines or any autoimmune condition
you want to avoid eggs if you have any
of these symptoms or conditions you
might be saying to yourself I don't eat
eggs or I don't eat many of them first
of all you probably eat more eggs than
you realize throughout your life did you
ever eat mayonnaise or thousand island
dressing or animal style fries or animal
style Burgers pastries cakes cookies
donuts many different breads or rolls
did you ever eat pasta and pizza crust
did you ever have cookie dough there are
so many foods that have egg in it and
you might be someone that's like well I
haven't had a food with egg in it in a
long time but it sits inside the liver
for a lifetime residue unless you
cleanse it out and if you got bugs it'll
feed off that residue and the bugs will
have a field day so enough anyway to
feed these symptoms and conditions even
when you're off eggs for a while let's
talk about this what the industry did by
raising pathogens on your favorite food
so that when you eat an egg and
gradually worsen your condition without
realizing it is
Despicable and it happens to everybody
and you eventually get something no
matter what everybody gets something
thyroid symptoms at age 40 migraines
headaches weight gain it the list goes
on and fatigue hot flashes body pain
eczema or other skin conditions like I
said acne now why would eggs play a role
because these conditions are caused by
viruses like Epstein bar and shingles
it's medical medium information that I
brought out there all through these
years and doctors are learning about it
every day and they're helping their
patients so herpes simplex which is cold
sorce the fever blister okay herpes
simplex 1 2 hhv6
hhv7 undiscovered hhv 10 through 16
right Epstein bar and over 60 varieties
of Epstein bar and mutations shingles
over 30 varieties of shingles and
mutations strepto coctus bacteria which
has hundreds of strains undiscovered and
over 50 different groups that's
undiscovered that were raised in the
labs by by the industry so what's in an
egg that these bugs like to eat let's go
there next all right protein and enzymes
but hey Protein that's why you're eating
eggs yay that's the whole point and
enzymes can't be bad right the protein
in an egg is attached to enzymes that
viruses can easily absorb through their
membrane because the proteins are not
mature they are in their development
phase so the enzymes are attached to the
protein a unique process that only
happens in an egg there are a large
amount of enzymes in a chicken egg
because the chick has not formed yet so
the proteins are unstable and the
enzymes help keep the protein stabilized
also the bugs feed off of hormones
natural occurring hormones in the egg
itself so if you're thinking hey wait a
minute I'm safe I I could do my organic
egg or I can do my backyard raised eggs
but no the egg is a unique ball of
hormones all eggs even organic eggs are
so H what happens when you eat an egg
let's go into that next how is it going
to feed a virus like how's that even
going to happen or a bacteria inside of
you you chew the
egg Yum Yum Yum you swallow it it enters
your small intestinal tract if there's
some hpy l in there right that HP Lori
is going to have a field day it's going
to have a picnic it's going to have a
nice brunch if there's some strep to
coctus in there you're thinking I don't
have strep wa what's he even talking
about this is ridiculous uh sibo H
that's strepto coctus um UTI bladder
infections yeast infections kidney
infections chronic sinusitus um sty
let's see the list goes on yeah people
have strup tock this all in their system
did you have strep throat a long time
ago because it's still in us if you have
a little bit of strep in your gut
because everybody does you can be
somebody with a small amount of bugs so
it's a small Feeding Frenzy that goes on
inside your gut and or inside your liver
or inside your bloodstream or anywhere
else eventually when the egg travels but
you can be somebody though with a large
Feeding Frenzy going on inside of you
and you have a lot of symptoms and
there's a lot going on with your health
and the bugs get little bits of the egg
the bacteria absorbs the egg through its
membrane the outer membrane that
protects the
bacteria over time you start getting
some bloating or digestive issues down
the road and you land yourself a sibo
diagnosis which most women are getting
at this point in time and a lot of men a
lot of men are getting that sibo
diagnosis as the egg travels through
your intestinal tract the egg is pretty
much like a gluey Goo now it's being
absorbed through the intestinal tract up
into the hepatic portal vein heading to
the liver so now the eggs traveling up
to the liver inside everyone's liver are
where most of the bugs are at plus
toxins
petrochemicals pesticides herbicides
fungicides toxic Metals Mercury lead
aluminum cadmium copper just list goes
on the list goes on okay but there's
bugs in there cuz bugs like being in
there too cuz remember what I was
telling you before Mercury feeds bugs
just enough well the Private Industry
the classified part figured that out
long ago so our liver has that too in
there so bugs like the bee in there they
love that spot but that spot egg gets in
there there too and that's where it's
like more fun the eggs coming up into
the liver here it comes and some people
have more eggs going on inside the liver
building up some people have more things
in the liver but here's the thing some
people have more bugs inside their liver
that's where it gets a little sketchy
like one Epstein bar two Epstein bar
three Epstein bar like one potato two
potato three potato they'll have all
kinds of different bugs in there they'll
have a Simplex in there if they've ever
had a cold s in their life well that
Simplex lives in the liver if they ever
haded shingles or maybe they have
shingles and don't know it because they
have back pain or jaw pain trigeminal
neuralgia or anything else going on but
the point is these bugs are in the liver
and that's where the party happens
that's the camp out that's the
campground that's the fair that's the
county fair it's happening in the liver
with all these bugs somebody will have a
couple different varieties of bugs
couple other different varieties of bugs
and some people just might have one or
two and they haven't really done much
yet but as the immune system drops over
time you're under stress your
adrenaline's pumping life isn't easy
you're not eating good you're eating
more eggs than other Foods some other
things are happening then that bug can
grow and take advantage of that egg
inside the liver and they love the liver
because that's where most of the food is
so as the eggs enter the liver another
Feeding Frenzy occurs that gooey glue
Trails up to that liver okay and the
viruses they don't have a mouth so
they're not eating like they're not
sitting down at a dinner table and they
got a fork and a knife and they're just
eating their food like that I know so
you know or they're not like an insect
an insect that's eating somehow or
drinking some kind of water off of a
leaf you know somewhere that's not it at
all viruses absorb Trace particles of
the egg through their membranes and this
is how science and research get the best
of us they even get the best of the
smartest people out there in health
because we think about well viruses must
have a mouth they must chew they must
eat that can't happen it's impossible so
viruses don't eat science of research
knows that they can dumb us down by
saying viruses don't eat you know
because they can keep us like that
because in our minds in people's minds
cuz I talk to people all the time I talk
to doctors and they're like viruses eat
they're like what do they have a mouth
they don't have a mouth they don't start
chewing their food I've heard that from
doctors and I'm not talking about
inexperienced doctors either I'm talking
about renowned experts in their field
like the real thing like 30 years
experience 40 years experience seeing
all kinds of people droves coming into
their offices for years they've studied
in all different fields of medicine and
they can easily get tricked by this one
because human nature is to think
that if something eats it's got to eat
Chomp Chomp Chomp it's got to like eat
something and that's where they get us
in their grips the industry because we
just instantly think an animal or an
insect has a mouth and just eats and so
what we need to know something about
this is that viruses and bacteria not
only eat but they
eliminate poison so they excrete poison
because what goes in has to come out
it's like anybody that eats really right
but viruses and pathogens absorb the
food through their membrane and then
release poisons and toxins through the
membrane out so that's how it's done and
this waste matter is highly toxic it
builds up in the liver over time makes
your liver stagnant sluggish and then
you get the heart
palpitations you get the weight starts
coming on the hot flashes the night
sweats you get a little bit of energy
loss digestion system doesn't work good
anymore all these different things
happen the viruses feed off of the goo
that's sitting inside the liver over
time and then you're like wait a minute
I exercise I take care of myself and
wait I got this pound on me this extra
pound when do I have an extra pound or
two more why is weight coming on easier
now like it doesn't make sense is it
because I'm aging is it because I'm
getting older and the pounds are coming
on it makes somebody gain weight to
people who feel like they would never
gain a pound ever in their life and they
start start gaining weight and some
people gain that weight so early in life
in their 20s and teens and it just
happens because the liver gets maxed out
easy and it gets filled up with all
these toxins and bugs the very thing
viruses and bacteria you guys know what
I'm talking about and as each year goes
by in your life in anyone's life a new
symptom or condition can develop or an
old symptom can come back and go and
come back and next thing you know it
your acne is back next thing you know it
you have acne for the first time or
eczema for the first time or psoriasis
or like I said before like weight is
gaining now and it's like why is the
weight coming on and or migraines or
floaters in the eyes or any kind of body
pain
fatigue and that's because the bugs are
starting to live their life inside of
our bodies and we're feeding these bugs
as we're living our life as each year
goes by but look look look the process
of developing symptoms and conditions
depends on a lot of factors I'm not
saying eggs are the sole reason out
there why everybody's sick it is one of
the sole reasons of how viruses and
bacteria started and were released into
the world but there's all these other
factors that allows the viruses to turn
into a sickness and eating eggs yes
that's one of them but there's other
things too it depends on what bug
somebody has is it aggressive is it
severe what kind of strain is is it what
kind of mutation is it what variety or
how weaken somebody's immune system is
it's important to keep our immune system
strong you guys it's so important I talk
about that for over 35 years but we
weaken our immune systems because life
is not easy here and it can happen to
any of us at any time we go through
emotional struggles that's a trigger we
go through hardships we get exposed to
pesticides and toxic heavy metals and
herbicides and all kinds of other things
too but it all depends on how many good
things you're doing for yourself what
tools are you using for yourself for
example are you doing the celery juice
because that's a tool to help clean up
the mess to help clean up the liver get
bugs out cuz the celery juice helps to
kill off bugs by destroying the membrane
that they use to even eat Foods they
like like eggs see so while bugs are
making mess inside of you all kinds of
messes you're working on cleaning up the
mess too at the same time so what tools
are you using and then it falls into
this whole thing check this out okay
like you're doing a tool that's good for
you you're using something that's good
like celery juice but you're still
eating eggs on your avocado toast see
and yeah you can still get acne or maybe
not acne as bad because your celery
juice is keeping things at Bay so you
can do things that are helping while
you're doing things that are hurting
look it's not your fault that you might
be doing something that's hurting they
ruined our eggs they did they destroyed
our eggs made them a problem it's not
like I got something against eggs and
you're doing something terrible far from
it you're trying to eat you're trying to
survive trying to live your life and I'm
trying to help you and trying to make
sure you have the info so you can
protect yourself so the industry doesn't
win you know the darkness the darkness
that the that's involved the game they
play they created the bugs they made a
world of sickness they make trillions of
dollars as the years come and the
centuries go by and you don't have to be
a part of that entirely you be like you
know what I can keep my eggs out but say
you want to keep your eggs in what tools
are you doing are you doing some celery
juice are you eating good overall are
you bringing in herbs wild foods are you
building up your immune system
do you know how to take care of yourself
cleanse the liver everything matters but
acne can sneak up on anybody when you're
still doing things that can feed the
bugs like eating the eggs this reminds
me of
cocaine like the binging out that
happened well happens today people are
on cocaine every day but it reminds me
of the late 70s and early 80s and mid
80s there was this trend and and I've
talked to a doctor about this and he was
talking to me about it he said you know
what's funny he goes this trend was
crazy back then it was like happening he
had patients come into the office that
were cocaine addicts and um so what
happened was people were snorting
cocaine for 3 days straight they didn't
eat anything they didn't drink anything
like they do now but they weren't taking
care of themselves of course you just go
on a binge and you just stay awake you
don't sleep a wink and you just do it
for 3 days until you crash and you burn
out you sleep and then you wake up and
then you look around and you head to the
health food store or to some store that
sells a bottle of vitamin C doesn't
matter junkiest stuff on the planet just
a bottle of vitamin C and you down it
and this trend was so you can do more
cocaine it was like you're doing
something good for yourself for a moment
so you can get back on the game the
cocaine game so another three days you
binge on cocaine you don't sleep a wink
you don't drink you don't eat anything
you don't take care of yourself you're
just lost somewhere doing it you crash
you burn you go to sleep you wake up
you're like what and then you're back at
the store for more vitamin C that's what
it was that's what it was about sound
familiar you're eating pretty good no
processed foods your ex exercizing no
gluten you're staying hydrated drinking
more water and you have a cheat day or a
binge weekend and you're eating whatever
and now comes Monday you're trying to
work it out in the gym you're doing
extra exercises you're drinking lots of
water you're trying to flush your system
you're trying to look into some kind of
neat little trendy cleanse out there and
you're gluten-free for a little bit
longer you're staying away from the
chocolate cake or some kind of cake and
then you do it again and you have your
cheat weekend again right but here's the
difference with eggs you don't know it's
a
problem you have no
idea nobody's going to tell you it's
classified information you're hearing it
for the first time in your life here on
this podcast or unless you read the
medical medium books
so that's the difference what is the
difference it's stealth it's classified
it's there to mess your life up and you
don't know it's bad so you're eating the
eggs You Got the Whole Foods you got the
eggs you got this good diet going on you
got your egg on the avocado toast you
got your egg your scrambled eggs in the
morning without your toast because you
don't want then the carbs so you're just
doing plain old straight scrambled eggs
with maybe a vegetable or an omelette
right and you don't know it that the
eggs are bad mad cuz the classified
industry ruined them on you and no one
told you and then you don't even get a
choice like the cocaine addict does cuz
the cocaine addict knows that cocaine is
bad for them they know it they're not
like oh this stuff is so good for me let
me snort another line like this stuff is
so good for me no they know it's bad
they're just stuck in the addiction
right but they get at least a chance
when they wake up out of that addiction
for a second to take care of themselves
a little bit like maybe take some
vitamin C but you don't get that chance
so you can't even counter your egg
addiction that nobody told you was a
problem so you don't even get the choice
unless you counter it by accident like
you're doing your celery juice as a tool
or you're eating good in other ways or
you're taking care of yourself or you're
getting a lot of sleep like whatever it
is you're countering it
and you're countering it by accident but
you know the scoop now eaters lose all
that's a scoop a classified industry
took your egg used it raised all these
pathogens created a world of sickness
pain and suffering with your egg okay
now you know like millions of other
people know the truth from medical
medium information that eggs are a
problem now now you have the choice to
do what a cocaine addict does take
vitamin C in between binging but your
choice is like hey I can actually do
some more celery juice take care of
myself better if I really want to keep
my eggs around at least you have a
choice but as time goes by and the eggs
build up inside the liver and we have
different relationships we spread more
bugs around pass more bugs around we go
into restaurants I've had people tell me
that they find Band-Aids in their salads
in some of the finest restaurants
because chefs cut their fingers people
who are working in the industry cut
their fingers they got Band-Aids on and
we collect more bugs we collect them
from public bathrooms we collect them
from all kinds of different ways so as
time goes on the scale tips and it's not
about juggling it anymore the scale tips
all of sudden the bad outweighs the good
it's not 5050 kind of ebing and flowing
where you're getting a symptom here or a
symptom there or you're feeling pretty
good and all is well but you're kind of
doing some good things for yourself
you're gluten-free you might drink some
celery juice you might try something
else and no processed foods you're
eating a few other good foods you're
taking care of yourself getting more
sleep but the scale tips we collect all
these new bugs we we live our life we
get more toxic our liver gets filled up
with more poisons and toxins we collect
more toxic heavy metals and then boom
someone breaks up with us betrayal our
adrenals are running we're in fight or
flight our immune systems lowering we
have some kind of relationship break up
or a divorce somebody cheats on us or
broken trust and that's there and the
scale is tipping and the eggs are still
in there they're still there and as more
and more cheat days happen you can't
kind of have your cheat days anymore
like that's not an option you need to do
more because as you're going through
life the scale is so tipped you're
starting to get a little bit of eczema
now more bloating maybe your
reproductive system isn't functioning
quite like it should and you get a cyst
for the first time in your life maybe
hypothyroid maybe that happens and the
scale gets tipped too far but if the
eggs are still there you have a choice
you can take them out you can get rid of
them and at least Levy the playing field
again bring in some more tools and you
guys get the tools from the medical
medium info so you can deal with your
heart PPS your fatigue your anxiety and
depression and your hair falling out and
the bloating and the thyroid problems
but what if what if here's somebody else
the millions of people out there that
don't have these tools and even know
that the egg is not a good thing and
it's not helping them they just start
their doctor Journey it's always good to
have a doctor of course and you have to
have those doctors and there are a lot
of doctors now using medical medium
information and they they'll even say
we're medical medium friendly Clinic we
medical medium friendly doctor
offices but the doctor journey is the
thing that then millions of people go on
they look for answers just like the
millions of people that have done it
before them over the last 70 years or
more that got in trouble with their
health because the classified Private
Industry created the world of chronic
illness and sickness and it's been a
mess ever since so you're on this doctor
shopping Journey you're looking doctor
to doctor you go to one doctor now
you're at a specialist now you're at a
neurologist now you're at a
pulmonologist and you go to one doctor
and he looks at you he gives you a label
for your condition whatever that name is
but doesn't know why you're sick he runs
a bunch of tests asks what you're eating
tells you to eat eggs you go to your
nutritionist your nutritionist doesn't
know why you're sick does the diet
analysis probably tells you never to
cleanse tells you that your body
cleanses on its own or something like
that and then tells you to eat
eggs you go to your chiropractor and
your chiropractor doesn't know why
you're sick but they want to help with
your diet too something that never did
in the past that's something that
developed in the last 20 years and
they'll tell you to go eat eggs you go
to your acupuncturist your acupuncturist
doesn't know what's wrong with you
doesn't know why you're sick with this
chronic illness and doesn't know why
you're suffering from all these
different symptoms but they'll tell you
to eat eggs you talk to your health
coach your trainer they don't know
what's wrong with you but they'll tell
you to go eat eggs as well and get
plenty of protein and whether you're
sick or you're not sick at all whether
you're somebody who's just partially
sick or you're not sick yet you get told
to eat eggs look check this out okay
public science and research medical
science and research doesn't know why
anybody's sick yet why do you think the
theory of autoimmune is out there where
they tell you your body's attacking
itself which isn't true it's a theory
was never proven and why do you think
they say autoimmune is also cause
unknown because science and research in
the public Arena doesn't know why
anyone's sick all right but classifi
Private Industry that started the
sickness the epidemic of the world
sickness as we got today they know why
you're sick the private classified
industry they know why you're sick they
started the whole mess they're the
reason why the epidemic of chronic
illness exists today they're the ones
that created it but what's crazy is the
public science of research and medical
science of research all the experts and
so forth they don't know why why
anybody's sick they don't know why
someone has eczema or lupus or what
causes it and we can play that game all
day long I think you get the picture
though and a label is not the cause
that's just to shut you up they still
don't know why you're sick like with
eczema it's like here's a cream good
luck see you later that's what they'll
say right and with everybody being such
experts like the public science of
research and medical science research
all the medical community
everybody thinking they're literally an
expert in health science research
studies all of it and what do they do
when you get sick they tell you to eat
eggs what about egg whites or home
raised chicken eggs can you do those you
know I got a friend who has a chicken
shed and she lets out all the chickens
and she tells me it's really healing and
therapeutic they just go all squawking
they go out they're pecking they're all
out and about they're all over her yard
she has a little fence going around the
yard and she tells me Anthony they're
eating insects they're eating seeds
they're eating bugs they're eating grass
they're eating leaves and she tells me
all this stuff and then she'll throw her
scraps that she has you know her
vegetable scraps and she'll and her
fruit scraps and she'll throw them out
there and the chickens are all pecking
through it she says it's the best thing
ever but she's got neurological lime and
she
finally gave in she was like you know
what I finally gave in I got the
neurological lime I contacted you and
you told me to get off the eggs and it
broke her heart her heart was just
broken from that and took a while to get
past it now she just collects all the
eggs which is still therapeutic and she
gives them to her neighbor who has
neurological lime but she gives them to
her neighbor because her neighbor said
she's not going to ever quit eggs she
loves them and she's not going to give
it up no matter what kind of Lyme
disease symptoms She's suffering from so
she brings them over to her neighbor cuz
her neighbor's going to buy eggs anyway
and these are the best eggs because they
ruined our eggs it doesn't matter if
they're organic or free range or
homegrown or from the best place on the
planet that was taken away from us no
matter what that's the hard part about
all of this because the eggs will still
feed the bugs in our bodies that to
create all of our sicknesses and I get
it you might be somebody that's like you
know what I don't have bugs I just got
to like something's a little off like my
microbiome or maybe my adrenals or
hormones are off or my digestion is off
or I'm allergic to gluten or something
and I got a great practitioner or a
doctor and they're just telling me these
things I get it if you're in that place
in life I totally respect that and but
what happens though when you've seen
your 10th doctor and you're losing the
quality of of your life and the fatigue
is so bad and your skin disorder is so
hard on you and everything else then you
just get to a point in your life after 5
years of this or 10 years of this or
maybe just a year of this where it's
like okay what's wrong I need an answer
because I've been there i' done that
I've I've been around I'm
seasoned what is the answer and then
then it's like what okay wait a minute
pathogens okay toxic heavy metals and
what are the triggers because with
people you can go down the road like
everybody else and symptoms may come
later you could be somebody that's
exercising and you're not sick right now
and all seems to be okay and then a
divorce it's a crash and then your
immune system crashes your adrenals are
FL flooding or a bad breakup or you get
cheated on or betrayal or a loss of a
loved one or even
childbirth that can lower the immune
system I've talked about that before
it's why so many moms get Hashimoto
thyroiditis 3 months after they deliver
a baby or they give birth and all these
things can happen so heartache alone
getting stabbed in the back is
devastating surges that adrenaline
lowers the immune system and the problem
can develop months down the road and
then there's other levels of stress too
like a lot of levels of stress that we
deal with and bugs can take ADV
advantage of that when the immune system
drops it's like when a woman gives birth
her immune system is protecting the baby
not the mom the baby and so because of
that her immune system 50% of it during
her pregnancy has been taking care of
the child the other 50% is taking care
of her but but things can happen because
of that and then child birth itself it's
over
90% of the immune system is taking care
of the baby to protect the child and
that's why if a mom has something going
on then all of a sudden the fatigue
happens the hair loss happens um
anything can happen after child birth
it's it's well known women develop a lot
of symptoms that reoccur later including
severe depression anxiety
but what's not known is why all these
symptoms happened after child birth and
months later after child birth research
and science doesn't know why any of that
happened and what the causes are and
because and they don't know also about
the immune system dropping during
pregnancy and when giving birth and that
every little bit counts for support with
the immune system when you're pregnant
and after giving birth but they don't
know that part so then it becomes a
mystery it's like okay your thyroid
problems your hypothyroidism your hair
falling out your migraines your aches
and pains your fatigue and all of it we
don't know why it's happening you just
got autoimmune or maybe it's genetic
maybe it's genes and they just start
going down that road and but they don't
know also what to do to protect you
instead it'll be the opposite and
they'll say well you need to rebuild
after that pregnancy you need to rebuild
after giving birth you should be eating
lots of eggs so keep the eggs in there
and that's recommended to every pregnant
woman who's either pregnant or after
they give birth it's the first thing
that every health professional does or
the second thing or the third thing is
what are you eating are you eating your
eggs so and at the same time the immune
system is dropping the eggs are feeding
more bugs nobody knows that's why all of
a sudden someone has chronic fatigue
syndrome and then we're back to this
whole whole thing of nobody knowing and
it's really sad look I understand if
someone can't let go of their eggs it's
a survival food for a lot of people now
I got people friends that' be like look
you can help me with anything don't
touch my eggs Don't Go Near them it's my
lifeblood it's my religion don't touch
it like I've heard that by from friends
I've heard that from even professionals
that have reached out doctors that reach
out for help and they're like why am I
sick aw and they'll be like look I want
you to do this do this do this and then
eggs and they're like what all a sudden
eggs like no way you can't go there and
I get it completely you know and try to
be kind of open to somebody else too
when you give this information out to
them like when you tell them look stay
away from eggs cuz you might get the
same kind of flak you might get hit with
the same kind of stuff keep a mind you
know keep your mind open and also be
cautious like tread carefully because
you wouldn't believe the kind of trouble
I get about the egg thing and wasn't
even my fault I didn't ruin the eggs the
industry did you guys know you know
what's funny you know what's funny if no
one knows why you're sick then how does
anyone know eggs are actually good for
you if no one knows how to keep us from
getting sick then why are eggs so good
for us there's all these anti-aging
people people out there they like
anti-aging live longer but they make
sure that you're on this balanced diet
and you got your eggs in that diet too
but the eggs aren't going to keep you
living longer when you got all these
bugs making you sicker and giving you
diseases and conditions including cancer
and all kinds of other things so it's
not one of those longevity Foods so
let's talk about science the science end
of things right in your mind you might
be somebody that's like well what about
the evidence that eggs are really
healthy for us okay what about that well
it's funny because paid for science
talking about eggs being that good for
us doesn't know why anybody's sick
that's incredible right or how about
this paid for Science and
studies not only doesn't know why
anybody's
sick but doesn't know classified private
evil industry from the past ruined the
eggs raised all the bugs that is sick so
here they are talking about protein
Source number one protein Source there's
nothing wrong with eggs at all they're
the perfect food that's the consensus
they got the Omega-3s they got vitamins
they got
nutrients and that's what they'll do and
it's all paid for studies what you won't
find you won't find a paid for study or
a bunch of paid for studies that
actually talk about why eggs are really
not good for you and here's the other
problem nobody knows in science land
science and research land or medical
science research land in public Arena
not classified public Arena knows that
those eggs will feed bugs so if that
study ever happened on a public level it
would be shut down faster than you could
think it would a bomb would blow up in
the place literally lab coats would be
flying everywhere it would be a disaster
that's what would happen if there was an
actual study where they were discovering
eggs actually feed the bugs keeping
everybody sick and this stuff got out
there forget it they don't want that
chicken out of the chicken shed running
down the street telling the truth about
what they did to the eggs and why
everybody's sick they'll never ever ever
tell you that your bugs that are causing
your sickness were because they raised
them for decades in last abs and let
them out they don't want that chicken
out of the shed they don't want nobody
knowing why you're sick they just don't
and look they'll never tell you that the
eggs you eat feed the bugs they raised
in Labs no one will tell you it's the
Wild Wild West when you get sick and
that's how they love it they love that
not the good people working for the good
science of research and for the good
meaning the good in pensions all the
different health professionals that they
got their heart in it and they want to
heal people I'm not talking about that
I'm talking about the classified Private
Industry that started this epidemic of
illness including what we're faced with
today you're on your own when you get
sick that's what
happens and if you don't think so you'll
realize that after you're fourth doctor
that you're on your own and maybe you're
someone that's not really sick or you
got just a couple little symptoms and
you're young and microbiome is an
example of making you kind of like
thinking well everything's good candida
I could deal with that um a little bit
of a hormone imbalance digestion is off
a little bit but man when you get sick
sick and that eczema is getting really
bad and your fatigue is getting worse
and your brain fogs taking over and you
got these unexplainable symptoms and
you're on your third neurologist and you
did all the testing and spent all this
money and you got this neurological
fatigue your anxiety's crippling then
you want answers and they're not going
to tell you why everybody's sick and
they're just going to tell you you
should be eating your eggs of course no
processed foods don't do processed foods
you know but that's not enough that's
not an answer and guess what plant-based
is not enough either because I know it's
some of you guys might be thinking that
are plant-based like o I'm off the hook
I'm off the hook man I don't eat eggs
but the problem is plant basers always
run back to eggs it's the first thing
they run to when they get a symptom or
they have a tooth problem cavity or an
ache and a pain and then boom they're
done with a plant-based diet they still
keep some of to some of the tools that
are in a plant-based diet like some of
the philosophy that's in a plant-based
diet the keep something but they'll
bring eggs in as their first food or
cheese they'll bring eggs or cheese
they'll hit the dairy I get it I totally
get it but being plant-based is not
enough because there's also residue from
years of eating eggs still inside the
liver and if you're not cleansing or
learning how to cleanse that out of your
liver to begin with you can still get
your first symptoms or your second
symptoms or third symptoms or a new
round of them while you're plant-based
unless you know why you got sick to
begin with paleo carnivore that's not an
answer fod map food combining clean
eating random supplements and no
processed foods are not enough and
they're not answers medical M
information is about answers yes getting
rid of eggs is one of the options one of
the choices you can make that can really
help and if you've been to 10 doctors
you're still going to be told to eat
eggs maybe your plant-based doctor might
be like no no eggs plant-based is the
way to go but I've seen plant-based
doctors get sick for the first time or
for the third time and something doesn't
feel right and they're off eating eggs
they actually go get eggs themselves
many people on a plant-based diet start
just eating eggs again and they won't
rip eggs apart too bad it's so funny
I've noticed in a plant-based movement
that eggs are coveted they're actually
coveted because you never know when
you're going to need to run back to them
so when the symptoms get the best of you
the first animal product you run to is
those eggs and hey look that's okay it's
like you get a little scared and you're
like oh my God maybe eggs are something
I need when the crap hits the fan it's
the first place you go it's one of those
Foods in the back of your mind that you
can lean on when things get
uncomfortable there's a law about eggs
you don't mess with them it's the best
food on the planet for you hands down
that's what everybody's told you know
what's a sick joke they raise viruses in
a lab on eggs the viruses cause
reproductive system diseases in women
and then you tell women to eat eggs for
their health which keeps feeding their
viruses and making the reproductive
system conditions worse it's really
really evil look let's face it no one's
allowed to talk bad about eggs it hits
the emotional core it's a comfort food
and considered a health food people
start putting their hardboiled eggs over
easy poached eggs on their salads they
make egg sandwiches and burritos avocado
toast with eggs I see it all the time
there's people out there and they're
like making their avocado toast and then
all of a sudden here comes a fried egg
out of nowhere and it gets put on top
it's like wait a minute wait wait you
didn't have to do that oh what and then
or scrambled eggs I see that too you got
avocado toast going on and all of a
sudden now there's a scrambled egg on
top and problem is with that then the
acne comes 3 months later or 2 months
later and nobody knows why it's like
wait a minute why am I getting a new
bout of acne or why am I getting acne at
all is it hormones no it's it's the eggs
it was feeding something inside of you
and you're not going to blame the eggs
ever even if you knew the truth
sometimes people still won't go there
it's like okay I know the truth but
there's no way I'm going there the
classified industry loves how we love
our eggs that's the first thing they
also love how we don't know what they
did to our eggs they want us to marry
those eggs till death do us part that's
what they want it's like an insurance
policy to guarantee we all get sick
someday they want our bugs to be fed did
you hear that that was the plan and then
sell
Pharmaceuticals keep people sick for
also other reasons too reasons that
aren't so great and it feeds the
industry and the industry's favorite
thing of all is that not only do we not
have a clue but we treat eggs like it's
the air we breathe we never question it
it's going to go on on forever and ever
and ever did you ever see that movie
Invasion of the Body Snatchers it's an
old movie from many years ago they leave
a pod by your bed that looks like a
cabbage so when you get sleepy and
you're ready to go to bed you're getting
all comfy and you're tired and then you
start falling asleep okay your body gets
taken over by a replica of yourself but
the difference is you end up mindless
your body was snatched and you do as
they say well this egg thing is kind of
like that we mindlessly eat our eggs and
we shut up about them okay don't say
nothing bad because you'll get your
grandpa upset especially if he's making
his eggs in the morning he's going to
start yelling trust me he will you'll
get your mom upset too she'll start
yelling look it happened to me I was 7
years old Spirit of compassion said you
know hold off those eggs and I was like
well I don't want to have that this
morning she was like what and it just
went out of control look you'll get your
best friend upset I got a friend who
yelled at another friend and freaked out
because the other friend didn't want any
eggs I mean and then or you'll just get
this whole thing where somebody be like
what do you mean you don't like eggs
everybody likes eggs uh you got allergic
are you allergic to eggs or you got an
allergy or something people just freak
out cuz they've all been body snatched
even our families they're taking over by
the body snatcher pod and you're the
only one left but if you complain and
say you don't want your eggs and you
tell them that those eggs are bad for
you then they'll leave a pod by your bed
and you'll get snatched you'll eat the
eggs for the rest of your life and
you'll be eating eggs all the time look
I get it no one wants to know they got
bugs in them no one wants to know that
they're feeding their bugs with their
favorite food when you think about that
it's really annoying it's like okay wait
a minute here that's my favorite comfort
food or that's my favorite food but I
don't tell everybody it's my favorite
food cuz some people be like I don't
really like eggs yeah they do when you
learn the truth about eggs that's
already helped millions of people
worldwide the medical medium information
people who were so sick and they needed
every Advantage they could get and it
counts when you're really sick and when
they rid the eggs from their diet it
changed their lives it gave them that
edge see I get it if you're not that
sick no one wants to know you got a bug
and no one wants to know you're feeding
your bugs especially if it's your
favorite food you'd rather think maybe
my hormones are off or adrenals are a
little bit problematic or my gut balance
is off or poor digestion or leaky gut or
got autoimmune or something but if you
get sick enough and it finally hits you
something's wrong and we need to get it
better getting rid of eggs is a good
start a really good
start they took a survival food the
innocent egg that we relied upon
utilized and needed for hundreds of
years and turn this food the egg against
us without our permission taking
something precious and meaningful that
was ours and weaponized it and raised
the very pathogens that are responsible
for sickness today without us knowing
without us seeing and without us getting
a chance to stand up for ourselves and
make a choice to protect our egg and be
able to decide for ourselves what is
right as we walk our path we want things
to be as they are not something else
that we know nothing about there's a
feeling that overcomes us all every time
we're in a store you remember it right
as you're grabbing a dozen eggs or more
there's an emotional attachment as we
open the carton hatch an automatic
button in us to make sure each one is
perfect and not one of them is cracked
we learn this from the beginning of our
life it's part of a deep emotional
connection before we're taught to
scramble or fry
they took a legendary food from us
surrounded by life-saving Glory they
snatched it away from us all and created
a forever lasting gory leading to
sickness of millions of people but
you're not supposed to know that story
the egg was used to take the breath away
of so many who did no wrong it caused a
historical neurological problem and some
ended up in the iron lung as the
innocent people stared at at the mirror
they couldn't go anywhere they were
filled with Terror they no longer could
look up and see the church St unless
they were looking down at the floor in
the
mirror how did this happen and what was
the way the truth is that men in the lab
coats opened the egg research and
science turned against this overnight in
just one day what does it matter and
there eyes it was six of one half dozen
of the other and who cared if each of
the eggs they opened up were from a
different hand mother what they did to
us and our eggs is surreal shows us once
again that the spiritual war both around
us and above us is real and that
Darkness runs man and the industries and
tries to decide how we receive our pain
and our suffering but this doesn't have
to be our Our Fate we have our own free
will to take control over our health and
not throw it all away because they know
nothing we can make our own decisions
and choices as we learn how to overcome
and beat them at their own game and as
we battle Darkness on our own terms not
their terms they're not the same using
the tools and the knowledge and the
inside truth from way above we can see
the light
and decide our own outcome that can make
every difference on your journey
searching Wellness so I leave to you a
chance and a choice that can bring you
to a place of empowerment and
peace as you bring your health back and
rise out of the
ashes see I believe in you and I
know you can
heal
[Music]
as you guys know I'm not a doctor any
information you learned here feel free
to take to your doctor at healthcare
provider if you found this show helpful
and informative feel free to share it
with someone in need of the information
if you like this show Please Subscribe
and leave a review on Apple podcast you
can also find me on YouTube Facebook and
Instagram ATM medical medium and for
more information on healing please visit
medicalmedium.com
thank you so much for
listening