welcome to the medical medium podcast
I'm Anthony
William hey everybody we're doing the
fruit picking meditation it's bad enough
our busy lives keep us from getting in
touch with nature and even if we do have
time to take a stroll in a field or walk
in the woods it doesn't mean we're
partaking in one of the most important
aspects there ever is and Ever Was and
that's fruit picking why is it important
because picking fruit heals anxiety PTSD
and rebuilds your spirit heart and
soul picking fruit is one of the most
powerful meditations in existence it is
a sacred Act of respect and gratitude to
the Earthly mother for the miracle of
food even if you you do it only once in
your lifetime it will be an experience
you can reignite over and over just by
thought to activate healing in your soul
this meditation can be just as powerful
and can reignite the past experience of
picking fruit or create a new experience
if you have never picked fruit before
each piece of fruit still on the tree is
living food that's connected through the
plant's roots to the living water from
deep within the Earth if you visit a
picky own apple orchard and you touch an
apple on the tree your cells will
resonate with the apples grounded nature
and peace will spread throughout your
body when we take the time to focus on
Nature's rhythms we activate trust and
faith within our souls we rewire our
neurons reverse anxiety and PTSD and our
efforts to live a good life will be
fruitful the fruit picking meditation is
for anyone who does not have access to
picking fruit whether because of the
time of year or any other
circumstance if you picked fruit before
this meditation will let you experience
it once again even if you've never
picked a piece of fruit in your life
this meditation is just as powerful
picking fruit is a part of our soul
spirit and heart and this connection
helps heal our spirit heart and soul
reconnecting with fruit picking is like
reconnecting to our very Soul's
existence to begin find a comfortable
position this meditation is best lying
down but you are welcome to do this
meditation sitting up you can be inside
or
outside now let's begin the fruit
picking
meditation when when you're ready close
your
eyes now take a deep breath
in and
release take another deep breath
in and release
now Envision yourself walking down an
Old Country
Road the sky is blue the sun is
shining and the road is made of dirt and
Pebbles see the Pebbles under your feet
as you're walking
you look up into the
distance you see an opening at the end
of the dirt
road you're getting closer and
closer to the end of the
road
and you notice that a fruit Orchard is
there you cannot tell what kind of fruit
is in the
orchard you reach the Orchard and notice
shiny red fruits all over the
trees
you walk into the Orchard and approach
one of the
trees you notice it's filled with
cherries there is a basket under the
tree you lean over and pick the basket
up you look back at the cherries on the
tree you reach out and gently pluck one
of the
cherries and place it in the
basket you reach out for another cherry
you pluck it and place it in the
basket you see one more
cherry a large
one it's slightly Out Of
Reach so you have to stand on your tippy
toes stretch your arms out as as far as
you
can just barely reaching the
Cherry finally you grab onto the
Cherry pluck
it and place it into the
basket it is warm
out and there's a comfortable breathing
that you feel on your
face you look to the
right and you see another fruit
tree the fruit on this tree is much
larger and also
red you walk over and you see that these
are
apples they are higher
up so you take your
hand place it on the
branch and gently lift yourself up on
your
toes you reach as far far as you can and
grab an
apple as you lower yourself down you
take the Apple from the tree with
you this allows two more apples to fall
off the tree and land on the
ground
see the apples on the
ground you place the Apple you just
picked into your
basket and you bend over to pick up a
fallen
Apple you grab that Apple off the ground
and you place it into your
basket you walk over a few
steps bend
over pick up the second Fallen
apple and place it into your
basket
you notice another apple on the
ground that you didn't knock off the
tree you bend over and grab the Apple
off the
ground you notice it has a
worm
that worm
represents
PTSD
anxiety
hardship trust
broken
losses as you are holding the
Apple a bird flies onto your hand
hand and grabs the worm right out of the
apple and flies off your
hand into the
sky something has been freed inside of
you you feel light as
air the sun is
shining a gentle breeze is on your
face the air is clean and
fresh you feel
relieved so you find yourself a
comfortable spot to sit down and rest in
the
grass you realize quickly you've sat
down in a strawberry
patch you have strawberries all around
you
you put one hand on the ground and lean
over and use your other hand to reach
out and pluck a ripe juicy strawberry
off a strawberry
plant you add it to your
basket
you see a larger strawberry on the other
side of
you you lean over put your hand down as
support reach out and pluck that
strawberry you place the strawber
into your fruit
basket you notice the sun is starting to
set you get up off the
ground and
stand you reach your arms out and do a
gentle
stretch you bend back down and pick up
your fruit
basket look towards the dirt
road and start to head out of the
orchard
you see the Pebbles and dirt under your
feet along the sides of the road you
notice wild blueberries
growing look to the left of
you you step off the road and walk into
a blueberry
patch
you crouch down in a squatting
position and start picking the wild
blueberries two or three at a
time and placing
them in your
basket you reach out out
again and take two to three more wild
blueberries this
time you can't help
yourself you put them in your
mouth you pick a handful more and place
them into your fruit
basket you get
up and start to walk out of the
blueberry
bushes back onto the dirt
road and start heading
home
as you are walking you get
hungry so you pick up one of your
strawberries out of your fruit
basket and place it into your
mouth as you're walking
along you bite into the
strawberry
chew
and then
swallow you take a few more steps on the
dirt
road and then grab a cherry out of your
fruit
basket and gently bite into
it you feel the pit in the
center and you spit the pit on the
ground
the juicy Sweet Cherry is unlike any
Cherry you have ever
eaten then you grab an
apple out of your fruit
basket a beautiful red blush
Apple you bite into
it
it's sweet and
juicy it's the best apple you have ever
eaten as the sun goes
down you feel
nourished you feel
safe your soul feels renewed
your spirit is
strong and your heart is
revived it's
dusk the Sun is
setting you get to the end of the dirt
road and see an old wooden sign
you read it in the light that is left as
the Sun is
setting the sign
says come back
anytime now take a deep breath
in
and
release you see
cherries
apples wild
blueberries and
strawberries take another deep breath
in and
release
you see the sun setting over the dirt
road and the orchard in the far
distance one more deep breath
in and release
now when you're ready open your
eyes you have now completed the fruit
picking
meditation your journey in life has now
been reinforced you have brought the
power of fruit picking into your very
own existence
every cell in your body was awakened by
this
experience all fruit trees have a soul
but their soul can never be fulfilled
unless we as humans are eating the fruit
they bear in order for us to feel whole
we have to have an unbroken Spirit heart
and soul fruit picking mends the cracks
of all three and lets us find our way
not be lost and live our life free the
very wounds we have come to know push us
up just like a fruit tree grows and over
time all that we've been through the
storms the weather the wind over the
ocean of Life allowed the beauty to show
your path will never be the same now
that you have experienced fruit picking
which will begin to reverse PTSD anxiety
broken trust and anything that's stands
in your way of you becoming a fruitful
empowered stronger enlightened being
when you reach up to pick up a divine
piece of fruit a message runs through
you connecting you from the fruit to the
ground your soul begins to spark as you
bring back the essence of you that was
lost and now it's
found you can rise out of the ashes
[Music]
see I believe in
you and I
know you can
[Music]
heal