how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William hey everybody we're talking
about potatoes it's a food that
generates a whole bunch of love and at
the same time a lot of hate when eaten
in the right way potato can help you
gain strength and deeply satiate
especially when eating straight but
whatever you do try not to take the
negative bait fear and confusion are
tactics to change your mind about this
innocent Spud that's far from a dud the
irony is it builds up your blood and can
extend your life and give you more time
we're constantly being misled and told
us food can make us feel dead it's it's
a night shade it's bad nothing good it
has stop it from entering your mouth it
will hurt you it's sad what was done to
the potato has caused a lot of Rifts
they fry them in oil and turn them into
chips scaring people to never eat them
again you better stay strict forever the
potato will be known to widen your
[Music]
hips this is a nice restaurant excuse me
waitress can I get a glass of water
we're not ready to order yet hey let's
get the fries do you want to share them
wait you want your own me too me too hey
you ready to order can we get a large
plate of your crazy curly fries
fantastic thank you oh my God these look
so good they're just so yummy I love the
crunchiness
are really
good do you think they're like a th000
calories no they're not 1,000 calories
pH I was kind of getting worried right
there for a minute what 2500
calories they're that bad it's all
starch uh I'll just work out tomorrow
more it doesn't matter I'll do extra
workout this is my cheat day anyway I'm
going to enjoy it and not feel guilty
it's all about
balance in some ways what you just heard
here wasn't a cheat day if it was just
the potato but while everybody's focus
on the carb aspect they're missing the
most important concern there is the oil
that's the cheat day part it's not the
potato it's the fat on the potato and
that's where the bad calories are doing
the extra work out the next day is only
to clean up the oil mess not the carb
mess the oil slick mess carbs on their
own they're safe carbs with oils and
fats are a problem any carb with oil and
fat is what the real concern should be
these days the potato always gets to
blame it always has in recent decades
and probably always will
mostly because the health world is a
pile of guessing games Hit or Miss hit
or miss miss hit hit Miss got it there
nope didn't work that might work uh
maybe that'll work later no it didn't
try again hit Miss again guessing game
There You Go Round the Corner Round the
Bend never ends guessing game when
you're sick for three five 10 years seen
more doctors than you ever could have
dreamed of and you're still sick and on
medications and tried everything
alternative medicine had to offer every
approach and someone tells you hey just
go try it whatever see what works for
you everybody's different did you try
what works for you go go you should try
it see if it works wait a minute just
see it works for me that's the answer
like that'll fix it after all the
doctors and all the years I've been sick
just see what works for me that's that's
how to do it that's how you're doing it
so that's how you're getting better so
you're better or wait a minute you were
never sick and you're telling me that um
don't we all just have human bodies and
when we're really sick there should be
an answer out there just try something
and see if that works isn't that like a
guessing game and within the world of
guessing games one of the things that
takes the blame is potato like must be
the potato did you take that out of your
diet cuz that could be causing all your
problems in the guessing game world
that's how it works when it comes to
having a health symptom or condition and
trying to find relief in the guessing
game world or hit or miss World this
could happen if you got acne the potato
did it if you have a weight problem the
potato did it there are countless
mistakes in the Health Arena what's good
what's bad is that good is that bad is
that bad yeah that's good no that's bad
and a lot of innocent bystanders got
mauled because of it the potato was just
sitting there mining its own business
and we grabbed it shoved it in a big gun
and shot it 300 M an hour across a field
and when it hit somebody in the head and
nearly killed them it was the potato's
fault not the dude who shoved it in the
potato gun and shot it it's the potato's
fault Let's Pretend something let's do
some make believe Let's Pretend There's
millions of people in the world that are
sick struggling and suffering with
countless symptoms and they've been to
all these different doctors exhausted
all resources looked at every scientific
study about their illness that they can
find and they were still sick with no
answers oh wait that's not make believe
there's no pretending that because
that's true it's reality okay okay no
pretending there's millions of people
sick no one knows why yes they got a
label for their disease or symptom like
fibromyalgia neurological Lyme Hashim
modus thyroiditis but still no one knows
the cause the true cause so it's a
random Blame Game a pick and choose
that's how it's done and since no one
knows why people are sick with chronic
illness we need a Fall Guy or as many
Fall Guys as we can find or produce or
get or just get somewhere find somewhere
or whatever and someone a Fall Guy was
thrown in the mix and a mistake was made
that's how all the theories of mistakes
are made or created because when there
aren't any answers to why someone's
suffering one mistake two mistake three
mistake four occurs one potato two
potato three potato four um one potato
two potato three potato four one potato
two potato what wait wait a minute
potato that's why everybody's sick right
now it's like the makers of the health
theories and mistakes stumble across the
reasons in a children's rhyme or hearing
something out there or finding something
because really you're grasping at straws
when you don't know why people are sick
excuse me excuse me is that potato on my
dish I can't eat that can you remove it
please what no it's cooked fine I just
can't eat it why uh it's cuz it's a
night shade um what's a
Nightshade not really sure but it sounds
really scary it sounds shady and my
health Guru told me to avoid it I think
it means they grow at night or they give
a lot of shade I really don't know I'm
told it'll make me sick am I still sick
yeah I got bad days do I still eat them
no how would I know I'm sensitive to
potato or night shades I have no idea it
just makes sense yeah I'm sick with
fatigue still and headaches brain fog
and I get dizzy and my digestion is
never good and I got aches and pains
it's probably the night shades right
mistakes are made every day and the
potato gets thrown in the PO of mistakes
when potato took the hit more than 20
years ago as being a problem no one was
looking at what was around the potato
the fixings the dressing The Works hey
good to see you let's sit down and order
something M these hash browns are really
good so buttery I love butter these eggs
are yummy too oh oh best pancake I ever
had hey waiter can I get an extra dab of
butter on these pancakes what's that
these are buttermilk pancakes oh good
can I get two strips of bacon on the
side and a little cream in my coffee
thanks yeah how have I been feeling well
been a little achy lately joints have
been hurting haven't been feeling that
great little tired my doctor says be
careful of the night shades oh I
shouldn't have had those hash browns
just now what was I thinking what gets
overlooked along with so many things is
the butter
the milk cream sour cream oils lard
cheese bacon vinegar Mayo egg and gluten
nitrates and
antibiotics these get ignored if you're
convinced it's the potato or a doctor or
practitioner got sold on the potato bill
of goods or read something in some
article or in a meeting at a convention
that potato was bad then you get nervous
and you avoid it there's no science that
can prove or ever proved that potato was
a problem or caused a problem and very
few people eat a potato by itself
without a dressing or a condiment or
foods like Dairy and gluten with it do
you know anybody who just eats Potato by
itself or with lettuce no oil no butter
no milk no cheese do you know anybody
just eating potato with none of that oh
you do you know somebody who ordered
just fries and only fries but wait did
you miss something they were fried in
oil or lard or he had some ketchup with
vinegar in it which doesn't help either
a person who isn't well has bigger
problems than a fake problem like the
potato it's a classic case of bait and
switch the cheese is fine the potato's
bad look over here the Butter's safe hey
the Butter's fine the potato potato's
dangerous hey over here the milk is good
but the potato's bad it's real simple
butter will set you up for a future
heart attack anyone who's somebody in
health telling you that butter is good
on anything or even in your coffee is
unaware and somehow missed the heart
attack memo the most important thing to
understand about food is what food can
cause a problem and why does it cause a
problem well you think the an are out
there avoid gluten process food fried
food you heard all of this it seems like
all the answers are out there already
there's nothing to know that's new so
when they say that food will cause
inflammation what food and why how how
does the food cause the inflammation
because there's no study or science that
determine white gluten causes a problem
no one knows it's all theories the
theory is not a proven factual
guaranteed answer that's why it's called
a theory inflammation caused by a food
is a theory science can't see what
happens when you choose something
swallow it and then monitor it with an
actual scope and computer and visualize
right in front of their eyes your cells
getting inflamed it hasn't happened and
it never will here's one for you why
would one person be able to eat whatever
they want and feel great while another
person never feels good and foods like
gluten make them feel worse but if it
was the food itself then no one would
get away with eating it one person's
inflamed one person's not if a food
causes inflammation then it's going to
cause inflammation in everyone but it
doesn't theories become sales pitches
someone's going to sales pitch you on
eltin Theory probably sell you a few
supplements too someone's going to sales
pitch you on a Nightshade Theory maybe
someone's going to pitch you on the
butter in your drink Theory or butter in
your water doesn't matter how much it
defies Common Sense the thing is some of
the theory makers don't even believe in
their own theories but they do believe
one thing the people are gullible and
will buy into these theories but what
they don't realize is is that people
aren't G
people are trusting there's a big
difference and these Theory makers take
advantage of trusting people and treat
them like they were chickens or cattle
any chance to cash out on a theory make
a brand out of it maybe make a lot of
money a theory that defies Common Sense
someone's going to do it people like to
gamble you like to gamble right gambling
is great who cares if you leave a
gambling place with only your box on
barefooted trying to call for a car
service because you gambled your car
away but you realize you don't have your
phone it's gone too lost in the bet so
let's gamble with your health on a
theory potatoes are bad you ready to
roll the dice is it going to come up
snake eyes are you going to roll a seven
who's got the Joker card you think your
cards will fall on a 21 you think that
little ball spinning around and around
and around is going to land on that high
number you got to watch out because the
potato is about to drop down a straight
flush and you want to be on the side of
the winner unless the brainwashing you
underwent stops you what brainwashing am
I talking about it's a Nightshade it's
got lectins It's too high in carbs
voiding nutrition make you gain weight
it's a white food that kind of
brainwashing and manipulating I'm not
talking about everybody who hears
something and tells someone something
else who tells somebody something else
because they heard something from
someone else who heard something from
somebody else who told somebody else I'm
talking about the people who make a
career out of playing guessing games
with People's Health the theory makers
why does it matter because it stops you
from eating a food that can help you who
cares well if you're someone who's
living their life a mattress in couch
Island and is really struggling to get
through their day everything counts they
don't have time energy money to waste on
another bad idea little things matter it
could be make our break in recovery so
being told you should fear a food that
could actually help you will only set
you back and not help you move forward
does a potato cause inflammation no it's
the foods that are eaten with a potato
that cause a problem they still don't
cause inflammation either but the milk
cheese butter corn oil and cream feed
viruses and bacteria inside our body and
then these bugs create the inflammation
they eat food they like and then
eliminate the food go to bathroom inside
your body we become the pathogens toilet
and this is really toxic they release
what I termed viral
neurotoxins these neurotoxins can cause
inflammation viruses and bacteria IA can
also burrow themselves into organs and
glands creating more inflammation so
it's not even the milk cheese butter and
gluten that causes inflammation when you
grab that milk carton of milk you pour
your glasses of milk there and you grab
it and you start sending it
down all your bugs in there are just
going like yeah yeah yeah there it is
there it is they start feeding on it and
eating it and that's how it goes and
that's what the problem is the bugs that
are inside of us are drinking the milk
that's why you could be somebody who's
95 years old anywhere around the world
or in some country somewhere and
drinking milk and everybody knows
they're drinking milk they're 95 years
old they feel okay they're living their
life everybody's like look how old you
are this is amazing and what do you do
it's like drinking milk well they don't
have the bugs and then when a
20-year-old drinks a glass of milk all
of a sudden the eczema the psoriasis an
acne breakout occurs stomach cramps
diarrhea bloating all happens and they
remove the milk and dairy things start
to get better and better and better
because they have the bugs so when that
person sends that milk down and drinks
it the bugs are drinking it at the same
time but guess what the potato doesn't
feed any viruses or bacteria but the
butter on the potato feeds the viruses
and bacteria potato starves viruses and
bacteria starves the bugs put butter on
the potato now we have a problem it's
like one is fighting the other the
potato is antiviral and the butter is
proviral and then we got eggs eggs feed
viruses and bacteria potatoes don't eat
eggs with their fried potatoes in the
morning you got a conflict of interest
one food is trying to save you one food
is not potatoes are a Nightshade what
does that mean the theory is that night
shade that are edible possess an
alkaloid that alkaloid could be
irritating to some people causing
inflammation what no one is told is that
they're looking at the alkaloid that the
leaves and stems of The Nightshade
plants have that you don't eat they're
looking at the potato leaves and stems
the tomato leaves and stems that's where
the alkaloid resides the alkaloid in the
tomato and potato is the normal edible
alkaloid different from the alkaloid in
the leaves and stems it's the normal
alkaloid in potato that's equal to the
alkaloid in lettuce raspberries Swiss
Shard Lamb's quarters blackberries
artichoke zucchini and every other
edible plant food certain people that
are considered sensitive to night shades
like potato have other problems that has
nothing to do with the potato there are
other things in their diet causing the
trouble that's feeding the root causes
of their symptoms and conditions the
problem is people eat the potato with
other things or they eat the potato
cooked wrong fried in oil baked with
cheese and cream mashed with butter and
milk baked or fried as a chip with bad
oil or combined with a bunch of fat
potato and meat potato and chicken
potato and pork potato and eggs potato
and oil potato and tofu which leads us
to another problem a diabetic nightmare
carbohydrates and fat combined causing
insulin resistance any carbohydrates and
fats combined causes insulin resistance
and the potato gets to blame the
carbohydrate looks like the culprit the
bad guy but what's really happening is
the fat is getting in the way of
insulin's job to send a message to your
cells to open up wide and then guide the
sugar into the cells so they get the
food they need and the fat gets in the
way and blocks it forget potato stick
any carbohydrate in the pitcher and the
exact same thing happens rice and
chicken the chicken fat blocks the carb
the sugar from the rice from entering
your cells pork and beans pork and rice
same thing happens there too quinoa and
oil oatmeal and peanut butter turkey
sandwich with meat and bread pasta and
butter the carb is always blamed as the
A1C Rises or hypogly lmia occurs or
hypoglycemia comes on but really it's
just a fat insulin isn't produced to dry
fat into your cells your cells aren't
Reliant upon fat they rely on sugar
glucose to survive so we can function
blood sugar means everything without
blood sugar we can't function they're
not testing your blood fat the fat
doesn't keep you alive it's not what's
important here it's not letting you
function on a day-to-day basis if it
drops down or you don't have fat in your
diet you feel great but without blood
sugar you're going to hit the wall or
the ground insulin isn't created for fat
it's created for sugar but the fat you
eat that enters your bloodstream stops
the glucose from entering cells it stays
in your bloodstream trapping the sugar
and driving up your A1C but the potato
gets the blame you know how you reverse
type 2 diabetes and drop your a 1 C and
put type 2 diabetes behind you and heal
you remove the fats and bring in lots of
potatoes Everything Changes insulin
resistance is gone I've seen it happen
thousands of times over the years this
isn't a theory it's been proven
successfully I taught a lot of doctors
how to do it for their patients let's
talk about weight and the potato will
make you fat Theory you're eating that
baked potato those french fries potato
chips cheesy potatoes mashed potatoes
you're going to gain weight put on
unwanted pounds that's what we're told
and it's all you hear or this is all you
hear carbs carbs carbs whoa too many
carbs lots of carbs but you won't hear
this fat fat look out for the fat the
butter the oil look out for the cream
the cheese look out for the milk you
won't hear that no one's going to say
whoa there's a lot of fat on those fries
whoa look at that grease everywhere that
oil look at the fat on those chips or
the fatty milk and cheese and butter and
the cheesy potatoes the mashed potatoes
like look out for that or the sour cream
on the baked potato no one blames any of
that instead they're just like carbs
carbs car carbs carbs it defies common
sense and you know what's funny it
defies reality what do you mean just
carbs these are fat bombs majority of
calories are coming from the fat and
combine the fat with the carb and then
blame the weight on the carb that's like
shooting the potato gun shooting that
Spud 300 mph across the field hitting
somebody in the head and blaming the
Spud and not the dude that shot him and
then getting off the ground dusting
yourself off and rubbing your head and
looking at the potato on the ground and
saying stupid potato all you'll ever
hear is the French fry as a carb not a
word about the oil like it doesn't exist
throw cheese on those fries and pretend
it doesn't exist it's all carbs there's
no cheese on there throw ranch or sour
cream on those fries or a potato and
pretend it doesn't exist there's no
Ranch on there there's no Ranch there's
no cheese no sour cream it just doesn't
exist we live in a pretend world when it
comes down to some of these things we
eat you're eating potato chips your
hands are smeared with grease all over
the place and you need a napkin to wipe
it you got grease all over your face
grease prints are on the glass of water
or something you're drinking
and you think it's a carb they tricked a
lot of people with that one it's the fat
that puts on the weight clogs up the
liver overburn it slows everything down
your liver can't store any more of it so
now the fat gathers all around your body
you better exercise you're told anyway
burn off those carbs but really you're
trying to burn off the fat meanwhile
you're on your treadmill and you're
thinking I got to burn off all this
sugar but it's the oil the but butter
sour cream the cheese the milk they're
the weight gainers I get it I get it you
know somebody who can eat whatever they
want all the cheese they want all the
pizza they want they don't gain any
weight not yet when their liver gets
maxed out they'll gain it down the road
everybody does as they get older weights
harder to keep off they're just lucky
they're not gaining it now people say
potatoes are a white food like processed
flour just because they have a white
inside but wait a minute to start with
an inside of a potato isn't exactly
white unlike processed white flour the
potato is a little bit of a richer color
they missed that second of all the
potato has a skin that skin determines
the color of that food just like a big
cultivated blueberry has a clear whitish
Center just like an apple has a white
pulp just like zucchini and yellow
squash has a white center zucchini is
green it's a green food a blueberry is
blue it's a blue food a red apple is red
it's a red food red potato is red too
it's a red food brown potato is a brown
food yellow potato is a yellow food a
purple potato is a purple food all these
simple mistakes gives us a window into
the possibility of what else is
everybody wrong about in the healthfield
the list is massive we haven't even
scratched the surface of all the
screw-ups the potato is a whole food not
a processed white food you take the
potato you cook it it's a whole food
it's a long sustaining complex
carbohydrate that's
satiating but before we talk about its
benefits we still got some more fish to
fry and some dice to roll if you heard
about lectins in your potato there's
something to know there's lectins in a
potato yeah just like there's lectins in
every single plant food there is that
you you eat and they're all created
equal unless someone spouts out an
opinion or theory that there's bad
lectin in a potato or tomato because
they're deciding they don't like those
and most likely because they bought into
an earlier theory that tomatoes and
potatoes cause problems cuz they're the
night shades oh wait you might be
someone that thinks well there's too
many eltin in a potato then versus
something else well if lectin were so
bad then why have so many people healed
eating potatoes and healed from
debilitating diseases somebody in the
field of Health stab the potato and use
lectins as the knife in the irony
lectins don't cause any problems they're
not the reason anyone has a symptom or a
condition on any level when you don't
know why people are sick we come up with
the most blatantly ridiculous unfounded
guesses we pull them straight out of our
behind and smear it on everyone
thousands and thousands of people healed
from debilitating diseases while eating
lectins and the lectin propagandists
pretend no one ever healed while eating
a tomato a potato or a lectin so what's
good about potato a lot let's start with
zinc it's a precious mineral that's not
in our food today a critical Trace
mineral needed to keep our immune system
strong and to fight pathogens there's
not a lot of zinc in Foods the soil
doesn't have zinc like it used to have
in the old days it's depleted so where's
the zinc when it comes to potato it's in
the skin the skin of the potato is high
in essential trace minerals it's a
protective sheath around the potato
around the pulp the trace minerals grow
into the skin the zinc helps to protect
us when we consume a potato it adds to a
protective shield our own immune system
when food science and research looks
into the nutritional value of a potato
they sample a larger portion from the
center of the potato and a smaller
portion of the skin or in many cases
remove the skin altoe discard it and
just test the skinless potato hey Frank
uh today we're testing potatoes look see
the sheet of paper it says uh you need
one potato peeler okay uh Frank you see
the potato peeler over there uh they say
remove the skin of the potato uh they
want a carbohydrate count and protein
count and fat count and to look for some
vitamins okay U just peeling the potato
here ow almost cut my finger with that
peeler um Frank what do we do with all
the Skins just throw them out meanwhile
the zinc is in the skin and it helps to
protect us zinc is an essential weapon
against viruses because viruses cause
autoimmune and much of the chronic
illness we're faced with today and the
zinc in a potato is not just bi aailable
but it's hyper absorbable which means
your immune cells absorb it quickly
instantly that matters when fighting an
infection that's a make or break it
matters if a bacteria and a wound is
going to spread quickly or not the zinc
enters cells easily because it attaches
to the glucose inside the potato the
potato has its own delivery system
meaning it's like ordering a pizza and
having it delivered to the house the
pizza place has its own delivery system
the glucose and the potato is the car
with the guy in it the zinc is the pizza
in his hand bringing it right to your
front door of your cells if you're
someone with trigeminal neuralgia jaw
pain neck pain back pain Bells paly
frozen shoulder fatigue burning skin
rashes migraines dizziness eye floaters
ringing in the years if you're someone
with fibromyalgia Lyme disease
rheumatoid arthritis multiple sclerosis
lupus pots enal syndrome endometriosis
PCOS and these are just some then you're
dealing with viruses in the herpes
family Epstein bar shingles virus hhv6
hhv7 sedom virus simplex 1 Simplex 2 and
you know what's needed to battle that Li
scene and it helps to SL slow them down
so your immune system can help defend
you and potato has Eline so let's talk
glucose sugar the carb everything that
we're all complaining about sugar it's
got carbs it's bad it's got what is that
Sugar carbohydrates that's bad stuff
well guess what potatoes possess the
right kind of it the right kind of
carbohydrate one that's received by our
intestinal tract as if it was Mother's
Milk good bacteria our intestinal tract
feed off of glucose from potatoes it
nourishes them it keeps them strong a
complex carbohydrate that grows
underground specifically potato has a
correlation to good bacteria potatoes
never see the light they're in the earth
while growing and many varieties of the
more potent good bacteria never see the
light either they grow deep within our
gut soil born microorganisms cluster
around potatoes as they grow in the
earth these soil born microorganisms
feed off of natural sugars being
released from the potato skins as they
expand during the growing process under
the Earth the potatoes sweat as they
grow they release water during droughts
and dry times these soil born
microorganisms feed off of this drink
the water they have a similarity to some
of our good bacteria that resides in our
gut it's a food they both have a
connection to the glucose and potatoes
the sugar is critical for restoring the
nervous system any neurological symptom
and condition means the nerves are
inflamed and a need to be fueled up and
restored anxiety depression ticks spasms
aches pains these are just some
neurological symptoms and conditions and
glucose and potato is restorative so
let's talk about the digestive system
from food poisoning to colitis potatoes
have brought back a lot of people from
living hell with their suffering one of
my favorite tools pieces of knowledge is
mono eating potatoes when in difficult
Health
situations I've seen just eating
potatoes for breakfast lunch and dinner
along with celery juice some lemon water
some lettu uses here and there I've seen
it bring back people from Crohn's
colitis sibo Celiac IBS ulcers acid
reflux hives gastritis gastroparesis
diarrhea cramping I've seen it recover
people from post food poisoning where
nothing else would one reason is because
potatoes are so soothing on the
digestive tract and nerves especially
dealing with colitis where there are
large pockets of inflamed tissue within
the colon which is unknowingly caused by
the shingles virus knowing these medical
me tools has helped save a lot of people
with their colitis and potatoes sue the
lining of the colon they don't aggravate
the lining it's not an aggressive food
it's a gentle food so let's talk about a
few other conditions many people get
diagnosed with sibo these days it's
bacteria in the small intestinal tract
but what kind of bacteria that's the
question right there medical communities
they don't know it's just like you got
sibo overgrowth the bacteria that's
what's happening down there but what
kind it's strep to coctus that's what
people don't know that's a dominating
bacteria inside people's guts and strep
likes to eat it likes to eat all kinds
of foods cheese eggs milk butter right
but strep doesn't like potatoes so when
you eat a potato it goes down the Chute
the tiny stringy fibers inside potato
grab on to strep bacteria and wind them
up balls them up and pulls them out of
the gut irritable bowel syndrome IBS
also caused by strepto coctus bacteria
the bacteria slowly eats away at the
colon lining and then tiny formations of
scar tissue occur potatoes are soothing
to the lining help feed the cells in the
lining wall and as it's doing that it
grabs onto bacteria it removes it out of
the colon let's talk about ulcers in the
stomach dadum small intestinal tract
colon ulcers are caused by bacteria and
viruses the canker stur virus which is a
herpes family virus creates ulcers the
lysine and potato helps to slow down and
stop the canker sore virus allowing the
ulcer to heal other ulcers are caused by
strepto octus and eoli potatoes bind on
to exposed bacteria as the potato moves
over the ulcers helping to drive the
bacteria out of the gut most varieties
of strep are antibiotic resistant or
partially immune to antibiotics but
strap and other types of bacteria cannot
become immune to what potato has to
offer have you ever had food poisoning
it hits you out of nowhere sometimes 12
to 24 hours after you've been exposed
after you've consume the food that had
bacteria in it or a mutated
microorganism or a food born toxin
Ow o oh my stomach hurts why is it like
this what did I
eat I had those nachos and I ordered
some fish oh my God I'm in so much pain
I I can't even talk I I'm nauseous it's
in the center of my gut like the pit of
my gut I got to get to the bathroom no I
need to get to the bed and lay there oh
I got to get to the bathroom we've all
been there before it's a brutal
experience sometimes even dangerous very
dangerous you have your meal hours later
you're feeling kind of sick and then it
hits you you get a little nauseous then
you get that terrible pain in your
stomach so uncomfortable could even go
straight to a point where you're just in
gnawing pain some throw up or have
diarrhea others have both could last a
day a week hard to get fluids down I
always tell people to sip coconut water
when coming out of a bat of food
poisoning but a lot of people have an
uneasy stomach for days after sometimes
a week after sometimes more than a week
sometimes months and any food tends to
not settle right or feel like it's not
digesting and pain gas bloating can
happen every day and potato on its own
is a powerful way to recover from post
food poisoning I've helped many do it
over the last 35 years sometimes it's
the only food it feels gentle enough but
satiating enough but gives you something
back so you can gain your strength
here's something to think about where's
your protein people worry about that all
the time what food you're eating where
you getting your protein every single
day potato it's not seen or viewed as a
food with protein in it meanwhile it
does have protein it's the quality of
protein that matters and it's
bioavailability the protein and potato
can be assimilated easy and broken down
easy another thing to think about is
trace minerals potatoes are packed with
them anyone that says potatoes are just
a ball of empty carbs void of nutrients
and minerals is unaware of the truth
potatoes grow underground they absorb
trace minerals potatoes are not going to
be considered as a superfood there's no
get-rich scheme with potato farming and
you can't fluff potatoes up and package
them up as a fancy new herb from the
Amazon or special ryome that has magical
powers in healing or superfood the
minute you say potato everybody's eyes
glaze over it's the ultimate food wait
no the ultimate taken for granted
healing food there's not a magical
special Majestic vibe that comes off a
potato nothing Sparkles when someone
says try some potatoes that'll help you
okay so the best way to eat potatoes to
get the best healing support from them
is steamed I know people love to bake
potatoes and fry them however you choose
to eat them keep them oilfree try not to
have them with fats don't have them with
chicken meat fish eggs other animal
products like cheese milk butter yogurt
cream or sour cream if you choose to eat
any of these Foods just don't eat potato
with them make it a potato night have it
by itself try to avoid eating coconut
oil olive oil avocado nut and Seed
Butters with potatoes but if you do
they're the best and the least
problematic of all the fats and if you
are to eat your potatoes with a fat do
it with avocado maybe a little tahini
try to keep the ratio from potato to Fat
to a minimum so you can get glucose and
healing properties to your cells for
Recovery if you don't have a health
issue then feel free to choose a plant
fat to eat with your potato but try to
keep the ratio of the fat still lower
than the potato avoid potatoes that have
a green skin or growing big Sprouts if
you need ideas on how to eat potatoes
check out all the potato recipes on the
blog at Medical medium.com or check out
the 75 healthy recipes in the book
cleanse to heal to help you move forward
with your healing you'll find recipes
like potato salad potato fries potato
soups baked potatoes hash browns potato
pizzas and so much more pot potatoes are
a legendary humble food that has no ego
when we see a potato we need to look
beyond what we already know and see far
past what we made our mind up to be
about this powerful healing Miracle food
the potato has been there for us we just
need to let it do its
job it's a let down it's no good stay
away from it you better you should it's
unfriendly ignore it steer clear avoid
it don't even think it's good for you it
will hurt you it's true that's what
you'll hear is Darkness tries to rip
something down that has only helped
others throughout their life all around
it spins the truth so everyone is
confound
times are changing they're trying to
phase the potato out of existence they
don't want it exchanging they want
healing
resistance there are people here now who
have it deep within their blood from
centuries ago and it's still in their
veins even if they don't know it allowed
them to stand up hold their head up high
swing their swords until they die you
help someone you nourished them you took
care of them you revived them you gave
them something to thrive on and then you
brought them back as The Daily Grind
pushed them hard and broke their back
and wasn't kind to them and you were
never rewarded only constantly being
thwarted who cares if you nourish their
cells P them out of living hell the
story will never be told no one cares
cares to tell and because of this future
Generations can't behold what you did
for humankind won't matter it's lost in
time so long be gone as we watch the
years go by most people forget what
happened learning from the past isn't on
their minds these days it's not accepted
and having a loss of perspective is not
respected the illuminated wants you
blind as a bad and your mind daed so
everything they do to ruin all the good
around us is forgotten because the
illuminated is rotten they want us kept
down waiting in lines in cities and
towns begging for food while being
stabbed in the arm by a mandatory needle
alarm because they want us harmed this
precious food strengthens our
intelligence helps us to connect to an
Angelic resonance brings us to to an
enlightened State away from negativeness
giving us the spiritual fortitude to
battle illuminated Darkness helping us
heal from disease no matter what we're
up against
regardless when you feed your body what
it needs it can fight for your life
allowing you to plant new seeds and heal
with
ease you can rise out of the ashes
see I believe in
you and I
know you can
[Music]
heal