welcome to the medical medium podcast
I'm Anthony
William hey everybody we're doing the
stargazing meditation there's a hidden
surprise way above the sky that will
always be there for you long before we
die to bring back and restore a part of
us that gets beaten down here on Earth
sending us on a spiritual search because
we get lost in the Lurch it's time to
find out what's behind the Stars far far
away from planet Mars you can't get
there by driving a car it would be way
too hard there's an easier way to reach
Above The Ether and heal the wounds we
receive from people that are meaner but
that's okay we can fix all the cracks
when our soul spirit and heart get
hacked the stargazing meditation has
your
back this meditation can be done during
the daytime or at night if you choose
the nighttime try to get a glimpse of
the Stars even if it's just for a moment
you do not have to see the stars in
order to do the meditation it will be
just as effective and Powerful there is
a built-in safety mechanism for your
soul so it can stay safe and never get
completely lost while being down here on
Earth your soul is here within you
inside you and if we're up against
emotional stress it can be hard on our
soul your soul is who you are it's what
lives on forever and ever as we go
through life we can experience hardship
and pain
from losses and difficult
experiences sometimes brought on by
others through betrayal and other
emotional struggles from everyday twists
and turns life challenges us with broken
trust emotional stress wrongdoing broken
promises and disappointments can make us
doubt ourselves make us wonder if we are
good enough if we deserve good things in
life we can lose ourselves and feel like
a part of us is missing the self-doubt
becomes a weight upon us in our soul and
can challenge our very being in
existence leading to anxiety
depersonalization PTSD and depression
one special way to rise from the
self-doubt and fear and heal the wounds
within our soul is to have a special
knowing that is always there for you
it's high above the Stars way way above
you it's behind the constellations just
way waiting for you to reconnect and
find yourself once again bringing back
emotional strength now let's start the
stargazing meditation find a comfortable
position you can do this meditation
lying down or if you prefer you can do
it sitting up in a relaxing State now
close your
eyes take a deep breath
in and
release Envision all the stars in the
sky above you the sky is dark but the
Stars Stand Out bright do you see
them now see yourself starting to float
upward into the air elevating higher and
higher into the sky
you're floating above the trees houses
and
buildings are you
floating you look up into the sky at the
stars and you start floating more and
more
upward clouds start rolling in high
above you
they start blocking you from seeing all
the
stars you start floating upward to the
clouds the clouds will purify you as you
enter them purify and cleanse you of
struggle broken trust betrayal hardship
and losses you start to enter the clouds
and the Mist is all around you
it's dark but you feel safe you keep
floating upward higher and higher
through the
cloud you start to surface out of the
cloud and above it you break through you
are
free look up ahead of you all the stars
are out they are bright nothing is in
your way now it's time to rest rest upon
the cloud making it your
pillow the soft puffy feeling underneath
you holding you up as you look straight
up at the
stars can you see the
stars they look brighter than ever and
they
sparkle tiny flickers and flashes of
Starlight reflect off the cloud around
you do you see the flickers of light
Now look up at the
stars what you see is the first layer of
stars they are the stars closest to
you can you see the stars
above behind those stars are more layers
upon layers of
stars other solar systems and Galaxy
GES Stars upon Stars the stars all know
you they know who you are they know your
soul far up Behind These stars is a
sanctuary a place where part of your
soul stays protected and safe the
essence of your soul the very place your
soul has come from this essence of you
you your soul is there so that you never
lose yourself it's there so you can
connect to it and gain Soul strength
this connection protects you from
emotional struggles broken relationships
broken trust let Downs losses and
emotional stress from harming your soul
completely while down here on Earth this
Bond can never be broken do you feel
this Bond that's behind the Stars
nothing can break this bond between your
soul and your Soul's Essence this is the
other side of your soul it's your home
now it's time to see your soul the
essence it's a mirror image of what your
soul looks like now do you know what
your soul looks
like it's coming towards
you and will show
itself you faintly see it in the
distance it's coming from deep within
the
Stars you will see a
visual it's about to show itself
completely
what does it look
like does it look like you is it
here do you see
it now take a deep breath
in and
release you're still on the cloud
loud you have made a direct connection
to the essence of your soul in the
sanctuary above way beyond the
stars take another look at the stars
before you head
back you're starting to sink through the
cloud it becomes
dark the Mist is around you as you sink
through the
cloud as you're falling through the
Cloud you feel safe and
warm it feels good to float through a
cloud you now exit the
cloud you're above the trees Fields
buildings and
houses and you're heading
back
you're getting closer and
closer
1 you're
back the connection has been made
now take a deep breath
in and
release now take another deep breath
release when you're ready you can open
your
eyes
you have now completed the stargazing
meditation you have reunited with the
essence of your soul a part of your soul
that is always there for you and is safe
and protected you don't have to search
for that sense of wholeness you're
looking for anymore you have found your
way home and no one can take this away
from you the special connection to
reignite a part of yourself has been
there for you so that you can strengthen
and reclaim your soul and heal wounds
that make us lose ourselves or feel as
if we lost a part of who we are nothing
can interfere with this powerful reunion
the search to find yourself has been
established you are home your soul has a
telepathic connection to the part of
your soul that sits beyond the stars
spend as much time as you like on this
meditation the more you stargaze and
complete this exercise the more you
rejuvenate your soul and bring the
sanctuary that's behind the stars back
to
you you can rise out of the
ashes see I believe in you
and I
know you can
[Music]
heal