how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William hey everybody we're talking
about modern-day vampirism now before
you jump into any conclusions we're not
talking about people with fangs in Black
capes leaving two bite marks on your
neck
that would be scary it's way worse than
that because it's real and it's
happening to you and it defies all
sensibility of the medical system what I
have to tell you is not an old folklore
story about
Transylvania instead it's about your
life your family your loved ones your
safety and life
preservation and if you have a chronic
illness it's make or break do or die
or get off the pot we're talking
about blood draw your blood tests I'm
not against getting your blood tested
it's important it can be a window into
important information about your overall
health but blood testing is still
Antiquated it's running on Old stats and
averages of people that have long since
been gone during a time period in
history when so much was so much
different than what it is today normal
standards in today's blood profile comes
from long ago past and hasn't been
updated blood testing is not a
definitive accurate 100% clear method of
providing somebody with answers to why
they're chronically ill but it's still
important lifesaving and good doctors
are learning to read between the lines
when they're drawing blood and see
subtle differences that can be very
helpful through those blood tests with
that said we have a bigger problem the
medical system has gone unchecked no
one's questioned it and it's one of the
biggest scams of our modern day Health
System it's modernday blood leing the
draining of our blood on a level that's
unprecedented and unneeded every time
you get a blood test and you see those
pretty little tues tubes fill up with
red blood right before your eyes there's
a few things that are terribly wrong
first thing is they're going to throw
all that beautiful blood away in the
garbage almost all of it or preserve it
not for you but for who knows second of
all the blood you see in those tubes has
your hard-earned
systematically produced body's precious
resource
sacred protection and health Shield your
immune cells your white count your
killer cells your white blood cells they
go into the tubes see you later
alligator bye-bye Miss American Pie
drove my Chevy to the levy and the levy
went dry you lost your immune system it
went out the window not all your immune
system left your body and went out the
window but depending on how much blood
was drawn a large part of the most
important part of your immune system the
weight count that patrols your
bloodstream has left the house as you're
walking away from your doctor's
appointment less full and more
empty sometimes you're told to drink a
little apple juice have a cookie you'll
build your blood back quick they say if
they say anything at all that's reckless
a reckless statement and a ridiculous
one if we're all about science specifics
details truth facts then this is the
most blatant negligent careless process
we have to date what do you mean build
back your blood quickly the variables
range on all levels how much blood was
drawn how weak is your immune system to
begin with how chronically ill are you
what kind of symptoms do you live with
what kind of Demands stress and load is
on your plate or your life what's your
diet like are you a man or are you a
woman and when was the last time you had
a blood draw it's not as simple as
you'll be fine eat enough food and
you'll level out you're lucky if the
even give you a tip to eat the system
will never get its thirst quenched they
will bleed you to death steal your blood
shorten your life by weakening your
reserves and never ever ever be held
accountable for it you might hold them
accountable after you hear what you're
about to hear you wake up with your
first symptoms you start Doctor shopping
like so many do and they take your your
blood no one knows why you're really
sick it's mostly low-grade viral
infections and toxic heavy metals like
I've always said causing your future
diagnoses you're autoimmune at your
doctor's office when they take your
blood how much blood are they drawing is
it four vials five vials s 10 14 18 24
28 more let's say they take five vials
those are five full vials in that blood
is your immune system and your immune
system took time to build it's keeping
you from getting sicker it's patrolling
your body looking for Invaders looking
for pathogens and even toxins and doing
their job gobbling them up when they see
them those toxins and Invaders are
mostly why you're at the doctor's office
Hashimoto's
fibromyalgia ra multiple sclerosis lupus
eczema psoriasis acne rosacea Vitiligo
dizziness tingles and numbness like so
many have fatigue especially that
neurological fatigue people get where
they just can't even walk and they don't
even feel like they're living their life
brain fog depression anxiety loss of
libido body pain neck pain back pain
hives asthma heart palpitations cold
sores TMJ trigeminal neuralgia back pain
migraines colitis digestive problems IBS
Crohn's
bloating caused by all these Invaders
and toxins that are inside our blood so
as they draw blood they're taking away
your offense and defense at the same
time that would probably be somewhat
okay acceptable if they didn't almost
throw all of your blood away but they do
they take a few drops at best a thimble
and toss the rest out to toss it
somewhere you go home and it takes weeks
even months to get that CBC that
complete blood count back to normal
white blood cells red blood cells
platelets but most importantly that
white blood count decide
the condition you are going to be in
with your symptoms and conditions no
one's aware or monitoring if they should
be careful with how much blood they draw
from you at any given time you could be
someone with a compromised immune system
meaning your white blood cells are
weakened low in numbers or on the edge
so your doctor is supposed to be
cautious keep your vials two or three
max if sensitive and maybe for max if
you're stronger and really it should be
half vials going to talk more about that
later but your doctor they're not taught
by the industry your doctor's boss the
industry that your immune system gets
taken out of your body with your blood
goes unused and is destroyed thrown out
thrown away or Worse stored somewhere
you may someone that doesn't build their
immune system back quicker than others
so instead of it taking four to 6 weeks
just to get your white blood cells
stabilized it takes four months and your
red blood cells instead of 3 months 6
months during this course of time your
symptoms can worsen it prompts you to
call the doctor again he's concerned so
he draws more blood this time he may
draw five to 10 vials wants to look for
additional problems uncover the mystery
you go home two weeks later your
symptoms persist and it's even worse
your doctor recommends a specialist your
specialist he doesn't care about the
blood work you had in the past most of
the time they never do he or she wants
to order their own blood work they may
want another five vials but they can
also maybe want another 14 vials or more
while they're busy looking at all your
numbers metabolic panel thyroid panel
your liver enzymes you're struggling now
you're in a state of being where you say
to yourself or to your spouse or
boyfriend or girlfriend or friend or
loved one I'm sick really sick the
specialist he wants you to come back and
do it all over again in six weeks
another round of blood you're now just a
giant blood bag a feeder for the system
the system that's broken your specialist
says let's check for Lyme disease we
need another 7 to 14 vials they won't
tell you you need another 7 to 14 vials
it's just that when they stick you and
they're putting another tube in taking a
tube out put another tube in taking a
tube out wait a minute where's this
going put another tube in taking a tube
out wait that's four put another tube in
was 5 6 7 it's 10 okay I'm still sitting
here 11 12 oh my God 13 14 and it's 7 to
14 miles goes quick 3 weeks after you
just had your last blood draw your
symptoms are worse than ever you can't
get ahead of yourself and you're caught
in a Perpetual state of survival you're
not thriving because you're kept from
thriving you see yes you were sick to
start with but you became sicker and no
one's checking the system looking out
for you because they take one of the
most god-given things you got inside
your body that stops you from getting
sicker your immune system they take it
and they're throwing it out out this all
too often happens to a lot of people
some people this just takes them
completely down bedridden for years some
over time it just ends their life
earlier they were blood L it to death
blood let it and the sicker you get they
draw more and more blood you get sicker
they take more blood 6 months later
you're sicker they take more blood
and they don't stop till you drop say
you're someone who's not sick and you
get your routine blood tests you get
five to seven vials every 6 months you
might be someone that's lucky you don't
have an Epstein bar shingles virus
simplex cega virus hhv6
hhv7 two or three strains of
streptococus bacteria that's about to
increase in numbers and give you your
first symptoms but the blood draw will
get you there quicker which means if
your viruses and bacteria were
designated to cause a problem when you
are 55 years old weight gain more acne
more problems fatigue the blood draws
combined with not the best food choices
and other factors your immune system
might get low at certain times in your
life it's going to happen when you're 35
not 55 your routine blood draw will
knock you slowly down as the years go by
and get you a symptom or a condition
sooner than it would have been and when
it does you'll be required to give more
blood and end up in the vampires Lair
now you're in everyone who gets a blood
draw walks around with a weakened immune
system and now you're exposed to the bad
flu covid mono strep staff Mera eoli
food poisoning shingles or anything else
that comes your way no one says stay out
of trouble Mrs Ferguson okay see you
later thank you for coming for your
blood draw stay out of trouble stay out
of Harm's Way just you know be a little
careful all right we just removed your
entire immune system practically stay
safe no one says that if you're lucky
after a large blood draw they may say
have a piece of candy a lollipop some
orange juice or apple juice or a cookie
and don't worry see you
later it's not anyone's fault at the
bottom this is a deception from the top
it's not the FLOTUS it's not the nurses
it's bigger than everyone it's big
Pharma and the handful of people at the
top with a mission to drain your blood
you don't believe me you know then why
else are they doing it because they made
a simple mistake or something someone
didn't get a memo nothing was fixed no
one thought about it if it's not on
purpose then it shows you that stupidity
controls the top of the medical system
you should bite your tongue next time
you think science knows everything and
has your back then it's Reckless Twisted
horrifying and downright demonic harsh
words you have no idea how many people
have died from getting blood testing
while living with chronic illness died
early in their life so let's talk about
cancer whether you believe in the truth
that cancer is caused by viruses and
toxins or you just think cancer is
genetic you still need your immune
system to keep your cancer in check your
white count controls your cancer your
white count gobbles up and destroys
cancer cells and most importantly
gobbles up the viruses that create
cancer cells you get diagnosed with
cancer most likely you've already had
symptoms and conditions you've been sick
already and you've had enough blood
draws previously knocking your immune
system down prior to your cancer
diagnosis or your blood draws started
right with your cancer diagnosis either
way they step up your blood draws you go
into rapid routine blood testing this
puts a constant drain on your immune
system system the one thing keeping you
from worsening think the cancer doctor
will mention anything no take blood at
will take no hostages and ignore any
Common Sense sensibility any reason or
reasoning your white count lives inside
of you in your blood for the most part
it's tragic when it has to leave its
home un
necessarily the sicker you get as a
cancer patient the more blood they take
the sicker you get the more blood they
take they drain you dry it's
devastating look if you have the
opportunity in the truth you have to use
that to keep people safe healthy and
alive I can see it now a lot of unhappy
doctors Specialists blood Labs what an
inconvenience this next bomb is as it
leaves the medical medium Cannon and
causes a crater in the broken health
system when the people find out they've
been screwed over they know they've been
screwed over big time see blood letting
never went away let's go back in time a
little bit 1600s 1700s 1800s you got
sick they cut your arm you drain into a
pan if you didn't recover from whatever
you were sick with they cut your arm
again and drain it into a pan you still
haven't recovered you're not one of the
lucky ones they cut your arm again drain
it in a pan and now you're
finished why is this much different than
today because it's not it's conventional
medicine's finest f up that of course
alternative medicine adopted as well CU
alternative medicine always adopts all
the conventional medicine fups they
don't know what's wrong with you with
chronic illness so they draw your blood
draw your blood keep drawing your blood
drawing your blood again draw it again
oh need more Blood let's draw it more
and more hey by the way you guys you got
to get more blood drawn and then hey we
need your blood get back in here got to
draw some more blood and throw it all
away you get sicker they draw more blood
and throw it away they don't drain it in
a pan but still you get sicker a
specialist will draw 7 to 28 vials and
throw it away you got a better chance of
living through it than a 100 years ago
than 200 300 400 years ago because we
have resources to help stabilize us at
our fingertips right we got still some
good medical technology I won't say we
don't we really do and that's the
difference back then they just laid in a
bed blood Le with no water for days
terrible environmental conditions
shortages on food no proper blankets no
IVs to support their organs while their
blood was being removed no oxygen tanks
but it's still all the same the handful
of people at the top of the Medical
Science and the medical industry carried
blood leing all the way over to the
heads of the medical industry now it's
still the same but it's done differently
you might be someone thinking no way I
get my blood work I'm fine yeah I got a
little acne my doctor checks my hormones
I'm doing good after my blood work this
is not me or maybe you're someone that
gets your thyroid checked after 6 to8
weeks or every 6 to8 weeks or every 3
months you're doing okay maybe you're
someone diagnosed with sibo got a little
eczema your routine blood draws seem
normal maybe you're someone with with
Celiac everything seems to be up to par
your symptoms or conditions come and go
you get your blood work everything seems
okay or maybe you're someone your
symptoms are on an even kill you're
eating better taking supplements and all
this seems a little farfetched but
little do you know you're still getting
a hunk of your immune system removed and
you have a lot lot of years ahead of you
for things to go wrong because of it it
happens when you least expect it at the
worst moments in life too you're
coasting along everything's going okay
you're used to your symptoms here and
there but then comes that one blood draw
that pushes you too far and knocks you
on your ass you're dysfunctional
fatigued brain fogged can't think right
a little dizzy and now you think it's
something in your diet wait AE minut
it's something I'm doing that's what
it's got to be my diet maybe it's this
thing I took uh maybe it's something
else you're checking your supplements
but you have no clue it was your last
big blood draw even if it was weeks ago
or even months ago it was the blood draw
that pushed you over the edge it was the
straw that broke the camel's back before
that you had a strong Constitution you
weren't that sick you might be still
young you're you're in your 20s and it
sneaks up behind you and bites you on
the ankle like a snake and you're up 10
notches with your symptoms and you're
down 10 notches with your health and the
confusion of why you're getting worse
only gets worse and now it's the
guessing games time the real guessing
games not the mini guessing games the
major big guessing games more than ever
before and once you burned out your most
recent doctor or he or she Burns you out
it's off to another doctor and more
fresh blood work and suggestions such as
did you try apple cider vinegar that
might help are you doing your charcoal
um yeah no keto that could be a good
direction to go uh paleo how's that
working for you is that a good way to go
are you getting your healthy fats CU
your brain needs all that fat are you
staying away from sugar and carbs are
you getting your fermented foods in are
you doing your probiotic iotics the
confusion goes on and it Carries On and
On you become fresh meat fresh meat
walking into that doctor specialist
office or the meat market you're a fresh
feeder happens to everybody with blood
draws over time there's a trend out
there not backed by any science just a
theory and the theory is becoming the
mantra for all alternative doctors and
practitioners it's your immune system is
all in your gut
heard that one yet that's a head
scratcher for me how can anybody trust
this since all practitioners and doctors
blood let everybody to begin with
they're wrong about the most important
aspects of medicine there is possible
the one they rely on the most for
answers your precious blood work and
blood supply but now they're right about
this your gut all your immune systems
working in your gut your entire immune
system is in your gut uh most of your
immune system is is in your gut do you
know where that came from it came from
probiotic and gut health companies
that's who came up with that theory uh
bias information anyone I hate to break
it to them but the majority of your
immune system is in your
bloodstream it's in your bloodstream to
protect your brain and your heart it's
in your bloodstream to try to stop
pathogens from going to your brain and
causing strokes and brain inflammation
it's in your blood stream to try to stop
pathogens from getting to your heart and
causing a blood clot or inflammation of
the ventricles it's in your bloodstream
to stop sepsis or blood poisoning or an
infection to your heart valve it's not
in your gut yes some of your immune
system is but the majority is in your
bloodstream your brain and heart are
Target number one for the enemy and both
are VIP to your immune system your heart
your brain are the VIPs to your immune
system but that's how misinformation
Trends are it's all in your gut immune
systems all in your gut just like they
said it's all in your head and then also
caffeine is good for you they say that
too it's good for pregnant women that's
what they say
now really or plunging in ice is good
for the body puts you in shock kills
your adrenals gives you mild hypothermia
but no it's good for your body uh how
about this when your brain lives on fat
oh really uh is that why they tell you
to eat sugar drink apple juice after you
donated
blood because someone at the top knows
if they don't give you sugar after they
theft at your blood you ain't walking
out of that blood donor's clinic or
doctor's office they don't say hey um
you just donated a pint your blood
here's a cup of coconut oil or here's a
cup of olive oil that's because your
brain is hungry it's hungry for sugar if
it goes without glucose for more than 5
minutes it starts to die but yet the
trend is to tell you your brain runs on
fat which contradicts what they tell you
after you've given blood who's right
who's wrong well next time you donate a
pint of blood or get a big blood draw
drink a cup of oil or eat a few
tablespoons of peanut butter and see if
you hit the sidewalk face down walking
out of there and if you're compromised
sensitive or sick with symptoms you'll
hit the sidewalk faster and harder but I
wouldn't do it because you need more
glucose for stabilization after having a
good amount of glucose removed from your
blood you remove the glucose you better
be putting some back in your sugar your
blood sugar as they're taking too much
blood from you they also took your
glucose not just your immune system when
you got your blood drawn the glucose
that keeps your brain alive which leads
to the next problem they not only drain
you of your immune system but they drain
you of your glucose reserves which for
the chronically ill means everything
neurological problems and symptoms that
The Chronic Leo have do worsen with the
loss of glucose and they take that away
from you too your blood sugar there's a
reason they measure blood sugar not
blood fat you can live without fat you
can't live without sugar the trendy
Health gurus think it's fat
that's real smart but hey they think all
your blood draws blood work blood tests
and how it's done is great normal F to
do until they hear this podcast and then
maybe start copycatting but they also
think your immune system's all in your
gut and many gurus think you're sick
because you haven't trained your neurop
Pathways to manifest your sickness to go
away because it's all in your head yeah
I love that one you know as if if your
mind is going to reverse the trauma the
physical trauma that's caused by
constantly getting your blood drawn yeah
okay okay every time they do a blood
draw your white count and red count go
out the door and whatever's making you
sick stays inside pathogens like viruses
such as Epstein bar the very bug behind
Hashimoto thyroiditis Lyme disease
multiple sclerosis lupus eczema Celiac
PCOS fibroids endometriosis stays in
your body because these Critters are not
in your bloodstream for the most part
that's why it's nearly impossible with
the blood testing they have now to find
active Epstein bar it's not a fullblown
infection in your bloodstream they're in
your organs glands and tissue where they
can survive your immune system and hide
and when your immune system is strong a
white blood blood cell sees an Epstein
bar virus Peaks its ugly head out of an
organ your killer cell Stomps on it and
destroys it but after a blood draw a lot
of your killer cells went bye-bye and
that Epstein bar Peaks its head out and
says I'm in the clear time to spread you
would think if your immune system's
being drawn out with your blood that
your pathogens would be drawn out and go
with it but they don't your blood cells
white count killer cells guard your
brain and heart making sure that Epstein
bar or any other pathogen doesn't get a
tollfree ride through your blood Highway
making a pit stop to another organ I
can't tell you how many times I
witnessed so many people get fullblown
mono after a blood draw because an
important portion of the immune system
that's inside their bloodstream has been
removed people get the flu after a blood
draw or any other bug going around
you're more susceptible or they get more
symptoms of what they're already
battling because pathogens travel when
they're not being controlled that's why
the immune system in your bloodstream is
so important but up until medical medium
information no one knew pathogens caused
any chronic illness just like they don't
know about the blood draw problem
Chinese medicine was unaware atic
medicine didn't know science and
research didn't know the vegans didn't
know the paleos didn't know Western
alternative medicine didn't know now
Doctors medical research and science are
using medical medium information that
Epstein bar is responsible or even
linked to a host of diseases after it
was already published but oh yeah
where's your science well science has
taken medical medium information
plagiarizing it and using it now leads
me to another critical point anyone
who's sick with any neurological symptom
brain fog depression anxiety bipolar
aches and pains Twitches spasms ticks
jerks chronic fatigue sleep apnea asthma
migraines jaw pain tingles and numbness
vertigo ttis burning skin weakness of
the limbs tightness of the chest needs
needs needs electrolytes and a large
amount of your electrolytes are in your
blood as it leaves your body during a
blood draw we get in trouble and then
your brain your neurons and your
neurotransmitters get hit hard and lose
those critically needed Trace mineral
salts and electrolytes this isn't even
considered these blood draws the petus
of deep-seated electrolyte Reserves no
one's checking that no one's caring no
one's talking about it no one even knows
your neurological symptoms worsen but
that won't take the blame the last blood
draw you call your doctor you're feeling
worse weeks after your blood draw and he
or she's going to need another blood
draw and not even realize that you're in
a glucose electrolyte and immune system
deprivation from your last blood draw
you know what the say bad thing is blood
draws they Spike our adrenals too every
time the needle goes in your arm ow or
anywhere else in the body your adrenals
release fight or flight
epinephrine your adrenals react to a
foreign Invader in this case the needle
that adrenaline can power you through
the blood test though it's a needle High
keep in mind blood draws take from us
it's not like an intravenous vitamin or
saline bag that offers nourishment to
counterbalance the adrenals during their
fight or flight response this adrenaline
response to the needle alone takes time
to recover for people who are weakened
in sick that calls for any needles or
treatments with needles needles can also
make you high from the adrenaline that's
released the medical industry secretly
relies on you getting this high from the
pin prick it Band-Aids the moment the
damage being done with too much blood
being drawn some people feel a temporary
lift like a temporary high as a needle
leaves the arm before they feel worse
later as the adrenaline surge wears off
check this out if someone gets an injury
and they get cut and they bleed two
three or four vials of blood worth
which is roughly around 40 m of blood F4
vials with 10ml vials right they feel it
they're traumatized can you imagine
getting a blood draw of 14 vials even
seven or 10 vials full vials or more
which leads us to the next part
hemorrhagic shock this is an under
studied area and even if it was a
heavily studied area it doesn't mean it
would be solid understood Ironclad it
could still end up as bad as cheap tin
foil research and science is known for
dedicating its resources to areas of
medicine and failing miserably it's why
they don't have any real answers for
chronic illness except for oh yeah I
forgot it's your genes it's all your
genes that's the answer for everything
now it's your jeans what a way out blame
the person don't blame science and
research CH it's your fault when it
comes to blood loss they believe 750 mL
of blood equates to a class one
hemorrhagic shock but for what body
weight I'm trying to figure that one out
um what condition someone has and what
body weight it's a heads scratcher again
it's not
studied what if you're 100 lb 750 ml
could be extreme ragic shock to a person
what if you're a 200 lb male and not 130
lb woman what if you're sick chronically
ill and 90 lbs like so many people who
get their blood constantly drawn are no
one in science and research are studying
the details or seeing the reality and
possibility of what kind of a effect
this could have on sensitive people
hemorrhagic shock is just a loss of
blood which means less oxygen and sugar
to the brain glucose but it means more
than that it means subtle but definite
shocks to other organs and when you lose
your immune cells to a blood draw what
about shock to your bones bone marrow
has to go into rapid production and deep
reserves are lost uh see you later Mrs
Fergenson thanks for giving giving us
all your blood today um hey look out
your bones are going to have to go into
a major workout there they're going to
have to develop a whole bunch of immune
cells fast as heck and uh you better
rest because your bones are freaking out
right now and when you're sick it's a
lot to ask for on your body your immune
systems already up against environmental
toxins pharmaceutical toxins toxic heavy
metals perfumes colon scented candles
air fresheners those are immune system
Busters smile car exhaust
Chemtrails coming out of the sky you're
breathing in when you go outside
pesticides herbicides fungicides
cleaning supplies detergents Cosmetics
fire retardant coming out of couches and
beds for Malahide leaking out of walls
mold dust radiation everywhere gasoline
petrochemicals Plastics and the biggest
one pathogens so it's a big Demand right
to call upon the bones in your body to
go into Mass production of immune cells
and to drain your spleen reserves of
stored white count your bank your white
blood count Bank you'll get told it's no
big deal no big deal you got plenty of
blood and your body will replenish it
the next day there's no definitive scale
that determines hemorrhagic shock
there's no guarantee there's no
guarantee it's perfect sloppy textbook
jargon from the science department once
again sloppy means careless understudied
never considered it basically boils down
to a phrase it's not enough blood to
kill you so who cares so you should be
good chalk it up we never tested their
theory on people to prove what level of
blood missing kills you we never did the
Fine Line testing but I think something
happened like 800 years ago someone
signed up for the experiment they they
walked into somebody
office they cut him bled him to death
and they calculated how much blood it
was that's a long time ago what about
the details we just assume that the
people who have led to death lost around
40% which is roughly half gallon of
blood well which is two quarts which is
roughly 2,000 milliliters no variables
no details no feline
definitions pregnant or not pregnant man
or woman thin or overweight healthy or
sick total guess workor on hemorrhagic
shock and how much blood it takes to die
also lacking all information and details
on what a healthy person versus someone
who is struggling with a health
condition of any kind with all the
science and research and technology and
factchecking and experts it's just a
shot in the dark a dart thrown at a barn
guess work the blood draw world is an
empty void of solid facts and data and
evidence and studies dead empty it's a
classic example of a broken system and
people lining up like paddle and sheeple
without any reason to question it uh uh
how much blood do you need um those
tubes are filling up pretty quick I'm
not supposed to question it right no
don't question it ever you guys know
what you're doing you know uh I had an
uncle that knew how much antifreeze it
took to take out of a radiator before
the car overheated I figured you guys
got to know way more than that and how
much blood it takes without hurting me
in any way uh what' you say come back
next month okay we'll do it all again
all right oh I'm done oh thanks oh I
just had a dizzy spell
the abusive nature of blood draw and its
unnecessary consequences is a prime
example of failure and even the best
doctors and health experts walk around
with a blood stain blindfold on let's
talk about the Fine Line before you draw
blood are you a female or a male women
have a constant revolving immune system
because they have the responsibility of
childbearing continuing human life here
here on Earth women's immune systems
drop in the rest of their body when
they're having their menstrual cycle 80%
of their body's immune system go to the
reproductive system to protect it during
its shedding cycle 40% of a woman's
immune system goes to
ovulation 50% of their immune system
goes to pregnancy in over 90% of their
immune system during childbirth it's why
women get symptoms or more symptoms
around these timelines it's why more
women are sick with chronic illness than
men men's immune systems are steady they
have this Advantage when it comes to
health a man can burn their immune
system to the ground yeah and destroy it
many do but it's a steady burn as it
crashes and goes to the ground if a man
and a woman get blood drawn for the same
problem on the same day the 220 PB male
will get the same amount of blood drawn
as the 120 lb woman if it's seven vials
or 14 vials they both get the same same
as if they both donated blood they both
get roughly 473 Millers or one pite
drawn regardless of their differences
that's a huge problem an embarrassment
for the medical system for research in
science it's humiliating for medical
research in science and people are being
trained to believe medical research and
science can do no wrong and that it's
above God the light the universe
whatever you believe in it's a cult at
this point it's become a cult instead of
what it should be or once was a work in
progress that has left a trail of
mistakes but perseveres forward let's
talk about your immune system your
immune system fights for you every day
it's gobbling up mold spores poisons
that float in the air other air
contaminants or pathogens like the flu
when a toxic mold Spore enters your
bloodstream a white blood cell has to
trap it and consume it gobble gobble it
lessens the lifespan of that immune cell
it weakens it let's talk about if you're
eating out at a restaurant everybody
loves to eat out in restaurants right
it's fun get out enjoy the night or
maybe a lunch out there's contaminants
in the food that you're eating you're
eating a sandwich from a restaurant
breathing in perfume cologne aftershaves
hair products scented body lotions and
oils air fresheners and scented candles
pesticides used for cockroaches and ants
in the kitchen conventional floor
cleaner table cleaner your plate has a
little leftover bleach on it from the
kitchen the waiter was just counting
money before he or she brought over your
plate the lettuce on your sandwich has a
little eoli on it from some raw meat in
the refrigerator that was sitting next
to it the vinegar in your dressing
that's a toxin all on its own coupled
with some sweat drops that contained
some staff or strep flew off the chef's
head along with a little dander filled
with liver toxins that you can't see on
your slices of bread or your sandwich
kitchen helpers in the back unpacking
greasy boxes off the delivery truck and
changing out the ice containers touching
the ice and their unwashed hands we're
touching everything in the kitchen
including needing a bathroom stop in
between it all loading boxes and then
having to use the bathroom yeah did they
wash your hands that good nobody knows
they weren't in there with them any
Airborne pathogen such as the flu that
you might breathe in from everybody else
being around in the restaurant your
immune cells they're being poisoned
poisoned fast because they have to
gobble up as much of these chemicals
contaminants and pathogens as they can
in a short amount of time to protect you
while you feel all good in the
restaurant feeling okay eating your
sandwich all is fine all is well an
immune cell can get filled up quick
filled up fast and it slows down
sometimes at a stand still it sacrifices
its life for you it gets overloaded your
white blood cells the Warriors got their
swords out they're swinging their swords
they're slaying dragons for you they're
engulfing multiple toxins and even
pathogens at any given moment when a
white blood cell is overwhelmed and
losing a battle two or three others come
to its rescue they got its back there's
communication between white blood cells
just like dolphins in the ocean which is
not even partly understood by research
and science but just like a boat can
instantly wipe out about half a dozen
dolphins swimming in the water a school
of white blood cells can get trashed and
thrashed hit hard injured and weakened
in A Storm of toxins and pathogens or a
larger School white blood cells can
disappear within minutes as you're
getting your blood drawn immune cells
are soldiers they're not indestructible
they can burn out we already have to
deal with that but the health system
trains us to think our blood is
disposable not really important seven
vials 10 mlit hey 70 ml here out the
door no problem 3 months later another
seven vials again out the door 3 months
later another seven vials again out the
door disposable in 6 months 140 MERS or
more disposable and I'm not even talking
about a 14 vile blood draw 24 vile blood
draw 30 vile blood draw
even more than that 48 times a year when
you're sick or more out the door how
many schools of immune cells clusters of
immune cells have been removed that's
like schools of
dolphins swimming in the Bermuda
Triangle and just
disappear thrown away without the
understanding of what it takes for your
body to reproduce them or what it takes
for your body to keep everything in
check that we just talked about and what
about when you get your blood drawn
who's keeping track of what's happening
in your life at the time you're getting
your blood drawn did the doctor's office
ask if you're under any stress where you
might need your immune system really
strong is a doctor's office asking you
if you got enough sleep the night before
your blood was drawn are they asking you
how much caffeine you consume coffee
matcha tea green tea tea black tea
energy drinks caffeine pills including
caffeine Pharmaceuticals how much
chocolate you do because chocolate
contains caffeine too because caffeine
breaks down the immune system every day
weakens it because it's defending itself
against your adrenal and highs and lows
like when you down your caffeine and
chocolate and it ignites your adrenals
to the overload point and your heart
rate increases as adrenaline floods your
system adrenaline is so toxic it wears
down your immune system white blood
cells can get torched by epinephrine
which means they can have a short
lifespan or shorter lifespan which means
your bones have to produce more immune
cells which means your doctor should be
drawing less blood from you during your
blood test to account for the stress
your immune system is under from the
caffeine alone are you a woman about to
go into your menstrual cycle or
ovulation where your immune system is
about to reduce dramatically in your
bloodstream and at the same time you're
eating half a bar of chocolate and three
cups of coffee a day and in this case
the doctor's office should want to know
to account for the amount of VI they're
about to draw but they don't they're not
asking about anything are you going
through a divorce a breakup a tough time
that can have an effect on your immune
system which leads me to another area
that's important pregnancy when 50% of
the woman's immune system is protecting
and monitoring the baby leaving her with
only half of her immune system for the
rest of her body so when a pregnant
woman gets a blood draw she's losing
another percentage of her white count
her immune cells which could be a big
trigger into postpartum illness of any
kind and even health issues while
pregnant and most importantly that blood
draw could compromise the baby instead
you'll hear pregnant women have more
blood and they should come in regularly
for routine blood tests while pregnant
doesn't matter how much blood we take
from them they'll throw away almost all
the blood with the mommy's immune system
in it which is needed to protect the
baby with no consideration of how her
immune system is juggling this depletion
at some point the body has to rob Peter
to pay Paul especially when it comes
down to protecting the baby and then
there's something else very important to
consider new relationships sharing
microorganisms and pathogens from people
we're living with newer old friendships
finding new partners in our life to
share a life with we all have our own
Petri dishes built inside of us and our
immune system has to adjust to normal
circumstances in life with us spending
time or being around others you may need
your immune system at its best and
strongest when you're falling in love or
moving in with someone to share the rent
and sharing bathrooms and kitchens or
immune systems adjust to these new
interactions with others as bacteria and
viruses and fungi cross-contaminate from
person to person it's normal but blood
drawn at the wrong time can happen and
the doctors they're not inquiring to
determine how many is safest in that
moment in your life to draw weakening
the immune system when the immune system
is already being weakened by protecting
you and keeping you balanced from new
exposures but details don't matter to
the alternative and conventional system
when it comes to drawing blood they
don't get to know the people good enough
before they Vamp them Vamp them steal
their blood throw almost all of it away
or sell it on the black market to
experimental
Labs we act like getting our blood drawn
is another errand during the day it's
just another errand let's see um I got
to go to the store I got to get a facial
afterwards um I got to pick up the kids
from school I got to stop and get 14
vials of blood
drawn um I got to get some takeout for
dinner it's just another errand for many
let's talk about donating blood they
take way too much blood in one donation
471 to 473 milliters one pint I'm not
against donating blood we are always in
need of it it's a lifesaving tool a
resource for the people who need blood
transfusions life-saving surgeries from
accidents with that said it's still a
bloody mess no matter who you are when
you don't donate that much blood you go
into Uncharted Territory there should be
parameters and critical guidelines when
donating blood to protect the person
giving the blood and figuring out how
much blood is safe for them to give any
amount of blood is going to compromise
them but the goal should be about
compromising the least possible over a
dozen variables should be set in place
are you under stress are you sleeping
are you male or female what's your
height what's your weight do you plan on
getting pregnant in the next 3 to six
months are you in a new relationship or
did you move in with someone new do you
use or been exposed to colog perfumes
sended candles air fresheners hair
products sended lotions aftershave
chemical cleaning supplies have you been
to the dentist recently a female are you
in ovulation or close to menstration do
you have any symptoms did you have
symptoms ever in your life do people
rely on you do loved ones rely on you
are you driving the next couple of days
are you hydrated are you jacked up on
caffeine or chocolate what's your diet
like why are you donating blood this is
not even exhausted list in order to
donate blood they should not make a
standard a pint they should take a half
pint at a time for a male who's healthy
and strong and less than a half pint for
a woman depending on many variables
height weight and everything we
discussed so far because Women's Health
and Men's Health is not the same far
from it care should be taken to protect
yourself from exposures after a blood
donation or a blood draw and important
steps should be taken before and after
to build the blood and Quicken immune
cell production without robbing Peter to
pay Paul you're still going to have to
take from Peter and you're still going
to have to pay Paul but the goal is to
not leave Peter homeless and you still
want Paul to get enough look we need
blood donations but we also have to look
out for the people who are donating if
we're giving them a pint of blood let's
make sure we're strong and healthy and
we take care of ourselves before and
after donating more on that later let's
talk about blood draws now if you're a
woman who's healthy no symptoms and
strong and above 150 lbs the maximum
amount of vials they should recommend
should be four whole vials no bigger
than 10 mlit each try to ask for half
vials and smaller tubes if possible
which becomes two whole vials if you're
healthy and strong under the weight of
150 lbs it should be three whole vials
try to ask for half vials not whole
vials if you are compromised in any way
with symptoms or condition also
considering the concerns I talked about
earlier maximum ask for two full vials
best if you do half vials with those two
full vials make sure it's half vials for
those two which will equal one full vial
if your health is really compromised and
you're under 100 lb maximum one full
vial and try to ask for a half vial keep
in mind they throw almost all of your
blood away very little is needed
regardless of what they tell you they
need ask your doctor doctor if it's okay
if they can take half FS so in the worst
case scenario you're worried about
speaking up or they convince you they
need the amount of vials they need and
they're about to draw five or more vials
ask for half vials the labs will take it
regardless of what the doctor says or
the labs say or the FLOTUS says this way
if you're pressured into 14 vials like
so many are pressured into by
specialists it would only equal seven
vials when they are half filled this is
still too much blood drawn especially
for someone who's sick with symptoms or
a chronic illness but it can help
protect the person avoiding large blood
draws is the best thing to do if the
doctor allows for half files to be
filled and sends them to the blood lab
the blood lab will receive them and
follow through with the testing the
blood lab may say to the doctors's
office we want full vials so we can do
additional tests later on not true once
they run those tests they don't go back
to that blood you have to get another
blood test if something went wrong at
the blood lab this happens all the time
you get a call from the doctor's office
hello what I need to come back in again
for another blood test uh something
happened at the lab um oh okay and you
have to come in for a few more vials if
you do have to go back in ask for half
vials and give yourself a little time
between to recoup doctors tend to try to
get as many tests done in one blood draw
as possible if this requires more than
four full vials of blood for a healthy
person and more than 1 to three full
vials of blood for a person who's
struggling with a health condition then
you have the option of asking to to
separate or divide the tests and to come
back another day for additional blood
draws for additional tests breaking them
up so it's not a shock on your immune
system taking at least 5 days between
blood draws is best unless it's more
urgent then sooner is an option there's
a lot of wastage and mistakes made at
the blood Labs they're blood hungry it's
a machine they're like wolves a
bloodthirsty machine it's not the people
working there at the blood Labs that are
the problem they're great they're mostly
good people doing critical life-saving
work it's not the doctor's fault they're
not the problem it's the system that
shrouds them it's broken it hasn't been
upgraded adjusted checked in over 80
years it's Antiquated even if the tests
become more advanced as medic medicine
advances it's like that decked out car
that's got Wi-Fi it still has rubber
tires gets a flat in the end because he
just got a rubber tire with air in it
there's parts of it that are Antiquated
blood draw for blood tests and donation
practices need to upgrade they need to
change for the sake of the People's
Health and the level of stress on
doctors watching patients get sicker and
deteriorate without realizing in it that
because of the blood draws it's one of
the biggest triggers to prolonging
chronic illness let's talk about other
forms of support if you're someone who
knows your blood draws scheduled you
know it's coming you're dreading it you
know hey I got to get blood and it's not
a surprise at the doctor's office that
you're unaware of that day like you
visit the doctor you're sitting there
and they're like hey let's take some
blood then there's a lot of great things
you can do to prep one week Advance is
an ideal place to start if you're a
woman try to time your blood draw before
you enter menstration ideally a week
after your cycle even a week before your
cycle because at these times your immune
system is strongest in your whole body
hydration is an ideal way of helping
your immune system stay strong before
you get the blood draw so starting a
week before you get your blood test
reduce or eliminate your caffeine intake
if you regularly participate in it
caffeine is extremely dehydrating no
matter how much water and juices you're
consuming it dehydrates the cells your
hydration never gets to a maximum level
because caffeine sucks a person dry
during this week incorporate celery
juice 16 to 32 ounces every morning do
not add anything to that celery juice no
lemon no water no ice no other fruit
vegetable when you drink water always
add a little lemon or lime to the water
this brings in calcium vitamin C and
other critical trace minerals glucose
too and nutrients also replenishing your
cells melons watermelons cantaloupe
honeydew try to stock up on melons you
can get a canary melon you can get khaw
there's other melons out there you can
find try to eat the melon Blended don't
add water don't eat the skin of the
melon 16 o to 32 o of Blended melon
daily best to do in the morning after
celery juice the melon helps build up
electrolytes and glucose reserves in the
brain tissue melon helps to hydrate bone
marrow during the day or dinner try to
bring in some steamed potatoes or sweet
potatoes keeping them oil oil free and
free of butter too sour cream cheese or
any other fat whether your animal
protein eater or vegan or plant-based
try to keep your fats lower be cautious
on how many radical fats you consume in
a week before your blood test radical
fats are foods that have a large
percentage of fat residing in it like
milk cheese butter oil
eggs meat chicken turkey fish lamb nuts
seeds nut Butters avocados soy too nut
milks almond milk even oat milk it's
high in fat try to keep any of these
options to once a day ideally for dinner
for example having your fish with your
dinner that's it snack on some fruit
throughout the day like apples and
strawberries and
blueberries wild blueberries would be
best bananas papaya mango and bring in
lots of leafy greens spinach preferably
for all the mineral salts they're
critical for building your blood and
strengthening your immune system medical
medium spinage soup is ideal daily if
you can't plan a week ahead of your
blood test then try to apply this days
before even if it's just one day before
carry these practices 3 to 7 days after
your blood test with the addition of 16
to 32 o of pure straight cucumber juice
in the afternoon or evening cucumber
juice helps to improve red blood cells
after a blood draw two apples a day
extra papaya and bananas where you can
for extra potassium and glucose any of
these food tips applied before and after
a blood draw will be helpful do do the
best you can even if it's just getting
your celery juice in Daily so the sodium
cluster salts can really charge up those
electrolytes in those neurotransmitters
as needed now let's talk about some
helpful supplements before and after hey
you can check with your doctor see if
it's right for you the supplements I
recommend are the ones that I use for
myself they don't have any alcohol no
natural flavors no preservatives the
cleanest and the best quality it's the
vimergy company they have something
called micro it's a form of vitamin C
for your immune system support vitamin C
is critical because your immune system
needs it more than ever because a part
of your immune system was drawn out of
your body with the blood draw another
supplement liquid zinc sulfate from
vimer G2 zinc is to support the immune
system that's going to be left over so
as part of your immune system is lifted
out of your body removed and thrown away
the part that's left needs the zinc more
than ever zinc also keeps viruses doile
so they don't proliferate so
easily there's also liquid
B12 form of adinos silk bamin and
methylcobalamin that's something I take
and Trust greatly the right B12 supports
all bodily functions especially the
brain function the reason why I like the
vimer gb12 It doesn't have the
preservatives in it the citric acid the
alcohol the natural flavors and other
stuff they throw in all the other junky
companies when a tree is ready to be
planted and taken out of its container
or root ball it goes into shock as you
place that tree into the Earth to plant
you want to slow its shock down you must
give it a feeding a range of nutrients
that includes even B vitamins for faster
recovery B12 is that shock Buster for us
it feeds us so when we're uprooted like
when we're getting the blood draw our
body gets the shock and we need to take
care of our body so the shock is eased
so it's less of a shock also magnesium
glycinate helps to ease any nerve spasms
that are affected from the missing
magnesium that disappears when we get
the blood draw after blood draws muscles
tend to tighten spasm and
twitch if you have other supplement
questions check out medical medium.com I
have a directory so you can look at the
best stuff that I think is the safest
and the most supportive out there also
for more support read medical medium
book one but the new edition Secrets
behind chronic and mystery illness and
how to finally heal the revised and
expanded New Edition
version our blood is ancient thousands
of years old millions of years old it
gets passed on from generation to
generation our blood has the history of
lineage it's a sacred precious resource
we can't live without it we can't create
new life without it there's a hidden
code and messaging in our blood that
hidden code in messaging is bigger than
genetics or genes itself uncovered Ing
and learning the mystery of what sits
inside our blood is far away from what
they believe is in our
DNA the evildoers on the planet know
there is information inside our blood
they just haven't cracked it they've
been experimenting with our blood since
World War I trying to make sense out of
it and at the same time pretending it's
all for us and our health and well-being
if they had access to the secrets inside
of us they would gain more control over
the human race they would clone humans
at a rate that would surpass all
imagination where does all our blood go
it's not used in the blood tests some
believe it goes down the drain there's a
great possibility it goes straight to
medical testing for reasons that are
totally
insane