how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about nutritional
yeast now I'm not trying to get the
nutritional yeast people upset God knows
it may happen when they hear what I got
to say but this is about the chronically
ill and we got to put aside all those
bad feelings because we have to remember
there's somebody sick out there laying
in their bed putting things inside their
body and it's important that they know
what it is now the yeast world isn't
just black and white there's a gray area
to be had get ready fasten your seat
belts because we're going for a
ride
no I'll meet you at the check out
yeah I just forgot something yeah I
forgot my no all right all right I'll be
I'll be there in a second I'm heading to
the bulk
bins huh yeah just get me can you get me
a drink over there too on okay all right
I meet you to check
out all right oh cool here they are oo
nice two kinds of noch oh nice let me
get my bag out here
yeah oh I love this
n oh sorry lady I'm
sorry okay here we go oh
sir sir you're Mo you're pushing me over
you're getting your yes there's you can
get your n after um I'm here
first
there's a few people lined up to get
their
n ah there we go
nice I can't wait put this on my
popcorn all right all right sir go ahead
sorry go ahead you got you're all set
ma'am all right heading to the
checkout everybody who uses nutritional
yeast loves their nutritional yeast
everybody who eats nutrition East
without knowing it's nutritional East
loves their nutritional East see it's in
a lot of packaged food it's an
ingredient that's added to a lot of
different chips a lot of different corn
Puffs and different kinds of rice puffs
and everything else it's like a batter
you know like a batter you know when
you're like putting batter on some
chicken or some fried chicken you roll
it in batter it's like rolling it in egg
and that just kind of gooey wheat flour
batter drop it in a frying pan it's like
having this
coding and it tastes so yummy now you
may be like I had never had it I don't
eat nutritional
yeast yeah you had it you had it there's
no question it's in so many different
things all you got to do is just buy a
hummus chances are it's going to be in
the hummus all you have to do is buy a
hummus behind the deli counter that was
pre-made in any store they scoop it out
they put it in a container it's like
here you go sir thank you can't wait to
put some chips in there it could be
loaded with nutritional yeast and
usually is my friend got me a bag of
kale chips I was like oh cool kale chips
I said thanks man I really appreciate it
like no problem he opened up the bag he
was eating it he's like these are so
good like I bet they are I bet they're
good flip over the pack man he flipped
it over and he was like crunching and
like sunflower
oil olive oil nutritional
yeast natural flavors I said wait did
you did you read that goes what go
nutritional yeast natural flavors too
but that's another story but nutritional
yeast he was like what is that yeast
like the kind of baker's yeast I was go
no no no no it's different than that so
he said it's got to be good for you
right I mean it's a health food it hits
all the marks it's non GMO I'm like yeah
yeah it says that on the bag glutenfree
yeah says it on the bag no additive
preservatives uh-huh but I said to him
it's not as good as you think it is it's
not as good for people to eat as they
think it is but he said kale Kale's
amazing right I mean it's incredible I
said Kale's incredible Kale's amazing
for you yeah but it's dressed up to be
something more than just kale it's got
the nutritional yeast in it he goes okay
okay okay just tell me what's wrong with
the nutritional yeast so there's little
things about nutritional yeast that
aren't good and there's bigger things
about nutritional yeast that aren't good
we're going to start with the little
ones the nutritional yeast World hangs
their hat on the nutrition aspect of
nutritional yeast the nutrients like
you'll hear out there well it's got a
lot of vitamins it's got a lot of
minerals in there it's got a lot of
nutrients and it's like whoa I'm sold
right there and the nutritional yeast
World they got to be in it for the
goodness of everything the well-being of
everything because there's a lot of
nutrients in there and so that's the hat
right there they hang up on the hook so
it's this nutrient profile that makes it
really intriguing because you think
about it there's vitamins there's
nutrients there's minerals in there
where can you go wrong and that's the
whole point of nutritional yeast it's
yeast that happens to create
nutrients and so the nutrients inside
nutritional yeast are good for us so if
we're sick and unhealthy and have
problems this seems like a viable source
of nutrients to help our health and
well-being it's kind of an easy cell
it's like whoa nutritional yeast it's
loaded with vitamin A it's got some B's
in there it's got some different
nutrients this is perfect I need that
right now because I'm kind of sick I
don't feel good I'm always into my
health I'm looking for things to help me
so this works and whoa it tastes really
good so what's my problem withut
nutritional yeast all the nutrients it
has that's awesome think about it that's
really
incredible well to begin with it's not
that many nutrients that's just a start
because it's not as packed it's not as
dense the amounts of nutrients aren't
high that alone is tricky you can eat
one orange and you supersede it what
nutritional yeast could ever offer you
if you eat one banana one tomato
one artichoke one asparagus you
superseded those nutrients and then some
quadruple Su tfold 20 fold a piece of
kale you blew nutritional yeast out of
the water the nutrient profile in the
nutritional yeast could not even stand
up to one leaf of
spinach one leaf of spinach the nutrient
profile through the roof nutritional
yeast
not really at all it's so mild part of
why they fortify it a lot of companies
fortify it they add you know like white
bread processed white bread they got to
fortify it you got to enrich it it's
enriching that's what the companies do
the big manufacturers do so big
manufacturers they throw a whole bunch
of bulk vitamins in into the nutritional
yeast because in the end there really
isn't a lot of vitamins in the
nutritional yeast so they got to fortify
it just like white bread look I know the
deeper I get into this episode the more
friends I lose I understand that when it
comes down to n people are highly
protective over their n but let's go to
the other little problem I have so this
one's a little different think about
this yeast
is not a plant right now I know there's
a lot of plant-based people out there
they want to eat plants I know there's a
lot of animal protein people out there
that want to eat plants you want to eat
your animal proteins if you're an animal
protein person and your plants and if
you're vegan or plant-based you want to
have your plants and your plants right
so where does the yeast come in that's
not a plant why are we getting all
excited about it why are we supporting
it so much why are we fighting for it so
much it's not a
plant plants are medicine plant food
medicine right if you believe animal
products are medicine because you eat
animal products well there you go you
can say that too but where's the yeast
what's going on with that see that's a
fungus that's fungi
that's not a
plant oh I get it wait wait wait wait
wait you're thinking mushrooms now think
like what's this guy talking about fungi
yeast it's a
mushroom no it's not it's different a
mushroom doesn't feed off of bad
things a
mushroom doesn't
feed off of Bad Things things in order
to survive an edible mushroom so edible
mushrooms don't feed off of Highly toxic
substances in order to survive a yeast
will and then you're thinking well wait
a minute the yeast nutritional yeast is
feeding off of
beets so that's not a highly toxic thing
it's feeding off of beets that shouldn't
be a problem
it's a really big problem I told you you
better fasten your seat bels so now
let's talk about this a bit an edible
mushroom doesn't just care about
itself an edible mushroom knows
someone's going to feed off of it a wild
animal an animal in the woods a certain
variety of insect specifically large
insects too people
humans it doesn't grow for itself edible
mushrooms grow for the person they grow
for human life animal life to
consume yeast grows for
itself it devours what it wants for
itself and it doesn't matter if what it
devours is extremely highly toxic sure
we can take yeast and we can throw it on
something that's not highly highly toxic
and it'll feed off of it but it will
feed off of it only for itself not for
consumption of itself not for an animal
or a human to feed off of but wait wait
wait wait you got me you think you got
me candida candida I talk about that you
know it's inside our intestinal tract it
feeds off of things right but you're not
supposed to be scraping someone's colon
of
candida and eating it you're not
supposed to be scraping out your own
candida or somebody else's candida out
of their intestinal track trying to grow
it so you can package it up and then
sprinkle it on all the food you want eat
it every single day hey I got my candido
over here you guys I got a big bag of it
you want it on your popcorn let me put
on
hey you guys did you get your popcorn I
got a whole big bucket of candida right
here came out of a a a guy down the road
he said he would grow it for me so he
kept on eating all this crappy food and
he's just yes candida was Goblin all
that garbage he was eating all that
stuff in his gut and he had so much
candida that you know he had a a
physician scrape it out and a colon
hydrotherapist uh get it out and then
they grew it I got barrels of this stuff
man it's better than nutritional yeast
you got to try this hey bring your
popcorn over here okay here here it goes
what do you think it's good right it's
real good if you think that a portella
mushroom you know the big old portabella
mushrooms you buy in the store it's like
honey I want to throw one on the grill
I'm going to make everybody some
portella mushrooms I got a whole package
of them here if you think that the Cella
mushroom is the same thing as yeast then
you're terribly mistaken no disrespect
but terribly mistaken so you might be
somebody that's like he's wrong still
all fungi fungi family they're all the
same they're all doing the same thing
he's wrong well let's take a look at the
plants for a second so I said before
plants are plants right fungi fungi okay
I get it but not even all plants are the
same so I'm scratching my head on this
one
because I just told my friend he can
actually take all the poison ivy out of
his yard he pulled it off of the oak
tree and then picked it up all the
ground and he had a barrel of poison ivy
and I said since it's a plant it's the
same thing he can do what he wants with
it so he made a poison an ivy bed and he
slept on it last night he said it was
soft and comfortable he's in the
hospital right now but the point is is
that I think I made a mistake because I
since it's a plant I told them it's all
plants and he's a vegan by the way and
this plants are all the same so because
fungi are all the same too PTO Bell
mushrooms same thing as yeast uh that's
what everybody tells me out there all
the Geniuses so so I I just figured the
poison ivy is the same thing as
asparagus and so he decided cuz it was
really soft and comfortable he made this
massive bed of poison IV and he slept on
it last night and um his his partner and
him are both in the hospital right now
on steroids because the truth is yeast
is not a
mushroom that's the truth a big old
portella mushroom a shant tril a button
mushroom a baby Pella a bear's mushroom
whatever it's not the same thing as
yeast they're different
creatures oh wait I think somebody out
there has me again uh-oh they're saying
well poison ivy yeah that's a poisonous
plant duh it's not going to be an
asparagus so um excuse me aw but
nutritional yeast isn't poisonous we
don't get poisoned when we eat it so got
you there
well all right let me just tell you this
one now yeast is a cleaner upper it's a
fungi that's there to clean and eat
anything and everything okay poison ivy
is a plant it's growing out of the
ground same Earth as you can grow
lettuce and everything else and you can
have a garden with lettuce tomatoes
cucumbers anything you want in there
asparagus and then you can have poison
ivy growing right out of that garden
soil
too yeast is a whole different Beast you
can have that growing on something
highly toxic even
dangerous and it will
grow right off of it and doesn't have a
filter or a processing system like a big
old mushroom portello can grow out of
some poop but it will take in the good
stuff to make it into a portabella
mushroom same way a tomato plant can
grow out of poop it'll take in the good
stuff turn it into a juicy tomato and
it's safe and you can eat
it well yeast isn't like that yeast will
grow off something highly toxic and if
you eat that yeast you
die okay nutritional yeast well it's not
highly toxic and you can eat it and you
don't die because they didn't throw that
yeast onto something super high
toxic but if they did there'd be no
filter there'd be no body and no filter
system it actually will grow and become
as toxic to what it's growing on equal
and that's a
difference similar to snails and slugs
snails and slugs don't have a filtration
system they can feed off of something
highly toxic and then if you eat that
snail or eat that slug you can die now
if a snail and a slug is not feeding off
of foliage or any kind of waste that is
highly toxic you can boil that snail and
you can have your escargo or any kind of
other snails there's so many different
snails and varieties out there fresh
water salt water whatever but if your
snail is feeding on something that's not
highly toxic and your slug slugs too are
feeding on something that's not highly
toxic you can then boil them up and eat
them but that slug if you don't know
where that slugs been if that slug was
on some dangerous plants dangerous
foliage dangerous sludge somewhere and
you picked up that Slug and said whoa I
know I can boil you and eat you you can
you actually eat slugs and you go and
boil it and eat it and then you die or
get deathly ill because that slug didn't
have filtration system and actually ate
what was toxic stayed in it and it
became highly toxic well that's what
East can do so let's head now to what
really bothers me like the big boy let's
go there now okay yeast nutritional
yeast is not toxic because you're eating
it you got your yeast it's all good and
I'm going to grab mine right
now I got my nutritional use right here
and you know what's interesting about
this nutritional use bag that I have
well it says n
GMO n
GMO I got peace in my heart peace in my
mind peace in my soul I'm doing a little
happy dance right here got my n GMO
stuff going and uh that's just freaking
awesome you know put wait I got a bomb
to drop oh my God I just realized right
now what a fool I've
been stupid ass I am the primary food
source for yeast nutritional yeast is
GMO beats what the hell was I thinking
all these
years I've been gobbling this stuff by
the truckloads
man I just realized it just now this
very second the primary source of food
for the yeast to grow on is GMO beat
it's sugary beats it's sugar beats like
oh my God like
du anyway you guys that's the big boy
right there and I'm going to tell you
something about that big boy that really
scares me the yeast becomes what it eats
you have to remember remember that yeah
of course I get it on paper they can say
technically it's not GMO so they can put
that on the package they can put it
right on there I'm grabbing the package
again says n
GMO that's interesting because all this
yeast that grew grew on GMO beats whoa
you guys are sneaky man you guys are
really really sneaky the type of yeast
they're using
sacris is growing on GMO sugar beet
remember when I said that yeast becomes
what it
eats that means nutritional yeast
becomes that GMO product but Legally
Legally they don't have to make that
connection for you on the package they
don't have to and they're not going to
shut down their yeast factories just
because of that minor little detail oh
wait oh my God you think I'm wrong again
because your nutritional East that
you're eating it's growing on molasses
they grow that one on molasses right so
I must be wrong again molasses is sugar
beat oh wait wait you got me again now I
think I think he got me again right
you're saying that the company you talk
to the sugar beads they use aren't GMO
oh really really all sugar beads are GMO
cross-contamination has happened the
majority of sugar beads used in
nutritional yeast making and
Manufacturing are 100%
GMO the small portion of sugar beads
that aren't 100% GMO are still 100% GMO
by cross
contamination the nutritional yeast
factories their phones are going to be
ringing off the hook after this podcast
comes out and they're going to be
telling everybody a really nice bedtime
story they're going to say oh no no no
no no not our Factory we have the best
quality beets you've ever seen our
nutritional yeast is all good and pure
they're going to make you feel nice and
good so you can keep your addiction
strong and we're going to go into the
addictive nature of it pretty soon but
we still have some horror stories to
tell with the GMO Factor now the problem
with fungus yeast that type of fungus it
has the ability to adapt change change
its chemical
structure change its nature to
survive that's what yeast does that's
why when someone has a yeast
infection they go to the doctor they
take an
antifungal it goes away they get another
yeast infection go to the doctor
take the same
antifungal and it's very tricky and
stubborn and it doesn't go away and then
they have to give that patient extra
antifungal finally it goes away then
they get another yeast infection go to
the doctor and then they have to give
them another type of antifungal because
you can't use the other antifungals it
adapted to those antifungals it
acclimated it over roded it Rose above
it
yeast has an intelligence to save itself
it has the ability to change so when
it's on top of GMO food molasses GMO
sugar beat it actually Alters itself
because GMO foods are toxic they have
toxins in them GMO toxins the yeast
changes its
structure it changes its actual cell
structure but no no one's monitoring
that no one cares just pump that stuff
out to the masses have them eat it all
they want more GMO sugar beets come in
which is highly toxic because it's a GMO
product and then the cell structure of
the yeast changes and changes meanwhile
no one's going to get $250 million the
magic number to get a group of
scientists together to take a little
lucky L at what's going wrong like
Frankenstein yeast Franken yeast no
one's going to take a peek into it you
know rosec colored glasses got to have
them on rosecolor glasses call the
nutritional yeast Factory and you're
going to
get nutritional yeast Factory here hello
hello yes yes what's your concern
customer uh
GMO there's no GMO in our nutritional
yeast huh
what kind of talk is that I'm sorry are
you saying that we're using GMO sugar
beat well um
maybe yeah and the and the yeast is
growing off the sugar beat uh yes it's
growing off our molasses yes yes our
good
molasses yes and and then uh what the
yeast is turning into something you mean
it's it's growing off the GMO and it's
changing its cell structure the hogwash
oh goash that doesn't even make any
sense yes yes we have the Finest
nutritional yeast there is we sell it to
all great places health food stores use
it I actually take it myself I like my
nutritional yeast um I just don't really
think there's a lot of Merit in this
this uh this GMO thing we're not GMO we
say it on the package we have every
legal right to say it's not GMO on the
package but yes
well I believe oh we'll we'll bring this
up in the next meeting and the next
board meeting but I mean I listen I'll
give you some free would you like a free
order I'll give you a free order sent to
your address would that make you feel
better okay okay that's what we'll do
see yeast doesn't like to die and yeast
doesn't like to be challenged so when
it's up against a predator like GMO
because GMO foods are actually a
predator food that's not a food to help
nurture us help heal us help fortify us
it's actually a predator food it's
designed in a lab it's dangerous we know
that about GMO food but fungus likes to
rise above it when it's up against
confrontation like that it changes its
cell structure it changes how it thrives
and how it grows because the yeast
doesn't want to die it wants to live
forever that's what yeast does that's
why a baker with Baker yeast which is
still yeast it's a little different but
it's still yeast can keep yeast alive
for a thousand years it can be in the
lineage of somebody in their home and
they can keep that yeast alive for
centuries it could be centuries old
yeast it doesn't like to die instead it
likees to adapt and when you give it
something toxic and dangerous to adapt
to you don't have the same yeast you
once had you have more of a
non-world
non-natural more of a super fungus just
like a super bacteria like MCA but you
end up with a super fungus fungus can
alter its own cell structure so it never
has to Forfeit a battle
and die it won't succumb to the law of
nature meaning the law of death it won't
succumb to being poisoned by something
unnatural and highly toxic instead it'll
supersede it and that's when yeast turns
into a Frankenstein yeast a Franken
yeast and it holds that toxin Superior
within itself it's being that GMO
product and reproduces itself over and
over again with that GMO product within
itself and that leads to another scary
thing kind of get ready for this one
fast in your seat belts nutritional
nutritional nutritional vitamins
minerals nutrients we're eating the
nutritional yeast because obviously
we're addicted and we'll talk about the
addiction part A little later but we're
eating it too because we think it's good
for us we keep on being told that it's
packed with vitamins and minerals and
nutrients so we say okay great this is
nutritional it's got vitamin B it's got
all this in it and this is great but no
one's realizing
something those are
GMO vitamins and nutrients that's what
nutrients those are the nutrients and
vitamins that the yeast
created from the GMO sugar beat becomes
a GMO new
nutrient GMO nutrients aren't fit for
human consumption they're not fit for
the human body our bodies can't thrive
on those nutrients they don't help us
heal they don't refill our
deficiencies they help us become
deficient GMO food pushes a person into
deficient land into
deficiencies the yeast is is growing off
of the GMO sugar bead developing and
creating its own Frankenstein vitamins
and that's what we're consuming another
thing which is really interesting
there's no regulation determining that
your yeast you're growing has to be on
molasses GMO
molasses you can grow your yeast on
anything you choose as long as that
yeast will feed on it
grow you can then package it up and sell
it so the gray area is really scary so
yes the majority of the production is
all about molasses which is GMO but
there are some people out there they're
picking anything they want to choose
from doesn't matter what food it is GMO
food for sure it could be anything it
could be sewage it could be engine oil
it can be petroleum
petroleum ready it can be petroleum
byproduct did you know that there is
Baker yeasts that grow off of oil waste
petroleum byproduct so that means
anybody can legally do that you can open
up a nutritional yeast Factory get a
petroleum byproduct or something toxic
like a sewage or a sludge from petroleum
byproduct throw a whole bunch of yeast
on it in it in your own of course
sterile containers it doesn't matter you
can still use the same facility the same
structure but you're using the sludge or
the engine oil or the petroleum
byproduct and waste and you're growing
the yeast off of that and that's the
yeast you're creating and now packaging
and selling it's been done before they
do it with baker's yeast they can do it
with nutritional yeast and there's no
rules there's no regulations and there's
no nutritional yeast police police leing
it and governing it just like there's no
real marijuana cannabis police that are
governing if someone sees an apit attack
on marijuana leaves that they can take a
can of raid and just shoot it all over
the place and shoot the plant down to
kill off those aphids no one's watching
that either the regulations aren't there
so what happens when we eat nutritional
yeast and it's Franken yeast so we're
chewing it we're eating it we're
swallowing it
it's this yeast That Grew off of GMO
beads it altered its self structure it
became something different it adapted we
then consumed it ate it it went down
into our intestinal tract and now it
becomes food for something else so this
will be interesting to know but yeast
eats
yeast yeast consumes yeast so now you
have yeast inside your gut you have
yeast in your small intestinal tract you
have yeast in your large intestinal
tract people have yeast on the rectum
every day just a big hunk of yeast is
just right on the edge of the
rectum yeast devours yeast problem here
though you have yeast inside of you like
candida that's going to have to then
feed off of this yeast the nutritional
yeast that has died you've consumed it
you've eaten it and it's not the same
kind of yeast it's a different yeast but
it's an altered yeast it's made
primarily out of GMO food so here you go
your yeast now is consuming a different
yeast that has information in it yeast
is
intelligent it holds information as it's
gobbling up the Franken yeast it's
computing
it's digesting information it's
receiving information it can change the
structure of the yeast that we naturally
have in us now we have bad yeast in us
we got good yeast in us we got a
combination of a few different yeasts
some people have even more some people
may have 10 varieties of yeast some
people may just have two but either way
it changes the yeast that we naturally
have in us because as that yeast is
cleaning up all that dead GMO yeast that
changed and the cell structure changed
and everything about it altered for
survival for
adaptation as our yeast gobbles up that
yeast our yeast starts to adapt and
change and if it's a bad yeast inside of
us it could adapt and change and create
infections that won't respond to
antifungals at the doctor's office or in
the hospital so now we're in trouble
there and then if it's a good yeast
inside of us it can alter and change and
end up becoming a bad yeast and so the
good yeast inside of us eats the bad
yeast and starts to change now what if
you're somebody that collected a lot of
yeast in your day public bathrooms
collecting it there restaurants eating
out a lot collecting it there
relationships Partners collecting it
there hospital visits collecting it
there there you could be somebody that
has a lot of different varieties of
yeast all kinds of yeast and then we're
putting in that nutritional yeast and
we're training and teaching all these
other different yeasts that are inside
of us to be different and that's where
things can go wrong that's where chaos
can ensue it's because our yeast will
start to learn behavior taking
information from yeast that isn't
supposed to even be here on any level
meanwhile somebody's micro biome doctor
like who's trying to help somebody with
the good of their heart and they're
using all their expertise that they have
doesn't even know any of this and they
might even be like hey nutritional yeast
is fortified and it's got vitamins and
minerals and oh you can keep that in
there just make sure you don't do any
celery juice but make sure you have your
nutritional yeast there okay so let's go
to the next big one if you're still into
your nutritional yeast I don't blame you
it's hard to let it go and it's
addictive and we we'll head there don't
worry but there's one other pink
elephant in the room and we're gonna
have to talk about it it's glutamic acid
whoa I know it I know it I know it I
know what's happening right now a bunch
of Ed guys are probably like okay he
doesn't know anything about this there's
no MSG in this at all my nutritional
yeast doesn't have MSG it's welln it's
not MSG so he'll say glutamic acid he's
trying to trick us but he's
wrong all right here it goes glutamic
acid isn't all plants it's in all
foods it's an acid that's everywhere so
why is it a big deal that's in
nutritional yeast like who hears it's in
everything because nutritional yeast is
a yeast that's why we're talking about
glutamic acid in a yeast we're not
talking about glutamic acid in an
asparagus artichoke Brussels sprout
banana potato green apple berry we're
not talking about that we're not talking
about glutamic acid in Dairy yes in eggs
and meat and chicken even pork that's
got glutamic acid in it but it's in all
the different foods but how much is it
in the different foods for example Le if
it's in an asparagus a Brussels sprout a
potato a carrot it's a lot less it's a
lower amount of glutamic acid another
thing too fungi is not a plant it's a
different form of glutamic acid animal
products most animals are eating plants
so those animals are eating plants
they're lamic acid is coming from
concentrations of the plant Foods
they're
consuming but ounce for ounce pound for
pound it's not a lot of glutamic acid
compared to yeast and people get carried
away with their yeast do you know
anybody who gets carried away with their
nutritional yeast because I know some
people they throw it on everything they
make a lot of food with it there's not a
lot of glut GLC acid in a carrot not a
lot of glutamic acid in a cucumber or
green apple or red apple or a Cherry
Berry a watermelon but it's highly
concentrated in yeast highly
concentrated in nutritional yeast
because nutritional yeast is a small
microorganism a small microorganism with
a lot of glutamic acid within it and
then we take a large amount of that
microorg organism we concentrate it it
becomes a powder it turns out it becomes
an MSG powder without having to add
MSG now remember the scientists they're
not going to do that looky L into things
they're not going to look at the yeast
that's feeding off of the GMO beats and
determine that that yeast is changing
and adapting they're not going to spend
the $250 million from a grant to get a
group of scientists to do that but
they're also not going to get a grant
for $250 million to have a bunch of
scientists look at the different
glutamic acid structures because they're
different compounds coming from
different places so a green apple
glutamic acid much different than a
yeast glutamic acid and they're not
going to take the time to do the lookie
look to do the looky L to take a look
and be like whoa wait a minute that
yeast that produces a different form of
glutamic acid and it's more concentrated
and it's
aggressive because that's what it is a
yeast glutamic acid is an aggressive
nature different than a carrot than a
steak but what they need to do the
scientists need to isolate the glutamic
acid from yeast take that isolation take
that concentration and feed it to mice
and they can watch the mice and their
behavior hey did you give the mouse the
glutamic acid tablet the glutamic acid
tablet the mouse ate the other Mouse the
Mouse is dead he ate the other Mouse he
had an anchor fit and now he wants more
glutamic acid tablets I went to the cage
and he ran up to me and he jumped up and
he want my other glutamic acid
tablet yeah he killed the other
Mouse but no one's keeping tabs they're
not keeping tabs of the GMO beats
they're feeding the yeast they're not
keeping tabs of the yeast and how it
actually evolves they're not keeping
tabs of the glutamic acid production
inside the yeast and the fact that the
glutamic acid production is actually GMO
it's a glutamic acid that's GMO no one's
keeping tabs of that and of course
they're not keeping tabs of the fact
that the glutamic acid is different than
any other type of glutamic acid than the
the type of glutamic acid that's in meat
beef poultry vegetables fruit to
different Beast all on its own and no
one's informing anybody about the
dosages how much they're consuming how
much they're eating and is it storing up
somewhere glutamic acid can store up in
the brain so wait a minute here we're
eating all this glutamic acid
concentrated forms of it in a lot of
yeast we're putting on our food we're
assuming large amounts of this gamic
acid where is it going it goes to the
brain so all this GMO gamic acid ends up
inside our brain no one's keeping tabs
on that either now let's talk about
dosages I see people they're pouring it
on they're giving it to their children
and it's not their fault they're just
being told it's good for them so that's
the sad part all on its own people are
being very generous with the helpings I
know somebody there like taking a
scooper and it's a scooper they use and
they use this big old scooper and it
just goes in all their food they make
dishes they make rose you know where
you're making soups and stews or making
dressings and ruse people throw it on
their salads they throw it on their meat
they throw it on their chicken they
throw it on all the food they're making
some people just eat it out of their
hand they're just popping it in their
mouth left and right right out of the
bag they put it on their granola they
have it on their snacks
they have it on everything people just
pop it in their mouth as they're
coughing and choking on it sometimes
because you can inhale it by accident
it's extremely addictive because yeast
glutamic acid mimics
MSG it becomes the ultimate comfort food
for so many people and I don't blame
them one bit I'm not judging anybody
okay I know we go through a lot of
hardships and struggles a lot of stress
and when we we find a comfort food that
feels good to us an emotional connection
happens and we use it as an anchor
nutritional yeast is a comfort food for
so many people I feel bad for somebody
who's listening to this episode when I
think about it because they may be
really eating a lot of it and then it's
about whoa what do I do do I wean myself
off how do I move this out of my life
it's really hard the problem with MSG is
it goes to the brain it gets into the
nerves it gets on the neurons in the gal
cells it
crystallizes MSG deposits build up
around neurons creating these little
crystallizations that interfere with
electrical impulses in our brain
chemistry creating a brain response
that's highly addictive I talk more
about this in the brain saver books
coming out and then there's gut health
intes tract Health glutamic acid from
nutritional yeast aggravates nerve
endings in the intestinal tract lining
if someone's got gas and bloating
Crohn's colitis or Celiac or some kind
of distension some kind of cramping
maybe flatulence maybe gastroparesis
maybe some type of intestinal tract
disorder nutritional yeast is the last
thing you want to eat it's an intestinal
irritant a colon irritant it's
problematic inside the intestinal tract
causes a lot of problems with the lining
a lot of food sensitivity doctors food
allergists they'll test you for a lot of
different allergies they'll have a big
old list of your food
sensitivities and most of the time if
not all the time nutritional yeast won't
be on the list and you'll be free to eat
all the nutritional yeast You Ever
Wanted by your doctor's orders Katie the
doctor will see you well Katie it looks
like your food allergist has came in and
it doesn't seem like you have a food
allergy a food
allergy a food allergy to nutritional
yeast after
all it saddens me so many good people
doing good things for themselves wanting
the best out of life wanting to heal
wanting to make sure that everything
they do is right it matters to them life
matters health is
everything they care about their loved
ones they care about their friends the
people they know they want what's best
for everybody around them and they want
to learn and they want to grow but then
comes Darkness
you just can't see blinders on and we
don't understand how capable Darkness
can be and we don't see behind the
mirror as we're looking at ourselves
that there are obstacles in the way of
our healing that have taken us and our
health but once we learn and find our
way we strengthen and never let anything
ever again again get in our way
knowledge is power and power of the
light so bright it kills the yeast that
grows as it fights and how do we trust
to find our way there's so much out
there we don't know that contributes and
it makes our body pay we want to feel
better than less than we want to feel
our best we don't want to be sad we
don't want to be left out we want to
know all of the rest when we think about
it we get tricked into putting things
into our mouth by telling us it's
healthy and it will provide a way out
but not all the things we eat are really
good for us and not all foods are the
same and are really safe for us when you
have the truth in your hands you got the
freedom to choose