how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about digestion
digestion has been a mystery to research
in science since the beginning of
research in science and nowadays it's
all about our gut all their problems are
because because of our gut we're told
but what do we really know about our
digestive system how much do we not know
where does it matter where does it make
or break us from healing or dying what
about more things happening inside our
gut than we could ever even imagine that
science research has no clue about right
now in this episode we're going to be
talking about the nitty-gritty we're
going to talk about things you've never
even heard
fasten your seat bels get your herbal
tea ready we're going for a
ride Hey where's my
station I got to hurry up and sit down I
got a pile of hot dogs yeah no it's my
first contest I I mean I usually I
usually just I'm with my friends when we
watch like a football game or something
and I usually eat like 20 hot dogs
really fast in front of them they always
laugh but I'm really primed for this one
the last guy I heard he ate 150 hot dogs
yeah and the guy it didn't even look
like it phased him I just know when I'm
up to about 40 hot dogs I know that I'm
wind it but I'm going to push through oh
oh wait wait I got to sign this paper oh
okay okay I'm sign am I signing My Life
Away In This Bar okay no it just says if
you get injured we hold no
responsibility okay
I'm all right I just signed my name okay
I'm sitting down all right I got to get
ready
okay okay hey you guys I'm happy to be
here too all right oh my God there's my
aunt my aunt and uncle yeah you ever
been to an eating contest where someone
eats like 10 pies really quick and
they're gobbling it down and there's a
line of people there and one pie after
another and they got it all over their
face and they're gobbling it down and
chomping it down or better yet maybe an
eating contest where it's a hot dog
eating contest right where there's this
plate in front of the person that has
like 100 hot dogs and everybody's lined
up and the goal is to eat the hot dogs
as fast as possible and you see some
guys they shove the hot dog down and the
whole hot dog slides down their throat
they didn't even chew it more than once
and they just got to shove it in as fast
as possible or maybe there's what is
there there's other ones too where a
whole bunch of tacos I saw one on TV
there was a whole bunch of tacos and a
guy ate like a 100 tacos and and you
couldn't leave a mess on the plate they
said at the end of the con like during
the contest they said the whole plate
has to be cleaned and one guy didn't
clean the whole plate so he lost there
was like a couple of tomatoes left and a
little bit of guacamole and some beans
and some meat sauce all left in the
plate and and then there's restaurants
that say you can eat for free if you
finish what they're selling right like
you look on the menu and they sell
something called the big big boy and
it's 10 lbs of chopped meat with like 50
meatballs wrapped around it pile of
sausage and I don't know and a whole
barrel of beans right and if you can
finish that your whole family can eat
for free but you got to be one person
sitting there at the table and they only
give you like two hours so you sit there
eating it and if you can get to the end
of that then the whole family eats for
free you know a friend of mine he didn't
do that but his friend did that at a
restaurant where they brought out this
massive 20 lb steak I don't know what it
was it was just so huge he said and he
sat there eating his friend sat there
eating it and eating it so that they
would be having a free meal he would win
in the end and he was eating it eating
it they had to rush him to the hospital
because he had this stomach cramp that
was so bad my friend told me that he
fell on the floor and he was in fetal
position on the floor trying to pass gas
and everybody in the restroom got scared
and the whole crowd gathered around him
as he was trying to push gas out of his
stomach and he was farting and then he
was kind of like an Agony moaning and
yelling my friend said it was so bad
they had a call Emergency Services 911
now this guy was only halfway through
his stake and he was a really big guy
meaning like he was
6'4 he was like
240 lbs uh he had some muscle on him and
everything and but he was known by his
friends to be able to eat a lot as much
as he wanted and drink too so he can
drink a whole bunch of beer and eat all
that now he said this is from him he
said that the reason why it happened was
because he ate something before this big
dinner he was eating and he knew not to
do it it's like one of those things
where you know better and you know you
shouldn't have or maybe postpone it and
do it another day at the restaurant but
he said he couldn't help it he wanted
the challenge but he had something
before it he had a cheeseburger an hour
before it and he said that didn't sit
right on top of what he was putting down
in and like I said this guy was a big
guy 6'4 body mass like big which leads
me to this other thing which makes me
scratch my head confounds me really is I
saw an eating contest and it's a bunch
of people lined up it was on television
it was like many years ago and there was
this woman with a bunch of men so there
was a bunch of men and they're all big
guys and then there was this woman she
was in the contest sitting at a table
and they were all going to eat the same
thing it was like I don't know a 5B
Burger something crazy it was something
that you just can't eat it's actually
scary and she won the contest which was
crazy to me because she was with all
these other guys they were big guys some
of them were like six feet tall 6 foot
like five or just really big guys and
that means their stomach was probably
really big she was like 105 lb and when
I think about that it boggled my mind I
watched it and I was like Spirit just
tell me what's going on here and what
was amazing is she could stretch her
stomach her stomach was stretching now I
always knew that your stomach stretches
absolutely people can eat a lot more and
you stretch your stomach more but there
was a vast difference here
with who was at this table there were
people that were much much bigger men
large stomachs eating a lot and she was
small petite and ate the same thing and
that's the miracle of the human body
that's the miracle of our digestive
system that's the superior strength of
our stomachs the world's not an easy
place to live confrontation obstacle
trials losses hardships betrayal that's
a big one right there so many people get
betrayed all through their life and in
this we tend to use food as a drug a
pill to sweep us away into a safe place
stress can do this and some of us we
overeat everybody experienced that
before or it's easy to do just run
across a little bit of stress have a
little bit of hardship hard times and
you see something and there it is
there's that chocolate cake there's that
Bagel there's that double deck or
whatever there's that croissant whatever
it is it's easy to fall prey to it it's
not even just that you might be saying I
don't eat croissants aw I don't eat
double decker cake whatever that is I
eat a whole big batch of macaroni and
cheese and I can't stop and I keep on
shoveling it in I eat a whole pizza not
a half a pizza or I eat too many slices
everybody has their own method it's a
survival method we tend to overeat hey
no judgment that's just life here and
wait you might be somebody that doesn't
overeat like that but you undereat you
don't eat stress comes along some
confrontation some hardship some
adversity maybe just a difficult time in
your life maybe you were betrayed and it
felt so terrible in the pit of your
stomach food was the last thing you
wanted and even as time kind of went by
and the Betrayal kind of eased off you
still weren't that hungry to want to
tank or eat a large amount of food at
once so you're the kind of person to
just just eat a little bit kind of just
for survival along the way that happens
too A lot of people run into this and
they just have that pit of stomach nerve
nausea the upset you feel like your
heart was swallowed and it ended up in
the pity of your stomach and the last
thing you want to do is actually eat now
why am I even talking about all this
because our stomach has to do what we
tell it to do it has to do whatever we
say or do it doesn't matter it has to
listen it has to obey because it's
sitting there it's not going to be able
to stop you it can't say hey don't do
that or whoa you're stretching me man
you're stretching me way too far or hey
I'm shrinking I'm shrinking over here
and I'm getting smaller and smaller or
whoa you stretched me way too fast whoa
that was a lot you put in in there just
now or oh my God I'm shrinking so much I
think I'm going to disappear on you
right now I think you got to put
something in the tank I know you got
some emotional stuff going on right now
I know you got hardships but you got to
put something in me our stomach is under
our beck and call it's under our roof so
when we swallow something it has no say
no say to what's coming down the pike it
just has to grin and bear it take the
brunt and maybe you're someone that
doesn't think I'm right about this
thinking I'm off the mark But I think we
got to have some respect for our
stomachs because our stomachs get
disrespected I'm wrong well you know
what I think about those stories you
always hear out there where it's College
it's a party someone sticks a pipe down
their throat someone's standing on a
ladder or a chair and they're dumping
all the this beer and alcohol down the
pike and someone's on the floor on their
knees looking up pipes in their throat
and they're trying to send it all down
into their stomach one shot and then
everybody screaming and then the pipe
flies out and spit goes everywhere it's
like do it again and someone else gets
there and does it again and then a few
hours later shove a pizza down the pike
down the gullet think about that
person's poor stomach but people don't
really think about people's poor stomach
they think about people they're like oh
wow that person had a great time or that
person overdid it that person did yeah
that person did way too much oh they're
kind of sick the next day but no one's
saying hey that person's stomach is shot
today hey that person's stomach is
really not feeling great today that
person's stomach went through hell last
night you should talk to that person's
stomach hey stomach are you okay in
there no one's doing that no one cares I
get it I get it this isn't you you don't
binge out or you never did anything like
this you're more balanced you're more
moderation or self-care day right so
yours is about well here's my self-care
day or here's my cheat day or here's my
moderation day um but you're the one
governing it right your stomach still
has to be at your beck and call your
stomach still has to be at your mercy at
your mercy
and maybe your cheat day oh sorry maybe
your self-care day or maybe your balance
day or moderation day because
everybody's calling it different now
different things it used to be called
cheat day so so maybe your self-care day
is different than somebody else's
self-care day or maybe your stomach
doesn't like your self-care day but you
like your self-care day maybe you like
your moderation day but your stomach is
like moderation this isn't the
moderation I need right now a lot of
people out there will tell you what they
need like what their needs are for what
they want to eat doesn't mean it's their
body's needs are being met doesn't mean
their stomach needs are being met it's
kind of like whatever their
Consciousness is right if we were raised
on a different planet and they only gave
you so much food like this or this or
this that's all you would have but
humans tend to
make
concoctions we like Delights we're
raised on chicken fingers we're raised
on fish sticks we're raised on Burgers
we're raised on fries with oil we're
raised on melted cheese that gets all
crusty and brown in the oven we're
raised on ice cream we're raised on a
lot of different foods
Abominations you might be somebody
saying he's wrong I listen to my body no
you listen to your Consciousness and
what it was trained to eat our
Consciousness the very thing attached to
the emotional centers of the brain that
means food's emotional we get emotional
and then our Consciousness plays tricks
it's interesting it's like no I'm
intuitively eating well I've seen people
say they're intuitively eating and what
they're eating I'm like whoa okay if
that's intuitively what you're eating I
got all the respect for you but man
that's SC with what you're eating or if
somebody that says well I'm eating in
moderation or I heard someone said you
could eat in moderation there
Consciousness then adopts that and it's
like well it fits into what I want to
eat I could say I'm eating this in
moderation I could get away with it but
our Consciousness can learn bad or good
it can learn bad and not so bad and
halfway bad and pretty bad or really bad
or can learn bad
pretty good not so bad or it can learn
bad all bad or it could be like whoa
good good good good good bad good good
good good good bad little bad good good
good your Consciousness can learn all
the good things and then it can connect
to that emotional center of the brain
and relearning can happen but there's
something you need to know your
consciousness
can be tricked you know think so well
Apple C of vinegar any Apple C of
vinegar likers out there that get mad at
me instantly when I even say it yeah if
you like it yep if you think it's
healthy for you yep if you use it every
day yep you've been tricked I know
there's some of you guys out there that
don't like vinegar or know apple cider
vinegar is not the best for you or maybe
your body reacted when you took it at
one time so you need something better
than that right let's do another little
test hey it's a test this is fun
chocolate
chocolate chocolate that's a good one
right there you like it you've been told
it's good for you it's yummy you get the
dark chocolate with no additives and
junk in it right you get the healthy
chocolate bar oh you get the cacao nibs
okay right you've been told it's good
feels good when you eat it man you're
flying feels
wonderful and what about coffee that's
another one right there people like it
they enjoy it we get addicted to it we
have it every single morning some people
have it three times a day four times a
day we're told it's good for us we're
told organic coffee is actually really
good for us too and our Consciousness is
tricked once again but that might be
your your moderation or your intuitive
nature or your balance or your self-care
day or your self-care hour every single
day which is you sit and have your
coffee you're liking it your
Consciousness is liking it doesn't mean
your stomach's liking it doesn't mean
your stomach likes it at all you see
those people out there they eat what
they want you watch them they go to any
restaurant they could sit down at the
restaurant they can order like surf and
turf they can order Lobster they can
order clams muscles oysters Lobster move
that over after they finish some of it
and then big old juicy steak comes with
butter on top whole bunch of onion rings
on the side maybe some other appetizers
crab cakes all of a sudden they're
eating crab cakes right or maybe they're
eating something else like some kind of
just soup that's loaded with oil on top
has dairy in it cheese parmesan cheesee
all sprinkled over it maybe it's just a
big bowl of
pasta with cheese or just fetuccini
Alfredo maybe it's just Cookies Cakes
and donuts ice cream and some pizza and
then they get sick now it doesn't mean
the food made them sick really in the
end it could have been anything
pathogens viral load Epstein bar
bacteria like strepto coctus immune
system problems toxic heavy metal
chemical exposure it could be anything
added all up and bundled up and then the
foods did not help a lot of people head
to the doctors when they're not feeling
good and they're getting sick and they
may go through a lot of doctors before
they even start changing their diet
sometimes they'll see two or three
doctors or more doctors these days will
tell you to get off the sweets and the
junk and any of the processed foods and
that's a good place to start but in the
end it's not too far far from what they
were eating
previously even if they go to the best
functional medicine doctor these days
they're still going to be eating pretty
much close to what they used to eat
except they'll keep a lot of the
processed food out the sweets the junk
but the protein will be there all the
fat will be there they'll still be
eating the meals they remember they
always remembered they'll still have
their chicken they'll still have their
meat now if they're a vegan they're
still going to have their nuts they're
still going to have their seeds they're
still going to have their oils they're
still going to have their beans they're
still going to have their vinegar and
they're still going to have their
chocolate whether vegan or animal
protein eaters they're still going to
have all those things but they're going
to put the brakes on the processed foods
and many people get improvements cuz
they clean up so much nasty stuff in
their diet so they start to improve in
different ways but then there's a lot of
people they only improve so much or none
at all and they're on the search for
something different because they go to
another doctor to another specialist and
another and the diets are all kind of
relatively the same even if they hit a
food elimination doctor in the end you
still got to eat you still got to live
so it turns out to kind of be the same
old thing maybe you can put in name on
it keto is one of the names it could be
another name a lot of people are naming
things differently to try to be their
own way but it all ends up the same kind
of food but just done a little
differently and whatever portions you've
been eating is relatively the same as
well so it's not just the advice from
your functional medicine doctor or
doctors about getting rid of the
processed foods the fried foods the
greasy Foods cleaning things up looking
out for what you're doing it's more than
that it's kind of the portions are still
kind of relatively the same you're
trying to survive you're eating what
you've known your whole life the amount
you're eating is kind of what you've
known your whole life since you were a
kid and your Consciousness is still
programmed to what it's always been your
whole life even though you've cleaned up
your diet a little bit and maybe it's
not just your functional medicine doctor
maybe it's your nutritionist maybe it's
your health coach
maybe it's your trainer maybe it's your
healthc care advisor maybe it's your
dietitian or it's something you read or
seen an influencer do and that's what
you adopted through your Consciousness
I'm going to try that but in the end
it's still close to what you've always
done in the way you've always done it
and then you're still not better and
then something inside of you tells you
you have to go further you're desperate
you're on your hands and knees you're
praying to God and at night wondering if
you're going to live your life the way
you want to wondering if you're still
going to live it all because the
symptoms get to you it's breaking down
your mind it's breaking down who you are
people around you aren't happy you're
being looked at like you're a complainer
or you're somebody that's just a
hypercondriac and you're just like I
can't take this anymore and nothing
seems right to what you're doing and
then something happens you break a
barrier you break down a wall and you're
like I have to find something something
doesn't matter what it is maybe fruit is
okay to do but I've been told it's so
bad I hear medical medium information
has healed a lot of people but it's
fruit involved and I've been told
fruit's awful by every single functional
doctor and trainer and dietitian that I
have to be very careful and just have a
little fruit once in a while and it's a
certain kind of fruit and but I need to
heal and then you look into it maybe you
grab a book maybe you read cleanse the
heel and you see smoothies in there but
specific smoothies and then you see more
fruit and then you see leafy greens and
wild foods and herbs and the whole thing
seems foreign maybe you didn't learn it
from medical medium maybe you learned it
from from somebody who learned it from
medical medium 20 years ago bring in
more fruits more vegetables more living
fresh fruits more living fresh
vegetables or maybe you picked up some
tips from a vegan more fruits and
vegetables and then whatever version you
found out there you tried you did it
something didn't feel right something
didn't sit right in your stomach weren't
feeling that great kind of confused
about it at all tried it for a while and
then rode it off it didn't work for you
and you saw something out there like I'm
going to eat intuitively or what my body
needs or moderation or
orthorexia whatever it was you were
turned off you didn't understand it what
you were putting in your body how your
body works you didn't have all the
details and you didn't know that what
your consciousness believes or wants is
much different than what your body needs
or wants now all these years your
Consciousness was trained to eat the way
you were eating and your body was
adapting to what your Consciousness was
training your body to do they were
working together all those years in the
past now you're trying something new
your Consciousness is struggling to what
you're trying to learn it's used to what
it used to know in the emotional Center
of your brain right Comfort Foods eating
a certain way your whole life it's
different now and your body was adapted
to all that for many years so your
body's like whoa this is different too
so it can feel uncomfortable both
mentally and physically but here's the
key you're sick you haven't been well
for a while now you got symptoms
conditions you've been seeing lots of
doctors you're burnt out you tried so
many things you've been there you done
that so you're desperate you know you
have to push forward you know you have
to try something new your body doesn't
feel good because it's used to what you
used to do your Consciousness doesn't
feel good because that's used to what
you used to do and you already don't
feel good cuz you're sick you got all
these symptoms you don't know if you're
coming or going you don't know if it's a
food that did that one day or you don't
know if it's actually a new symptom you
don't know what your doctor said it
might be these things and your friend
said it might be this and you're
thinking like what is wrong with me was
it something I ate a couple days ago is
it something I'm doing wrong wait a
minute that symptom feels the same as it
always was hey that's a symptom I had
two years ago I think when I journaled
it I don't know I'm losing my mind do
you remember the thing we talked about
earlier the stomach stretching and the
stomach
shrinking well that's a part of all of
this it's the part when you're gravit
ating to a new type of eating a way you
really never ate before in your life
much different than the small condensed
high fat high calorie meals you were
used to all these years or the large
condensed high fat high calorie meals
you've been used to all these years some
people eat a lot more of that some
people eat a lot less of that the people
who are eating less of that their
stomachs shrinking they live their life
with their stomach really shrunk small
and then there's people who eat a lot of
that they're walking around with their
stomachs expanded stretched every day
either way they're both eating
relatively the same kind of food so
let's start with the person who has a
stomach that's shrunk all these years
they walk around with a shrunk stomach
did you ever run across a person who had
a banana one big banana they couldn't
even get the whole thing down they
peeled it they're eating it they're
moving through the banana and they all
of a sudden have a look on them like oh
my God this is just so much they get
down to the bottom of the banana and
they ate it and they're like that was a
lot do you want me to eat another one
are you crazy I can't eat two of those
big bananas now if you chopped up that
banana or sliced it up or sliced up two
bananas and put it on a plate lined it
up all against each other it's going to
be roughly around the same amount of
food as a chicken breast it's not going
to be the same amount for a lot of
reasons but it can look the same volume
maybe even more and so what happens is
someone who has a shrunk stomach is used
to a small chicken breast and that's
what they're used to they're not used to
a watery banana cuz a banana has water
in it it's got pulp fiber yes it's got
protein in it yes it's got a little bit
of fat in there but it's protein fiber
water SU suar and it's volumous so
someone with a Shunk stomach be like oh
my God it was hard to eat two whole
bananas that was really hard I just want
my chicken breast with a little cheese
on top well that chicken breast with a
little cheese on top or a sauce that's
fatty and oily is really dense really
dense in caloric action too now there's
fat in there there's calories too but
there's fat you got the protein but it's
dense in the stomach and it feels like
it's a weight so when you eat it it's
all you need to someone who's got a
shrunk stomach who's been eating like
that all these years then when they peel
a big old banana bag and they're eating
it it's hard for them to get down to the
end of that banana God forbid they have
two or three bananas never mind a
smoothie with three bananas wild
blueberries oranges maybe some leafy
Greens in there the person with the
shrunk stomach the small stomach from
all these years of eating small
condensed meals is going to think that's
a large amount of food so if it was a
smoothie with all that in there it would
be too much they would only be able to
have half a glass of that smoothie or a
glass of that smoothie at best and they
would nurse it it's just way too much
food instead of a hardboiled egg
something they are used to a lot of
people that have this the shrunken
stomach where it's small and shrunk all
these years they're used to like a
poached egg a hard boiled egg a fried
egg with a little piece of toast a
couple of strips of bacon on the side
maybe a cup of coffee maybe a little
chocolate treat later or they'll eat
small little meals throughout the day of
treats and things they like until they
have their dinner which is a small
chicken breast again or a small 4 o
piece of meat and here's the problem the
banana is not going to have enough
calories to match that slice of toast
believe it or not the poached egg the
two strips of bacon they a little
chocolate treat the banana won't equal
that two bananas won't equal that the
calories that they're used to are fat
they're dense and then they sprinkle
about little treats with sugar like the
bad sugar in it throughout the day so
they're getting their little sugar highs
they're getting their adrenal and
caffeine high while they're doing their
dense little meals and having little
treats in and around it but they're not
eating a large amount of food or they're
not eating larger amounts of food their
stomach is shrunk their stomach is small
they eat one banana it's not enough to
get them by but yet the banana is too
filling it's taking up too much space
two bananas Three Bananas taking up too
much space a whole smoothie is too much
for them to drink in the morning they're
used to a hardboiled egg two strips of
bacon little piece of toast they don't
even finish it all they have a cup of
coffee they have a treat somewhere in
the middle of it all they'll have a
treat in the middle of the day they'll
have sugar and another cup of coffee
later to get some calories but they're
not having a large amount of food at
once so you have a smoothie it has less
calories but it's the foods you need to
heal here they are they're sick and they
need to move to these fresh Fresh Living
juicy
fruits and they can't get there the
thing is is that smoothie could be more
food than they've eaten in a whole day
not more calories than they've eaten in
a whole day just the volume a big old
smoothie of all that liquid in there the
juice in there the pulp the fiber and
they're not used to that and that could
be more food and that smoothie than
anything else they've done in a whole
day now we're not even talking about the
salad now what about a big salad people
have small salads and they have small
salads with dense things in there
they'll have feta cheese they'll have
tuna in their salad they'll have salmon
in their salad that's really popular
hardboiled eggs in their salad ham in
their salad cheese hard chees is in
their salad croutons will be throwing in
there a few of them maybe but the salad
isn't a lot of greens like lots and lots
of greens in their salad so what if we
have to do that now we have to get a
salad and then we have to have things on
there that adds into it too it's a lot
of food what they usually do is they'll
have this little salad with all these
dense things on top like the egg and the
ham and the tuna and the salmon also
added oil so they'll have oil on top of
that dense small salad a fatty dressing
once again really dense
small portion their stomach is still
shrunk their stomach's small and the
Smoothie is already beats out anything
they've had all day as far as size and
then the salad properly done where you
have lots of lettuce a decent Siz bowl
of spinach three or four
tomatoes cucumber steamed brussel
sprouts steamed potatoes steamed red
potatoes steamed sweet potatoes steamed
asparagus or raw asparagus chopped up
and thrown on top raw onion on there
squeeze of lemon orange juice squeezed
on top of the salad all of this way too
much and if they only ate a little bit
of this meal a little bit of that salad
with all those fixings on it and just a
little bit they would be starving it
wasn't going to meet the caloric nature
of the dense caloric Foods the small
caloric dense fatty meals that they eat
and what they're used to eating their
whole life so they'll need to eat more
of the salad they'll have to learn how
to stretch their stomach even if it's
just a little bit so they could have
more of these Healing Foods now even if
it was just a salad that had tomato and
cucumber on it it would definitely not
be enough calories for them they would
be starving they would be looking for
sugar somewhere they'd be going to their
famous treats that they usually do and
this is why I like the avocado it's a
transition food it's a great food to
transition somebody who has a shrunk
stomach from eating dense small meals
their whole life but yet needing foods
that are juicy and vital to heal but
can't quite make that transition the
avocado is a great way to do that so
they have their small salad and then we
put an avocado on that salad avocado has
that dense nature and if you do have a
little bit of steamed vegetable or
steamed potato or steamed sweet potato
the combination of a little bit of that
steamed potato and the avocado and
anything else that's in there with the
lettuce becomes much more denser because
you have that fat slick on that salad
something there so ingrained that
they've known about in their diet system
their whole life having that dense fat
or that oily dressing or that cheesy
topping you treat the avocado as if it
was an egg that's how you get by that's
how you use it as that transition for
them it feels like it was almost like an
egg or something it was almost like
something dense and fatty as you're
working on making your salads bigger
more leafy greens more Tomatoes more
cucumbers or a bigger smoothie in the
morning or more fruits or just a half a
papaya and eating the whole thing or one
or two big mangoes you work on getting
that volume in you that's filling up
your stomach stretching the stomach a
little bit and gently it may not feel
comfortable you may be confused at first
but it's allowing more calories of the
healing foods so they don't run scared
run hungry think they intuitive Natures
off thinking they're not doing balance
or moderation right and then running
into a snag finding some Trend out there
going in opposite direction never
healing and getting stuck this is where
the details matter because I've seen
people out there they were sick and they
had to find a way to heal and then when
you taught them about hey here's the
smoothies here's the bananas here's the
steamed potatoes here's the leafy greens
here's the wild Foods here's the Frozen
wild blueberries next thing you know it
you get a call from them and they'll be
like I can't do this I'm starving to
death I need protein fast I'm going to
my keto doctor immediately I I just
can't do this anymore and you're like
wait a minute wait a minute wait wait
what did you eat yesterday I had a half
a mango in the morning um in the middle
of the day I had a salad and I can't do
this it's just too much like wait how
many bananas did you have none yesterday
I had a banana 3 days ago though it's
like that's not enough not enough
calories it's like well it's seemed like
enough when I ate it and I just can't do
this I have to have my chicken and I
have to have my other stuff and my eggs
and I have to have my cheese I can't do
this anymore and I'm like wait a minute
we have to have more calories you got to
put more banana in you in the morning
more papaya in you get the smoothie and
you maybe your salad can have some
avocado on it let's do a whole avocado
and even that
they'll be like a whole avocado a whole
one okay that's kind of a lot and what
they don't realize is that even if they
went back to their small dense meals
with their stomach being shrunk and
their small intense high fat high
calorie little meals they'd still be
looking for all their sugary treats all
day long in between their pieces of
chocolate and their sugar and their tea
and any kind of other treats and snacks
maybe small amounts of it but they would
still be looking for those little bits
of sugar high in and out of it so either
way they need their calories somewhere
and so we have to find them in good
places like the steamed potato and the
fruit and the winter squash but we have
to stretch the stomach a little bit more
than what they're used to now don't get
confused when I say stretch the stomach
you might think why do I want to look
bloated why is this guy trying to
stretch my stomach I I don't want to
like have a stomach sticking out it
doesn't work like that doesn't mean just
because you're stretching your stomach a
little bit internally it doesn't mean
your abdomen is going to be sticking out
and reaching out not at all it'll just
look the same it'll be the same flat
stomach if you have a flat stomach now
if you don't have a flat stomach you
already got bloating that's a different
story you're already bloating stretching
your stomach has nothing to do with you
bloating more or bloating less if you're
bloating that's another problem that's
other issues that's already happening
and that's going to be there and if
you're already bloating you already have
all kinds of other things like low HCL
low hydrochloric acid which is why what
you're doing with your diet is so
helpful because this takes you to a
place to eventually fix and correct that
problem but a lot of people are bloating
because they have strepto coctus
bacteria inside their gut they got
ammonia they got putrifying proteins
from years and years of food they've
eaten that didn't digest well they got
liver problems stagnant sluggish fatty
livers they're bloating for a whole
bunch of other reasons and stretching
your stomach a little bit to get some
Healing Foods in to fix everything isn't
what's creating that bloating now let's
talk about the opposite side of the
spectrum an expanded stretched stomach
now we're we're not talking anymore
about a shrunken stomach from small
condensed meals and the stomach shrinks
and gets small we're talking about a
stomach that gets big talking about an
expanded and stretched stomach this is
from somebody eating larger portions and
it doesn't have to even be that much
larger but larger portions of the same
condensed meals instead of one drumstick
they want two drumsticks every night
they want four drumsticks they want four
four drumsticks and two chicken wings or
instead of two slices of pizza they want
half of a large pizza instead of two
slices of a medium pizza or say it's
somebody that wants a macaroni and
cheese but not just a bowl of macaroni
and cheese they go in for their second
bowl and their third bowl and their
fourth Bowl because they want a big bowl
of macaroni and cheese and so that's how
they do it or maybe a big bowl of pasta
instead of a small bowl of pasta or when
they make scrambled eggs they don't do
two scrambled eggs or one scrambled egg
they do six scrambled eggs you know and
so what they're used to are large dense
portions of the same foods and then they
still need their treats and their sugary
treats and their chocolate and maybe
they need a lot of food because they've
had a hard time feeling satiated
something in their mind meaning wasn't
connecting to something physically in
their brain they needed more calories
they needed more glucose they needed
more calories because they're going
through some hard times they're
struggling they're under stress their
adrenals are running they had a hardship
they had a loss maybe they're being
abused maybe they were betrayed and the
need for more fuel came in or they're
working so hard or they have a little
bit of insulin resistance they're not
getting enough glucose to the brain so
they're just requiring more but either
way their stomach is stretched they're
used to eating larger condensed meals
condensed fats but larger
portions and they're even gaining weight
and they don't even have to gain weight
maybe it's somebody that didn't gain
weight but they're still eating this way
and then there's somebody who gained a
lot of weight and they're eating this
way I know people that eat larger
portions of condensed Foods they've been
raised is to eat and eatting their whole
life but they eat larger portions
because they're up against so much
stress hardship or losses or they've had
a hard time in their life they're under
stress and they're taking care of a
bunch of people they're working really
hard maybe they have two or three jobs
they're not sleeping much at night
they're working a lot of hours a day
sometimes seven days a week so they
require more and there's people that
aren't working that hard don't have a
really hard time but they're requiring
more too because they need it for fuel
for their brain because they have other
issues their brain has other problems so
it's not like someone wants to eat large
portions they may be eating larger
portions because of other issues and
it's what they've adapted to in order to
survive and let's just say this person
gets sick the person who's eaten larger
portions their whole life and they have
a stretched stomach or even just a
little bit more stretched stomach than
someone with a shrunken stomach and they
get sick and they need to find healing
and you give them a salad with a
cucumber and a tomato on it and a slice
of potato or something or you give them
a smoothie and it's just two bananas and
some wild blueberries they're going to
look at it and be like well I might need
more than this they're not going to do
the opposite of the other person who
said oh this is way too much I can't eat
a whole banana a lot of people who have
stress stretched stomachs get derailed
when they're eating Healing Foods when
they're trying to bring in these healing
techniques and healing Tools in food and
they derail because it's not enough for
them so you have to be like look you
need to eat more calories you need to
eat more because you used to eat these
dense meals but these larger dense meals
and your stomach stretched so you have
to make sure we do more we do a few
bananas in your smoothie with your water
blueberries have some apples later on in
the morning or you might have to bring
in more steamed potatoes not just one
little steamed potato and that happens
to a lot of people where they just start
with this little steamed potato they're
used to eating more larger portions of
dense cooked meals with lots of fat in
them but when you say hey look have
steamed potato you take a look and they
just put a little tiny steamed potato
they chopped it up they threw it in
their salad and they're like oh my God I
was okay for a little while and then I
got really hungry because they needed
two or three potatoes or four steamed
potatoes is what they needed now steamed
potato if anybody needs to know right
now it's a healing tool it's a healing
food I talk about it all the time so
it's not that we're against animal
protein in the moment it's not one of
those shows where no animal protein or
know this and know that we're talking
about healing cleansing healing Foods a
steamed potato is a very healing food
there's no fat there's no overt fat
right there so you don't have to worry
about all this fat inside of it so in
order to heal a lot of people need to
lower their animal fat consumption just
like vegans need to lower their nut fat
consumptions and oil fat consumptions in
order to heal as well so it's all in
that field what's hard with somebody
with a stretched stomach is that they're
used to those larger amounts of calories
the chloric action the dense fats so
when you dial it back you have this
other food now it's not as high in
calories it's not as dense in fat so
then we have to eat a little bit more of
these foods which could leave them
feeling unsatiated like hungry so they
go to bed a little bit more hungry than
usual and they're not used to that it's
foreign to them they were on 10,000
calories a day now they're on 3,000
calories a day and they're confused or
they were on 5,000 calories a day and
now they're on 3,000 calories a day or
2,000 calories a day depending on how
sick they are what's really wrong with
them too so that's another thing to
equate into this but usually there's
people they don't know it but even
though packages and calorie counts are
certain ways if you look online or
anything they're not not accurate so
none of those calorie counts are
accurate when it comes down to dense
caloric or dense fat foods people don't
realize nuts are more calories and more
dense in fat than people really know so
how many grams of fat or how many grams
of whatever people don't realize that
there's more to it than that and it's
not quite correct some people walk
around eating 10,000 calories a day
8,000 calories a day but don't know they
met that level in the health World alter
native Health world it's one siiz
fits-all if you haven't noticed out
there here's a prime example of how it's
one siiz fits-all when you look at
chicken and you say well how many
calories are in 2 ounces of chicken how
much fats in 2 ounces of chicken and you
look it up they're just looking at 2
ounces of chicken but they're not
looking at 2 oz of whose chicken what
chicken right the conventional world an
alternative World they work together I
don't know if you noticed it either
they're both embed together it's all one
size fits all here's the example a
chicken in one Farm could be raised
entirely different and have a much
higher fat content much higher calorie
content a chicken in another Farm could
be really lean could even be lean and
mean lower fat lower calorie but no
one's ever looking at this they just
look at the rec book how it's
institutionalized for alternative
medicine believe it or not where you go
and you look fact check oh 2 ounces of
chicken equals this and this and this
but that's not reality people walk
around eating a lot of calories and a
lot of fat they don't even realize
they're eating that's why you can be
tanking down 6 7,000 calories a day
8,000 calories a day and not even know
because theck chicken you could be
eating from the Farms you're going to
eat them at could be really really high
in fat same goes for any food that's how
strange it is fish same thing eggs same
thing cheese same thing no one has the
right number so if we're all about like
it's got to be science it's got to be
scientific even a study so that means if
a study itself is doing something where
they're
studying like the amount of fuel a mouse
needs they're not even equating to what
the mouse is even eating like the
science is never straightforward it's
never really factually right it's not
it's because we go by the one size fits
all world it's never exact so when a
bodybuilder or exercise buff or trainer
is counting calories counting macros and
they're really trying trying to keep
track and they're portion controlling
and they're counting everything they're
not even counting anything right because
they're using the one siiz fits all
ruler the one that says here's exactly
how many calories are in a banana but
there's different bananas from different
Farms from different regions that have
entirely different things in them and
then there's different chickens from
different places around the country and
around the world there's different pork
there's different lamb there's different
beef there's different eggs there's
different cheese there's cheese that's
very thin it's got less fat in it more
sugar in it and there's cheese that's
all fat but they're not counting any of
that and all those things matter greatly
how was the cow fed there's grass
growing in regions that have less
protein in it there's grass that grows
in regions of the world that have less
fat in it traces of fat yes that are in
grass and so cow are eating differently
their meats designed differently so when
we do the one size fits all thing it's
completely distorted in all wrong so
nobody knows really how many calories
they're even eating which leads to a
problem because they could be eating
more calories more fats than they ever
even knew they think they're counting
their proteins fats and carbs they think
they're doing their macros right they're
counting their macros right but they're
not they're totally Off the Mark you're
Flying Blind this is one of thousands of
mistakes made in the health world if
you're starting anything healing doing
healing tools healing foods you don't
have to do it all at once you don't have
to do the whole thing throw the kitchen
sink in there all together get do baby
steps incorporate one thing at a time
little bit at a time take one day at a
time be easy on yourself you don't have
to think oh my God I got to stretch my
stomach no don't have to even think
about it but you got to think about this
though what you're feeling as you're
doing it got to be easy on yourself
there because a lot of people they're so
inflamed in their intestinal tract their
Vegas nerves are hypers sensitive not
just their Vegas nerves but little tiny
nerve endings come off their Vegas
nerves going to the intestinal tract
lining so that when food's moving
through your intestinal tract through
your gut you're feeling it you're
feeling it massage the walls of your
intestinal tract which could kind of
feel uncomfortable if you're somebody
that's highly inflamed so then you're
like oh wait my food's not digesting
that banana I ate isn't
digesting um that salad I ate isn't
digesting and so you kind of get nervous
you don't know if it's working because
you might be somebody that's used to
bread and butter bread and butter just
kind of moves through you like a sticky
gummy glue doesn't massage anything you
might be somebody that's used to eggs
eggs kind of liquidy into a weird liquid
paste that sits in the middle in the
intestinal tract and doesn't touch the
walls of the intestinal tract it doesn't
massage if you have a banana banana
moves through and gently
massages because it's working on healing
the gut so you might feel a banana move
through you a lot of people they'll eat
some papaya and then be like huh you
know I can kind of feel something
different I have a different feeling
inside of me and they're confused at
that different feeling and it might not
even be uncomfortable at all it just
might kind of make you aware and when it
makes you aware you might get scared
because you're changing your diet you're
eating different foods the foods are
actually touching things inside of you
massaging things they fiber everything
the pulp all of it and healing foods do
things inside of us that help us and we
end up feeling that they're cleaning the
mess up so these foods are cleaning
things up they're cleaning all the junk
in us too they're loosening up pockets
of bacteria they're moving around
deposits that were stuck on the walls of
the intestinal tract and colon that are
putrified and rancid and hardened and
clung to the walls of the intestinal
tract these healing foods are waking
things up moving and shifting things
feeding the nerves that attach to the
intestinal tract Linings while all this
is happening healing is happening inside
the body and it might be scary it might
be like what's going on I'm kind of
getting aware of this this is a
different feeling I feel what is this
then you might get scared you might be
like huh I can't tell meanwhile to
toxification cleansing healing purging
of the liver is happening see all these
things are going on and we can sense
them we could feel them and it can make
people go the opposite direction
sometimes because they're used to being
inflamed and sick but not feeling the
food move through them instead they're
used to just being bloated sick maybe
crampy and constipation maybe IBS and
other problems but they're not used to
feeling their food so much this is New
Sensations that happen when you do it
right when you do it right when you know
how to use these foods to cleanse when
you know how to use these foods to heal
and you understand your stomach how to
protect your stomach and then when you
bring in celery juice and you can baby
step that you can start small and not
have to go to 16 ounces on an empty
stomach or 32 ounces on an empty stomach
yet but when you bring in the tools like
the lemon water and the celery juice and
the smoothies and the heavy metal detox
smoothie and you bring in your leafy
greens and you bring in your steamed
asparagus and steamed brussel sprouts
and steamed potatoes and your wild foods
and your herbs and you bring it in baby
stepping in something changes you end up
moving forward and you discover and
unlock the healing process in you and
your consciousness the
Consciousness that adapted all these
years to what you used to eat all those
years ago starts to change and the
emotional centers of your brain connect
to the new
consciousness of your body
healing and it's the most powerful thing
you could ever
do our
Consciousness is not who we
are because our Consciousness can be
become something else something we don't
want to be our Consciousness is
powerful but it's not something that
defines us to exactly who we're ever
going to be because we can use our
Consciousness to change and
grow if someone is living their life and
they make mistakes along the way through
hardships and hard times and they make
decisions that they believe was not a
good thing they have to be easy on
themselves because our Consciousness in
that moment was only doing the best it
could with the capacity of what it's
learned throughout the years but we can
turn to another Direction and our
Consciousness can grow it can become
something different it can help us make
decisions that's right for our body
right for our needs and then it becomes
our best friend our best ally not our
enemy seeds become planted within our
Consciousness seeds of things that
aren't good for us seeds of things that
don't make us better they take us down
along the way we get told all the time
what's good for us what we should do
what feels good listen to your body
and do the things that are trendy out
there the trend train doesn't care about
really what's going on inside someone
it's all about making somebody else's
Consciousness happy in a different way
but we can take control of our own
Consciousness and we can lead it into a
direction of safety and well-being for
what we truly need instead of our
Consciousness filled with noise and busy
work words controlling us we can retach
and Infuse knowledge and wisdom into our
Consciousness and support the
supernatural resource so it becomes a
star that lights the
way