how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about
intermittent fasting have you ever heard
the expression what goes up must come
down well intermittent fasting is kind
of like what goes up up up come comes
crashing down years later it's so sad
when a new trend comes to town and takes
everybody down and then takes him
straight to eating disorder town a lot
can go wrong and it often does the
damage is done and it shows up long
after the health crime it wasn't what it
seemed to be all this time the science
applied is flawed at best the results
looked clear but not after a few years
get ready strap yourself in this is
going to be a bumpy
ride hey you come here too really
awesome I haven't seen you here yeah I
get my coffee here all the time yeah you
noticed I know I'm doing the
intermittent fasting thing totally you
see my gut it's down I know the bloating
is down you look good too man you're
doing it really how long you been doing
it few months incredible what what what
did you have for dinner last night sorry
you had pizza oh hold on on the line's
moving
up okay yeah the pizza yeah that's
that's cool I had a burger last night
yeah it was great I had it at 9:00 last
night you had it at 6:00 last night
that's awesome you know everybody's
doing it a little different uh-huh I had
a big salad the other
night yeah and then after the salad I
had a burger too
well okay hold on I got to order hey yes
can I ma'am hi can I have a black coffee
with a shot of espresso in there awesome
and I need uh I need to get a double
shot of espresso on Ice to go that would
be awesome okay thanks yeah I know I do
espresso all the time oh man it gets me
through the day do you do you do you
remember like when you get that dragging
moment cuz that's what I get you get it
too like in the middle of the day I'm
dragging and then all of a sudden the
next coffee I do like the espresso I'm
taking with me I bring that in and I'm
back to square
one I know I know somewhere around 4:00
it get a little
jittery but every now and then I cheat
and I bite on a piece of chocolate and I
Know It kind of ruins it but it doesn't
yeah I know all right listen okay thank
you all right I'll catch you around all
right bye what kind of intermittent
faster are you do you wait till 12:00 no
right two that's more like it maybe
you're like one of those 3:00 in the
afternoon and it hits you and you're
like all right I gone far enough maybe
you're a
4:00 maybe you're like 6 maybe you're 8
to 4 68 who do we appreciate the
caffeine right that's what we really
appreciate is the caffeine
because without
it the crazy thing with the caffeine
part with
it same thing but it's just another day
what happens is we get that high we get
that high and by the end of the day
we're coming down we're coming down and
then we got to Gorge we got to eat what
do you like to eat oh you're a healthy
one right you're a healthy person you're
doing like the salad and the protein and
lean protein and the vegetable and you
got it all together at night when you're
doing it friend of mine it's like all
Pizza Man the end of the day he's like I
waited for this I earned the right for
this pizza man then he just gobbles the
whole thing down but everybody's got a
Different Twist you know some people
like to eat differently at the end of
the day some people do like more like
4:00 then they'll do it again at like 7
but they went till 4:00 without eating
and that's a feat waiting to 4:00 when
you think about it one of of the things
that's a head scratcher for me this is a
big one right here it was a guy thing to
start is kind of funny right
intermittent fasting wasn't a girl's
thing it was a dude's thing you know
dudes that never had a health problem
dudes that never been sick dudes that
don't know what it's like to have
chronic illness you know like aches and
pains and fatigue and blurriness and
dizziness and all kinds of different
problems just wanted to get like more in
shape in the fact of like losing their
belly a little bit the intermittent
fasting thing didn't start with women
who are chronically sick because let's
face it if a woman's really sick and
they don't eat until 6: at night not
only are their adrenals going to go down
for the count their blood sugar is going
to drop they're not going to be able to
function they're not going to be able to
walk they won't be able to drive they
won't get glucose to the brain blood
sugar to the brain they'll just be shot
so it started out like with a dude that
wasn't sick so it's like a dude thing
and the crazy thing is when these things
keep on getting out of hand in the
trendy world all of a sudden everybody's
doing it and then no one's keeping track
of the downfall The Fallout the
casualties no one's watching any of that
no one's seeing someone who shouldn't be
doing that does it and they get hurt
right and that's just the obvious direct
hurt that comes across right at the
beginning of somebody doing it when
they're not well I'm not talking about
someone who's healthy enough strong
enough can work out they do it for one
year two year three year four year and
then all of a sudden their hair's all
falling out and all of a sudden they got
fatigue that's
unexplainable and all of a sudden
they're getting waking when they're
sitting there eating hardly anything
everything just starts falling apart
that's Fallout that comes years l later
for a healthy woman right that
intermittent fast you don't think it's
happening
oh I see it all the time out there and
so do a lot of doctors I talk to so do a
lot of people I talk to it's out there
it's happening but remember it started
out with like healthy dudes like strong
dudes that decided to stop eating bacon
and eggs and sausage in the morning
they're like you know what I'm kind of
done with the six eggs in the morning
and the sausage and the bacon and and
you know I tried not to do the toast
anymore I got rid of that and I just
started doing my protein breakfast which
was the egg two slices of ham around it
or sausage and egg Patty with no bread
but eventually it was a dude thing where
was like no I'm just not going to eat
this heavy meal in the morning and I'm
just going to fast and it kind of got my
tummy down so it was a guy thing all
along and now you got women who haven't
been sick yet writing books doing things
doing podcasts teaching other women to
do it but no one's saying you can do it
for a little while because you'll
probably get away with it if you do it
you're going to be sick down the road
and if you do it you're going down for
the count that month no one's monitoring
any of that no one's looking at any of
that because remember it's one siiz fits
all out there every time it's one siiz
fits all intermittent fasting one siiz
fits all no one's looking at all the
subtleties and how everybody's different
it's always one siiz fits-all in all the
Alternative Health world it's painful
but true that's getting you upset I'm
sorry but it's the truth I want to ask
you something is there any moms
listening right now um would you let
your daughter not eat the whole entire
day until 600 or 8:00 at night on
espresso all day long not eating
anything would that be a smart idea cuz
I'm scratching my head over here would
you let your son do the same thing n e
the whole entire day hey Michael um
don't bring that lunch to school and do
not buy lunch at school make sure you
just avoid food all together can you get
a Starbucks coffee yes get a bunch of
them just drink it all day and Mommy's
going to make you dinner tonight uh
we're going to eat about 10:00 at night
okay all right see you have fun at
school or what about your 5-year-old
right it's like Madison put that piece
of toast down no put it down down do not
have that egg no do not have those
grapes put it down you're not going to
eat till about 2 o' today yes
Madison I'm going to put some coffee in
your
lunchbox and tell the teacher it's not
coffee just tell the teacher it's
something else
and yes and then at 2 o' you can have
something to eat okay so stop Madison
put that piece of toast down I don't
know that sounded kind of bad to me I
don't know how that sounded to you guys
it's like shouldn't we be teaching our
children like what we do should be good
for our children right because they're
learning from us yeah I mean that's what
they're doing it's like um yeah Mommy is
not going to eat
yes um why um mommy doesn't want to eat
mommy's on a new diet yes Mommy is on a
program um mommy's not going to eat
lunch yeah mommy's not going to eat
dinner either uh maybe like at 9:00 at
night Mommy's going to eat oh you want
to do that oh no no you don't want to do
that Britney no um Britney no you have
to eat today yeah don't
I I know I know you're watching mommy's
is crazy yeah you know how Mommy's crazy
she just does these different diets and
stuff like that yeah no I want you
Britney you should eat today yeah that's
actually really important because you
know how your blood sugar gets a little
kind of crazy and your blood sugar's
like off and remember when you were like
faint in gym class no you have to eat
something okay yeah I know you want to
do what Mommy wants to do I get it but
yeah but mommy has to do this this is
what she has to do for herself okay or
how about if you're taking your child to
the doctor so you're taking your child
to the doctor and the doctor
says uh Mrs Cooper we're going to do
interment fasting for your daughter
she's getting some weight so she's
gaining weight and we want her to start
eating at 6 every day so we like this
organic coffee let's make sure that your
daughter's using this organic coffee all
day long and she doesn't eat because
we're going to do the intermittent
fasting the expert way and she can eat
anything she ever wanted at night I
don't care what it is ice cream Mrs
Cooper um macaroni and cheese pizza do
you like pizza Daphne do you like pizza
she okay great pizza's perfect uh dapan
you like pizza perfect pizza party every
night Mrs Cooper at your house but she's
not allowed to eat the entire day but
she has to drink some coffee and you can
teach her how to drink coffee you and
your husband drink coffee every single
day so this is the new program we're
kind of doing here so I think it would
be a great idea we get her on CU she's
she's she's gaining a little weight we
want to lose that weight you know what's
weird I'm
detecting eating disorder oh my God like
when I think about it I'm like starting
to have visions of Eating Disorders all
through my head is it just me am I just
being crazy or something but I'm like
I'm smelling an eating disorder like I'm
seeing an eating disorder more than
that this is like eating disorder land
when you think about it right now I'm
just thinking about it now just by doing
this and talking to you
guys I feel like I've developed an
eating disorder just from this alone all
right let's be honest we're talking like
that can create a serious eating
disorder right all right you don't
believe me okay do you know how many
people were taken away locked up taken
away in a Patty wagon because they
didn't want to eat do you know how many
teenage girls were locked up taken away
given ECT because of it do you know how
many people were hurt throughout the
years and years and years unfairly
terribly unfairly in an evil way
actually but not eating all day long
would warrant an instant label of an
eating disorder a mental condition for a
young person the parents be freaking out
the mom would be just in total disarray
it would uproot an entire family
Calamity would ensue they would take
kids away they'd be seeing counselors
after counselors after counselors if
your teenager daughter teenager son
wouldn't eat and wanted to do this kind
of thing but because now it's fake
science approved and it's the trend and
people are doing it it's all of a sudden
accept it oh my god when I think about
it how many kids were taken away from
their families families destroyed
children's lives ruined when I think
about that custody losses of children
all of that because you know they
weren't eating which is terrible because
they shouldn't have been taken away so
many of these families destroyed so many
problems it's not easy in the eating
disorder World a lot of tragedies happen
in different ways but how much how many
drugs and medications that children were
put on teenagers were put on like
dangerous
drugs because they had an eing disorder
and then when I think about like
intermittent fasting is everywhere it's
everywhere it's on every magazine it's
all over the Internet of course doctors
are preaching and teaching about it
every day right you see it everywhere
books out this out influencers doing it
all the time it's flooded the entire
system podcasts there's all these
podcasts about it all on its own when
you think about that all the young
people are seeing this
everywhere they're seeing it on social
media they're seeing it on the internet
they're seeing it on TV they're seeing
it in movies it's just all over the
place it's perfectly fine it's just
intermittent fasting oh it must be solid
with science everything must be perfect
with it yeah no just don't eat as long
as you don't eat and don't eat just
don't eat that's the message see what I
mean it's you can't go it's not like eat
it's don't eat don't eat don't eat and
whoa no you're a loser you broke your
intermittent fast at 1:00 you better try
harder you get kind of mental about it
what about the OCD based around it I
mean think about that you start getting
into this whole pattern of you start
hating on yourself how do I know I've
seen it out there young people hating
their own guts hating themselves
thinking they're crap because they broke
their intermittent fasting day at 1:00
or at 2:00 in the afternoon or at 12:00
and they gobbled something down because
no one's really teaching them it's not
the best thing to do there's other ways
to do it and they end up gobbling
something down at 2:00 and they feel
like failures and then they go into a
depression but no one's talking about
this it's like we're always worried
about our children not eating we're
always worried about eating disorders
there's a history of that out there so
let's just create a billion more Eating
Disorders but make it seem like it's an
okay thing it's perfectly fine to do
everybody's doing it it's science
suggested or there's experts everywhere
there's dudes there's women they're
experts now at it they're teaching about
it health coaches nutritionists oh why
don't you try intermittent fasting maybe
your son can try intermittent fasting
too maybe both of you guys can do it oh
what's the best way to do it make sure
you're doing caffeine all day and don't
eat
anything it sounds insane because it is
and we get numb that's how it works here
you get numb to punishment you get numb
to stupid things that are happening you
get numb you just get used to it like
you don't know it's happening anymore
you just become with it part of it you
just let it happen you it just you coast
along with it no one sees it no one sees
anything wrong in it no one thinks of it
as anything it just naturally evolves
into
something
spooky and evil but it doesn't matter
because you can't see it cuz you're
blind you got eyes but you can't see and
it's just you just go along with it and
then everybody goes along with it and it
never
stops and then just stick a name like
science on it somehow like license it
license it by giving it the science okay
because there was some kind of BS study
that wasn't a study that monitored five
people for a certain amount of time but
then never monitored them at all in the
future to what happened to them to what
they're doing now to maybe how things
have gone wrong and everything else and
I notice they're always monitoring
somebody who has no illness or no
serious illness like neurological
illness like Tremors and Shakes
severe fatigue brain fog blurry vision
like all of it combined tingles numbness
on the body weakness of the limbs all
kinds of different body pain everywhere
jaw pain neck pain all of this severe
insomnia they don't use any of those
people because if you starve those
people they're going down their body
won't be able to handle it you know
we're talking about people that are
bedridden too let's add that in say
somebody's bedridden or spends a lot of
time on mattress Island you take
somebody on mattress Island who's
struggling even a young person on
mattress Island who struggling and they
only have a few good hours a day where
they can kind of function enough the
rest is they have to just rest and you
take all their food away till 6:00 or 7
at night and they give them a big old
sloppy greasy fat meal afterwards
they're going to get really sick
adrenals are going to be gone nervous
system is going to be gone they're just
gonna have it much harder but they're
not using those people if it was so
great if intermittent fasting was so
great you guys wouldn't it get the real
sick better it doesn't get the real sick
better but it's for the not sick or
someone who's got like A1C is up there
or they got like maybe type 2 diabetes
pre-diabetes right they're not really
sick they just need to back off those
big fatty meals in the morning which
we're going to go into detail but in the
end it doesn't make them better better
down the road or maybe they're not sick
but they got some weight on them or they
not only have some weight on them the
cholesterols up a little bit but they
can go and go and go they're not
bedridden they're not on mattress island
with mysterious chronic illness
neurological conditions they're not
suffering or struggling they're not
dealing with severe fatigue they're
living their life they're healthy except
they got some stuff going on but they're
basically healthy they just been living
off the lamb you know eating too much in
the morning all these years sausage
bacon eggs you know fast food
restaurants greasy fried food in the
morning you know egg sandwiches every
single morning or just something heavy
in the morning like lots of fat in the
morning butter like butter heart attack
butter and they're bloated they've been
eating a big breakfast every day for
many years or eating a big greasy lunch
all these years they have a doughnut in
the morning a cookie in the morning a
coffee and then at lunchtime they have
some greasy thing or some fast food or a
meat sandwich or a deli sandwich it just
catches up to you after a while and I
noticed that these intermittent fasters
they always start a vigorous exercise
program at the same time as they cut out
all that heavy grease in the morning but
take somebody who's chronically ill
who's on mattress Island even a young
person they can't exercise hardly anyway
they're really sick you take their food
away they're going to
suffer they're going to suffer greatly
and sure someone who's on mattress
Island shouldn't be on eggs and bacon in
the morning and grease and have greasy
fatty meals during the day and pizza for
lunch of course not but the point is his
intermittent fasting World believes any
food in the morning any kind healthy or
not including fruit makes it so you're
not intermittent fasting so the messages
don't even do a healthy meal in the
morning so that person who's on mattress
Island and that young person who's
really sick gets the message whoa I'm
not supposed to eat anything I just
can't eat anything and everybody seems
to be getting so much better on the
intermittent fasting so I better try
this because that 42-year-old dude that
never had a problem who can exercise in
the gym all day and drink all the coffee
wants he's doing it and he seems to be
an expert cuz look at his little
magazine article or his interview on a
podcast and no one's accounting for
really what's going on because remember
it's one size fits all inter fasting is
a hack that's why it's for a dude that
never was really that sick who finally
cleans up his diet and decides exercise
or a woman who cleans up her diet never
had any real health problems
you know can handle like 90° heat no
problem can go part of the day without
eating no problem at all drinks whatever
they want drinks alcohol at night
exercises when they want and decides to
clean up their act like I want to live a
healthier life I'm gaining a couple of
pounds and I'm getting a little bloated
you go on the hack the intermittent
fasting hack where you starve yourself
drink coffee have a meal at night whoa
floating going down a little a bit hey I
could still exercise for an hour in the
gym this is working out okay it's the
ultimate hack for the nons so sick
person or the not sick person meanwhile
when you're really chronically sick it
makes you sicker and sicker and sicker
so someone would say wait a minute okay
someone who's chronically sick gets
sicker from this then why am I getting
better from this Oh no you're improving
from the hack at first you'll pay the
price later it's already happened you'll
see and I'm going to cover that now
there's an Empire or Empires built on
intermittent fasting when Empires get
built and Believe Me Empires when
they're getting built and built and
built they throw every single term they
could and every single scientific term
and everything catchphrase you name it
into it it becomes a monster out there
and then it's built
on the backs of the chronically ill
because the chronically ill doesn't heal
from it doesn't help them it's not
serving them it's not serving the people
who are really down and out struggling
trying to survive all it's doing is
getting some people who overindulged
their whole life many of them just had
it made gained a few pounds wanted to
exercise wanted to drop some of their
bad habits and pushed them forward a
little bit that's great and all but what
about the chronically sick what about
the chronically ill what about the
people who are really suffering what
about the wave of chronic illness that's
developing right now in this world what
about the chronic Le watching all the
propaganda out there on intermittent
fasting watching all the not so sick
people who throw out those glowing
reviews on how their weight went down
and they're feeling more energetic and
their Skin's a little better meanwhile
they were just people that weren't that
sick but the chronically ill they get
sucked into this because they're
thinking they're just as sick as they
are but it's not true when people have
tingles and numbness and aches and pains
and burning skin on fire severe insomnia
feet are feeling like they're lad you
can't walk dizziness blurriness blurry
eyes severe brain fog panic attacks
every single other day I'm just naming a
few symptoms Tremors tick spasms severe
OCD and they just get tricked into it so
the empires are being built sucking in
all the chronically ill that think
everybody's sick the same way they're
sick it's a trick they're not remember
intermittent fasting is all about that
dude that was never sick decided to try
to get looking a little better so he can
meet his new girlfriend got into the gym
knocked out the steak and eggs in the
morning notice it was working and it
took off from there so the chronic leel
they're all buying into it though
they're thinking this must be the way
this must be where I'm supposed to go so
they're buying into all the programs and
all the different clicks meaning they're
clicking all the websites and
subscribing and paying subscription fees
for websites because they're seeing all
these people intermittent fast and their
doctors are like have you tried
intermittent fasting that might be
something good for you well let's see I
could barely take a shower my legs feel
like lead my Skin's on fire I've been to
10 neurologists let me try the cint
fasting I saw this guy out there he ran
10 miles and then hopped on a bicycle
and then he looked all triming good and
yeah his hair might be dyed and he's got
implants and veneers in but the guy
looks like he's he's doing great and I
think I could try to get like that
people don't realize it's more than this
now I'm not denying someone doesn't get
an improvement with intermittent fasting
to start with if they're a person that's
got a constitution they're strong to
start with no real health problems at
all and they start intermittent fasting
they hack it they do it and they see
some improvements I'm not denying that
so anybody out there listening that's
saying oh he's so wrong I know this one
guy my coach my trainer does this my guy
does this I'm not doubting any of that
because when that coach trainer or
friend or person did the hack
intermittent fasting hack and got
improvements it was helping them because
For the First Time in their life they
stopped that big old bacon egg sandwich
in the morning they stopped all that fat
in the morning maybe they stopped cakes
cookies and donuts in the morning or
Bagels in the morning maybe they didn't
eat that in the morning ever they just
drank coffee but their lunch was pizza
from fried food Burgers hot dogs chicken
sandwiches fast food maybe even
home-cooked foods frozen foods but they
were all drenched in fat they were fatty
foods and maybe they stopped eating
those lunches and so they went their
morning they went their afternoon and
they waited to nighttime and they got
into some healthier options like leaner
protein say not as much bad carb not as
much oil on things they were just eating
like some chicken breast they shed a few
pounds got a little energy back started
working out more and it worked for them
they got by they had a constitution they
were strong then you got the person
who's been into health for a while they
didn't have all greasy Foods in the
morning that wasn't their thing they
left the standard American diet along
time ago they've been bouncing back from
vegan to animal protein to veganism
again plant-based then animal protein
they've been doing it for years they got
a few symptoms they're not so so sick
yet but they've been told they've had a
thyroid imbalance adrenal issues
hormones are imbalanced they're not
really really sick but they've had
enough doctor visits throughout the
years they got nutritionists they care
about their health they care about their
well-being they look at everything out
there that's healthy they're always
reading things they get books all of
this but they don't have a neurological
disease they're not suffering from
something neurological where they're
bedridden or a mattress Island they're
living their life they're running around
they're hitting juice bars they're
hitting vegan restaurants they're eating
some animal products once in a while
they do back and forth they're always
trying to look for the new trend and the
new thing but it's still not working for
them they have a problem they know
they're not healing they know they're
not improving they're saying to
themselves is this as good as it gets
these are the people that do peanut
butter smoothies in the morning throw
MCT oil in everything have coconut oil
in everything do different types of
smoothies with almond butter in that
assai bowls with nut butter on them eggs
and a stir fry eggs and an omelette with
some spinach in it or some type of
vegetable avocado toast they'll have
that too beans they'll play around with
different beans lunch should be a salad
hardboiled eggs thrown on top maybe
chicken in a salad or Pizza in a
gluten-free crust or tofu maybe they'll
have some type of soy product or another
smoothie with protein powder in it and
some Nut Butter they pride in eating
healthier options they got experience in
the health realm they've been around
they tried a lot of different things
some things worked in the moment some
things didn't then they got advice from
somebody else and tried it it almost
worked tried something else but they're
heal just isn't where it should be and
then they hear about intermittent
fasting and they're like what don't eat
so stop my smoothies in the morning stop
my vegetable burritos in the afternoon
all right I'll just give it a try doing
it doing it I'm starting to feel a
little better my bloating is going down
I think I have a little bit more energy
something's working okay I think this is
really great I think I found the Holy
Grail this is incredible so the thing
that these two groups of people have in
common is they have a nervous system
strong enough to actually handle the
caffeine high the caffeine syndrome they
can drink matcha tea green tea they can
drink Kombucha Tea which is caffeine
they can drink coffee espresso all day
long they just don't do water all day
long because if they were somebody that
was sicker and couldn't handle that much
caffeine all day long because they were
too sick they had chronic illness
neurological problems
and they just did water only they would
never survive it you wouldn't function
from water from the time you wake up
till the time you almost go to bed
basically and then you eat then it
wouldn't be enough calories enough blood
sugar glucose to keep you going but
these two groups of people have a strong
enough nervous system they didn't get
sick enough yet so they're able to
partake in the hack thinking it's the
Holy Grail it's moving them forward and
then it all crashes down the road later
now there are a bunch of people out
there that can't go that long they can't
go to the end of the day till almost
night time before they go to bed they
have to start eating at 2 they have to
start eating at 4: or 3: or six the
latest because they don't have a
constitution like some other people do
that's why the oniz fits-all gang
doesn't realize everybody has a
different problem a different Health
State a different mental state no one's
all the same but they create a trend to
try to package it up as everybody's the
same everybody can do this you can do
this tomorrow but it's not really true
or accurate there's people that have
panic attacks by 1:00 in the afternoon 2
o'clock in the afternoon and they have
to back out of intermittent fasting they
have to quit because it's cranking up
their anxiety and their nervous system
and their constitution isn't is the same
as somebody else the reason why a lot of
people say try it it works for me see if
it works for you cuz it doesn't always
work for you that's why it's a crapshoot
it's a guessing game because you don't
know what state that person really is in
there's people they fall apart by 11:00
in the morning if they don't get some
type of fuel in them and then there's
people that are under a lot of mental
stress they're under enormous pressure
they have needs their system needs more
and then there's people that have like
two or three jobs at once really
demanding work they work really hard
morning till night they need a lot of
fuel for their brain they need a lot of
blood glucose they can't just stop
eating and only be on coffee that might
last for a little while but after a week
or two they'll bottom out they'll crash
they'll hit the wall and then maybe
there's somebody that doesn't have have
a lot of Demands doesn't have a lot of
work they're into self-care only because
they have all the time in the world they
wake up in the morning and it's all
about their personal self-care they
don't have to go out do a real demanding
job maybe they have a lot of resources a
lot of money and what tires them out is
they take vacations all the time that
person might be able to sit around all
day keep themselves busy go do
appointments but on caffeine only like
that's all they need is caffeine at
least till 3:00 in the afternoon 4: in
the afternoon and then they can eat
something their demands on their brain
and what people are asking of them you
know like a school teacher with all the
students and the students needing help
all the time and the faculty and all all
the different things you have to do and
the schedule you're on it eventually
gets tiring and then that's different
it's like you need fuel it's why School
teachers are known to actually be like
whoa is there donuts ready over there
because we need one is there a bagel
already we need it you can't just be
empty stomach the whole entire day while
you need to have your faculties working
and maybe you're somebody that thinks
I'm wrong and that you have a really
busy schedule you know because you're
running around you're doing a lot of
things well often what people don't
realize if someone's not working a
really really demanding job but yet
they're really busy they're driving
around and doing appointments usually
it's about self-care so you're being
serviced all day long got the massages
while someone's working on you you're
not working on them so if you're a
massage therapist you're going to need
some fuel for your brain you can't just
be working on four patients in the
morning four clients massaging them
really hard hearing all their questions
giving them all these beautiful things
you're saying and affirmations you're
telling them giving them light and love
working on them that's demanding you
need fuel for the brain so if you're
intermittent fasting as a massage
therapist you might eventually bottom
out and hit the wall but the person
who's getting serviced that person
getting self-care they're receiving all
that they can be on caffeine all day
many of them if they have a constitution
and they weren't that ill they can do
their appointments they can get their
nails done and they could be serviced
all day it's like your nails done your
massages your facials then your doctor
appointments your doctor's working for
you they're saying hey you know this is
what you need and you just sit there
okay I stand and you leave or your hair
appointments they're working on your
hair now you're not the hair dresser
who's standing up for 12 hours a day
trying to work on people if they're on
caffeine only every single day until
6:00 at night they're eventually going
to burn out cuz they need glucose for
the brain and they're going to hit the
wall but if you're sitting there getting
your hair done you're being serviced and
a lot of people who have a lot of money
and they have the resources and they can
travel and they can do all these things
they're constantly being serviced so
they can just focus on their self-care
maybe try intermittent fasting hold back
meals because they can focus on that
it's a big difference once again the one
siiz fits all method fails it's failure
failure failure the industry and the
trends they're all one size fits-all I
can say it it's the truth I know it
pisses somebody off but it's the truth
it always has been the industry is a
onside fits all model like take a
hairdresser get a hairdresser she's
standing on her feet or he's standing on
his feet for 12 straight hours
counseling the clients therapy
hairdressers do therapy on their clients
it's not just cutting hair they actually
counsel them many hairdressers should be
paid like psychiatrist fees and think
about all that and then it's all the
chemicals they're under too hairdressers
have to inhale all the chemicals and
that gets in their bloodstream they need
blood sugar to defend themselves not to
mention it's a physically demanding job
their needs are going to be different
than someone else especially if the
hairdresser isn't well or has already
Health compromises the game changes
again same thing for a school teacher
massage therapist bus driver or a doctor
that's actually working a doctor that
actually has a practice a busy practice
demanding practice they're there at the
office they walk in they see the patient
they walk out they walk in they see the
next patient and the next patient
they're working doctors why am I saying
that because there's doctors that are
claiming the intermittent fasting
program worked great for them but
they're not practicing doctors there's
thousands of them out there now they're
on the internet they're YouTube doctors
they're podcast doctors they don't work
they have a team team of people working
for them for their social media they
have money they're using money for ads
and advertisements they're running an
entire Empire they don't work on people
they don't have to counsel people
therapy with people they don't have to
give people bad news about their health
they don't have to do anything they're
not working with people anymore the
demand changes so the doctor who's on
his feet all day who has a busy practice
may not be good with the intermittent
fasting program on caffeine the entire
day they might have to have lunch but
the podcast doctor or say doctor that
wants become famous and wants to be a
social media doctor but not work a
practice anymore that doctor is working
on their self-care they're doing their
little ice baths and their cold baths
and their cold showers and they're
breathing and their meditation and
they're doing their exercise program
they're eating the way they want they're
focused on their foods and they can do
their intermittent fasting too because
they're not working
now to understand intermittent fasting
and how it's flawed you have to start
with the name intermittent fasting now
if everybody is supposed to be such
experts like you're counting on Experts
like you are like you're thinking well
I'm putting my health in your hands so
you're obviously an expert intermittent
fasting Empires so you obviously must
know science uh many of you have degrees
so I'm putting my health in your hand my
life in your hand well to start with
here's how it's flawed it says
intermittent fasting well the body's not
fasting just because you skip breakfast
you're not fasting just because you skip
lunch you're still not fasting just
because you skip dinner it doesn't mean
you're fasting either you're just
intermittent eating you're not
intermittent fasting you're intermittent
eating the body is not fasting unless
you've gone 24 hours without any kind of
carbohydrate any kind of fuel source and
even 24 hours is a little edgy 24 hours
and 1 second is even better the 1 second
after the 24 hours you see our body
isn't in fast mode until the sun
rises and then the Sun sun rises
again the sun rises you're not eating
you go all the way till the sun rises
again and you haven't eaten yet that's
when the body starts its fasting mode
when the Sun rises our brain expects to
receive food at some point and if you
don't eat in the morning right when the
Sun rises and you eat later
our brain is still expecting to receive
Food it's the daytime our brain is
active we're
alive we're not sleeping brain is in in
shutdown mode requiring less glucose
it's
awake as it's waiting for food and it
doesn't receive it it sends a message to
your
adrenals and your adrenals start
releasing ad adrenaline cuz there isn't
any glucose for your brain because
you're not eating first thing in the
morning you're waiting so adrenaline
Rises it takes the place of glucose it's
not a great thing but it's doing it
because your brain is waiting and the
glucose is what your brain really needs
so the brain uses the adrenaline as a
glucose
substitute as the day goes on you start
heading to noon Sun's at its highest
point Point your brain is still not
receiving glucose so more adrenaline's
produced as a substitute for the glucose
your brain is hungry though it's
starving for glucose it's looking for
glucose but as the day goes on there's
no glucose yet there's no food your
adrenaline's pumping adrenaline's Rising
adrenaline's getting to the brain to get
the brain by
as night time comes the brain is
thinking it's going to be fed again
because the Sun is setting the brain is
thinking surely I'm going to get my
glucose but if you don't eat for dinner
and you go to bed your brain shuts down
when morning comes again and the Sun
starts
Rising your brain doesn't activate your
adrenals anymore right at the 24-hour
Mark the brain shuts down the adrenaline
needs it stops the adrenals from running
and shooting adrenaline out the brain
has decided it's not going to be fed so
it goes into almost like a sleep mode
even though you're awake it's a fasting
mode it's the 24-hour Mark it's from
sunrise to Sunrise you're not running on
straight adrenaline anymore you're in
fasting mode that means time to lay
around if you want to fast if the person
is trying to fast it's time to lay
around not work hard not drive around
not do anything not think too hard your
brain doesn't have the fuel it needs
you're actually in fasting mode now
that's why intermittent fasting is not
intermittent fasting you never fast
you're not fasting you're intermittent
eating the real name is more like that
maybe the better name would be
recklessly eating because that's really
what it is why is it Reckless because
you're killing your adrenals and you're
starving your brain at the wrong time
see when the brain is really in fast
mode when you've gone 24 hours on water
only no calories of any kind not even
lemon not even lemon or lemon water that
would stop the body from fasting it has
to be 24 hours
only water for the brain to realize
we're in fasting mode it has to be
sunrise to Sunrise and 1 second after
the
sunrise this way the adrenals shut down
and the Brain protects you this internal
mechanism inside the body when we truly
are fasting intermittent fasting Trend
it's the
opposite people who actually are experts
in in intermittent fasting the science
Buffs or the expert Buffs or the people
that are out there promoting it and
doing it and think they're actually
doing a service for so many people out
there don't realize this they don't know
about this internal mechanism they don't
know how the brain works they don't know
what's happening to the adrenals so when
you intermit and fast the trendy way
you're not really fasting instead you're
running on adrenaline you're robbing
Peter to pay Paul over and over and over
again until it all start to crumble how
did say crumble well there's not going
to be a study on how it crumbles no
one's going to really know no one's
going to know anything but I'll give you
a couple little pieces of information
say you're a woman you're young you want
to get pregnant someday you're planning
on having a baby when you're 30 that's
the time frame you're kind of like
projecting and then or manifesting maybe
you're manifesting I'm going to have
children children when I'm 30 that's the
right time for me and then you're
intermittent fasting for a few years
before that happens and you're burning
out your adrenals you can't quite tell
because you're so caffeinated you're
caffeinated continuously you got the
stimulants going maybe you're not doing
intermittent fasting every single day
perfectly maybe it's a few times a week
it still chips away what happens is the
adrenals start to break down they start
to lose the precious reserves they need
and women need adrenaline to give birth
a baby just doesn't pop out it's
adrenaline that allows that to happen
adrenaline saturates a mom's entire
nervous system central nervous system
and every single nerve in the body so
that the baby gets projected out so the
strength is there the core the chi if
you want to use that word that inner
strength it's there because of
adrenaline and you need those strong
adrenals what happens with a lot of moms
their adrenals are already toasted
sometimes they're toasted by their
second baby or their third baby they
have to have C-sections or they have
really difficult births because their
adrenals were not where they needed to
be and then they were fatigued
afterwards and their adrenals were
missing hormones and then the hair fell
out a couple years later and they had
other problems your health starts to
deteriorate as you go on down the road
intermittent fasting I'm not saying
makes all that happen but it's a big
contributor to that adrenal weakness and
then you got the liver problem that
occurs the liver has to absorb and
sponge up all that adrenaline that free
radical adrenaline that's floating
around the bloodstream constantly see
adrenaline is a threat to the brain long
term the brain is just sending a signal
like I want to be fed there's no blood
sugar to be found there's no glucose not
enough glucose to be found so I have to
send a signal to the adrenals and get
some adrenaline out to feed me for the
moment but it's only temporary for a
couple of hours then I need to be fed
but couple hours goes by and nothing's
happening there's no glucose someone's
not eating because they're sitting there
with their conscious ious their
Consciousness is being trained by the
intermittent fasting people to withhold
the food so that Consciousness is saying
no hold back from food meanwhile the
brain is like don't do that to me I need
the food what are you doing I need that
glucose and fuel so the brain says sends
a signal and the adrenals are releasing
that adrenaline but time is passing too
much time is passing it's becoming a
threat to the brain now because that
adrenaline is getting getting old it's
being released it becomes toxic after a
while the brain is like whoo we need
glucose fast we need fuel fast it's not
coming and then the liver becomes a
sponge it soaks up all that adrenaline
from the morning from not eating all
that adrenaline from early afternoon
from not eating and then more adrenaline
is released all over again it's this
vicious cycle the brain becomes
desperate by 2:00 in the afternoon 3:00
in the afternoon and it's triggering the
adrenals sending a signal to release
more adrenaline the liver's already been
overburdened it's already sponging and
sucking up all that other adrenaline all
day long now more adrenaline is being
released and the brain is becoming more
desperate by the minute and more
desperate by the minute and then people
who are intermittent fasting are
actually prompting their adrenals more
and more beyond all this because they're
bringing in caffeine remember black
coffee no calories in there you're not
allowed to have sugar in your coffee
when you're intermittent fasting well
that's the rules anyway I'm sure people
break the rules into do different things
but the rules are you can't have a sugar
in there you can't have cream in there
either you have to have black coffee or
espressos Black Coffee iced coffee but
it's got to be something like that
you're allowed that maybe tea matcha tea
but no cream and sugar no calories for
the brain on any level no glucose for
the brain now hm you get energy from
that caffeine from that black coffee
how's that possible caffeine doesn't
give us energy because it's not an
energy source caffeine is not a glucose
it's not a calor but yet it goes to the
brain and doesn't give us energy even
though it does what does that mean how
does it work I'll tell you how it's a
stimulant it makes the brain scream
help me to your adrenals caffeine is a
drug it prompts the adrenals flooding
your body with
adrenaline that's what it does you get
energy from caffeine what no not from
caffeine you get energy from what the
caffeine's doing to your brain and
adrenals and that energy is fake energy
because it's coming from instead of a
fuel or food source it's coming from the
depths of your body and its reserves
your body's precious energy source it's
not energy that you should have messed
with it's not energy that should have
been played with it shouldn't have been
played it's your deep deep resource it's
what keeps us going it's the resource we
have inside our organs in our body it
needs to be preserved for the rainy days
for the hardships and things that come
away for the stress the confrontations
it's there for other reasons for
childbirth it's there for stressful
situations it's there for a car accident
it's there for a fender bender it's
there for something that you're up
against it's there for that relationship
breakup it's there for when the
boyfriend breaks up with the girlfriend
the girlfriend breaks up with the
boyfriend and they're just in agony it's
there for that divorce it's there for
that lawsuit it's there for that problem
people are up against it's there for all
the different things that people in this
world struggle with it's there for when
you're told that you're a bad person
when you're not a bad person it's there
for all these different upsets
emotionally and physically that's your
precious reserves it's there to protect
you and guess what we're throwing it all
away because of a bad idea now your
adrenals produce a lot of your hormones
reproductive hormones too women's
reproductive hormones and in the
Alternative Health industry it's all
about hormones lately everybody's
worried about their hormones everybody's
going to their doctors they're getting
all their hormone profiles they're
looking into everything they're worried
about the hormones reproductive hormones
all kinds of hormones thyroid hormones
everything and then we're intermittent
fasting and we're damaging and injuring
one of our most profound hormone
producers which is the adrenals and then
wait all that intermittent fasting isn't
good for the liver it's not great
because the liver has to absorb all that
adrenaline all day long and that
caffeine too and it starts to slowly
hinder the liver the liver is a hormone
producer as well but wait a minute I get
it you're somebody that's like you're
wrong totally wrong ew I know somebody
their blood work looks better from their
intermittent fasting they got a good
doctor they're looking at all their
stats and levels and I I went and did it
too and my blood work looks a little
better too
I'm feeling a little better as well I
just don't think you know what you're
talking about but see those results are
a snapshot in time that's what it is
temporary results for cleaning up
cleaning up what once was not great
lifestyle right all the different heavy
fatty foods in the morning or fatty
foods at lunchtime maybe processed foods
a lot of people they do intermittent
fasting they come off the ride they come
off of the fast foods they come off the
pizzas they come off of the burgers the
lunches people know what it's like to
eat a pizza for lunch you know what it's
like right remember those days remember
have a pizza for lunch you have more
than a few slices and now you're just
like half asleep and maybe you eat
better than that and it's not about
pizzas but the reason why people get
results with the intermittent fasting
the real reason is because they stopped
the fats and that's why they get results
like blood sugar sugar gets better as
far as the A1C pre-diabetes can start to
calm down maybe they feel a little bit
more energy for the moment but either
way they're getting some results and
they're getting results in their blood
test because they lowered the fats but
not just lowered the fats they stopped
them but here's the tricky part that's
quick results those are quick it's hack
results we get in trouble later
because it's not sustainable bigger
problems happen later brain problems
neurotransmitter chemical problems
neuron problems gal cell problems
adrenal problems central nervous system
problems liver problems all these things
develop later it's sometimes Fast 6
months blood test looks good doctor's
kind of happy everything's hey you're
intermittent fasting you're doing better
you're exercising oh wait a minute why
are these liver enzymes up all of a
sudden this is strange eight months
later oh it can't be the intermittent
fasting because it was giving you
results see the psych out the psych out
is you get these quick results for a lot
of people but all these other problems
happen later but because we got some
results from the start it's referenced
so the doctor has it on his sheet and he
references it can't be the intermittent
fasting that's making your health go
downhill now sir or ma'am because we
have on record that you were improving
from the intermittent fasting from the
start so a year later we're seeing these
other problems happening like brain fog
confusion
anxiety Panic
depression other issues too and then
we're seeing things change but it can't
be the intermittent fasting because it
showed on record it was concrete there
were benefits you actually were healing
something was changing we were seeing
results and that's where the psych out
is the psych out is is you get these
quick hack results but nobody realizes
the consequences that happen later the
ramifications that occur later and
nobody knows and the later doesn't have
to be 10 years like oh 10 years down the
road that's when something will happen
well I'll rather just do this for the
next 10 years and worry about it then no
it can happen six months two months
later a year later three three years
later 10 years later for sure but it
happens I know what you're thinking
there's real science behind this like
there's science there's professionals
well there's Empires built on it lots of
professionals involved in it now and I'm
really Off the Mark let's talk about the
benefits now that so-called science
stands stands by and how intermittent
fasting is so beneficial so let's go
through some of the claims that are out
there like the claims that seem to be
hardcore where they hang their hat on
them okay here's one reduce insulin
resistance well scratching my head here
if you don't eat in the
morning you're not going to have high
insulin resistance because there was no
food eaten in the morning so therefore
the pancreas didn't release
insulin therefore there wasn't insulin
resistance and then I wonder since I've
been talking about that for 35 years and
published it almost 10 years ago that if
you keep the fats out in the morning you
don't have the insulin resistance and
I'm wondering did they get it from there
or if they did discover it themselves
recently fine
but at the same time it's not rocket
science it's not hard to figure this one
out if you don't eat in the morning your
pancreas isn't going to produce all that
insulin you're going to have lower
insulin production less insulin
resistance and yes they're correct
there's going to be less insulin
resistance so that claim is correct even
though there's details they're missing
and we'll explore that a little later
let's go to the next benefit that they
claim human growth hormone increases
that's the claim so they say that human
growth hormone increases and this is a
great
thing yes it does
increase on the blood test but it
doesn't increase at all so let's go into
how and why what they don't realize is
the same amount of human growth hormone
is being produced but they see more of
it in the blood test and the reason why
they see more human growth hormone is
because the the fats in the bloodstream
aren't there anymore because the person
stopped eating they're producing the
same amount of human growth hormone as
they always do the difference is there's
no fat to absorb it the fats you eat in
the morning in your breakfast enter the
bloodstream and choke out the human
growth hormone and they can't see as
much of it on the blood test also the
fat in the blood on the blood test is
harboring it absorbs some of that growth
hormone and they can't see it either
through that Avenue because it's in the
fat itself they're not testing it in a
serum in order to determine if that fat
actually Harbors growth hormone but yet
the same amount of growth hormone is
being produced every day it hasn't been
increased it's the same amount now
science doesn't know the fat is
harboring growth hormone to even test
for it in the blood because they don't
know it's about removing fat and that's
why people get benefits or improvements
they think it's just removing food so
they're not looking at the fat and they
won't look at the fat as being the
problem because everybody's promoting a
high-fat diet now here's the other piece
they're missing when you take the food
out of the diet in the morning you
remove the breakfast and you don't eat
the reason why human growth hormone also
elevates is because of a detoxification
process happening when you remove food
specifically the fat which they don't
know but when you remove food in the
morning you can cleanse that means
you're releasing old outdated hormones
that are deactivated they don't work
anymore because that's what the human
body does it takes estrogen and
progesterone and testosterone and it
eliminates it and same with human growth
hormone it's
detoxifying out of the liver out of
organs it's hitting the bloodstream and
you're peeing it out you're eliminating
it out but if you take a blood test
you'll see more of it when you're not
eating more of it will be in the blood
test but they don't know these
differences they just say oh wait look
okay write this down and then they make
this big claim it increases your human
growth hormone but it's so generalized
the details aren't there it's flawed
science once again one size fits all
the tools they're using like in this
case doing the blood test is still
measuring only one aspect of it but not
measuring all these other aspects of it
so the tools they're using are one size
fits-all tools so let's go to another
intermittent fasting claim cellular
waste removal now this is interesting
because I'm scratching my head right now
the intermittent fasting people the
Empire's built don't believe in
cleansing they say the body does it
itself and never needs a detox or
cleanse mm info all these years is all
about cleansing and detoxification of
cells and organs so we can heal and then
presenting tools to help us do that now
they're saying when you intermittent
fast cellular waste removal occurs so
I'm just scratching my head here and I'm
trying to see what this really is and
it's waste removal um so waste coming
out of a cell what waste that's
detoxification that's cleansing so what
they're saying is your cleansing okay
now that makes sense in a way because
when you stop
eating you start to cleanse now get this
though they just think when you stop
eating food that's not correct really
when you stop eating fats you start to
cleanse so you can eat fat free food or
food with no over at fats in the morning
and still cleanse but they don't know
that which means you can still get
cellular waste removal the term they use
now because they didn't want to use the
detox term or the cleanse term because
hey they wanted their own term so they
said let's do waste removal but yet the
body doesn't need a cleanse and the body
doesn't need a detox we'll still stand
by that and what they don't realize it's
removing the fat that allows for their
claim cellular waste removal to even
occur not removing food itself if you
eat an orange in the morning you still
will have cleansing power and ability
you still will have cellular waste
removal if you eat an avocado in the
morning you won't get cellular waste
removal anymore and that's how that
works all right let's go to the next
claim they got cell
renewal oh
boy all right this is interesting so
they say sell renewal when you
intermittent fast okay well if you're
jacked up on caffeine all day long not
getting any nutrients in you and then
you top it off with a big sloppy greasy
crappy meal at the end of the day uh I
don't know how much sell renewal you're
really going to have and here's the
other thing here's the real detail
that's important there's no way to
determine if it's cell renewal they
don't have the tools yet in science
because you will never know the
difference between how much cell die off
you're having and how much cell renewal
you're having it's impossible to
determine science might be able to
determine it 500 years from now but all
we have is a theory right now because
they can't measure there's no measuring
tool in existence right now that can
measure how many cells are renewing or
being created versus how many cells are
dying or weakening we don't have that
scientific tool yet it doesn't exist so
what they're doing is theorizing because
it sounds exciting it's like whoa this
creates cell renewal this is amazing and
it's a claim they can make that gets
everybody excited and no one's going to
really doubt it and anybody in health is
going to be like sell renewal that's
awesome because it hits the whole
anti-aging live forever Market
can cells
renew yeah but you need something to
make that happen you need something more
than caffeine all day and a sloppy meal
at the end of the day you need
antioxidants mineral salts trace
minerals phyto chemical compounds
anthocyanins glucose macrominerals you
need all of these plus more and you need
them entering the body more than once a
day but most intermittent fasters are
not into the cell renewal game they're
in the cell destruction game they got
the caffeine cranking all day long they
got the adrenaline pumping all the way
adrenaline is corrosive it's cell
damaging that's what adrenaline does
caffeine cell damaging and the other
problem is they're not eating a pound of
spinach at the end of the day and a
whole bunch of fruit where you're
getting those antioxidants the glucose
and the phytochemical compounds they're
eating a burger they're eating some
chicken they're eating other Foods I'm
not saying chicken's bad or Burger's bad
or what's good or bad I'm just saying
there's no Healing Foods there's no
powerful tools there they're not
drinking 32 ounces of celery juice at
the end of the day a pound of spinach
and a whole bunch of asparagus that's
the last thing they're eating now let's
head to their next hypothesis their next
claim beneficial gene expression so gene
expression gets better okay so you get
better
genes um so what they're saying the
hypothesis is because they haven't seen
it but they think changes to molecules
involved with genes could help with
longevity so it could be related to
longevity that's the hypothesis now when
you really break it down there's nothing
there at all they don't see anything
they have no scientific proof nothing's
there but it's a great one to kind of
throw into the mix gets people excited
really nothing to say about it because
it doesn't really exist so there is
nothing to say about it sure if you're
doing something better for your health
you hope your genes are getting better
in this case they haven't seen it they
don't know but they're just going to
assume it's even possible okay so here's
our next claim weight loss well all
right um You Take Away food for as many
hours as you can for as much of the day
as you can you eat
less uh yeah there's going to be a bunch
of dudes out there that are going to
lose weight and you'll notice out there
if you talk to enough people they start
their intermittent fasting program at
the very same moment in time they start
exercising or cranking up their exercise
they're not eating and they're like
starving so then they're like I better
start exercising keep my anxiety down or
whatever but either way there's
different people doing different things
but most of the time they start both at
the same time of course if you're not
eating anymore and you're exercising
more you're going to start losing some
weight I know there's people who've
already been exercising and they're just
eating whatever their high fat meals and
their normal programs whatever and then
they start to intermittent fast while
they're exercising the same way and
they're losing weight too cuz they
stopped eating I know there's some
people out there that are going to say
no I eat the same amount of calories as
I always have I just eat it at the end
of the the day and not really cuz you
don't really remember what you used to
do the binges and the different times
you used to eat and the different foods
you didn't have it all down you weren't
measuring every calorie ever now you're
kind of more mindful but no you're
eating less calories and so many are
trying to control their Cravings so they
like their intermittent fasting program
because they're controlling their
Cravings they're like craving all day
but they're trying to say oh no wait I'm
just going to keep the coffee going in
and I'm going to just keep that under
control and I'm going to reward myself
at the end of the day and I'll eat
whatever I want at the end of the day
but I'll hold back all my Cravings all
day long but here's the other thing
people don't realize their stomach
starts to shrink starts to get smaller
because they're not eating all day and
they're just doing some different
liquids like say coffee for one right so
by the time of the night time comes or
the end of the day their big meal isn't
as big as their meals used to be because
their stomach is not stretched as much
so their stomach is shrinking so the
meals aren't as big at the end of the
day it's another reason why they're
losing weight so yes the claim of losing
weight is actually real but here's how
it works it's real because you stopped
eating fat because eating fat makes you
fat fat makes you fat that's how it
works this is why people who do high fat
diets and work out and lost some weight
years ago end up having to go and do
intermittent fasting years later because
they can't keep their weight under
control anymore they're working out they
seem to be doing all the right things
they're eating healthy meals but they're
keeping the fats in they're doing the
nut Butters the lean proteins and
they're having their MCT oil and
everything else but they don't realize
it it's all fat and then they need some
carbs once in a while so they throw
those in too but they're trying to do it
in a balanced way and it worked for them
for a while because it got them off the
standard American diet many years ago
and they became Health experts in a way
they started training they started
exercising and they started doing all
that and then the weight wasn't
controllable anymore and they're like
What's the next phase and they hear
about intermittent fasting so then they
stop eating all together for most of the
day because really reality the constant
high fat diet is not sustainable the
constant healthy high fat diet that
everybody's on that gravitates to after
you've been on standard American is not
sustainable so when you grow up you go
to college or you grow up and you do
whatever and you're getting older and
you're eating standard American you eat
what you want you have your pizza here
you do what you want here and the weight
is gaining you want to exercise and get
the weight off and then you go high fat
keto or high fat whatever or some type
of other healthy high-fat diet and you
say whoa found the Holy Grail I know my
deal I count my macros I'm eating my
proteins I'm eating my fats and then you
start getting sicker or something goes
wrong or weight starts gaining and
you're like what is going on and you run
into some trainer or some guy at the gym
who's like you should intermittent fast
man everybody's doing this so now you
leave your high-fat diet which was not
sustainable and now you head to not
eating at all until the end of the day
and you think you found the Holy Grail
again but you didn't because you hit the
wall when you intermittent fast as well
it takes time happens at a different
moment for everybody but you end up
hitting the wall you're back to square
one you're eating fats all over again
it's not sustainable then you're
intermittent fasting then you're
vacillating back and forth constantly
intermittent fasting for some weeks then
going back to eating high fat diet
healthy high fat diet for some weeks
then intermittent fasting and then
you're just rebounding you're going back
and forth back and forth cravings and
all not getting the things you need and
you're just running around in circles
and you're chasing your tail because
both intermittent fasting and a healthy
high-fat diet are not sustainable long
term so let's cover a couple more claims
this is fun heart health improves heart
health okay well if you stop pancakes
with butter all over it sausage bacon
eggs ham cheese cream in the morning and
you don't do that anymore and you don't
do it for lunch either hm I think you
might be getting better heart results
somewhere along the way for sure
cardiovascular you're not butter heart
attacking yourself to death you're not
tanking the butter and hopefully no
one's putting butter in their coffee cuz
that's a heart attack in a cup but and
that's also intermittent fasting has
gone wrong if someone is doing that and
the funny thing is yeah there's a lot of
intermittent fers that are doing all
kinds of weird things and that's one of
them so yeah of course heart health
improves you're not killing yourself
eating all those high fatty foods for
most of the day it gives you a chance
gives the heart a chance like is it
really rocket science I mean they didn't
know that but they have to figure that
out now like you don't need a couple
hundred million dollars in a study to
try to figure that one out but wait I'm
M Aken they didn't figure it out now
because they didn't know it's removing
the fats that are giving them heart
relief they just think it's removing the
food so I guess they need another 20
years or 50 years and $500 million to
someday realize it was the fat that was
causing the problem not the food it's
like you go to the scientist and say are
you guys uh food uh or fat you get you
get the correlation so the next claim is
May prevent Alzheimer's okay uh May
prevent
Alzheimer's I don't know where they got
that from there is not one single case
in the world of someone who was dying of
Alzheimer's intermittent fast and then
recovered it doesn't exist but they're
claiming May prevent Alzheimer's they
got no proof it never happened happened
they don't even have one healing story
of a grandma that doesn't know where she
is doesn't know what street she lives on
she has Alzheimer's it's really bad the
whole family's worried they're losing
her they don't have one healing story
like oh my God my grandma she was losing
it she was dying from Alzheimer's in
fact they were like well she only has
like a year left and she did
intermittent fasting you guys she
withheld from food all day long we had
her jacked up on coffee she ate a big
old sloppy meal at the end of the day
and she healed we don't have one healing
story so I love when they say may
prevent Alzheimer's and then we're
supposed to chomp at the bit
like oh my God like that's incredible I
better start now the other thing is how
many grandmas can starve themselves the
entire day like 16 hours without food
like does your grandma do that how many
grandpas can do that does your grandpa
do that or is he in the cookie jar or is
he in the cakes and goodie jar or the
cupboard getting a snack out like are
you kidding like how many Alzheimer's
patients that are Grandpa or Grandma
that you know can sit there and not eat
all the way until 8:00 at night or 6:00
at night huh they usually eat chocolate
cake and everything else Under the Sun
and on top of that if they have
Alzheimer's you got to be the one to
feed them right if they're really bad
off you got to be the one to get them
the meals so are you going to be like
well I'm doing experiment on my grandpa
right now we haven't fed him yet he's uh
he's might be hungry uh his blood sugar
might be really low doesn't have any
energy he doesn't seem he wants to go
outside and do anything so we're holding
food from him let's see it's 2 o' I'm
looking at my clock now no grandpa not
going to feed you I know you you got
Alzheimer's but no we're not going to
feed you uh four o'clock Grandpa We're
Not Gonna feed you yet 7 o'clock at
night no grandpa we're going to try to
do the intermittent fasting program that
this Guru does you know this Guru
trainer guy or whoever we're going to
feed you at 9:00 tonight and then you
can eat okay I'm GL grandpa I know you
waited the whole day but we're going to
do this every single day to determine if
it helps prevent Alzheimer's you know
when you really think about intermittent
fasting and you really break it down
like starve your kids starve your
teenagers starve your young adults
starve your
grandparents to try to get a result
because you don't know what else to do
it's insane all right so let's do one of
our last
claims uh reduce
inflammation okay reduce inflammation in
the body so if you're intermittent
fasting the claim is you can reduce
inflammation in the body well yeah you
kind of can there's a good chance you
will the reason why is because you're
not having gluten in the morning they
don't know that but you're not having
gluten in the morning you're not having
dairy in the morning they don't know
that either and then you're not having
eggs in the morning they don't know that
because they believe eggs is a great
protein and you're not eating corn in
the morning you're not doing soy in the
morning but they don't know that see
they just think food in general you're
not eating food and because you're not
eating food you're reducing your
inflammation but they don't know what
causes inflammation unless they know the
mm info all these years which is
pathogens cause inflammation but they
don't know that they don't know that
Epstein bar or shingles or set a
megavirus or or Herby simplex one or
hhv6 causes inflammation in the body
they never knew that that's original
Medical meeme information all these
years published information that science
actually uses and takes medical meum
information for themselves IL legally
and so but they don't know this they
just think food food stops you don't eat
food anymore in the morning so
inflammation goes down they're like yay
we found something but they don't know
why because you're taking away specific
things that could be in the mix of that
food like gluten which feeds virus uses
eggs which feeds viruses corn soy Dairy
which feeds viruses pathogens and
bacteria those things eat those very
specific things and then those pathogens
create the inflammation but they're not
there yet they're not that far advanced
yet they're just at the point where
they're scratching their head going okay
food's removed that person's aches and
pains are less oh here's a great claim
May reduce inflammation so let's talk
about a little bit of a different topic
here swelling edema a lot of people are
swelling they feel swollen and when they
intermittent fast the swelling goes down
but like I said remember this it's not
sustainable because people who are
swelling wafer back and forth they
vacillate back and forth they stop
eating their swelling goes down and then
they got to eat again and they're eating
eating and then they get swollen again
and now they have to stop eating again
and then they desell they desell they
swell they Dell they swell swell more
swell more and then boom have to go all
the way back intermittent fast
intermittent fast so they're fasc
relating back and forth swelling
dwelling now how do they dwell from
intermittent fasting they're stopping
the food that are contributing to their
swelling because inside the food is the
problem what food what is it is it
gluten is it dairy products is it eggs
you might be like I don't do gluten but
you do eggs I don't do eggs but you do
cheese what is it and so these different
foods feed pathogens but that's just one
Avenue right there I'll give you another
option what if you're somebody that's
like I don't do dairy I'm vegan I'm
plant-based I still swell I eat very
healthy aw I have oatmeal I put peanut
butter in my oatmeal I have avocado
toast I do different things I have
smoothies with protein powders
plant-based protein powders and I find
aw that if I stop eating alog together
my swelling goes down yeah well in your
situation it's liver it's an inflamed
liver pathogens inside the liver itself
a liver that's overburdened stagnant and
sluggish maybe you got too many heavy
metals combined with it all but your
liver is struggling so you have to stop
your plant-based Foods in the morning
even if those plant-based Foods AR
necessarily feeding pathogens that you
have it's still burdening the liver
you're at the point in your life in your
health where you actually have to
withhold from food to get a result to
get the swelling down because the fat in
your Foods the peanut butter the almond
butter the coconut oil the avocado
whatever it is those fats are burdening
the liver so much that you're in a
different position in your life you have
to stop those fats even if you're
plant-based in the morning or you have
to stop your plant-based fats during the
day the daytime as well so you're that
person that's like well okay in the
morning I'm not eating those anyway and
well if you're eating them during the
day it gets in the way as well and then
you might be that plant-based person
that's like well I intermittent fast and
I found being a vegan I don't eat
breakfast I don't eat lunch yes I drink
coffee yes I have caffeine I try to push
all the way to 4 5:00 6:00 before I eat
yeah you're withholding all those fats
again and then your swelling goes down
the fats are contributing to the
swelling and fats also stop the body
from cleansing or healing so that you
can't get rid of pathogens if you're
always cranking the fats in the diet and
the Bummer is it's so sad because Health
influencers have no idea why anyone is
really sick to begin with but they're
pushing everybody into intermittent
fasting as if it's a cure then when they
do eat they eat the wrong Foods so
people aren't being taught to go the
right direction to heal or what to eat
they're not eating healing foods for
their actual symptoms and conditions the
very reason why they're getting sick now
a lot of people are intermittent fasting
because of swelling because they're
getting so inflamed and swollen and
their body doesn't feel good it's not
just fat or weight of fat it's water
retension and for years I've talked
about this where if someone's overweight
they may only be 10 lb overweight with
10 lbs of water retention and edema they
may not be 20 lbs of fat on their body
they may have 10 lb of fat or 15 lbs of
fat and 10 lb of water swelling fluid
they're retaining fluid and I've talked
about this for over 35 years when
someone says well that person's 250 lbs
when they're supposed to be only 180 lbs
they got you know that much more fat on
them it's like well wait a minute there
could be 30 lbs of retaining fluid edema
happening and then the rest is fat so
when that swelling goes down in a day
they look like they lost 10 pounds like
10 pounds fast 10 pounds a week
especially if they just stop eating all
of a sudden they lose this initial
swelling they don't lose fat they just
lose all this water retention the fluid
the swelling of the
fluid but different people swell for
different reasons cuz I know the
alternative movement want once again's
one size fits-all they just think
everybody's got the same swelling
problem but they don't some people are
really viral low grade viral infections
and these viral infections inhabit their
liver making their liver so sluggish and
toxic that their lymphatic system starts
to gain fluid because their liver is so
clogged up and then you might have
somebody else it's a little different
it's not just a low grade viral
infection and somebody else might have a
stagnant sluggish liver without the
pathogen problem the low-grade viral
infection instead a really fatty liver
with lots of different toxins in them
and then you got people with salt
addictions they're salted out they got
salt deposits inside of them everywhere
their liver has salt deposits in it
their bloodstream is high in sodium they
got salt everywhere and then they're
addicted to the flavor they need that
salt flavor and there's people that say
Hey I I don't add salt I never add salt
to anything no way I'm not really big on
salt meanwhile they're eating so much
salt they don't even realize that they
go buy a sandwich somewhere and the
thing is salted out 10 Ways to Sunday
because they don't know and then they go
eat over somebody's house or family
makes them something to eat or salt and
coffee that's another thing people don't
realize it they make coffee more
addictive because the coffee shops put
salt in the water sodium is in the water
at the coffee shops it's salty coffee
and everybody's drinking it down and
they don't realize it and then sauce is
everywhere different condiments and
sauces tomato sauce salts everywhere and
then restaurants eating out takeout food
even if it's healthy vegan takeout food
or vegetarian takeout food it's extra
salty everybody salt it out and then
they'll have some chips healthy chips
they're salty too salt gets so out of
control they're swelling they're
swelling everywhere they stop eating
they intermittent fast they don't
realize it but they just back down the
salt that brings down the swelling that
alone now you'll often hear from people
who intermittent fast that they can
think more clear they got Clarity like
they're not as fogged and one of the
reasons is they're avoiding a lot of
foods in the morning or during the day
that would bog them down slow them down
and starve their brain of glucose for
example they're eating high fatty foods
during the morning or during the
afternoon you get high blood fat high
blood fat creates insulin resistance it
stops critically needed glucose and
sugar from getting to your brain and
when that glucose gets to the brain you
think more clear now what they're doing
is they're avoiding all food altoe so
they're avoiding the fats they're not
having the fats anymore but they're
having the caffeine so now they're
running on adrenaline and they think
more clear in the moment but this is
robbing Peter to pay Paul again because
in the end you get burnout
neurotransmitter burnout neuron burnout
brain deficiencies you lose even
precious resources like melatonin in
your brain and you just slowly burn out
over time anxiety creeps up depression
creeps up and then you break and you end
up quitting your intermittent fasting
program how do we nourish ourselves how
do we give our body what it needs all
the nutrients all the glucose all the
trace mineral salts how do we fuel
ourselves so we can function without
being jacked up on a drug like caffeine
how can we give ourselves the nutrients
we need to power us through the day but
yet not get sick instead reverse our
conditions and our symptoms and live our
life to the the best of its ability and
not have to be on a stimulant how can we
do it in a kind way a kind way to our
body kind way for our children our
parents our friends our loved ones we
don't naturally come into this world and
someday say I don't want to be a fireman
I want to be an intermittent faster I
don't want to be a school teacher I want
to be an intermittent fasting person no
I want to intermittent fast hey I'm in
fifth grade right now hey do you guys
want an intermittent fast someday where
you don't eat all your fun foods and
don't eat pizza and anything else and
breakfast is what do you mean no more
waffles in the morning Lego myo no more
that uh no more cereal yeah no we're
just going to starve ourselves all day
long until the end of the day at night
really does that sound like a good idea
yeah that's what we're going to do I'm
going to go to college and someday be an
intermittent fasting person and when I
go out to lunch with my friend in
college I'm going to say well I'm not
eating until 9:00 tonight that's what I
aspire to be and do it's not a natural
process to just withhold food every day
so how do we do this right to start
there's not one way to do it everybody's
different everybody has different
problems some people have a really
strong Constitution they haven't been
taken down by pathogens they don't have
a lot of heavy metals they don't have a
lot of toxins and poisons that person
might just need some celery juice in the
morning and not have to eat till noon at
least they're getting their Trace
mineral salts and a little bit of
glucose and hydration and then it all
depends on what time you wake up in the
morning you might be somebody that wakes
up really early or somebody that wakes
up at 10:00 in the morning 11:00 in the
morning that changes the game too if you
wake up really early you start your day
early and you go to work you're going to
need some glucose eventually so you
might need some fruit or smoothie so not
just celery juice or cucumber juice or
just lemon water you might need all of
it and then some apples along the way to
take you to noon what you want to do is
leave out the fats no nuts no seeds no
nut Butters no oils no coconut oil no
MCT oil no eggs dairy products Meats
chickens keep the fats completely out at
least before noon you're not bombarding
your blood BL stream with all that fat
fat blocks the sugar from getting into
your cells fat blocks the glucose from
getting to your brain fat creates the
insulin resistance not the sugar and
that's a mistake made with intermittent
FS they don't know this so they withhold
all food starving their brain starving
their body starving their liver their
bloodstream loses the glucose what
people don't think about is their heart
is a muscle muscle their muscles need
glucose it's critical but if there's no
glucose because you're holding back all
the food you're starving yourself from
the sugars you need then your heart is
not getting the glucose the sugar it
needs to feed itself your heart gets
stressed your brain gets stressed your
liver gets stressed your body gets
stressed and this is something
intermittent faster don't realize
they're doing but at the same time
they're feeling a little better because
they're not eating so much garbage and
so much fat throughout the day so the
goal is to cleanse detox restore renew
cells for real get nutrients to them get
sugar to the brain sugar to the heart
get mineral salts to the brain and
nervous system all of this while being
productive living your life not
overburdening your liver not tanking out
on fat all day meaning you're eating
fatty foods throughout the day not
realizing it and getting insulin
resistance instead you're you're getting
better workouts fueling your heart
fueling your muscles fueling your brain
and nervous system and being productive
now listen there's a lot of ways to do
this good ways to do it right so many
different options you might be that
person that doesn't want to eat till
four or six but yet you need some kind
of fuel but yet you don't want to
actually eat food well then that's when
the juices come in that's when coconut
water comes in that's when lemon water
comes in you could always do the lemon
water and then into celery juice or
cucumber juice then into coconut water
and then do that until 4 or 6 but that's
only if you're somebody with a strong
Constitution you're kind of used to not
eating that much food or fuel but what
if you're somebody that's sick and you
got a lot of neurological symptoms and
you need more fuel or you're up against
a lot of stress now here's a little
disclaimer there's lots of options
because that's the whole point it's not
one size fits all each person is at a
different place in their life there are
people that they got to eat something
every hour because of their adrenal
glands their adrenals are shot they have
to make sure they fuel themselves every
hour hour and a half and then there's
people who do want to eat fat at some
point during the day they don't know it
but they feel like satiated on some type
of chicken or meat and it's the fat
that's kind of giving them that
satiation at night well save those fats
to the end of the day that could be a
whole another person where all day long
you're doing lemon water water your
celery juice then your coconut water
then a fruit smoothie then a salad baby
with steamed potato and then at the very
end of the night you have your animal
protein or your plant fats or something
like avocado salad again or you have
something else like a nut butter if
that's what you live on that you love
everybody's different there's so many
different options say you're somebody
that gets up and coconut water works
good for you so you can do a lot of that
and then you're not big on fruit so do
some oatmeal can do some maple syrup or
honey in your oatmeal but don't do the
nut milks the nut Butters don't put the
fat on top of the oatmeal cuz that's
when you get in trouble and then if you
do like a little bit of fruit you can
always put some berries and other pieces
of fruit on your oatmeal if you'd like
that might be able to carry you to
lunchtime or after if you're somebody
that's trying not to eat as much at
least you got some kind of fuel to fuel
your brain and fuel your bloodstream
with all the glucose you need and then
you might be able to do some steamed
vegetables that day and some steamed
vegetables on top of a salad of greens
leafy greens so you're getting all your
mineral salts but on that salad don't
put oils don't put avocado don't put
chicken don't put fish don't put Bean on
there don't put eggs on there you don't
want a fat on there remember you're
keeping the fats out if you don't want
to be fat free for the day the fats come
later at the end of the day if you're if
you're an animal protein person that's
when you apply the animal proteins
because animal proteins equal animal fat
so at the end of the day your animal fat
comes in then if you're a plant-based
person plant fats comes at the end of
the day that means if you're somebody
that always eats nut butter or avocado
you're bringing those in later on your
last meal of the day really preferably
so you're doing your intermittent
fasting in a way you're doing the thing
that you avoid it all day which is the
fats but you do it at night at the end
of the day but this is the healthier
version because all day long you're
getting fuel and the things you need a
lot of influencers are adopting medical
medium tools with their intermittent
fasting programs they all drink celery
juice in the morning and then they drink
their coffee all day long and have their
meals at the end of the day the celery
juice is carrying them helping them
bringing things back to them that's why
they're doing it the sodium sodium
cluster salts and celery juice are
feeding their brain their
neurotransmitters their neurons it's
making them stronger while they're doing
something that's not good for them like
caffeine all day the celery juice is
allowing them to do more of the things
that aren't helpful at the same time the
celery juice is restoring their
hydrochloric acid reserves because their
stomach glands are depleted of HCL it's
part of what contributes to their
bloating and then a lot of them have
bacteria problems in their gut bad
bacteria strepto coctus that contributes
to the bloating as well and the celery
juice is killing off the bad bacteria
lowering the amounts of bad bacteria
they have in their gut and then the
celery juice is also knocking other
pathogens down a lot of people have the
epine bar and the lowgrade viral
infections so they got a little bit of
that mild fatigue and they got a little
bit of aches and pains and they don't
feel good so the celery juice is
knocking down down the viral load and
the bacterial load and restoring the HCL
and at the same time the celery juice is
bringing bile reserves back restoring
the liver and helping them cleanse all
that's happening from their daily celery
juice every single day but then they
still tell everybody they're
intermittent fasting and the credit goes
to the intermittent fasting but they
don't tell someone they're doing the
celery juice so the next person says
well I'm going to do the intermittent
fact fting and they don't do any celery
juice if you're looking to customize an
option that's right for you for what's
happening inside your body because
everybody's different with what's going
on inside of them different pathogens
different pathogen loads toxic heavy
metals different toxins and poisons
different life experiences like
stressors different demands and
hardships then check out cleanse to heal
so a lot of different cleanses in there
a lot of different protocols you can you
can customize it to what's right for you
you can learn about the lemon water
learn about the celery juice learn about
the heavy metal detox bie there's a
heavy metal detox cleanse there's a
medical medium morning cleanse there's
mono cleanses in there if you have
serious digestive problems you live with
a lot of bloat pain gastric distress the
book has a lot of information in detail
so you can customize it for yourself so
you can learn how to work with not
having the fats so you lose the insulin
resistance and you can do cleansing and
healing and you can also use the book If
You're an animal protein person or if
you're a plant-based person also there's
the 369 cleanses 369 Advanced cleanse in
there and the anti-bug cleanse because
so many people are buggy they got
sicknesses and symptoms because they
have so many different varieties of bugs
H pylori and the herpes simplex one the
h hb6 and the Epstein bars everybody's
dealing with something inside of them
that changes the roles the medical
medium book series it's there for people
to customize their healing to do what's
right for them because not everybody's
the same and one size doesn't fit all in
order to heal everybody has a different
experience and a different problem and
so we need to address it and we need
options so people can customize and take
their healing as far as they need to go
before we get to the ending of the show
just want to leave you with one last
thought when we're intermittent fasting
we're doing it on planet Earth we're
doing it here in this solar system this
planet is the size it is takes 24 hours
for it to revolve and turn for the sun
to rise and the sun to
rise think about being in a different
solar system on another planet and what
would intermittent fasting be like there
what if it was a planet that was larger
than the earth very well could be and it
took 48 hours for that sunrise for that
sun to rise or took longer and what
would it be like during the day as
you're intermittent fasting instead of
fasting for 12 hours and not eating food
before you eat your dinner you might be
waiting 20 hours or maybe even 30 hours
just wanted to leave you with that last
note it's easy to be confused about food
feel stuck about what we are eating feel
lost about what we are choosing what
we're trying to avoid the road map to
Healing is hard when we don't have a
clue it's not our fault everyone going
through a struggle ends up scrambling
it's true when you're young and strong
and haven't been in the shoes of someone
who has been there who's been deeply
wronged and is really sick and what you
reference in your life isn't what they
the really sick have referenced in their
life it's like the wild west out there
in the world of Health everyone who's
Alpha and their ego won't back down and
they are not yet affected by sick
and try to make a name for themselves
not all are like this though there are
Angels Among the masses and there are
beacons of light who have been through
hell and back and have every right to
preach and teach classes wise ones that
fought their way out of the woods broke
out of unwellness left the darkness and
then became reborn with purpose and
knowledge and of great compassion for
the ones that have been misled All Along
The Path they know what it was to feel
barely alive and just about half dead
but have more words of wisdom now than
anything said in the trendy Health realm
of games that mess with people's heads
remember these words for they are tall
and the truth derails the darkness so it
doesn't stay above all the confusion and
delusion the medicine delusion
creates its own
downfall and all that's good and healing
sits in your hands and allows what you
wanted all
[Music]
along