how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams body swelling fluid retention
edema lymphadema plague a lot of people
whether they know it or not people swell
but why that's the magic question there
are reasons real causes in this episode
we're going to explore them all we're
going to clear the mind of confusion
around this chronic conditions so many
struggle with the only requirement is
can you handle the
truth yeah no I got to hang up yeah I'm
at a bar I'm meeting an old friend I got
to talk to the hostess all right I'll
I'll catch you later yeah hi hi is I'm
here to see an old friend haven't seen
him in 20 years yeah Barry did he did he
come here cuz I can't see him he's not
here he is where is he that's him that's
Barry Oh my God all right yeah I'll I'll
go up to
him Hey Barry hi good to see you man I
haven't seen you in years yeah hey
thanks yeah no I'm trying I'm trying
trying to look my best hey yeah uh what
happened to you do you have like a
disease or something are you okay
well your head's like three times bigger
than it was in college and I'm just
wondering is it something
that yeah what you don't think it's
bigger oh man I mean look at this old
photo of
us check this photo out because I've
been looking at it before I got here cuz
I want to like show you all our old
photos look look at your head in this
picture and then your head now is three
times bigger than this it's a
swollen don't think that happens it does
when guys don't see each other not
everybody there are a lot of guys when
they don't see each other for 15 years
20 years 25 years or more old college
buddies they were really good friends
drank a lot when they were young
together had a lot of fun maybe even
played Sports together and they meet up
later and right when they see each other
that's a conversation that has happened
a lot where one guy he don't care he'll
just say it because it's a buddy of his
he'll even laugh about it and then he'll
just get a drink but he'll say what
happened to you man like what's going on
are you seeing the right doctor are you
watching your weight and it doesn't even
mean they're
overweight what happens is when we swell
we change as the years go on and our
heads get bigger even our chest can get
bigger our frame can get bigger but it's
not supposed to get bigger but it does
so it's not just their head gets bigger
but their nose gets bigger did you ever
see that out there like somebody's nose
it's two times bigger than it was or
three times bigger than it was or it
gets really bulbous lots of veins on
there to or just red did you ever see a
guy where the nose is just protruding
it's all all swollen and big cheeks all
swollen and you also see it in people's
faces and heads where it's almost like
even above their eyes their foreheads
swell out their ears get bigger they
even get red it's like it happens over
time as the years go by two or three
years another two or three years 10
years later 15 years and it just
develops it's like some kind of
metamorphosis you know you might be
thinking well yeah sure when someone
gets overweight everything's just going
to get bigger but I'm not talking about
that I'm not talking about weight yes
you can have weight you can be
overweight and still have this
additional problem but this is a
separate
problem you could be thin and everything
just gets thick widens out and
everything just gets big including your
head everything and not be overweight
yes you can have EX excess weight and
this additional swelling problem of
things just kind of
enlarging because that's what it really
is everything's enlarging it's
swelling but it's not just in
intermittent or acute swelling that
happened at one time it's a slow slow
development and you can't see it you
just live your life and it happens every
every single day now there are people
that see any kind of
subtleties women see subtleties they see
if they're swelling a little bit or it
goes down but that could be bloating and
fluid retention see people can have flu
retention for years they expand with
fluid retention they feel like they have
fluid retention they feel the swelling
women feel that and then it goes down
then it goes up goes down but that's
separate that's sep separate than a
thickening an expansion of tissue that
happens over time as the years go on a
thickening is different than lymphatic
fluid buildup where you're swelling a
little bit you go to the lymphatic
massage therapist get some work done you
feel better for a couple days and then
it starts all over again and you're up
and down little bit of swelling fluid
retention and then it goes down little
bit of swelling
goes down you have a little too much
salt goes up you eat a little too much
party food goes up don't eat for a half
a day goes down go see the lymphatic
massage therapist goes down and then it
just does this thing and you play this
game this is different because you can
play that game live your life but
there's this other thing happening as
the years are going on it's this
thickening of connective
tissue this widening that happens
we just start expanding and still you
can have that fluid retention still you
can go to see your massage therapist and
lymphatic drainage massage can still do
all that but you're still getting wider
and it doesn't mean it's weight it
doesn't mean it's fat or anything like
you're gaining all this weight of course
you can have that too you can be
somebody that's gaining weight so you're
moving up on the weight and you have the
fluid retention and swelling
and your thickening which is a different
thing and we're talking about the body
widening and thickening the connective
tissue and the joints and everything
expanding there are people who get their
lymphatic
massage for years decades and as the
years go by they get it they're eating
pretty good they're eating pure enough
they don't eat a lot of processed foods
a lot of times they'll go on a healthy
keto diet or even a healthy vegetarian
diet or healthy vegan diet they care
about their health they exercise
regularly they take care of themselves
they sleep good they try to get 10 hours
of sleep every night and they're back to
the massage therapist and they're
getting wider as the years go on thicker
as the years go on you see a photograph
of them when they were 25 years old and
then you see them when they're 45 years
old something's changed and it's not
about aging has nothing to do with aging
just that by the time they got to 45
years old something
happened something happened within their
body some kind of transformation occurs
everything thickened up and widened and
it wasn't aging that did this and all
these years they did their fluid
retention Management program the fluid
retention Management program was
caffeine a diuretic always kind of
peeing out all their fluid not staying
that hydrated all those years so they
didn't have that much water because
they're kind of afraid of it they're at
their massage therapist they're at their
lymphatic massage therapist and they're
afraid to crank in all the water because
they feel like they're just going to
balloon up so they done all this
management over the years including
things like body wraps all kinds of
massages different diets different
exercise programs dry brushing INF red
sauna steam
saunas Steam Baths all these things but
as time goes on it was just management
as the years go by managing yes
sometimes their vices little alcohol
when they want to sometimes too salty or
greasy oily foods but they were managing
and taking care of themselves in between
it all and doing that lymphatic drainage
Mage constantly and as the years gone by
something still happened and it was
Unstoppable for some reason they just
got thick and their head
enlarged not just their head thickened
up but their body thickened up even
their feet thickened up but why well
we're going to head there in a little
bit we still got a lot more to talk
about and what I notice right now is
that young people people in their 20s
that are into Health are doing the
lymphatic drainage they're going to see
the massage therapist they're getting
lymphatic drainage done and they think
they found the Holy Grail now I support
lymphatic drainage I support massage
therapy I think it's one of the greatest
things out there but it's been out there
it's already been out there it's not new
we already have Decades of women using
this management tool and still by the
time they turn 40 it could be subtle but
there is a thickening happening to the
tissue tissue connective tissue to the
joints sometimes it's more noticeable as
it's happening throughout the years and
it's not so subtle but it could be
passed off as excess weight gain so if
weight is gaining it's like well no it's
cuz I'm gaining too much weight so then
when you try to lose the weight you
obviously thin out a little bit and see
think that must be it but there's this
other thing happening within it all this
actual ual tissue expansion that's
occurring but when you're young and
you're just dealing with some bloating
and you want to look your best and feel
your best and you don't feel that great
and you're into Health it's easy to be
like oh my God my lymphatic drainage
massage it's the greatest I'm so happy
let me go on social media I'll do a post
about it now and talk about it and then
it Trends and today since swelling is
becoming so big so many people are
swelling out there by the millions
because it's becoming an actual symptom
and condition that's happening to
everybody that social media is blowing
up about lymphatic drainage and
lymphatic massage for your swelling but
no one's saying that we've had
Generations before all of them before
the young people that already did it
been there and done that years of
lymphatic drainage to try to manage and
as the years went by their tissue
expanded and these same Generations also
did the body wraps they did the dry
brushing they did different diet
programs they intermittent fasted they
waved back and forth vacillated from
eating to not eating but what's the real
reason we're swelling and need a
lymphatic massage what's the real reason
to begin with the lymphatic massage is
not the real reason you're swelling to
start with that's just a a Band-Aid
until you swell again a day later or 3
days later or a week later what caused
the swelling allowing you to have to go
get a lymphatic drainage massage you
know what's crazy is according to
alternative medicine and conventional
Medicine Science which they teach a lot
of professionals is that the body
cleanses itself so you don't need to
cleanse or to do a cleanse or to do an
actual juice or anything because your
body takes care of itself but those same
people same professionals say oh you
better go get a massage you better go
get a lymphatic massage so basically you
become a te on a cow where you have to
be milked every other day because your
body can't do it itself but I'm confused
here cuz they say your body cleanses
itself so why are they then telling you
to go get a lymphatic drainage massage
if your body cleanses perfectly
naturally all on its own and why do we
need a manual squeeze you lay there on a
table and somebody has to push and
squeeze and massage and rub anywhere
they can find that feels a little bit
more swollen especially anything
lymphatic that they can actually access
I've always been supportive of lymphatic
drainage massage and massage and but
I've also been mindful that it's a
luxury because not everybody has $100 a
week or $100 every 3 days or two days to
get it done or the time maybe they're
busy a lot of demands in life they're
working hard maybe they don't have the
excess cash maybe it's not a resource
that they have to do but yet on social
media of course I see a lot of people
like just had my drainage massage it was
incredible I'm going to get it again in
a couple days I'm going to get it next
week and and my massage therapist wants
me there five times a month six times a
month and I'm adding it up and I'm like
some massage therapy now it's like $150
some is like $60 if you're lucky but
lymphatic drainage somewhere Falls in
that area where okay well it's five
times a month or six times a month if
you have that resource to manage things
incredible but I'm always about getting
down to the actual problem fixing the
root the root cause of why this SW is
happening all the time and again we're
just managing so we're not fixing the
root problem because as each year goes
by the tissue expansion is developing
and that's not being stopped by a
lymphatic massage and that's not being
stopped by a regular massage that's
helping with managing fluid retention
but it's not stopping that thickening
that happens with everybody as they're
getting older each year goes by and each
decade goes by and everything just
starts to expand and get bigger I posted
a video about edema and swelling and
it's pretty interesting I would love to
read you some of the comments I thought
the head getting larger was part of
middle age it's so unattractive a person
responds I know someone who started
having this problem in their early 30s
age is not a factor in some cases here's
another I feel swollen all the time
can't figure it out eating healthy but
healthy foods causing me to feel bloated
I feel better when I don't eat at all
someone responds me too I feel like our
food has been poisoned from all angles
thread continues on I started doing
lymphatic drainage massages and they
have helped me so much I'm way less
swollen another person try vibration
plate after another person same goes
with me feels like I'd rather not eat so
I won't feel that way another person
says this is Meo too when I don't eat I
feel so much better another person says
me too I feel best fasted me too another
person another person I was eating clean
keto but still didn't lose weight like
carnivore until I stopped eating the
vegetables too another person said I'm
currently in a winning path someone else
me too I feel like a puffy marshmallow
I'm still getting over breast implant
illness somebody else try fasting for 48
hours did wonders for me when I swelled
it's like a hard reset on computer lost
14 quick pounds cuz fluids were sponged
to my body the next response I've gone a
day without eating and I did see a
difference in the swelling but no energy
to do anything with a sad face another
person try cutting out vegetables only
eat fruit with seeds and grassfed meat
with heaps of fat another person I do
eat grass-fed meats and grass fed butter
and olive oil ghee but lots of veggies
not much fruits I'll try cutting the
veggies out thank you with a heart
another person from experience veggies
bloat you and give you gas and make you
feel funny cut it out papaya pineapple
coconut water eat one large meal at
night a new guy says stop eating all
carbs and the swelling will go down so
other person said oh my God I thought I
was alone another person nope you're not
alone it sucks and it's getting worse as
I get older and then same but I went
carnivore and lost 55 lbs in 4 months no
exercise I also take NAC supplements for
liver and nitrous oxide for blood flow
someone responds bentonite clay for
calcium form Googled it give it a go
removes toxins from your body other
person bentonite clay is not recommended
it ruins the intestinal tract somebody
else awesome some info thank you I'm
learning how to live with crohn's and a
naturopath told me to try it goes to
show there's bad so-called good
this other person chimes in intermittent
fasting and minimum eating of carbs and
sugar and more protein stop my swelling
and inflammation and this other person
most days I fast 23 hours and I eat one
meal a day it's not always easy to do
every day and every day is a new day and
then oh my God those are all my symptoms
it's horrible with a sad face but yes
this is very true thank you for
explaining this in more detail another
person exercise daily to combat this
running helps and then Barbie says
running genuinely does help even if it's
10 minutes a day and then I've always
had this problem like I was full of air
it's inflammation eating processed foods
fast food soda Etc it's all poison
someone else I feel swollen all the time
and I eat very little someone said me
too another I can relate with this don't
have migraines but my face is rounder
since 5 years ago but I'm the same
weight another person key equals
intermittent fasting this other person
thank you for the validation doctors
just look at you like you're crazy when
you tell them you feel
swollen and somebody else yes that's me
right now another person yes I need help
from this and somebody else so what can
we do for this and then somebody said
says is this a new phenomenon is it
something that has also been prevalent
in the past
Generations new person says this is my
daughter another person and here I was
thinking it was menopause somebody else
my legs swell in the summer so what can
we conclude from these comments to begin
with everybody's swelling or has some
type of flute retention problem and
they're struggling but what was their
Solutions like all their Wise
information to help others one was just
don't eat that's one like go 20 3 hours
without eating well I don't know if
that's going to work for people who got
to work a job or if they have a
demanding schedule um let's see what was
another one okay eat lots of grass-fed
beef and ghee and olive oil oh that's a
stomach ache I'm already feeling when I
think about that because they were like
don't eat any vegetables
okay so so if I was needing help and I
went on that thread and I was like well
I need to find some help in here okay so
don't eat any vegetables but eat a lot
of ghee a lot of people just stopped
eating is is that the best way to go
just stop eating it's not sustainable
really because it's a roller coaster
ride as some of them stay they just had
no energy and it was really hard to do
and intermittent fasting may not not be
the best route there's a lot of
drawbacks and it's not easy to do check
out my podcast episode on intermittent
fasting it's almost 2 hours and it's
highly informative now when somebody's
swelling and they say they're swelling
is it the same swelling that someone
else is going through is it the same
swelling somebody else has or if
somebody's bloating and they feel kind
of swollen is it the same bloating and
swelling as someone else
or when someone says their hands are
swollen like their fingers are swollen
and their joints feel a little bit
swollen is that the same as somebody
else's
bloating or is it all the same or is it
really different well there isn't a
one-size fits-all here everybody does
have different nuances
subtleties different reasons for
bloating different types of swelling
some people bloat in their digestive
tract and they feel like they're
swelling but it's different than someone
else who's not bloating in their
digestive tract but yet they're swelling
underneath their skin and then there's
someone who has all of it they're
bloated and they're swelling and then
there's someone who has a weight gain
issue where they're gaining weight so
they're gaining excess fat and they're
swelling with retention fluid retention
and they can have digestive bloating
plus tissue
expansion and if they're a woman they
can have their period if they're a man
they're not going to have their period
so that part of the swelling may not be
in the mix and some women swell a lot
more during their period and some women
swell a lot less there's endless
combinations of swelling too and fluid
retention 100 people can have swollen
hands and and 100 people can have a 100
different reasons why they're swollen in
the hands because everything changes one
person ate this the other person ate
this one person has this problem inside
their body and the other person has this
problem inside their body their swelling
may look almost the same but it's not
the same even if it looked the same it's
not the same one person can have
endometriosis and it's contributing
adding into all their swelling in a
different way another person can have
IBS intestinal tract issues they're on
the toilet a lot they're aggravated
their intestinal tracts inflamed they
have diarrhea another person has fatty
liver liver is all congested stagnant
sluggish overworked overburdened another
person could have gout somebody else
could have an entirely different issue
around all of this they could have a
really bad chemical sensitivity it's
never going to be the same the exact
measurements the exact type of fluid or
amount of fluid or amount of tissue
expansion or the amount of gas inside
the intestinal tract either or how the
intestinal tract is built and how it
moves and the peristaltic action
combination of bloating with the
digestive system swelling with the liver
and lymphatic system and the
reproductive system and then the amounts
and the locations the locations of a
fluid locations of the swelling are
going to be different for everybody so
why is everybody swelling how come
everybody swelling everybody's got some
type of flute retention or some type of
layer on them or swelling so let's go
into the different causes we're talking
about mystery swelling mystery fluid
retention we're not talking about if
someone has a clearcut case where their
heart is having a problem or kidney
failure and they're swelling because of
kidneys and heart a big part stems from
the liver that's the place where a lot
of Calamity occurs our livers get toxic
as the years go on see your liver is a
filter like a fish filter in a fish tank
that's filtering the water your liver is
filtering your blood it's filtering
everything before the lymphatic system
even gets its chance your liver is doing
it at first your lymphatic system was
never designed to handle what the world
throws at us we're talking about
pesticides herbicides fungicides the air
freshener chemicals the fragrances the
Colones perfumes all the different
petrochemicals and the toxins that fall
out of the sky all the different
Pharmaceuticals all the carpet cleaning
solvents and chemicals that come out of
carpets all the secondhand smoke all the
vaping all the psychedelics in the brain
all the different recreational drugs and
all the chemicals that are used on them
when they're growing nanotechnology
falling out of the sky now
nanotechnology and the Pharmaceuticals
hair products chemicals and those body
products makeup and then tattoos the ink
itself all the toxic heavy metals I know
people say well that wasn't my tattoo
ink but all ink has toxic heavy metals
even the vegan ink or the cruelty-free
ink but either way all of this wasn't
for the lymphatic system but it became
the lymphatic system's problem but it
was never supposed to be our lymphatic
system was not our main filter it was
just there for our normal bodily
problems and functions our liver is
supposed to take the hit it's the Fall
Guy It's supposed to take on the toxins
first that are in this world see we're
not supposed to naturally be up against
the toxins we're up against but the the
industries create them and then we get
exposed to them and our liver it's a
first line of defense that's the big
filter all this blood is rushing through
the liver it's that big massive filter
it's grabbing onto toxins poisons
pathogens toxic heavy metals chemicals
and it's collecting them to keep the
blood clean enough to protect the heart
your lymphatic system is critical its
job is to clean and purify by to get the
bodily waste some of the bodily waste
out of the bloodstream and if some of
that bodily waste is a pathogen a
bacteria a microb a virus then the
lymphatic job is to suck it up and have
your lymphocytes try to kill it your
lymphatic system is dependent on the
liver to do the big cleanup because if
the liver doesn't do the big cleanup
including pathogens and all the
industrial toxins and exposures if the
liver doesn't do that well lymphatic
system pays the price the liver gets so
overloaded and so bogg down so fill the
toxins and poisons it starts to get
sluggish stagnant fats even get balled
up inside the liver the liver starts to
slow down and slow down it can't produce
its bio reserves it can't function as
good as it needs to be and then the
immune system inside the liver starts to
weaken and the lymphatic system relies
on the liver's immune system to handle
the big pathogens the pathogenic
infections the Epstein bars the shingles
viruses the hhv 6s the herpes simplexes
it's there to handle those pathogens so
that the lymphatic system lymphocytes
don't have to take on the whole storm
but it all goes wrong what starts to
happen is the liver starts to break down
it can't handle it itself because it's
so overburdened so stagnant and sluggish
it's not even just the chemicals and the
pathogens it's also the way we eat it's
also the things we use like the caffeine
and all the vinegars the liver's already
up against so much but we bombard it and
then throw the alcohol in the mix or
drinking and the liver has to suck up
the alcohol
it becomes a problem over time where
your liver the filter weakens starts to
break down yeah it might look good at
the doctor's office they might not see
anything wrong with your liver yet but
they don't see everything anybody who's
been sick long enough knows that they
don't see everything so the liver starts
to not work properly and then the
lymphatic system has to work harder but
here's the thing it's not equipped to
work harder and that's why everybody's
swelling and that leads us to tissue
expansion tissue expansion is not
lymphatic system expansion tissue
expansion is all the poisons and toxins
that got out of the liver and the
lymphatic system couldn't process or
handle them or clean them those toxins
and poisons and chemicals went into deep
connection itive tissue and deep into
the organs deep into the brain deep into
the
spleen deep into the intestinal tract
lining deep into the skin these tissues
got saturated overloaded with multitudes
of toxins and poisons and pathogenic
waste year after year after year decade
after decade even in the bones and then
everything started to widen out tissue
started to expand joints started to
expand this is beyond just fluid
retention this is beyond just lymphatic
fluid this is toxins and poisons and
pathogenic waste that found its way into
the guts of the person and I don't mean
intestinal tract I mean into the core of
their Essence into their bones and
connective tissue and tendons
right into their joints and organs and
it expands because cells expand because
cells themselves that are made in the
nerves and the connective tissue and the
joints they can't hold all the poisons
and toxins so they inflame and swell and
then there's the dead cells all the
cells that have died they didn't get
flushed out they didn't cleanse out
lymphatic system didn't cleanse them out
liver didn't cleanse them out all the
dead cells that gathered around the
joints tendons the connective tissue in
and around the organs create a swelling
all on their own so an expansion happens
with our organs and tissue and Bones
because we have all this dead tissue
intertwined in all of it that never
escaped while surrounded by living cells
that are also filled with toxin and
poisons and they're at their limit and
is everything's swelling we need more
blood so vessels develop varicose veins
are a prime example of excess veins that
are actually growing to feed areas that
were expanding because of a lot of
toxins and poisons either from pathogens
chemical exposure or even weight gain or
even scar tissue or injuries that
expansion called for more veins to be
produced but see this expansion is
subtle all through the body as well
where you don't need a varicose vein but
these tiny blood vessels are created all
around expanding tissue so a thickening
happens if the liver doesn't get what it
needs to toxification Cleansing the care
it really needs to carry us through life
it enlarges gets stagnant sluggish gets
filled with too much poison and Toxin
and then
those poisons and toxins fill every
organ they fill the brain they fill the
heart a heart can enlarge as the years
go on because it gets so toxic because
of the liver being a weakened filter
expansion of tissue can happen in an
obvious way too not just internally
where you can't see it or can't see the
blood vessels internally it can happen
externally in a way like when someone's
nose gets bulbous and big there's lots
of more new blood vessels in the nose
that have grown so the nose got large
because it has more blood vessels and
more tissue this expansion is obvious
when it comes down to a nose but it's
not obvious when it's inside all of our
other connective tissue and everywhere
else in our organs we can't notice it we
just notice the person is expanding over
the years so you take a look at a
picture when they were in college when
they were 20 years old and then you take
a look at them when they're 50 and you
see the difference when the liver is all
filled up there's no room anymore in it
to hold all those toxins so those toxins
end up leaving the liver escaping or
going straight through the filter
straight through the liver in the
bloodstream and then the lymphatic
system gets way overburdened it can't
handle that toxic load so the toxins
have nowhere to go there either but the
lymphatics system still draws the toxins
in problem is the toxins stay in the
lymphatic system they have nowhere else
to go and then you need more fluid in
the lymphatic system to dilute the
toxins so then the lymphatic system
keeps on receiving more fluid drawing
more fluid in to try to dilute the
toxins that are inside the lymphatic
system so a trap occurs a catch 22 in
the lymphatic system lymphatic system
needs to try to filter but it can't it's
too overloaded so the Vicious Cycle
keeps on carrying on and carrying on and
as that's happening more fluid is
building up accumulating in the
lymphatic system with more toxins what's
interesting though is this can happen
with the entire lymphatic system the
entire lymphatic system within the body
so you can't see it's more fluid based
in one area versus more fluid retention
based in another area it's the whole
body is retaining fluid because the
lymphatic system is overburdened within
the entire body this can be hard to see
on a person one person can have a very
thin layer of this what that means is
their whole lymphatic system is slightly
swollen so the retaining fluid the
retaining water but you can't quite see
it the person may be able to feel it
though and then there's the person that
can see it they can look in the mirror
in the morning they can see when it's
gone and they can look in the mirror at
the end of the day and they can see when
it appears cuz it can build up all day
long at night their liver is trying to
detox trying to cleanse trying to push
whatever it can out by morning
everything is down a bit this is why
people who are more swollen at the end
of the day des swell in the morning and
the cycle goes on every single day this
person though know has different times
and moments in their life where all of a
sudden they're like whoa they're in
front of the mirror and they're like
everything's down I'm looking good I'm
wearing the pants I want to wear I'm
wearing the shirt I want to wear I like
this look and then a week later they got
the layer building up again the fluid
retention is building in their system
their whole body is getting that extra
fluid retention they put their pants on
they put their shirt on and now they're
like oh I don't like this and then it
looks like they're gain gaining weight
they're getting fat when really they're
not gaining weight they're not gaining
extra fat they're gaining extra fluid
and that extra fluid is just pushing
everything outward and this is where a
lot of confusion lies you think you're
getting heavier and heavier but you're
not gaining lots of fat you're gaining
lots of fluid there's people who yes are
overweight they do have 10 lbs of extra
fat on their body or 20 lbs of extra fat
on their body but yet they're 50 lb
overweight they have 20 to 30 lb of
fluid retention and that's where a lot
of confusion lies that's why when
someone says I intermittent fasted I
didn't eat for 23 hours or I didn't eat
for 48 hours and I lost 27 lbs what
happens is they didn't lose 27 PBS of
fat they lost 27 pounds of fluid but
here's the problem you have to eat it's
the only way to sustain be functional
have your brain working you can't always
be on no food so then when you start
eating again living your life the fluid
builds all back up again and you're back
to square one there's so many different
variations somebody may be only up about
three or four pounds of fat on their
body with 10 pounds of fluid somebody
else might have five pounds of fat on
their body 12 pounds of fluid someone
may have 5 lbs of fat on their body and
5 lbs of fluid and someone else might
have 75 lbs of fat with an additional 40
lb of fluid there are endless
combinations no two are alike
everybody's different there are so many
variables within everyone they're not
exact they can be off the mark on ounces
they could be different in pounds but
none of them are the same but that's not
the only differences there's differences
everywhere for example what's causing
the person's lymphatic swelling what's
causing their flu retention is different
than somebody else with their flute
retention for example somebody could
have Epstein bar inside the liver and
that Epstein bar virus could be feeding
off of mercury inside the liver then
releasing a Mercury based neurotoxin
into the bloodstream because the liver
is so overburdened it can't contain it
all when that neurotoxin starts floating
around in the bloodstream it finds its
way into the lymphatic system so the
lymphatic system draws it in but our
lymphatic system isn't used to such an
unnatural Toxin and poison so it sits in
the lymphatic system and then requires
more fluid to build up into the
lymphatic system in order to control
that toxin how does the lymphatic system
control the toxin the immune cells have
to eat up the Toxin and that's where
your immune system gets overburdened
inside the lymphatic system you got an
army of lymphocytes inside your
lymphatic system they're there to clean
up the mess but they can die they can
expire especially if the toxins and
poisons are very strong the more toxins
that enter the lymphatic system then
more fluid has to be in the lymphatic
system your lymphocytes can't be in a
small amount of fluid while up against a
large amount of toxins and as the larger
amount of toxins build up inside your
lymphatic system you need more
lymphocytes but more lymphocytes can't
do their job cleaning up the toxins if
there's very little fluid because the
toxins are now turning the fluid into a
toxic sludge so then a requirement
occurs need more fluid more fluid goes
into the lymphatic system to give your
lymphocytes and immune cells a chance so
they could swim around the toxins and
gather them up this is why when somebody
gets a lymphatic massage at this point
it pushes the fluid out and a large
amount of toxins Escape into the
bloodstream and that person if they're
chronically ill and they're dealing with
any kind of condition or autoimmune tend
to get sicker after lymphatic massage if
someone isn't that sick and they don't
have a lot of fluid buildup inside their
lymphatic system and they get a
lymphatic massage they may not feel it
so much it may feel more of a relief so
they had that drainage occur and they're
happy but someone else could be really
sick and have a lot more fluid now
here's the difference too someone's
lymphatic fluid could be a lot more
toxic than someone else's lymphatic
fluid someone might have a different
Toxin and a different poison in their
fluid somebody else might have less of a
toxin less of a pathogen based toxin not
as toxic so when the the fluid escapes
into the bloodstream the person doesn't
get so sick but the person can get sick
if it's really toxic and it escapes into
the bloodstream but here's the next
problem we just think that this fluid
magically leaves us after we pushed it
out of our lymphatic system so if
someone had a lot of toxic fluid in
their lymphatic system and they had a
lymphatic massage they think oh good
will just pee it out and alls well it
doesn't always work that way a lot of
the toxins end up back into the liver a
stagnant sluggish toxic liver a
dysfunctional liver the toxins go right
back up into it but since the liver
can't hold on to any more toxins because
it's stagnant and sluggish it sends it
back out now it's recycling it ends up
back into the lymphatic system 3 days
later the person's blown up again 5 days
later the person's blown up again a week
later they're blown up again because it
just recycled you pushed it out it went
through the liver then it went back up
into the bloodstream back into the
lymphatic system it's a vicious cycle it
keeps on circulating and then the
person's like whoa I'm back in here
again I have to live here at my massage
therapists because each day it builds
back up sometimes it takes a day
sometimes it's three days days sometimes
it's 5 days our lymphatic systems are
one of the most important body systems
we have so everybody's focused on the
lymphatic system while missing the liver
what they're doing is they're
overlooking the core of the problem the
place where it all starts if we don't
fix the liver we can't fix the lymphatic
system but the liver is no fun to work
with it's like okay I have a liver the
liver is stagnant what do I do what do I
take what do I eat lymphatic system
massage that's actually fun well it's
fun for a lot of people that's what I
hear every day well I'm just going to go
and get serviced I'm going to head there
relax ah I'm on the table oo I'm
thinking about nothing but mantras
thinking about my affirmations my
massage therapist is amazing such a
great person I'm relaxing ah this feels
so good ooh I'm stagnant here okay that
feels good ooh yeah I'm a little sore
here Ah that's nice getting this fluid
out of me it's so great the liver no fun
it's like what I can't have a martini
what I can't ever drink what I can't
have a greasy fatty meal what I have to
worry about what I eat I have to worry
about what I take liver that's the
problem no let me just go to my massage
therapist I'll get my lymphatic massage
she or he can do all the work let them
do the work that's their job I want them
to service me but me what 32 ounces of
celery juice I don't know if I want to
do that today huh spirulina no not going
to do that huh heavy metal detox
smoothie uh maybe not I have an
appointment at my lymphatic massage
therapist I think what I'll do is just
lay on the table think about waves on
the beach think about that vacation I
took years ago think about about things
that make me happy and get my massage
massages are very healing old old staple
going back thousands of years when the
first human being put their hand on the
other human being there was a feeling it
had touch is critical for a lot of
people massage is healing in so many
ways I've said this forever and you get
instant
gratification instant results and a lot
of people like that like the swelling
goes down for a lot of people people
really quick and it feels so good ooh my
body feels so good after that massage
it's like instant gratification you can
even see results right away I always
recommend to my family and friends
people I love get a massage it's very
healing very powerful and if you get a
really good massage therapist incredible
really helpful one that cares has
compassion even better if you're
somebody that's really sick has a lot of
flute retention
you're living with a lot of that flute
retention it's really hard and you have
to get lymphatic massage a lot I
recommend trying to fix the core issue
get down to the liver start to do
healing tools clean the liver up so that
you don't have to get lymphatic massage
every day or other day or three times a
week so you don't have to constantly
force the fluid out fix the liver clean
the pathogens out and the toxins out
kill the pathogens help support your
lymphocytes and the rest of your immune
system and eventually take yourself out
of that vicious cycle and then there's
people with severe lymphadema where
they're swelling in their leg their
whole leg swollen they're swelling in
their arm swelling in their breast
swelling in their feet their calves
where it's severe and they have to use
compression stockings and they're
suffering from lymphadema because they
had an injury or they had a surgery y or
they had breast cancer something else
happened or an obstruction is going on
and they're dealing with some severe
lymphadema in a certain section in their
body and even then it's critical to fix
the liver rebuild our immune system our
immune system is not just our
lymphocytes and our lymphatic system so
if somebody has a damaged lymphatic
system from an injury breast cancer or a
surgery then that's okay because our
immune system is in other places too we
have an immune system in our bloodstream
that's where a large amount of our
immune system is we have an immune
system in our liver we have an immune
system in other organs so this immune
system needs to get coddled it needs to
be cared for it needs to be recovered
and that's a Powerhouse for us so not
only do we fix and heal the liver but we
also heal the liver's immune system and
our immune system throughout our body
lymphatic problems aren't genetic now I
know there's misin information out there
the gene blame game that's out there
where anything anybody has they'll just
be like whoa It's your genes it's your
genes that's doing it you got bad genes
faulty genes lympha is from your Gene
problem genetic man and that's the
people are told all the time it's not
genetic There's real true causes it
could seem genetic if our parents or our
ancestors had it or somebody in our
family has it and we're like whoo it is
genetic but no no we still have the same
Epstein bar virus passed down from our
family pathogens are passed down from
our family line it's not genetics it's
bugs passed down toxins passed down too
toxic heavy metals passed down from
generation to generation to generation
or the new generation of people got a
new exposure all together so the whole
family the whole family line in that
generation got that recent exposure if
someone's not that toxic they're just
slightly toxic they don't have a lot of
neurotoxins and dermato toxins they
don't have a lot of pathogens and
pathogen waste they haven't been exposed
to a lot of different chemicals if that
happens their lymphatic fluid will be
clear it'll be a clear fluid now if
someone's really toxic and they've been
exposed to a lot of pathogens a lot of
bugs they're fighting a lot of lowgrade
infections they gotten a lot of
diagnoses like
autoimmune then that fluid isn't clear
science of research says it's clear but
it's not it's got a yellow tinge to it
sometimes it could be very yellow
sometimes it could be pus-like colored
because if it gets too dirty and the
lymphatic fluid is too gunked up it will
be and if the fluid gets too
then what happens more fluid has to go
into the lymphatic system Sy to dilute
all the toxins and poisons and then that
person's lymphatic system is now blown
up larger so now someone is retaining
more fluid lymphatic wise they're
swelling more and they're more
uncomfortable and this leads to
something that a lot of people go
through all the time which is hot
weather sensitivities to when it gets
hot outside or really humid outside so
summertime comes around it's really hot
out really humid and the person's really
uncomfortable they're sitting outside
and they can't stand it any longer
because it feels like the swelling is
enlarging or they feel like they're
swelling more than someone else and then
somebody else that doesn't have that
fluid retention is fine in the Heat and
they look okay they look like they're
dealing with it they look happy they're
doing something maybe an activity and
then somebody else they're actually
suffering it's like I can't handle the
Heat or the humidity I have to stay
inside it's just just hard on my body I
feel just like so bloated or swollen
what determines the difference between
someone with fluid retention not
handling the humidity and Heat versus
somebody else with fluid retention
handling the humidity and heat is the
toxic nature of the lymphatic fluid so
if it has that yellow tinge to it if
it's dirty fluid if it has a lot of
toxins and poisons and the color of the
fluid isn't clear inside the lymphatic
system then they're going to struggle
more because when you're in the heat and
humidity in the Sun and you're highly
toxic and the fluid retention is highly
toxic the body reacts differently it
weighs you down makes you feel more
swollen makes you feel more
uncomfortable toxins in the lymphatic
fluid react to body heat so if you're
somebody and you're out in the sun
you're hanging out it's really a hot day
it's 90 it's humid outside and your
body temperature starts to raise your
core temperature starts to raise if your
lymphatic vessels are filled with toxic
yellow fluid then as the core
temperature raises in your body and it's
hot outside the toxins and poisons
create additional heat and then more
expansion occurs from the heat CU it's
not just the fluid that's Heating up
it's the toxins inside the fluid that
are heating up and those toxins start to
expand and if someone is that toxic they
usually have toxins everywhere else
floating around they have toxins
floating around in their bloodstream and
in other organs so when the heat happens
outside the humidity goes up they feel
not good and then when they go inside
the house and they're in air
conditioning they're not feeling great
that day because they're so toxic the
heat expanded a lot of the toxins
throughout the bloodstream and the
organs and then they feel unwell and
they feel like they got sun sickness but
they weren't outside in the sun for a
long time but yet they feel sick after
being in the sun that means that if they
were to go somewhere to a beach or sit
outside for a long period of time in
heat and Sun there's a good chance they
are going to feel very sick a day later
or that same day or the end of the day
because they're so toxic and they have
not only toxins in their lymphatic fluid
and they have the fluid retention but
they have toxins floating everywhere
else inside the body if you're curious
of what kind of toxins these are it
could be neurotoxins from low-grade
viral infections dermat toxins from
lowgrade viral infections toxins from
all kinds of different bacteria and
viruses along with toxic heavy metals
other chemical toxins all floating
around so now let's talk about when
people say I feel best when I don't eat
hey I stopped eating I don't eat for 21
hours and then I have a meal I try not
to eat for 2 days it's kind of hard but
I do it anyway hey I only eat meat I eat
beef all day and then I top it off with
some ghee I won't eat a vegetable hey I
feel better ever since I quit sugar well
they didn't quit sugar they quit
everything not just sugar I feel better
when I quit sugar um hey I feel better
just drinking a little bit of water and
then eating like every other day all
right so let's explore these when
someone says I feel better now that I
quit sugar now when they say that you
think wait a minute what were they
eating well they weren't eating sugar
you know like a box of sugar or a bag of
sugar in the grocery store where it's
processed sugar and you're just doing
tablespoons or sugar cubes right when
you're a kid and you have a sugar cube
it wasn't like they were eating a whole
bunch of sugar cubes all day long what
they're talking about is processed foods
like cookies cakes Donuts treats ice
cream coffees with lots of sugar put in
and cream or iced coffees with lots of
sugar and cream baked goods uh
croissants with powdered sugar on top
candy bars like really bad candy bar
bars and then those health food store
candy bars that are supposedly good
candy bars that have all that sugar in
it too either way candy bars and then
maybe like candies but like gummy bears
with gelatin in it and all kinds of yes
a little bit of sugar but natural
flavors gelatin other additives
preservatives and when you think about
it is a candy bar all sugar is a
croissant all sugar is a cookie all
sugar is a cake doughnut or ice cream
all sugar no it's not there's sugar in
there but there's also all this fat or
additives or flavorings there's all this
other junk or some type of grain that's
not a good grain but yet when the person
stopped eating all of these they say I
feel better when I'm not eating sugar um
you weren't eating sugar yeah you kind
of were eating a little sugar that was
in the mix no you are eating milk
proteins Dairy you're eating all this
other grain like bad grain you were
eating gluten you were having lots of
fat you were eating butter you were
eating lard you were eating vegetable
oil you were eating all these other
things MSG additives red dye number one
you were eating all of that and when you
quit all those processed foods those
cakes cookies donuts and all of that you
started feeling better but what you tell
everybody else is I quit sugar and that
made me feel better so then somebody
else hears that and they'll go oh I
better quit fruit because fruit has
sugar in it so that person said they
quit sugar and they're feeling better I
better stop eating my apples meanwhile
there's all these health professionals
that say that out there oh quit sugar
look out for sugar and they just add to
it they spread a bad message and then
everybody's confused so what about when
the person says I only eat meat try that
that's the best way to do it grasp that
beef only and then I give myself a treat
and I have some ghee and then they say
they're doing so much better well
they're mono eating what happened was
they were originally confused about what
they were eating before all these years
because they were eating cakes cookies
donuts growing up they were eating
cheeseburgers because they like their
meat but they were eating the whole
cheeseburger they got rid of the bun so
now they're grainfree so now they're
moving out all these other things they
hear dairy's bad from someone so they
get rid of the dairy but a lot of people
who just eat meat do eat dairy too but
if you get somebody that mono eats only
meat they're doing the elimination deal
where they're eliminating all these
other Foods now when they eliminate
those other Foods they're eliminating
things that may have aggravated them and
they didn't know they were eliminating
some packaged food that has MSG in it
but they didn't know the MSG was causing
the problem or they're eliminating
gluten right dairy products they're
eliminating grains but some of those
grains were actually okay but they never
tried it where they only did Mill it
only so they decided to stay with the
fat which is the meat they were on a
high-fat diet All These Years anyway and
in the end when they decided to Mono eat
to try to do the food elimination they
kept with the fats and they kept with
the thing that they've been taught the
most as far as what the body needs high
protein high fat so they kept with the
meat but they got some results for a
little while mono eating can give you
results even when it's something not
great eventually all the fat from the
meat catches up to them because now
they're on just a meat diet meat diet
only and that catches up because they
need calories they need some type of
fuel and you can't get that from a piece
of meat because there's not enough
glucose in that piece of meat there's
only a little bit so then they start
hitting the wall after about 3 months
and they decide to bring in more meat so
they're eating more of it now they're
getting bloated they can't go to
bathroom good they're feeling kind of
sick they have no vegetables or leafy
greens in their diet and now they hit a
wall now they don't eat at all and
they're doing this thing where they
don't mono eat all day they take a day
off the next day they fill themselves up
with meat and they mono eat the meat
next day they don't eat and now they're
every other day and they're losing their
strength and losing their energy then
they find that they have to eat every
day to some degree so they do the
intermittent fasting but they only use
their meat they don't eat all day and
they have a whole bunch of meat at night
one meal a day eventually that doesn't
work anymore either that it's back to
the old drawing board which means a
binge eventually happens of other Foods
they're with a friend somewhere they're
out getting something to eat they're not
sticking to their diet in that moment
and they just lose it and they eat about
five slices of pizza and on their way
home they're like I'm going to get right
back to the drawing board I'm going to
get right back to eating my mono meat
that's when I felt the best I remember
and they're just stuck in the Vicious
Cycle all over again this is just one
example of trying to hack your bloating
and your swelling and your digestive
discomfort there's hundreds and hundreds
and hundreds examples and what they are
it's about people coming from a high fat
high protein diet right with some
goodies thrown in the mix too that
aren't good some processed foods and
they're in that realm and they have to
crawl out of that realm and so when they
do they do different approaches one
person might do a keto diet that works
for a little while then they have to
intermit and fast and do keto another
person might just do the carnivore
another person might do a vegan version
or a plant-based version it's all nut
Butters and nut Butters and stuff like
that at the end of the day and then
eventually they have to stop eating for
a day because they just get so sick
they're still doing the high fat diet
high protein diet and they don't realize
they're just stuck so everybody then
plays these guessing games like well I'm
not swelling that much today I better
not eat again this is working for me for
a minute let me do this green juice too
oh let me try this and they're just all
over the place each day is different
each month is different there's hundreds
of variations but they all have
something in common they all come from a
high fat high protein diet vegan or
animal protein they also have something
else in common they all have something
wrong with their health so why do they
feel better when someone says well I
just don't eat and I feel better that
way another person will be like I'm best
when I'm fasted another person is like
I'm better at one meal a day my swelling
goes down yeah when I don't eat that
much my swelling goes down why is that
happening how come their swelling goes
down when they stop eating for a while
because they stopped burdening they're
already overburdened liver and they
stopped burdening they're already over
burdened lymphatic system they stopped
eating they started cleansing they gave
their liver a break from all the fat
they eat and this is why the swelling
starts to go down what's interesting is
all these people stopping their eating
and their swelling goes down they're all
eating different diets all of them like
some are vegans some are plant-based
some are keto animal protein some are
just
carnivore it's a whole bunch of
different people some are just processed
foods just all they do is eat fast food
and processed food but either way it's
all these different diets no one's
eating the same diet but when they all
stop they're all like I feel better I'm
getting the swelling down I feel a
little better because they all got that
other thing in common they're all eating
all this fat so it's all this fat lard
butter oil nut Butters avocado processed
oils it's all that fat that's the thing
that they got in common yeah they got
different diets they all do it a
different way one person eats eggs in
the morning another person has eggs in
their salad in the afternoon another
person has eggs for dinner but they're
all doing the eggs oh and if they don't
do eggs then they're doing cheese if
they don't do cheese then they're doing
nuts either way they're all doing the
fat and the high fat it's burdening the
liver and that's what's in common on
that part now someone could only be
doing greasy fried fatty foods like
processed foods right from a diner
processed foods right from a fast food
takeout and they'll get the same results
when they stop eating as someone else
does when they eat a vegan diet filled
with nut Butters they all stop eating
their swelling goes down they're all
getting the same results even though
diets are vastly apart if we never feel
good when we're eating it can cause a
lot of confusion let's just face it
that's why when some Guru out there like
somebody in health that seems like they
got it all together they say well I
don't eat food's not important I eat
when I feel like it I can go days
without eating everybody goes
ooh that's the answer that's the Panacea
it's this Guru guy sits on a Mountaintop
and he meditates and he goes to all the
Retreats and everybody knows who he is
and he says he doesn't need to eat he's
like a lizard you just need one meal a
week and this guy's got it all down and
I feel sick when I eat and I try every
healthy diet there ever was every trendy
diet and I just can't eat but this guy
this guy here this Guru he's got it all
down he just doesn't need to eat that's
what I have to gravitate to like that's
the mission and you'll see the
consistencies out there people who are
into Health they're doing a certain diet
they get a whole bunch of people on
board everybody's watching them 6 months
later they alter their diet it's not
working but who cares about the six
months of people that watched them and
tried it too like who cares about them
all messing up or being in the dark or
not knowing where to go and being lost
switch gears so now that same influencer
or health professional or Guru is is now
doing a different take a different diet
so now it's a whole 6 months more of all
that watch me now watch me now here's my
morning routine here's what I do during
the day I'm on this new thing ofama jig
I'm taking this and then everybody
follows along and they're all following
along and it gets all messed up again
and then they shift gears again but it
happens over and over again you could
watch it sometimes it's just years and
years if they've been in it long enough
if somebody has been doing this for 5
years it's 5 years of mistake akes and
different directions and who pays for it
the people that watched and got invested
and they put their health at risk they
invested into what the person was doing
they lost 6 months or they lost another
year another year of what they could
have done for their health and the
reason why it went downhill was because
of the consistency what the health
professional they were watching was
doing was being inconsistent it's every
change every 4 months 6 months or every
year and that in consistency was proof
that the professional or the influencer
didn't know what they were doing to
begin with it was all hacks and
makeshift bait and switch it was all try
this get quick results instant
gratification oh doesn't work sorry guys
didn't mean to put you through that in
the last 6 months let's start again but
yet they really don't say sorry to
anybody they just go quiet for a while
reinvent themselves or act like it never
even happened and then you get new
followers
and the old ones just dissipate and fall
away so if we're at the point in
Everybody's Health and where we are
today that we all have to just stop
eating and that's the only way out and
that's the only fix then something's
terribly wrong because if we're not
eating and we're just starving ourselves
all day long or only eating one meal a
day then we're not getting the things we
need for our brain our liver our heart
the rest of our body systems our nervous
system we're not giving all these
different body systems what they need
we're just skating by playing around we
need to actually fix problems like
really fix problems core problems we
need to fix our sick livers we need to
get them cleansed and healed we need to
get them restored stagnant sluggish
overburdened livers we need to protect
our nervous system get it fed give our
nervous system the feedings it actually
needs we have to make sure that there's
ample glucose in our bloodstream enough
glucose to feed our organs our brain
starts to die in 5 seconds if it doesn't
get sugar so we have to make sure we
have enough glucose so the brain can
receive that Sugar our heart also needs
glucose too our heart's a muscle our
heart can thin out the walls can weaken
in the heart the muscle walls can weaken
we have to make sure there's enough
glucose getting to the heart our brain
also needs electrolytes Trace mineral
salts phytochemical compounds
antioxidants our immune system needs to
be fed too it needs the zinc it needs
the minerals it needs the trace minerals
to keep it strong it needs glucose as
well our liver needs glucose too it
needs strength to actually cleanse and
detox the liver has its own immune
system the immune cells inside the liver
also need to be fed too phytochemical
compounds from Foods antiviral compounds
from Foods getting into these immune
cells making them stronger we can't just
run on our own adrenaline all day long
because we're keeping food from our
stomachs we're keeping food from our
body we can't just run on adrenaline and
caffeine all day long because we're
trying to stay on a caffeine high and
we're withholding food but using
caffeine as a diet diuretic to try to
keep the swelling down we just can't
walk around with our blood sugar low
either bumping into walls passing out
fainting a lot of people faint it's a
big thing right now they're withholding
food their blood sugar goes really low
they get really cranky they get
emotional too without that blood sugar
or they have a fainting spell happens
every day but what do we do go back to
the food we used to eat go back to just
processed foods no go back to our
healthy keto diets
uh wasn't working before go back to our
mono eating meat uh that wasn't working
really either go back to our vegan diets
well why is everybody stopping to eat
their vegan diets and withholding food
all day well that's not working what do
we
do hey is Barry here oh thank you he's
at the table over there okay great
thanks Barry Oh my God you look amazing
your nose it's half the size remember
when you're your nose was all bulbous
and it had the veins sticking out of it
yeah it was oh it's it looks
amazing your head your head shrunk your
head shrunk in a good way it looks like
it's not going to explode now amazing
Barry what you been doing medical medium
you got cleanse to heal the book out of
the library oh my God that's so great I
like well that's awesome what are you
doing you're doing the morning cleanse
heavy metal detox
whoa you did the 369 advaned whoa that's
amazing anti-bug cleanse you're doing
next month oh you customized your own
supplement protocol from cleanse to heal
that's really smart yeah I know because
what you had going on was your own thing
and you customized it amazing you look
incredible awesome what do you want to
eat huh all right right I'll get a
steamed potato too let's
eat it's never
easy when we don't feel at ease we feel
sluggish inside our body doesn't feel
that peace our confidence in ourselves
minimizes as our swelling over time
maximizes and we want to jump out of our
skin as the pressure inside of us
swells some have it so bad feels like a
sin they never feel level and never feel
well they go through so much some say
it's living hell the answers out there
when we're down and out are lacking not
eating at all has all the backing it's
understandable to withhold the food we
love when your stomach extends you wish
the problem would end and the next day
begins the problem's not solved there's
so much more to who we are there's no
way we need to be under this long
uncomfortable spell it doesn't have to
be this way over time it can be resolved
internally inside of us inside our veins
we have fortitude we have a light we
have a universal connection to up and
Beyond we have a deep healing well what
we truly go through only God really
knows our heart is pumping our
bloodstream is running the blood and
fluid is living proof that our
unrelenting spiritual and physical
strength will prevail and overcome we
don't have to fear our food we don't
have to be scared of a food
run it's not our fault we should be
allowed to eat what we want but
instead all of a sudden the carpet is
pulled out from under us and we go down
holding a cinnamon
bun original published Medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion