I have a guest with me today she
uncovered a plot by a group of Rivals to
take down medical medium and our
community by spreading false claims to a
major media Outlet to be safe she chose
to record the calls legally and they
were caught
red-handed we're talking about something
awful terrible really the unimaginable
attempting to take the medical medium
down which really means trying to take
down the medical medium Community when
you hear the plan the plot it's
heartbreaking it hurts it stings a group
of people up to no good when you listen
to what you're about to hear you be the
judge a premeditated plot a longterm
multipl step plan to purposely create a
quote postm medal medium era their words
not mine breaking down the faith and
trust of so many who rely on the medical
medium information to keep afloat move
forward and get their lives back and
Escape mattress Island I can only say
this brace yourself for what was EXP
exposed and uncovered this time really
fast in your seat belts I know I'm still
in shock myself it's one thing to
believe this deception is happening in
the world of health and wellness it's
another to see it's true and even find
out who is behind such a plot and why
they are really doing it and hearing it
all from the horse's
mouths holy we need get this guy
off the internet first chop at the tree
parting of the Red Seas take him down
take the SC multiple steps down step one
in this process there's no coming back
from that I'm still in
shock literally I'm still in shock when
I even think about this never mind
hearing it like that what we're going to
talk about today is a plot by Rivals and
competitors that were planning on taking
the medical medium down that was the
whole plan they've been at it for a long
time and they want to take the community
down to they want it all gone everybody
I'm honored to
introduce who I call my hero right now
truly my hero Amber vicaro she's an
alternative medicine practitioner who
has been part of the medical medium
Community for over six years she's
extremely knowledgeable about The
Chronic eel she knows what they go
through how they suffer she knows their
struggles she's helped so many people
get their lives back Amber did you ever
think in a million years you'd be here
today talking about this I absolutely
never thought that the events of the
last few weeks would occur this has been
the most shocking experience of my life
and I've been through a lot I've been
helping people for decades I've been
looking after the chronically ill making
sure they get what they need it's
heartbreaking this is happening like how
did you feel emotionally when you first
discovered
this first I definitely felt completely
outraged I wouldn't have believed that
it were real if I didn't hear it with my
own ears I felt extremely betrayed on a
personal level and then I felt extremely
hurt and bet trade for you and for the
community and for all of the people who
I knew that this would impact I got
incredibly angry when I discovered the
malicious intent behind it all and the
level of trickery that I was
witnessing I felt extremely frustrated
with the amount of corruption that is
and has been allowing something to
happen that should never be able to
happen it's a helpless feeling to
realize that this is something that had
been brewing and building for years it
was happening behind my back back behind
your back behind everybody's back as an
attempt to be an underground takedown
because these people don't want to be
held responsible and then as I saw it
all unfold before my eyes I knew that I
had to do something to help to stop it
you that's heartbreaking that you even
have to go through that that you even
have to experience this right now you
know I always like refer the health
world right now and lately as dog eat
dog it's just like dog dog e dog world
just and here I am just doing my thing
right making sure I'm getting
information to people providing
information all that I can and meanwhile
when I used to say well hey a knife gets
stuck in my
back this time I mean that doesn't even
describe it
really and it's it's really a Despicable
plot that was being planned and it's
still being planned it's still there
it's still
happening and you know when you think
about how many people are sick with
chronic illness when you think about how
there's a plot to put out a story out
there just reasons to
create what they said quote a postm
medal medium
era which blows my mind when I think
about that right there it's
Unthinkable so you heard somebody
actually say postm medical medium
era yes somebody didn't just state it as
a goal but essentially attempted to
recruit me as a leader in what they
called the so-called postmed medium era
which meant that they are hoping to take
medical medium down I I've been thinking
about this for a long time like you
definitely have an opportunity to be a
leader in what I would call the postmed
medium area
that's insane you know when I think
about that when I hear that first of all
it's a new experience to me like I've
heard things over the years but that
takes it to a different level that takes
it to a whole another thing think about
that you're doing all these
things you're helping people for decades
you're putting out
books you're looking out for The Chronic
Leo and then somebody's trying to
actually
create this situation this plot where
they want a postm medical medium era so
when I hear that I hear
extermination like I
hear get rid of it all no problem just
get rid of it all and put it in the past
it reminds me of like something from the
war or end end something or forcefully
just try to get rid of something and
that right there I mean that's just
something that takes it to a new level
so it's not even just hey I don't like
medical medium and I choose not to
follow his stuff or I choose not to
follow his page this is an entirely
different situation never seen anything
before in alternative medicine with
competition or anything of the sort this
isn't even that anymore so it just
reminds me of the medical medium is over
kind of thing
versus like when the the movie came out
or the doc or the Netflix came out like
this is It's G to
happen holy
there's going to be a documentary
about it all that's our vision I mean
it's not we first you have to publish
the article and then once the article is
published then people start bidding on
the piece because Anthony is so um he
has such a presence and if it just stops
said the article I'm guessing that like
there would be some buzz in the medical
medium Community for a few months but
like really I think then it would kind
of die down but ultimately the
way to really get the word out is like
would be like a Netflix documentary you
know
so um once you hit that level of like
being exposed there's kind of no there's
no coming back from that the intention I
have is that it's going uh a Netflix
series like bad vegan will be made about
Anthony L and it will be a hit
because what he pulled off is
unbelievable I mean and the celebrity
angle like this thing this Netflix
version is GNA go bonders holy we
need to get this guy off the internet
like we need to just take it all
down that's crazy to me because I know
who all these people are
and you've helped all of them too
haven't you in their Darkest
Hours many of them in their Darkest
Hours I mean I can recall as if it was
yesterday helping
out certain members of this plot of this
group
and I helped them in their darkest
hour I guess this is the thing she get
it's very sick and
disturbing you know people act so
spiritual out there they act like they
do no harm they act like they're
positive there's people that sit there
with a waterfall behind them they got
their hands and prayer position right
and people in this group do that they'll
have a waterfall behind them they're so
spiritually evolved
and this is what they're up to and this
is what they're
doing and I know one
member of this
group that doesn't even believe evil
exists meanwhile they don't care if they
Crush everything the medical medium
Community people who need things people
who are working on their healing
process and they want to put out this
article and then they want bids on the
article a documentary against the
medical
medium and they don't even really know
what happened they don't even have the
information
correct and that's how sad it is and I'm
sure that bids in a documentary mean a
lot of money like
Millions well it's not
$5,000 it's not
$2,000 it's not
$10,000 and they split it all or
somebody splits it or the media company
gets $10,000 it's a lot of money it
really is and it's money off of my back
and the medical medium community's back
on stories that are unfounded made up or
texts taken out of context without
putting the whole truth and that's how
they do it in this day and age they take
something well that's a fact because
that was your text right there but they
don't put all of the truth and
information around it and what really
happened in the whole
story you can just make up anything now
and just try to take somebody
out Amber how did this even
happen so this is a very long and
complex Story and there's no way that
I'm going to be able to explain it all
adequately on here today but the short
version starts with somebody I know who
I really believed was my friend we had
spent a good amount of time together
connected over health I did see some red
flags along the way with him as a person
and I did know that this guy was no
longer supportive of medical medium
information but I have friends who have
all kinds of different belief systems
that I connect with on certain things
and don't align with on other things and
I thought that we could continue being
friends on some level despite that
but the red flags started to really add
up in the fall of last year when he had
a conversation with me in which he
actually tried to convince me to
dissociate myself from medical medium
information because in his words it
would be a better business move in case
anything ever happened to
Anthony as further conversations ensued
more recently I was so alarmed by what I
was hearing and I could sense that there
was something that was really wrong
so I looked into recording laws and
began to legally record my phone
conversations with him and with other
people he introduced me to for my own
protection and safety and because I
wanted to really understand what was
going on and what I was
hearing I was introduced to all these
people via text threads through this
friend of mine a whole group of
individuals that in my phone calls with
them admitted to colluding with each
other that ref referred to themselves as
an elite group that one even said she
had to commit horrible acts to become a
part of
so well you're not a part of it Amber
you're in the inner Inner
Circle and you know you you have to earn
your right to get in that Circle yeah
there you go you've earned it then uh
that's a rare spot to be in of course
I've committed horrible acts but you
know you didn't even have to do anything
bad in you're here
so I see like when I hear that I hear a
few different things I
hear you know an elite group I hear
inner Inner
Circle I hear horrible acts to get into
the Inner Circle I hear earn your
right this spells cult c l
t how many times have I heard oh medical
medium oh it's a cult or look out
medical medium is a cult and and then
don't don't do medical medium and
meanwhile when I hear that aite group an
elite group that's plotting to take down
an entire Health movement and that's the
goal and when all that's happening and
then you hear like the recruit
policy is what I kind of hear in there
actually it is what I hear in there and
this I don't know anything more cultish
than that yeah you could hear my nervous
Laugh In that clip well yeah no I heard
that you're
like you're like actually nervous you're
like what do I do it sounded like you're
like what do I do in this moment what do
I
say well you're not a part of it Amber
you're in the inner Inner
Circle
and you know you you have to earn your
right to get in that Circle yeah there
you go you've earned it then that's a
rare spot to be in of course I've
committed horrible acts but you know you
didn't even have to do anything bad in
you're
[Laughter]
here you know when I hear that again and
I hear your nervous laugh and I hear the
cackle
after the the
recruitment attitude and the
recruitment um Vibe it just saddens me
and when I think okay okay if that's the
only thing and it's that but you have
hours and hours and
hours of recordings and information that
would make people's head spin yeah yeah
there's there's so so much more here and
after that point this group went on to
describe to me their problems with you
Anthony followed by an explanation of a
multi-step plan that they had been
working together on for over a year to
take medical medium and the medical
medium Community down using a false
narrative involving a deceased
person and I decided to hear them out at
first because I thought there may have
been a
misunderstanding but the more that I
continued to listen I realized that
nothing was added up adding up I would
be thinking that's not correct I know
that that's not true that's not correct
their main point that they were trying
to convince me of it was all centered
around a story that each of the people
in this group had a different iteration
of their timelines were all different
and wrong each of them had information
that conflicted with another version
they couldn't get their story straight
they were missing pieces that didn't fit
together I would have a call with one of
them who would tell me a story one time
and that would be different from and
conflict with the story that the same
person would tell me on another call the
next day they would reference
information that I knew to be untrue and
some of them claim to have been
around when the evidence shows that they
weren't While others claimed that they
weren't involved in ways that the
evidence shows that they were
and you have all of this
recorded I do I do I do I have a lot of
hours of recordings of these
conversations where they then went on to
further describe their plan which
included using their connections to
specifically seek out a journalist and a
publication that's known for doing
negative pieces that turn into
documentary sales and a journalist who
would publish an article in a mainstream
media Outlet using this false narrative
with the ultimate goal of it causing
enough controversy to lead to selling a
negative documentary exploiting their
deceased
friend they gave me examples of NE
negative articles turned into
documentaries that they wanted to use as
a model both examples came from the same
publication and one of their examples
was written by the same journalist that
had sought out this group wanted to be
anonymous sources and hide behind that
anonymity all throughout their execution
of this plan so that they can
essentially say and do whatever they
want drop this bomb of an attempted
character assassination even if it's
based on falsities so that they can reap
the benefits and never face
accountability for the damage that they
intend to
cause it's damage that ultimately
affects the chronically ill and that's
something that I have a major problem
with you know
um like usually on the medical medum
podcast even though we talk about
hardship and losses and people
struggling and I still keep a li heart
and I just can't find that light heart
throughout all of this that you've
discovered that um that you have exposed
and um you're bringing to light and I'm
still I'm still in that kind of shock
phase I think maybe I'll find a lighe
heart as I go along when I hear this
group wanted to be anonymous so it's
like Anonymous sources and they wanted
to hide under that throughout the
execution of a plan so they could
essentially just say whatever they
want that's what they did and then drop
the bomb out there out there in the
world so the communities can see it too
and everything and they're dropping a
bomb character assassination bomb that's
what they're dropping and it's based on
falsities and so when I think about
that and then here's the other thing
don't face accountability on it oh I
could just be anonymous spend some
stories I don't have to face any kind of
accountability I don't have to let it
affect my business let it affect um what
I'm doing in the health
scene because some of these people are
public figures some of these people have
been in the health scene for quite a
while and it's like oh let's just drop
the bomb on AW and then we'll go on our
merry way no one will know different and
you you uncovered it you discovered it
you caught them is what you
did and it just blows my mind just
totally blows my mind
yeah unfortunately they put me in this
position uh with their attempt
essentially to recruit me and uh it just
it went on and on and even Anthony in in
the way that they were describing this
to me in their own words they said that
even the journalist that they sought out
was questioning and didn't even know
what to make out of what he was being
told the group explained to me that they
basically threatened the journalist they
described point him here and pointing
him there giving him a lot of Direction
and hammering into his head their
narrative and just gave him a lot of
direction for this piece we gave him a
lot of clarity sort of like he he's
having a hard time wrapping his head
around a lot of it had like really
hammer in his head like what's going on
and like explain the details and point
him towards this point him towards that
but I I was upset I said like he you are
scared you're scared like what's going
going on what's the delay like you you
have everything it's on the
phone you have all this stuff like more
do you eat and then I basically threaten
them so hammering the head of a
journalist basically threatening a
journalist um pushing the narrative that
this group of plotters
wanted and while exploiting a deceased
friend I don't even know what to say you
know when I even like when I hear that
just as a coming out of my
mouth it's just one thing but it's true
factual and it happened that's another
that's an entirely other
thing and so it's like you're not
supposed to do that so if you really do
have some story or you have a story or
you wanted to talk to a
journalist you're not supposed to sell
it to them in the sense where you push
it on them you make sure you hammer it
into them if they're
struggling to see really what's
happening in the story you're not
supposed to then threaten them and from
what you have heard it's way more than
this this is just a tip of the iceberg
right I mean from what you said this is
nothing compared to what's
there and and then to kind of like
basically force their narrative upon the
journal list in that media
Outlet is just
unbelievable I mean I know a lot is
happening
today but I have not heard anything like
that yeah definitely haven't heard
anything like that so it's the furthest
thing from what would be fair accurate
or balanced journalism when a story is
true you don't have to force somebody to
see it your way they explained to me
this group that in order to achieve
their ultimate goal of selling a
negative documentary to
Netflix the way that they wanted it to
be produced and filmed by people within
their Inner Circle they needed to first
publish a negative piece against medical
medium that would lead to more negative
pieces
and I know I'm just extremely extremely
Beyond disappointed that a media company
would support this colluding from Rivals
and competitors who are purposely
plotting the takedown of medical medium
so they plotted a plan they threatened
the
journalist they stayed Anonymous for the
most part it might might be somebody
that's not or whatever for the most part
many of the people that you have and
you've recorded more than three people
you've
recorded like seven sources you told me
and that that alone is unbelievable like
that's
mind-blowing and for them to do this and
then they want the article to come out
the one they actually forced a narrative
upon and shopped it specifically to a
media company and journalist that
purposely writes
negative docu documentation like
negative articles and creates negative
documentries and then to hear that they
even like the inside group with
connections and having something to do
with the documentary in some way just
blows my mind
how and
then yeah it's it's just it's
unbelievable it is unbelievable and
there's so much that came out of these
calls too so much more again than I will
be able to even talk about today but one
big thing is that throughout these calls
I kept hearing familiar terms such as
truth Seekers and then I started putting
pieces together and realizing that every
rumor every incident every seemingly
random thing that I've seen occur and
spread negatively in the medical medium
community over the years has likely
originated from this group and that this
group had been using others who were
active in the community to further their
own agenda while attempting to remain
anonymous themselves so that they're not
held responsible and I was witnessing in
these calls an attempt to be recruited
into the group the same way that others
have been and in fact they told me about
three young women whose names I
recognized that were already sought out
and recruited before me
and then she started a group uh
Instagram chat so we're all in a group
Instagram chat
together and that was the conversation
where you know you came up um and I was
like yeah like they they they said
something like like I'm convinced that
Amber is like paid by them and she'll
never say anything bad about I was like
no that's not the case trust me Amber is
like a very high quality individual like
and I think when she has the right
information she will
um she'll see this the way we see it see
the facts the way we see them and they
were like oh my God if that happened
like all hell's and
break do you know these people I know
these people I definitely know these
people and they were working on these
young women for months the guy who I
thought was my friend was talking to
them about me the whole time behind my
back and they were reving in the idea of
how many people would be hurt and upset
if I turned against medical medum with
them it was like they saw me as some
weird sort of prize because they knew
that if they could get me away from
applying medical medium information it
would destroy the movement even further
so that's like the goal it's that is the
goal actually so you
indoctrinate why does this sound cult
every second you
indoctrinate other people other
influencers in the
community um and you you lead them
out you tell them falsities so they go
oh my God medical medium so bad and you
pull them out you recruit
them and then they go on social media
and they finally have that moment where
they're like okay it's my time to shine
and I'm going to say all these falsities
and just talk about how bad medical
medium is and how it's Ault or how it's
whatever
meanwhile they're literally being
indoctrinated and recruited into a real
cult that is not only spreading
misinformation but recruiting young
girls yep like recruiting young girls in
the medical medium Community I don't
know anything sicker than that so it's
like let's
recruit these young
women get them just brainwash
them with
misinformation
and and that's what you that's what you
learned what I learned is that the
strategy of this group is to try to
capture people like those young women
with a manipulated story of a deceased
person who isn't here anymore to speak
for herself or to defend the truth of
what actually happened they might throw
in some other random misinformation to
add to their story of why you shouldn't
trust medical medium because they try to
act like they have some special
information that you just don't know
even though all these people still
admitted to applying medical medium
information into their own lives yet
they say that they don't trust you they
just don't they they explicitly say that
they don't credit The Source they use it
and don't credit the source and I
literally heard them out on all of their
points for a total of over 17 hours and
I can tell you that every everything
that they think they have is a bunch of
Twisted
misinformation their false narrative
story is the guise that they're using
but what these calls also made clear to
me is that some of these sources are
part of this plan because they're
actually being driven by some of it is
misplaced grief some of it is people
being driven by guilt but most of them
disturbingly are being driven by
self-interests and what they would stand
to gain financially and otherwise from
the impact of a medical medium
takedown and at the same time it's like
Amber is a prize if we can get her out
of medical medium then think about how
many people will be like well if Amber
left medical medium
information then oh yeah like
something's terrible terribly wrong it's
how many young women can we get you know
on our side is what they're basically
doing and you were like this prize like
oh wow if you get Amber out of medical
medium then forget
it then just there you go um and so
that's what was happening and you were
like being groomed it's like no let's
get you out of there um and 17 hours of
recording between how many
people between um seven
people that's just extraordinary
absolutely extraordinary yeah yeah it's
really weird to think about it like that
but that really is what they kind of
said in their own words was their goal
um with me and they they just they kept
using the phrase truth Seekers truth
Seekers and it's just it's so Twisted
because they're they're are real truth
Seekers right and then they're are fake
truth Seekers Seekers there's a huge
difference between the two and I thank
God that now I have the evidence to show
the medical median Community the
difference if these people were real
truth Seekers they would have their
facts straight they wouldn't be
contradicting themselves and each other
constantly they wouldn't come across
like they had something to hide they
wouldn't be showing signs of guilt they
wouldn't have told me that I was asking
too many questions the minute that I
wasn't blindly going along with their
narrative they wouldn't have they
wouldn't have to work so hard to drill
their story into a journalist's head
they wouldn't be spreading Flatout
misinformation that's been disproven and
they wouldn't have ulterior
motives medical medium and the community
is being unfairly targeted and now I can
see clearly that it's been going on for
a long time I really honestly would not
have believed it I wouldn't have
believed that there was actually a plot
to destroy the community like this
unless I had heard it myself the way
that I did I captured this group in
these recordings demonstrating
everything that I've said here in their
own words and the top leaders outlined
their role in this plot I will
definitely take responsibility for one
I've been one of the people that's been
pushing for this uh if you want to take
the the list of people of why this
article's coming out and why it's coming
out in a um mainstream publication is
number one is the number one responsible
I would be number two you be number
three be number four it was us four who
like decided this needs to
happen I'm speechless actually when do I
when am I speechless on uh my own
podcast
so there's so many different there's so
much here it it's it's really incredible
when I think about it it's not only just
trying to recruit you over and everybody
that sees you then just ditch medical
medium and medical medium information
there's that and then there's a
recruiting of other people young women
in the
community um and then essentially
brainwashing them with
misinformation um so they feel like
they're on the right side of history and
I think you even told me that in one of
the recordings there was something like
that in there
and I
mean you have hours of
this and that blows my mind all on its
own and then you're saying there's some
people that you saw Within These
recordings that you
heard that had a lot of
guilt not guilt in what they were doing
with taking medical medium Community
down and medical medium down um but
guilt for other reasons associated with
the original story uh of misinformation
involved with the deceased person and
all of that
and and then Drilling the head of a
journalist um getting them to see the
direction they needed to go for another
documentary all of it I'm just
scratching the surface right from what
you've experienced yeah yep
absolutely absolutely just scratching
the surface this is just an overview for
now I just felt so strongly that
everybody in the community needed to be
aware of what was going on I have many
many hours of recorded calls involving
so much more so many more details so
much more deception and more people and
you know it's just this is the last
thing that you and the chronically ill
who are already up against so much
should have to be dealing with and
that's clearly not what the people in
this group that we're talking about
today are caring about um I wouldn't be
here talking about this unless it were
absolutely necessary they put me and Us
in this position to have to stand up for
what's right and to defend the actual
truth and most importantly the
chronically ill I think about if you
didn't um discover this if you didn't
witness it and you didn't record it
legally like you did which is incredible
um I I really sit here and I say well
what would have happened you know sure
there would have been you know um some
medical me community members would have
would have been like you know what no
way you know I stand behind them but I
think about the
Fallout uh the insanity when none of
this would be discovered and this plot
went through it's it's at least you
discovered who why what and where you
discover the truth about who's behind it
you discover the truth about the
misinformation with with the media
company and the people that were
plotting it and pushed it upon the media
company for their own personal gain and
other reasons too plus financial gain
all those things involved the bias
nature of it all and when you know if I
think about it for a minute and say well
what if Amber didn't discover this and
they were able to just do what they
wanted to do and anonymously just
disappear and go off with their careers
and everything else and like they had
nothing to do with it and fake names in
the article and everything else Under
the Sun and when you think about that
I'm like wow I don't I really I wonder I
wonder I mean the Fallout and people
being hurt with all of this and
meanwhile it's a Sinister deceptive plot
happening with Rivals
authors and
Rivals it doesn't get any more hideous
than that actually
and you're my hero and you're the
community's hero
and
honestly I I thank God that you did what
you did I thank God and I know that you
did one of the reasons why because you
mentioned it too is like your
safety you saw if this is this Sinister
and this is this like backstabbing and
deceptive and and these were supposed to
be your friends or one of them was
supposed to be your friends from what
you're were
saying I can understand why you were
scared I can understand why you um for
your own safety want to protect yourself
and I'm just I'm grateful and thankful
that you brought it to
us this the whole plot so that we can we
can then share it together uh with the
community and I'm truly grateful yeah of
course it's yeah it's this is something
that
I I I mean I never saw myself hearing or
or experiencing and it's been a really
tough past couple of weeks but I uh I
feel like it's a blessing that I found
out the information that I did um
because I think this will help us to be
able to stop what's going on and to warn
the community of this underground
attempt are we going to be doing more of
these you have a lot of information
you have a lot of
recordings you have uncovered a lot of
Secrets and uh plots and
plans and um are you going to come back
on are we going to are we going to
venture into any more recordings any
more
information we've got a whole lot more
to cover Anthony this is a huge story
there's so much that we haven't talked
about there's so many different angles
and aspects and twists and turns to it
it's really really wild and really
unbelievable so there's there's
definitely more there's definitely a lot
more to say okay all right I'm happy to
hear that I'm saddened at the same time
I'm saddened for all of it and what they
planned and what they're
doing and um I'm grateful that she'll
come back on medical meme podcast
and and we can just take a look at
everything else because trans Arc is
critical the truth is the truth if it's
really the truth and you have actually
proven it uncovered it factually the
recordings the people and the Sinister
plan and that there is the
truth yeah Yep this is unprecedented and
you really can't argue with people
describing their own plan and their own
agenda in their own words on an audio
recording you'll often hear out there be
on the right side of History meanwhile
being on the right side of History can
be a gamble because it could be the
wrong side of history and that history
is a jumble of bits and pieces while
someone in their words fumbled and the
history turns out to be a spin
of madeup facts but the facts aren't
intact because they were lies from the
beginning that were off track and the
right side becomes the wrong but it
never mattered because they only care
about their cause and if the cause was
created by
misinformation while the goal is to get
into distribution to cause as much
damage is possible to a healing
Revolution where people around the world
found real
solutions but you laid down a bet
thinking what you were doing is heaven
sent but in truth it's
hellbent as you laugh while you're
getting ready for bed instead of praying
to God you're praying I'm dead but all
of a sudden God sends the light and the
angel is in sight and a hero is blessed
to bring the real truth exposing
darkness and holding the light giving us
a god-given right to defend ourselves
for a god-driven plate and to protect
the underdog from the bullies that lurk
the night spreading lies while hiding
behind their
[Music]
lies