I have a guest with me today she
uncovered a plot by a group of Rivals to
take down medical medium and our
community to be safe she chose to record
the calls legally and they were caught
red-handed we're talking about the plot
a group of Rivals planned in a
premeditative way to take down medical
medium and the community make it go away
take it all down but they got caught
caught
red-handed they got found out if they
didn't no one would be the wiser never
before has this ever happened in a
health and wellness space when you
listen to the plot your jaw may hit the
floor strap yourself in for episode two
get ready for the next round of the
plotter
recordings holy we need to get this
guy off the internet first chop at the
tree parting of the Red Seas take him
down take the scale multiple steps down
step one in this process there's no
coming back from that when I just hear
those again and the intentions behind
them I mean you I'm still in shock first
of all but you can feel the negative
energy and the sense of their goals and
the more recordings we hear the more is
uncovered
it's bone chilling back with me on the
medical medium podcast is Amber vakaro
who the medical medium Community is
calling our hero right now I'm honored
to have you here Amber today we're going
to go through some more recordings that
were obtained legally and of these
Anonymous sources who are actually
plotting the takedown of the medical
medium and the medical medium community
and when I say that I mean I mean I I
just can't believe what they were doing
but the facts are there the
information's there and the recordings
are there
undeniable and it's just it's just
unbelievable for the people who haven't
heard the last episode if you can and
you have a moment try to catch up and
listen to 35 episode 35 part one plot to
take down the medical medium Amber first
can you give us a little recap on some
of your re recordings from the last
episode of course in part one we talked
about how there was an attempt to
indoctrinate me into a group a group of
people with health and wellness
businesses that have plotted a
premeditated plan to go to a journalist
at a mainstream media outlet with a
manipulated story that would if all went
according to their plan caused so much
upset that the medical medium Community
would would all come crashing down and
in the process they're exploiting a
deceased person shaping a story that
they want to the way that they want to
spin it leaving out facts and content
cherry-picking evidence that suits a
preferred narrative with a plan of
publishing additional
articles and ultimately to sell a
negative documentary and how we talked
about how I obtained legal recordings of
these phone conversations
versus like when the the movie came out
or the do or the Netflix thing came out
like this is this going to
happen holy
there's going to be a documentary
about it all that's our vision I mean
it's not we first you have to publish
the article and then once the article is
published then people start bidding on
the piece the intention and action I had
is that it's going h a Netflix series
like bad vegan will be made about
Anthony and it will be a hit
because what he pulled off is
unbelievable I mean and the celebrity
angle like this thing this Netflix
version is gonna go boners I I connected
him with a lot of people to it he really
appreciated Ash and I and then just gave
him a lot of direction for this piece we
gave him a lot of clarity sort of like
he he's having a hard time wrapping his
head around a lot of it had to like
really hammer his head like what's going
on and like explain the details and
point him towards this point him towards
that but I I was upset I said like he
you are scared you're scared like what's
going on what's the delay like you you
have everything it's on the
phone like you have all this stuff like
what more do you need and then I
basically threaten I will definitely
take responsibility for one I've been
one of the people that's been pushing
for this uh if you want to take the the
list of people of why this article's
coming out and why it's coming out in a
um mainstream publication is number one
Ash is the number one responsible I
would be number two be number three
would be number four it was us four who
like decided this needs to
happen so this is what this group of
plotters did to sell a story to sell
their narrative they had to hammer it
into the head of a journalist Point him
here and point him there
and ultimately threaten him and today
I'm going to unpack more of the content
from the calls that I had with these
plotters as part of the attempt that
they had to recruit
me that really speaks to a serious lack
of credibility in each of them as
sources
and had given me seeds she planted seeds
that I had not heard when I saw the
documentary and then when I saw the
documentary and I flipped that that's
when I started collecting way more
information I went back to I asked for
more first of all I want to point out
here that this plotter is stating in his
own words that what ultimately turn what
turned him against medical medium wasn't
a story it wasn't a piece of information
about a deceased person it was him
watching a documentary that a co-plot
husband helped to create which made him
think to himself that could be Anthony
that was his light bulb
moment next he says he turned to a
source that he deems as being reliable
who made him so confident that medical
medium was problematic that he became
the number two instigator of this entire
takedown
plot Jes is like a CIA agent I mean this
and she'll be happy to talk to you Amber
you can talk to anybody you want in this
story but she like went and found
pictures of him in his high school
yearbook can I hear that one
again jokes is like a CIA agent I mean
this and she'll be happy to talk to you
am you can talk to anybody you want in
this story but she like went and found
pictures of him in his high school
yearbook so that sounds like the
plotters or are looking for anything
they can find I guess they're in my
yearbook looking for
pictures and I heard CIA
agent so I guess there must be something
these plotters are doing so and when I
even think back to the other Clips you
you played for us there were four people
they had like a ranking system so it was
like 1 2 3
4 and
they
brought this plot to the media company I
what it looks like too through all of
that and it was inspired by a
husband who actually does
cinematography meaning that was
involved and I'm just so blown away in a
sense where I'm I'm actually in
shock in shock so but really I was just
a seeker of Truth like you
are I just wanted to know the truth so I
was surprised he talked to me on the
phone and we talked for a good long time
but one of the stories he told me I have
no idea why I don't remember why our
conversation went here but I think this
is the underlying thing for Anthony all
the time is that
um I think in his childhood growing up
in in Maine mhm and it's a it's a
different world um especially back then
um and he probably didn't fit in I think
the kids picked on him a lot he was
mentioning stuff that how the boys um
when he was he had a little job after
work after school like a little work job
and he was walking home and they set up
was winter time and they set up a a
snow um trap I what to call it whereas
when he walked by a certain spot they
all bombarded him with
snowballs and he's still telling the
story to this day to
me so apparently it hurt him a lot both
physically and mentally I think he was
like bloody and bleeding and you know
you have to go home and explain to your
mom
why why you're all beat up but I think
that was a common thing the kids were
mean to him
so
um I don't know know maybe he snapped I
don't know he just has this strong will
to feel important that's what I say to
kind of get back at everyone you know to
be something really special so here we
are again this is this is somebody who
this group is relying on for so-called
factual information that ultimately the
journalist ends up relying on for
factual information and and we have
again the truth Seeker phrase truth
Seeker truth seeker and I want to talk
about this so-called truth Anthony is
this is this a story that you shared
with this
woman I haven't experienced a childhood
experience like that so I'm you know
confused about that that seems like the
story from the movie Elf where buddy and
Michael were in Central Park and they
got attacked by some kids and some
bullies that's what it reminds me
of ow son of a n
[Music]
cracker
run and he's still telling the story to
this day to me so if I hear that clip
correctly that
recording she's saying I'm still telling
that same snowball fight story today or
maybe the other day or it sounds like
now I'm still telling that person the
story but I haven't talked to this
person in
years
um I don't know maybe he snapped I don't
know he just has this strong will to
feel important and that's what I say to
kind of get back at everyone you know to
be something really special and I really
don't think it's
spirit I think he I think he has a
mental disorder actually because there's
so many things things that are signals
for
that maybe he really does think he hears
voices you know there's a lot of PE
people with schizophrenia out there and
they think they hear voices as well and
not necessarily bad
ones basically this woman doesn't
believe in your gift which is fine right
to each their own but she's filling in
that Gap by diagnosing you as if she's a
psychiatrist when she's not based on
stories that you never actually told
her and one major theme that I observe
from these recordings is that several
people in this group weaponize the fact
that they've ever spoken to you
personally at all even if you were not
actually close to them in reality and
they use it as leverage to position
themselves as people who have Insider
information to recruit others and as a
marker of credibility to say whatever
they want about you in general so we
know talk to a lot of people
um and gathered all kinds of information
he has a ton
from here this plotter is saying that
the journalist that they sought out for
this mainstream media article got a ton
of his information from this
woman and I'm not exactly sure that she
sounds like a reliable source to say the
least you don't know like when he woke
up from the coma did like was he did
does he is he mentally Disturbed does he
think he hears a voice um I mean are
these people who do like crazy
sacrifices of like I don't even know who
knows like like like are they acting
like they're Christian but they're
really killing little baby like I don't
know I it's
crazy so this guy is plotting a plan
with a group of people a group of
plotters they've taken it to a major
mainstream media
outlet and at the same time they're
plotting they're associating me with
sacrificing babies or killing
babies while they're being anonymous
sources
and yeah this is this is amazing
actually but there's like no one more
trustworthy than Robbie so I know that
whatever he shared with you is like
spoton can we hear that one again but
there's like no one more trustworthy
than Robbie so I know that whatever he
shared with you is like spot on the most
trustworthy that was really interesting
to me is that what we're calling someone
who's making up horrifying allegations
of sacrificing and killing
babies who completely hid this Sinister
plot from me for over a year and who
plotted behind your back Anthony and
behind everyone's back well I'm so glad
you're on the team of the good guys at
least I don't know about good but at
least
honest got a mix but at least we're
trying to be honest about it is it
possible to hear that one again well I'm
so glad
you're on the team of the good guys at
least I don't know about good but at
least honest
got a mix but at least we're trying to
be honest about it throughout these
recordings the plotters contradict
themselves a lot like this here it's at
first at first it's we're the good guys
and then well I don't know about good
but at least honest and then she says
it's well we're trying to be
honest this is who was named as the
number one source
and she's here contradicting herself
again and again as she's referring to
herself and her fellow colluders Anthony
that's not even his real name by the way
I'm not sure if you know that it's not
um it's not no it's not what is
it um I don't even know I don't care
anymore that's not his real name
though this plotter was so confident in
the negative things that she was saying
so confident in saying that Anthony is
not your real name and yet she doesn't
actually know what it is she doesn't
know she doesn't care it's like she
can't even be bothered to get her
information straight before spreading
rumors Anthony that's not even his real
name by the way I'm not sure if you know
that it's not um it's not no it's not
what is
it um I don't even know I don't care
anymore that's not his real name though
okay so that's not my real name I'm
hearing the in interesting part is the
person doesn't even care to even know
but this person is a source that's
supposed to be relied upon when I was
growing up no one can pronounce my last
name right and so my school
teachers and other people would call me
Anthony William and Anthony William is
my legal name that is my real name my
real name is Anthony and so when I hear
that it sounds like my name Anthony is
not even my real name so if that rumor
is going around I could see people being
like whoa that's not even his real name
but it's Anthony William that's my real
name and that's what I go by and so and
there's nothing wrong with trying to
maintain a little bit of privacy too but
my name is not hidden by any means my
last name's not hidden at all it's easy
to find it's not as if it's being hidden
but throughout my life my family has
called me Anthony William my mom calls
me Anthony William even up to this point
now today and that is my legal name and
Anthony is my first legal name
too throughout these recordings I found
that this group often conflated privacy
with dishonesty they're acting like
you're deceiving people when Anthony
William is your actual legal first name
and middle name your last name is out
there like you said you're not hiding it
there's nothing wrong with wanting to
maintain some privacy meanwhile these
plotters didn't want anyone to know what
they've been up to and what they've been
doing I'm not I'm not afraid of
Anthony um I'm being strategic if I
wanted I mean I thought about when I
talked well do you want to be off the
record on back I'm like what do you want
to do here and the truth is I I'm I
would be happy to be on the record and
just like say Robbie said that but the
the Strategic reason behind that that's
not smart because I'm I have a different
I'm I'm building something different
with my life and I don't want to be
associated with with this in any way
shape or form I want to just completely
distance myself and be gone I will not
be in the documentary my name will not
be in the article I'm I'm just
leaving that's tragic in so many ways so
I'm speechless in the moment want to
hear that because what that plotter is
doing is telling a journalist whatever
they want to tell him going
Anonymous the person's not afraid of me
the person just doesn't want to be
involved at any level after the
basically the bomb is
dropped and and a documentary happens
because that's part of the plotter plan
altogether but this person works in the
health
space is a business
owner or Works in in business in the
health
space
and here that person is
basically plotting to plan or
strategically plotting to plan the
takeown of medical medium and the
community the journalist is allow o it
that's a whole another
story and to unpack this I mean I could
sit here we can sit here and unpack this
for a long time but I know we have to
move on there's so much more but this is
a person working in the health space
competitor rival whatever you want to
say a plotter with a group of
people directing a
journalist staying Anonymous going on
their merry way to keep doing what
they're doing in the house space in the
health field not having their name
attached to anything and they're not
afraid of me at the same time and all
this is perfectly fine to the
journalist perfectly fine obviously to
the media
company I find it
despicable great like he's really he's
really easygoing and if you say to him
like I want to talk on
background um or I want to talk off the
Record or however you want to do it if
you say I don't want you to quote
or say you like you know put my name
anywhere he's happy to do that and he's
also like he change your name if you
want you know a particular statement to
be said but you want to use a different
name you know just make sure you are
upfront
about anonymity you know do you want
your name mentioned or not be sure you
say clearly what you
want um and on my recommendation for
that you know what that is is to not
don't go there um you know you don't
want to be sued for any kind of
defamation of
character so on these recordings I'm
pretty sure that what is being described
here is not how real journalism is
supposed to be conducted and one of
these plotters is clearly aware that
what she's saying is most likely
defamatory it's like she's going to go
after you but she's not going to put her
name behind it it sounds like she's not
confident in what she's saying and
concerned that what she's saying might
not be true and some of these sources
won't put their names behind their
statements because they admittedly don't
completely stand behind their statements
so if he had if he had picked something
out that was like yes like I stand by
that statement like 1,000% every single
moment of my life like I'd be I would
have been like yeah you can use my name
but the the things that he asked me to
go on record were like not things that
I um I was just like I don't I mean I
said that that's not really
like something that I feel like super
strongly about it feels important to
have my name behind it so I ended up
saying no and he was very kind about it
I mean he asked me to explain why and I
did but he didn't like push me about it
at all
so that's a major red flag to me I think
that that sounds like something the
journalist something that the journalist
should have pushed her on if she doesn't
feel comfortable with what she said she
shouldn't have it in print the fact that
the journalist knows that she doesn't
even fully stand behind what she said to
me that shouldn't even go in an article
then I really don't even know what to
say about this when you unpack this one
the person doesn't feel comfortable
standing behind their statement that
alone right and then the person isn't
even
1,000% uh confident the statement is not
just stand bable but can even be seen
the person wants to be anonymous in the
back end but that but the yet isn't
standing behind the statements doesn't
want them out front on
record journalist seems to be fine with
it I mean it just seems like a
weaponization of some kind it's almost
like just fit anything in oh you want to
be in the backend then fine you don't
have to stand behind these comments
we'll put them in the
article but don't worry we won't same
your say your name maybe they'll even
change a name of course put a fake name
it's a type of
wordsmithing for
sure it and they do this I think to make
the reader feel any way they want them
to
feel and they kind of put what they want
to put in even if the person isn't
standing behind
it
and this should be the bigger story
because this
is yeah this is
unconscious
yeah it's it's not a natural situation
it's not a natural story it seems as
though these people don't know much of
the story or they don't feel comfortable
standing by their own statements and
there's some misinformation mixed in and
then you've got a journalist listening
is that this stuff is all you know real
it's it's kind of like a favoring of the
plotted plan and it's it's that falls in
the line of I mean some character
assassination territory it's like you
can keep you can take sources that are
filled with misinformation and then you
can weaponize it like you said you can
slip in a factor or two somewhere around
it and then you make it as if it's law
or complete truth and uh it's really
interesting it's it's it seems like it's
a way of telling the story the way that
they want the reader to read it and so
obviously I had some questions about all
of this as I was listening to to this
group of individuals I was trying to
figure it all out I really truly was not
asking a huge amount of questions I was
mostly just trying to hear these people
out as you can hear in the recordings
that we're sharing
but it was interesting to me that
throughout this process they quickly
became uncomfortable with me asking
questions at all you might want to stop
talking to some to people at some point
I mean I can't imagine you you don't
have enough information by now I mean
again I don't know how much more you
need to know Amber but yeah
um obviously go ahead I'm just saying
like I'm just looking out for you like I
guess my question is how long do you
want to stay in the state I think
Robbie's kind of frustrated with me
because I've been asking questions and
it's for me
too this group of plotters feels so
strongly about you being so problematic
that they have taken it this far so as
to plot to take you down to take the
community down yet they don't even know
medical medium information that well
you've probably read the books more
thoroughly than I than I
have well the first one I actually
really liked the first very first one
that came up out it was kind of real
except for the stories I kind of skipped
over those but you know all the
protocols and stuff were very helpful
and the information seems
sincere
um whether it's right or not I don't
know but it certainly was interesting
and I had never heard of what he was
talking about before I met him so I am
grateful for that because I think what
he's mentioning is very
real This Woman This plotter is
admitting that the information is
helpful she's also saying that she
skimmed through it so she didn't really
study the book she didn't really study
the information and then at the same
time she was telling me that
practitioners come to her to learn from
her all the time and she was suggesting
that I could come to her for
practitioner support and
education are there people who are
applying medical medium information
still who call you and ask for advice
absolutely yeah that's mostly what
I have I have very few clients that
found me outside of medical medium and
you know word of mouth is really
big um you know and when somebody
mentions you on social media yeah you
know you well you're probably there
right now with getting recommendations
and people love Word of Mouth from
others or being helped yeah yeah but
also so practitioners who are applying
medical medium information will ask you
for
advice oh yeah yeah yeah this plotter is
positioning herself as an authority as a
health practitioner when it seems as
though she doesn't even really know
medical medium information she doesn't
believe in spirit it sounds like she
really only read the first book it
sounds like she skimmed it at best there
are eight books plus a ton of other
resources if food were the only key to
healing which is what Anthony implies
really
um so but I
mean I mean do you do you ever hear
Anthony talk about anything other than
what to eat not not a lot right I mean
he does get into some spiritual stuff
and things but not
really yeah I mean he had talked about
he's got like the Angels he's got the
the soul healing techniques he's got in
the healing path resource he talked
about which I think that like that
doesn't that's something that nobody
really comes across anymore he talked
about the importance of like exercise
and sunlight and and all of those other
sorts of things that's good yeah I have
he the healing path but not for a really
long time
yeah well that's right he did mention
some of that yeah I don't know he really
focuses on food though
now
so here I wasn't going to I wasn't going
to go into explaining more I wasn't
about to try to give this woman a lesson
on how all of the books and how all of
the resources are about so much more
than just how to eat I wanted to see
what she knew and it became really clear
to me that this group again does not
really understand medical medium
information for what it is and yet their
sources they feel so strongly about you
and the information being problematic in
some way shape or form yet um they admit
to applying it in their own lives
explicitly without citing The Source
maybe you can still take that following
and just you know do Your Own Thing
aside from medical medium you know not
without like like Robbie said without
mentioning him but still uh teach people
what you've learned and what you what
you practice yourself and what works for
you and kind of work on it from that
perspective since you have a already you
could now do I when I talk to people
about health and wellbeing use a million
things that I've learned from him 100% I
mean getting this information out in the
world he shouldn't care who gets credit
for it I don't know any healer any real
healer that wants to have credit for
things and trust me you didn't you know
you you didn't need to credit Anthony
for what you've learned and you can do
that without ever using the word medical
medium or Anthony William you know here
this group is coaching me on how to not
site the
information they're coaching me on how
to plagiarize the
information unlike them I site the
source and I always will because it's
about
integrity it's about caring about other
people it's about people needing to heal
citing the source is about respect not
citing The Source ends up in and people
putting their own spin on it even if
they don't mean to it gets tainted right
by human interference the information
gets changed and further distorted as it
gets passed down the line becoming
something else entirely like a game of
telephone where no one can fully get
what they need to heal and you know it
just it makes me question the level of
compassion that this group has for
others citing the source is not about
Anthony it's not about you Anthony it's
not about you seeking notoriety in any
way shape or form I know that it it
comes from a place of deeply caring
about people and people having access to
the original pure information which just
so happens to be free you can access it
all for free so that the people who are
struggling and suffering can take it as
far as they need to go this group they
want to Brand themselves they want to be
somebody they all have businesses in the
wellness space they're trying to
convince me to have no
Integrity they're essentially saying
that all of the copyrighted original
information is free
game they want rights to that they feel
entitled to that they feel entitled to
continue on with their
brands meanwhile they want a postm
medical medium era they want it all down
they want everyone to stop mentioning
medical medium at
all these people with these intentions
are the main sources behind this plot
and this article they're plagiarized
from other books who were his mentors
before him like yeah everybody knows
that apples have X vitamins and Z
vitamins and his information is very
very very basic vitamins in an apple is
interesting because the medical medium
information the books they really don't
talk much about vitamins that's actually
what everybody else does out there
because that's essentially as as far as
science and research goes and I know
that you and I Anthony could talk for
hours about what makes medical medium
information completely unique and
original um it's quite an insult to
oversimplify the information like that
and to try to discredit how unlike
anything else that's out there that's
ever been done before in history his it
is and whether people want to admit that
or not it's true and then we've got this
plotter who's accusing you of
plagiarizing
information it's a serious accusation so
when I think about that and I see what
the plot are saying that's a serious
accusation first of all my publisher
would never let one of the medical
medium books out the door if it was
plagiarized on any level
they have a lot of
editors they uh purposely look for
things like that they can't just let the
book go out because these books are
symptoms and conditions and a lot of
intricate information about the body all
that stuff has to be cited from studies
and places of origin that could be like
medical clinics um articles that are out
there from doctors it all has to be
cited it can't just be thrown into a
medical medium book and then sent out
the door by the publisher so there's no
such thing as plagiarizing in these
books and these books would have to site
every single thing everywhere out there
the publisher wouldn't have it in any
other way so yeah so that that
accusation is ridiculous he's very he's
very smart and
[Music]
um yeah probably has some kind of
personality disorder potentially
narcissism
and I I don't know what else I found
that to be a really interesting
assessment coming from a group of
individuals that refers to themselves as
Elite but I'm letting you know
like we are an elite group of people
we're we're in in Elite category you
know I want to play this clip again
again in a minute because recently one
of these plotters claimed that nobody
ever they tried to claim that nobody
ever referred to themselves as Elites
and I want to display that I'm not
putting words in these people's mouths
these are actually things that were said
by them on these recordings I also want
to point out the fact that you Anthony
have never referred to yourself as Elite
you've never referred to yourself as
being above anyone or anything of the
like there's this really twisted Dynamic
with this group where it's like
everything it seems like everything that
they're accusing you of is actually what
they're doing and how they
are but I'm letting you know
like we are an elite group of people
we're we're in in Elite category you
know and by the way Ash do need to work
Ash has ever ever the woman is she had
family money a lot of it yeah you know
private plus did I hear that correctly
can I hear that back that clip and by
the way Ash didn't need to work Ash has
ever ever the woman is she had family
money a lot of it yeah you know private
jet and
plus so basically they're saying they're
an elite
group you've shown the all the
recordings so far or a fraction of them
really from what you said you have but
you showed recordings showing that
they're plotting this plan they went to
the media company mainstream media
outlet they are strategic about
it and they even have a ranking system
like the number one person involved
number two number three number four and
now I hear one of the people has a
private
jet they don't have to work or work for
a
living and they have what seems to be
lots of family
wealth and I don't have a private jet I
have to work for a living I have to work
to make sure I could bring this
information to everyone to the
public and there's no pay
walls and there's no programs nothing
like
that of course I don't mind when people
mon their websites or do what they want
to do with their businesses but I don't
monetize my website like other people
do
and meanwhile this person has a private
jet lots of wealth seems to be the
number one plotter from what it looks
like with the list and ranking
system
and yeah I mean I'm speechless really um
I come from the working class that's
where I come from from but apparently
this is an elite group they're saying
that in in these
recordings
um so yeah and knowing that these
plotters are
actually looking to get that documentary
together negative documentary all of it
plus the article and then when you look
at the plotters and the information they
don't even care to even want to know
what my name
is but yet my fate is in their
hands and the community's Fate is in
their hands of this plot it's really
interesting yeah so let's let this group
speak for themselves more about their
plot I mean when you think about this
from a journalist perspective this piece
is unfuckingbelievable I mean this is
this is a journalist dream I mean you
you want I mean the celebrities the
number of books
sold yeah it is awful and that's why
this there's an article coming out about
him I don't know if you know anything
about that it's not a good one y I would
not want to be on that train when that
article comes out just saying I think
there's there's a lot coming is what I
think which is why it's really good that
they're telling them now yeah we're
hopeful that once the Articles out um
one of the directors or producers that
works with
will uh you know become interested in
telling the story really well oh cool
awesome I'll pass that on to my husband
he was a cinematographer for that he
primarily has been working in
documentary last few years Britain was
on the phone and I was like I was like
look guys like Britain I was like you
have the connections like you were the
cinematographer bad vegan like can't why
don't you just go like this talk to
people yeah and then and then like
that's when and that's when Ash went
because like theoretically without me
pushing this along why the didn't
Ash go
to months prior right like what took why
did she do that like I feel like I is
yeah okay that would make a lot of
money no question I'm in
shock as I stated in our in part one
this group appears to be using a
manipulated story of a deceased person
in order to drive out their
goals what we're uncovering again and
again is I mean again this is just kind
of scratching the surface it's it's that
there are so many more layers to this
this the deceased person it seems to me
in all of these 17 hours of calls that
I've had all these
recordings um with these people as part
of this group is that the story
is essentially a guise that really draws
people in and really makes people feel
like oh you know medical medium is so
bad and but then as I was really
speaking to these people and and hearing
them out about what was problematic
about you to them a huge percentage of
it was just all of this other stuff it
was there were all of these other layers
and all this stuff underneath the
surface these stories these rumors all
of this Twisted
misinformation and then you can kind of
see in the recordings in their own words
in a lot of these clips what is actually
going on behind the scenes and maybe
what's driving these people in in ways
that I don't know if they realize um but
maybe some people who are involved in
this are being driven by as I said
before some potentially misplaced grief
or potentially guilt about their own
involvement with the situation something
like that but it seems like a lot of it
is being driven by nefarious intentions
and by what some of these people can
stand to gain personally professionally
financially and otherwise from the
Fulfillment of this plot this plan I'm
seeing yeah I mean I'm in I don't even
know what to say I like I can't get my
words together because I'm hearing
cinematographers um Making Connections
Making Connections about the documentary
that they're bringing to the media
Outlet I'm hearing that I'm hearing
money uh is is involved I'm
hearing a person talk about how they
wouldn't want to be on this train when
this article comes out which is which is
means they all knew they're all
plotting it's their connections to the
media company it's all in these
recordings I heard it's it's a
journalist dream because they're selling
it to a journalist saying hey this is a
journalist
dream um I hear they're talking about
how many numbers of book sold um things
in that nature uh this is a
premeditated plot who can do this it's
unconscious doesn't matter how much
damage is done to the community doesn't
matter anything they have a strategy and
a plan in place it's all there in the
recordings I don't even know what to say
when I hear these
recordings can you replay that clip the
important clip I mean they're all
important but the important clip about
they had the idea first the plot and
they took it to the media company Brit
was on the phone and I was like I was
like look guys like Britain I was like
you have the connections like you were
the cinematographer bad vegan like why
don't you just go like just talk to
people yeah and then and then like
that's when and that's when Ash went
because like theoretically without me
pushing this along why the didn't
Ash go
to months prior right like what took why
did she do that like I feel like I inst
it so it wasn't the media company that
took upon the story upon themselves the
recordings say everything it turns out
it was their idea that's the instigator
there and then the husband has the
connections to the media
outlet and they took that plot to the
media
Outlet um sounds like took the plot to
the media Outlet using husband's
connections
too um and this is before it even
started so this is even early on
so what this plot is saying
it's Unthinkable it's just
Unthinkable yeah and like you were
saying before it's these are we're
showing motives we're showing true
intentions by these people saying these
things in their own words were showing
all of this colluding and and just
really interesting Dynamics and how this
story all came to be and there's a
serious lack of concern for the damage
that essentially they intend to to cause
so can you talk more about that and and
how this process has has affected
you well it's affected me for sure but
the worst part is it's it's affected the
communities because I had to Forfeit the
book I was going to do for this year
that was going to be released in October
but there's no way to do it so it was a
spiritual book that everybody was
waiting for um so I had to cancel that
um four months straight with hundreds of
questions from a
journalist
and
the I mean the crazy thing is it's just
yeah I haven't worked in four months for
the community at all so when you those
are the things that I care about the
most never mind the the damage you know
involved with you know my family and um
you know all of that involved it's it's
really the big part for me is is the
future of getting the information out to
the community and all that so this is
the first time since I started putting
books out that I've had to
Forfeit and actually just cancel the
whole book um for for this year for sure
so yeah there's it's it's affecting my
life of course but it's affecting
what which is what I always care about
the most which is the community and
people who are struggling that's always
just number one for me you know anything
in my life it's it's secondary anyway
but still it's it yeah hasn't been
easy yeah it's that's I mean for this to
have
affected the spiritual book that I know
everybody in the community was so
excited about and so much looking
forward to it just there there really
aren't any words um for how unfortunate
how how disappointing how awful this is
and again hearing the true intentions
behind it all this this whole thing is
just completely
unprecedented it's something that's
never happened before in the health and
wellness industry there it's going to
take some time for us to unpack this
layer by layer and I'm great ful again
that I have the pure evidence straight
from these people's mouths to be able to
really show people what's been going on
because there are a lot of twists and
turns to it and and I just want to also
point out the fact that you Anthony have
been talking about this all year you've
been talking about this even I remember
I think before that I you've been
talking about this for a while that
there are people who have been trying to
take down the community that that's
something that has become major issue
and that people are not citing the
original information back to Medical
medium and um in the community and and
this group you know has been persuading
others to join them and to do the same
and I know that a lot of people didn't
really kind of believe what you'd been
saying didn't want to believe it that
there was really something like this
going on and so it's extremely sad um
unfortunately it's true and now
everybody can hear it for themselves is
any chance to play the last round of
Clips again for for everybody and I
personally want to hear them
because
um I I just still can't even believe it
I mean when you think about this from a
journalist perspective this pieace is
unfuckin believable I mean this is this
is a journalist dream I mean you want I
mean the celebrities the number of books
sold yeah it is awful and that's why
this there's an article coming about him
I don't know if you know anything about
that it's not a good
one I would not want to be on that train
when that article comes out just saying
I think there's there's a lot coming is
what I think which is why it's really
good that they're telling them now yeah
we're hopeful that once the article's
out um one of the directors or producers
that Britain works with
will uh you know become interested in
telling the story really well oh cool
awesome I'll pass that on to my husband
he was a cinematographer for that he
primarily has been working in
documentary the last few
years was on the phone and that was like
I was like look guys like Britain I was
like you have the connections like you
were the cinematographer bad vegan like
why don't you just go like just talk to
people yeah and then and then like
that's when and that's when Ash went
because like theoretically without me
pushing this along why the didn't
Ash go
to months prior right like what why did
she do that like I feel like I is it so
he instigated it and instigated the
number one plotter and a number one
plot's husband to use connections to go
to the mainstream media Outlet to get an
article going about a deceased person
who happens to be a a friend of the
plotters friend of mine using her
death and then having an article done by
the media company so that bids when it
comes out one of the plotters says I
don't want to be on that train when that
comes
out all pushed by them and then when the
article comes out bids for the
documentary start and then the husband
has connections to producers this is
everything I heard on those
recordings
and this is allowed by mainstream
media from what it looks like these are
highly highly compromised sources that
are Rivals business owners in the health
space knocking out the medical medium
medical medium
Community would probably be very helpful
for some of
them
from my opinion from what I'm seeing
from
these
recordings of their exact
words um do you have any
so there's more than this you have hours
and hours of
this yes there are still hours and hours
of a lot of content from these
recordings to unpack um and and I intend
that we'll we'll keep going with this
and and continue peeling back these
layers so
so investigator journalist you're
actually on the
scene and you have uncovered a plot and
uncovered a planned
plan I've never seen anything like this
in in alternative medicine or the health
and wellness space ever in my life and
I've been in the health and wells in
this space for a very long time and I've
never seen anything like
this um yeah and it sounds like their
plan is in the works and their plotted
plan is is happening
so
um I think that uh your
recordings
are extremely extremely powerful and the
community I'm sure appreciates you
bringing this to light and um and
exposing the plotters and exposing their
plan and um I thank you and we have the
community I'm sure they thank you too
and
truly honored that you're
here it's the
morning you get a
call it's a roller coaster ride waiting
for you to take a
fall they send you on it they got some
balls the fear and worry begins to rise
it feels it it will never
subside you might die you're taken away
from what's truly important service to
the people first private life always on
the back burner and hope someday you get
to enjoy it but I doubt it everything
gets put on hold as you battle the
devils in the ones that want my name
sold very bold as they try to run you
over with the truck
they never show kindness they don't care
no one yells duck you go down you hit
the ground but you're not running you're
sinking but you're not drowning and the
tide begins to turn when the real truth
Burns you never learned that the
vultures eat your liver and overreach as
they go for your gizzard mistakes are
made and they breach now it's time the
skit flips the clowns once beaming go
screaming as they run out of town fall
on their faces how does it feel now as
you trip keep in mind you're far from
perfect you think you're the a
message to remember when you're down
here we are all sisters and brothers
some love one another some love to be
gas lit while some just love The
Gaslight While others just love to fight
and some become self- lovers who are you
to say you're better than the other be a
tree among a forest of different
creatures as you get older you find
you're not Supersonic and you learn that
your actions become your
teachers