how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams there's a term out there that's
intriguing to the mind it's interesting
catchy trendy too it's micro doing ah
when you hear the word micro do
or the word micro doing something
happens you instantly go what what do
you mean micro do sounds
scientific sounds like it's helpful
sounds powerful sounds like it's going
to do something for
me and if you're somebody that actually
has a past or experiences with drugs
recreational drugs maybe you partied a
lot maybe partying helped to take you
away from Life take you away from
stress and the term dosing or dosed up
is in your mind it's just there you know
the word dosed or
dosing or hey I'm totally dosed up it
holds power so when you hear the word
dose there's power involved and then say
you're somebody that never did any
recreational drugs you just lived a
straight line and recreational drugs
wasn't in your past or present it's not
in your life but but there's a word in
your
subconsciousness in your Consciousness
it's dosing or dose where' it come from
conventional medicine the doctor you
just remember it here's one dose take
one dose a day you heard it you feel it
you hear it it holds power
dosing and dose holds power on the
subconscious and Consciousness it holds
power on the mind then there's something
called fear fear about
oding
overdosing that's another powerful word
term that's etched in our mind
Consciousness and subconsciousness so if
you're somebody that played around with
recreational drugs or still do you know
know not to
OD you know it in your soul and your
being that it's not a good thing you're
cautious to how much including just weed
how much weed you smoke in a day and
then you hear it out there you read
stories you hear it on the news somebody
overdosed this person overdosed last
night they died this person ODed it's
scary it could mean death
and that resides in the Consciousness as
well the term OD overdosing
overdosed connects to dying death but
when people don't feel good in general
they're struggling mentally emotionally
they got health issues they want a
remedy they want
medicine some type of medicine and you
ask anybody who does Recreation ational
drugs at one time in their life or they
still do it now and you ask them why are
they doing it so how come you're doing
it and you'll get an answer I don't feel
good I feel sick I got anxiety I have
depression I have
depersonalization I have all kinds of
mental issues I have severe emotional
trauma I have Old Wounds hurt pain and
even people who didn't start that way
they didn't have any of that at least
they didn't think they did they got into
recreational drugs and they were taking
something and over time they took more
of it more of it than it was interfering
with their life making life more
difficult and then got to a point where
they needed help and then someone would
say why are you doing it and they'd be
like
well I just life's been really hard I
have a lot of problems and I just went
and grabbed it and started using it it
made me feel better but at the start
they were just partying and the reason
they took more and more of it and kept
doing it wasn't just the addiction part
it was because they were self-medicating
they were looking for medicine they were
self-medicating and then there's people
that say they have self- control they
can control their addiction they can
control their partying they can control
how many pills they take that the doctor
gave them and then there's people that
don't have
self-control it's endless
consumption Nothing Stops them but
either way everybody knows there's power
in the word
dosing
dosages
ODed dose so no matter where ever
someone is at in their life whether they
took something in the past whether
they're on a medication now in the
present whether they feel pretty good
whether they don't there's a word that
catches their eye and it's micro doing
right when someone says it I'm micro
doing right then anyone who hears that
is like ah what and all kinds of things
run through their mind one is how come
the doctor never told me that how come
the doctor handing me a medication
didn't say we're going to make you micro
do or we're going to offer an option to
micro do or how come the guy I partied
with the other day didn't tell me about
micro doing how come I didn't hear that
when I was partying 20 years ago how
come I never heard that before when I
was hanging out with a bunch of people
and they're all doing drugs many years
ago in college and how come no one was
saying how about micro do hey you should
micro do at cocaine hey you should micro
do at Molly you should micro do at
ecstasy it's mind-blowing micro doing
the term instantly you also think wait a
minute is this scientific is science
involved did some scientific body figure
out that if you reduce the dose or make
it appropriate in some way leveled or
measured that we can take what we want
and get something out of it and since
your doctor's not going to still say
anything about micro doing the
alternative doctor is not going to say
anything about micro doing your
chiropractor is not going to say
anything about micro doing you're not
going to really hear about it anywhere
besides kind of on the scene that's
where you hear it on the scene and then
you like it because it gives you a sense
of control because you can't trust
yourself you know that in the past heck
people can't trust themselves with a bar
of chocolate they'll gobble the whole
thing
down and then you think this must be
some kind of
controlled design it's micro doing
someone else can handle it they can hand
me that little tiny dosage and say we're
micro doing and then I can take that
tiny dosage and take it with confidence
feeling like there's control over it and
I'm not going overboard I'm not pushing
it too hard or too far there's something
about that it feels safe there seems to
be some type of safety mechanism built
into this everything is okay if you
micro do it that's the message that
comes through and then you hear a bad
stories of the past or you remember
certain stories that somebody told you
of the past or you experienced something
in the past such as a bad trip you
remember a guy having a bad trip you you
remember this girl having a bad trip you
remember somebody having a bad trip they
went too far they were injured by
something whether it was a large dosage
of
iasa whether it was a large dosage siloc
cybin whether it was a large dosage that
night of ecstasy whatever it is you
heard they had a bad run it really hurt
them they were injured by it and then
you think aha that aha moment micro do
we figured it out the world figured it
out everybody did science must have
figured it out all the shamans must have
figured it out everybody anybody
involved people must have somehow come
to some conclusion that we have
masterminded we have found the key to
all of it it's not about what we did
before we were doing it all wrong it's
micro doing that's the answer now now
and it's proven there must be something
behind it it's ingenious it works it
feels safe and then you hear another
term or word associated with micro doing
attached to it it's called The Plant
medicine you hear that word plant
medicine and suddenly you're like whoa
and the term plant medicine holds power
because we know plants are important we
know plants do have medicine in them one
way or another and we feel comfortable
with the term plant
medicine that word plant and that word
medicine combined with micro doing and
we're sold we're done sign me up what's
interesting is we only use that term
plant medicine or people in the health
movement only use that term plant
medicine when it's about something that
is scary something that is toxic
something that may not be good for you
in small dosages or certainly not large
dosages something that could even be
dangerous and that's where the term
plant medicine falls in the term plant
medicine around substances that are
toxic reminds me of a carjacker you just
call a car
borrower and the strange thing is
there's no scale from 1 to 10 on how
mean or bad that carjacker is just like
there's no scale between 1 to 10 on how
talkx IC that plant medicine is some
plant medicine could be considered soloc
cybin mushrooms and one mushroom can
pack a wall up versus another mushroom
that can just have you barfing and sick
all night and another mushroom that
could have your liver shutting down in 7
days or your kidneys on the edge of
failure but yet you could pack it all up
to plant medicine that's all just like a
carjacker one carjacker might punch your
window in
grab you pull you through the window cut
you up really bad hop in the car and
drive it over you on the way out another
carjacker might just come up to you and
say Sir ma'am get out of the car I'm
taking it or just like that one mushroom
that almost caused liver failure or that
one mushroom that almost shut down your
kidneys after a week the carjacker just
puts a gun to the window shoots a bullet
through it hits your face and then takes
your car there's no scale there's no
measurement there's no way to measure it
it's just the term plant medicine the
thing is really the term plant medicine
should be all about fruits leafy greens
herbs wild Foods vegetables that are not
mind altering in a bad way or adrenaline
surging in a bad way sources of plant
chemical compounds that actually help us
heal plant medicine should be about
blackberri
wild blueberries lemon balm Rosemary
Ginger thyme celery spinach cilantro
shitake mushrooms that's just a few
example instead plant medicine is being
used to give benediction to psilocybin
mushrooms also known as magic mushrooms
or shrooms iasa or even cacao matcha tea
green tea and then if you leave plant
medicine you go into toad medicine frog
poison
the alternative and conventional
medicine world has a lot in common with
the micro doing world and plant medicine
world what's in common they both don't
know why people are sick still bold
statement true and there's a reason for
it no one knows why someone has anxiety
depression bipolar disorder
OCD nobody knows why they have it no one
knows why people really have brain fog
fatigue or a marad of other neurological
symptoms nobody knows why someone has
autoimmune no one knows why someone's
living with a painful chronic condition
and chronic symptoms that plague them
for years and even decades in their life
conventional and alternative medicine
don't know why someone has anxiety and
plant medicine and micro doing world
don't know why someone has anxiety it's
all one big guessing game soup the
conventional doctor doesn't know why you
have depression yet offers you an
anti-depressant the alternative doctor
doesn't know why you have depression
either yet offers you a better diet
regular exercise routine the
recommendation to get rid of processed
foods and the instruction to take some
vitamin D and
multivitamin not every doctor visits
going to yield the same recommendations
it could vary it could be anything
perhaps your doctor believes you have a
gut problem maybe have sibo or candida
leaky gut a microbiome issue maybe
that's to blame maybe your conventional
doctor believes you have a chemical
imbalance or a neurotransmitter issue
dopamine deficiency whatever the case
it's still a case of guessing games we
don't know why you're sick we don't know
why you have depression or any other
chronic symptom but the guessing games
don't stop there with alternative
medicine conventional medicine
they Branch out widespread interest in
psychedelics and micro doing the same
guessing game technique leads us there
too someone search for anything to try
any answers it leads them to the door of
the darker side of plant medicine I've
heard this argument a 100 times out
there or more psychedelics micro doing
is ancient and because it's Ancient
Ancient medicine then it's safe it's
been happening for thousands of years
this is not to disrespect anyone
involved in iasa ceremonies or any kind
of indigenous technique of spiritual
healing indigenous cultures have also
grown bananas indigenous cultures have
also grown spices such as vanilla bean
cinnamon turmeric and ginger these are
non-toxic and have healing properties
well some of these can be self-limiting
and irritating in large quantities keep
that in mind they're not dangerous
at the same time though whether we're an
indigenous culture or not we can all
grow eat and play around with poisons
many non-indigenous people become guides
or practitioners who administer
psychedelics and even toad and frog
poison when someone out there Falls ill
they have a lot of different symptoms
now they're struggling mentally
emotionally they have mental health
issues because of the condition and it's
even part of their symptoms and they're
looking for answers to their chronic
illness and they're desperate to try
anything and then they get further
injured in the process Landing a life of
much more suffering and hardship than
they already had with their condition
people in their lives may pass it off as
I had a bad trip cuz I did the frog
poison and the toad poison or the iasa
or I did something else people can pass
it off like you just had a bad Trip Man
sweep it under the carpet call it a day
it was your journey and that's something
that people are told it's like that was
your journey that was the
process and they'll say It was supposed
to happen it was meant to be they had to
learn something from it you grow from it
meanwhile it was an injury and not a
positive experience of any kind for
anyone and maybe no one even realizes
that their brain health is declining
from that injury and maybe no one knows
it or understands it but either way they
could easily have a steady decline in
their health because of that trip or
that psychedelic
experience the term micro doing makes us
feel safe ah micro doing to the human
psyche micro doing also implies that
there's some kind of scientific nature
involved we feel secure in the sense
that there must be some kind of Science
advising it that some type of study has
been done there must have been a whole
bunch of studies that proves efficacy
but maybe you learned this already in
your life or maybe we all know this that
scientific studies are just a whole
bunch of never-ending games of trial and
error theories that become outdated by
other theories and more theories than
supersede those theories labeling drug
use as micro doing provides a sense of
safety to a wider variety of people now
it's tempting to many more people who
would have never ever gone there never
would have
partaken any way possible unless they
felt that warm fuzzy feeling that
science might be behind it and micro
doing and psychedelics are no longer for
that Niche crowd of people who just go
into the desert sit around a campfire
and drink a whole bowl of psychedelics
marketing has happened a tactic that
pulls in a much bigger crowd and that
crowd got bigger and bigger and bigger
because they're looking for Relief so
they're doing everything in Edibles and
all kinds of micro doing left and right
to a point where big Pharma is like no
no no no no no we need to bank on this
so big Pharma are going to be taking
over the Psychedelic world soon and big
Pharma is going to be in charge of the
dosages the micro doing micro doing
takes on an air of intelligence
something intellectual about it so when
you're talking to someone they're like
hey micro doing try this you can micro
do that here's a psychedelic here's some
toad poison you can micro do this you
can do these micro doed Edibles it's
like whoa you're smart there's something
intelligent about hearing that it's like
wow this is a smart guy or a smart
person or this is seems intelligent here
there's something behind here it's
educated smart and well educated in the
process that they're actually trying to
push on you it's like whoa this sounds
like a good thing and that guy's really
smart and maybe that person is really
smart maybe they are intelligent maybe
it's true to some degree that the person
offering a micro doing technique knows a
lot about the theory yet even if you
know a lot about a game it's still a
game just being straight out here
whether or not anyone wants to hear this
there's still going to be a lot of
people injured from psychedelics people
who went into it into micro doing
therapies with a migraine for example or
something else and ended up with worse
migraines because of it and you're going
to hear more and more of that come out
down the road it's going to be a wave of
people and they're going to like oh my
God I've been injured by this you're
going to hear it out there it takes a
little time because right now it's
uncool to complain when you're doing the
micro doing you just better be quiet and
deal with it deal with the journey deal
with what it is any bad experience was
just spiritual and move on but there's
going to be a lot of people that are
going to be like no I have to speak out
it's going to shift and you're going to
see it out there what psychedelics do is
put the body in a crisis state
so when you're taking some of these
psychedelics the body goes instantly
into a crisis State when we go through a
crisis State and come out of it we
change in some way as a person it's like
surviving a 10ar pile up on the freeway
your car flips over two or three times
you're tossed about and you seem to get
out of the car walk out of it alive with
a mild concussion while others around
you died there's something that happens
inside of us when we survive any kind of
Crisis whatsoever and that falls into
spiritual change and when we induce
ourselves with a toxic chemical compound
that throws our body into chaos after it
subsides we feel we spiritually grew the
addiction process this is a big one the
addiction process that occurs with any
dose of
psychedelics the addiction to
how did we survive that what a heck of a
ride my spiritual teacher told me how
much I've grown by doing it I think I'm
ready to do it again one of the
addictive aspects of psychedelics is the
adrenaline surge the roller coaster ride
it's when any poison or toxin hits the
bloodstream the adrenaline
explodes poisons enter our bloodstream
and that adrenaline surge happens the
roller coaster ride that poison is
foreign the psychedelics the frog toad
poison the psilocybin iasa it's all
foreign to the body your body has to
protect the brain so your adrenals
release a blow a spill a massive spill
of adrenaline it becomes a steroid
compound instantly steroids are there to
try to stop a crisis it's your natural
steroid maker your adrenals release that
steroid your adrenaline to stop the blow
from being hard to the brain heart and
lungs so it doesn't take a hit so hard a
micro do of psychedelics triggers off a
brain alarm because the brain starts to
get poisoned the brain then sends an
emergency signal to the brain stem and
then out to your adrenals looking for
for the adrenals to save your
brain and that intense adrenaline blend
that's pouring out spilling out of your
adrenals is released to stop Strokes
from occurring and blood clots from
forming that adrenaline is there to thin
out the blood and open up blood vessels
because guess what the blood vessels are
starting to close so the steroid
compounds in the adrenaline are there to
keep the blood vessels open so they're
not getting shut down swell and close
down from the
poisons yo dude get in here man it's on
TV now check out this commercial yeah I
love it is there anyone out there who
still isn't clear about what doing drugs
does okay last
time this is your
brain this is
[Applause]
drugs
this is your brain on
drugs any
questions when a toxin from psychedelics
or like toad poison psychedelics frog
poison psychedelics enters into our
bloodstream our immune system sees it as
an Invader as a psychedelic poison
enters our bloodstream our immune cells
try to devour it and when our immune
systems try to devour it it bulks up our
immune cells climb on top of each other
it becomes a ball like a big snowball
rolling down a hill a mountain more and
more immune cells keep on coming to Aid
the other immune cells and they all try
to Devour the
poison this leads to a small blood clot
developing our immune system has an
intelligence built into it our immune
cells know that a small blood clot is
developing
our immune cells also know something's
coming to rescue it a corrosive
substance something that's coming from
our adrenal glands something that can
dissolve the blood clot something that's
strong now adrenaline isn't as strong as
kerosene it's not like paint thinner but
it's strong in its own way it's there to
thin out the blood it's there to destroy
the the blood clot that the immune cells
were building by devouring the poison
it's there to separate that blood clot
to send the immune cells on their way
with the poison inside of them this
lowers the blow to the brain this
process lowers the blow that the toxins
from the Frog poison toad poison or
psychedelics or iasa psilocybin or
whatever it lowers the blow to the brain
stem in the brain and then that
adrenaline opens up the passageways like
a steroid so there's less constriction
in blood vessels in the brain and other
places in the body so that poisons that
the person ingested can leave the brain
and body easier this whole process
becomes
chaos this chaos is part of the
addiction process of psychedelics the
adrenaline that's released to thin out
the blood so that the person does
doesn't stroke out also goes into the
brain and gives the person the ultimate
high at the very same time the chemical
compounds the toxins in the psychedelics
are saturating neurons causing
hallucinogenic effects it's this
combination of that big adrenaline high
from that big adrenaline burst to save
the person to keep them safe as much as
possible combined with the toxin itself
from the psychedelics
gives the person the addiction and then
there's the aftermath what goes up must
come down the aftermath is the coming
down part the adrenaline high now
leaving your body and becoming an
adrenaline low our body is in the
process of recovery now as the poisonous
chemical compounds from the psychedelics
are
dissipating and we survived it we
survived a another night or another day
it's not exactly the same as being in a
party where you got totally completely
drunk and stoned and puked in the
bathroom all night long and then spent
the next day in a stoer and a hangover
yet there are
similarities
regardless whichever toxin or compound
or substance you sent through your body
you went into survival mode they're
parties you'll never forget get
experiences that become etched in your
Consciousness the parties we never
forget aren't cures for depression the
parties that we go and do aren't the
parties that actually get rid of our
anxiety in the end the parties we never
forget don't get rid of our brain fog or
fatigue or neurological symptoms the
parties we never forget only worsen them
one of the saddest parts of psychedelics
is knowing that somebody out there
25-year-old or 28-year-old or anyone who
doesn't have any idea why they're sick
they've seen a number of doctors tried a
number of
medications they can't find relief
mentally or physically and then they
stumble into the world of this can heal
you physically and spiritually just try
this micro doing it's one thing if
you're not healing so you take some
junky vitamins or try a range of animal
protein and plant-based diets try a few
different therapies and healing
techniques try conventional
Pharmaceuticals and you're still stuck
and you're still sick that's a better
place to be than getting caught up in
the world of psychedelics believing that
maybe you have a spiritual block that's
keeping you physically ill when we lose
time and we're really exhausted and we
don't have answers that are working or
helping the next easy cell is it has to
be you you're the problem this is a
spiritual issue a mental and emotional
problem the psychedelics will shift
something within you you'll be told
bring you to more spiritual growth take
you on a spiritual journey or problems
can be solved so the outcomes in how you
feel physically and emotionally can
improve and be healed or you'll start
hearing that the psychedelics will
change your brain chemistry on a
scientific level so that you can find
relief symptom relief relief of chronic
illness and there's some type of
systematic chemistry that changes inside
the brain when applying
psychedelics on even a pharmaceutical
level in the future to find out more
read medical medium brain
saver many of us want to feel we have
control over what we're putting inside
our body
micro doing gives us this false sense of
security that we're in control our
Consciousness and thought process can be
very different from even defiant to what
our body and soul really need or want we
might say no micro doing is controlled
it's careful I'm going to heal with this
our physical brain and our metaphysical
Soul are not saying that our physical
brain is saying don't let that poison
enter this Temple it doesn't matter if
that's psychedelic is trendy right now
in this time in history and in earlier
times in history do not let it enter the
temple the ghost that lives inside our
brain our soul is saying don't shorten
my time here on Earth and slow down your
spiritual
growth original public published medical
medium information gets stolen and
poached by podcast doctors social media
doctors influencers and medical clinics
medical medium information has never yet
been proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits in and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
cast is not man-made it comes from above
from a higher source whatever you
believe in whether God the universe the
light or the Creator or if you believe
in nothing at all that we're just
floating through space together on this
rock know that the information you hear
on this podcast is separate from all the
other noise out there it comes from a
different place a pure untampered with
Advanced Clean uncorrupted original
primary source a higher source Spirit of
compassion