how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about the bloodb
brain barrier the bloodb brain barrier
has limitations and vulnerabilities it's
only Geared for the small stuff not the
big stuff the small stuff not all the
poison and toxins environmental waste
and so much that we're up against every
day our human body is not geared for the
levels of exposure we experience on this
planet a bloodb brain barrier never
anticipated the Industrial Revolution
and the classified medical industry
where pathogens dominate the
revolution convincing us that our bloodb
brain barrier can handle anything
convincing us that our human body is
equipped to handle anything is basically
saying our human body is equipped to
handle nuclear waste we're told in many
ways that we created here on the planet
so we should be able to handle it we
created it we should be able to handle
it our bloodb brain barrier should have
no problem no problem at all protecting
us against anything protect us against
nuclear waste right or any kind of toxic
material
right Max
Max put put the toxic barrels over there
put the toxic barrels over there oh oh
oh you spilled it you spilled it don't
worry don't worry your bloodb brain
barriers got you
covered yeah yeah you don't need to
shower that off just get back to work
but our bloodb brain barriers take care
of all that toxic
waste no one I repeat no one is
measuring the levels of toxins in our
environment no one I know everybody
thinks there is somebody I know
everybody thinks there's an agency I
know everybody thinks there's some kind
of scientific body that it's all taken
care of that's what we're taught we're
taught that in
school everybody's taught that that in
college they're taught that at
universities they're taught that in high
schools they're taught that there's
this Universal knowledge or knowing that
everything's taken care of that
everything's okay with the environment
because
surely
surely no one wants to destroy the
planet that we live on I mean
surely but that's the problem nobody's
really watching nobody's keeping keeping
an eye on it and then there's the whole
climate change thing climate change well
that means in some way that somebody's
watching over the planet right like all
the pollution and the toxins and
environmental waste it's all covered
under climate change so if everybody's
so worried about climate change then
everybody must be monitoring some way
somehow the destruction of the planet
there has to be some science behind that
there there has to be some body of
government or body of science that's
actually keeping an eye on all of this
but that's where it's misleading there
isn't on another note did you ever think
about the whole global warming thing
remember that's where it started it was
global warming science was saying global
warming we were taught in school that it
was global warming but what happened to
global warming the Earth isn't heating
up anymore it's not warming up anymore
we were taught and told that it was
Ironclad solid to the
core set in stone that it was global
warming and suddenly it all changed
that's it now it's climate change that
means whatever happens it just falls
under climate change but global warming
don't even say that word anymore you
don't get laughed at you got to just
kind of like never even remember that
phrase because science was
wrong that's why and now climate change
science is right but what about 10 years
from now is science going to be wrong
again because science isn't really right
about anything because I'll tell you
right now when it comes down to this
nobody's really looking no one's
monitoring it's just a bunch of Talking
Heads that's what it is now it's not
real science behind something actually
trying to figure something out because
no real science is watching over truly
the toxic waste on this planet and the
levels of the toxic waste they're not
watching the
Chemtrails as they're just falling down
they're not monitoring or testing what
the planes are releasing in the sky that
are being dumped in our lakes rivers on
our fields on our grass on our Lawns on
our heads none of that is being
monitored it's just
Phantom I was always told by my source
since I was younger that it's global
cooling planets cooling down little bit
at a time but cooling down one of the
reasons is from the Chemtrails alone
clouding up the sky blocking the
Sun that part alone is cooling down the
planet never mind other forms of toxic
waste what about planet Mars planet Mars
is
freezing temperatures drop it gets real
cold yeah because there was toxic waste
on that planet through
Wars that planet self-
imploded basically lots of Wars lots of
Destruction planet was
annihilated toxins everywhere in the
atmosphere and it just
died absolutely just stopped and ceased
and died Mars is dead Planet just
starting to probably come back and
spring back to life in some way after a
very long period of time it's also a
chil planet there might be some warm
spots at different times just warm
enough but it gets cold and the
temperature drops after we destroy this
planet at some
point same thing's going to happen but
what does it matter the bloodb brain
barrier takes care of everything it
stops everything from getting into our
brain it protects us everything's okay
hey hey you heard it out there don't
worry it has to cross the bloodb brain
barrier nothing can cross the bloodb
brain barrier right that's what we're
told so what does it all matter medical
research and science medical
Industries don't want to admit there are
toxic heavy metals in everybody's brains
they don't even want to entertain the
idea and publicly known medical research
and science they're in the infancy
stages of just recognizing izing
pathogens being responsible for chronic
illness if they're that early in
understanding chronic illness if they're
at the beginning process of
understanding pathogens being
responsible for chronic illness barely
at the beginning process then how
advanced can they possibly be
understanding our body's complexities or
mechanisms such as the bloodb brain
barrier our bloodb brain barrier was not
meant to handle any of this we act like
it's this impermeable substance this
impermeable structure this wall that
stops things that it has no limitations
we're taught that no don't worry about
it blood brain barriers got it all
covered it can't get through there
nuclear waste Industrial Waste solvents
yeah solvents you're exposed to solvents
every day and don't even know it toxic
heavy metals all someone has to do is
use the term bloodb brain barrier to
make us feel feel like we're all warm
and fuzzy and protected nothing could be
wrong don't worry about that you got a
bloodb brain barrier and yet the reality
all these things and more passes through
the bloodb brain barrier pharmaceutical
companies big Pharma they design drugs
to pass through your bloodb brain
barrier they try really hard to do it
funny thing is the drugs that they don't
believe pass through the bloodb brain
barrier still pass through the bloodb
brain barrier so what is our blood brain
barrier for what was our blood brain
barrier originally designed for well
I'll tell you to keep natural mostly
bodily toxins out of the brain like when
someone has a little too much uric acid
in their system because they have a weak
kidney issue if you have a weak kidney
or kidney disease your uric acid's
building up in your
bloodstream that is not supposed to
cross the bloodb brain barrier it's a
natural phenomenon a natural process
it's a natural bodily function fluid
it's a toxin our body is dealing with
naturally we have a kidney problem we
have uric acid built up in the
bloodstream it's not supposed to cross
the blood brain barrier if someone gets
a cut and it goes too deep and there's
an infection developing and even sepsis
could be possible from a blood infection
developing from that deep cut that
infection is not supposed to cross the
bloodb brain barrier that's what it's
for and get ready for this one if
someone ingests a toxic plant that's
been on planet Earth for 10,000 years
and grown naturally on the earth and was
never meant to be human food the bloodb
brain barrier is there to hold back at
least some of the toxins in an effort to
prevent the brain from going into toxic
shock and still toxic chemical compounds
from that plant will still cross the
bloodb brain barrier but some will stay
behind our cerebral spinal fluid which
surrounds our brain and spinal cord is
supposed to be pure the good stuff it's
supposed to be
uncontaminated it's supposed to be clean
that's the goal gold standard in this
time on planet Earth our cerebral spinal
fluid is not pure though it's not the
gold standard it's supposed to be but
it's not it's harboring chemical soups
from industry pathogenic byproducts
toxic heavy metals and a crap ton more a
thousand years ago our cereal spinal
fluid may have just had some toxic heavy
metals in it but that's about it from
drinking water water in the cities from
lead pipes there wasn't any Industrial
Revolution plants all around the planet
spewing out Mercury and toxins and all
kinds of other poisons it didn't exist
it was just some lead from drinking
water and the occasional drinking of
mercury Elixir thinking it might give
you longevity or heal a chronic illness
today we walk around
polluted the blood brain barrier
has
limitations if an industry creates a
battery and then that battery sits in
the car and it corrodes and someone
actually tries to change that battery
and there's battery AET that appears on
the battery and then gets consumed
accidentally it's going across the
bloodb brain barrier if a child gets a
hold of a little battery and start to
chew on it and the acid leaks and burns
the child's throat it's not just just
the burn on the child's throat causes a
lot of problems it's the acid crossing
the bloodb brain barrier industrial
toxins and mercury and other toxic heavy
metals are going to enter the brain
they're going to cross the blood brain
barrier when we think about the blood
brain barrier we hear it or we talk
about it it seems so strong in our minds
it's like a barrier we hear the word
barrier you look up that word barrier
it's serious it means like a wall it
means something blocking or
protecting barrier but really it's
really not like that at all it's a thin
construction it acts as a type of thin
filtering wall of tissue it's tissue
it's not this incredible wall built out
of stone and
rock the bloodb brain barrier is not
even as strong as your skin your skin on
your face skin on your arm it's way
weaker way thinner than any of that if
you slap on some cologne or perfume
right on your skin it's going to go
right through your skin absorb through
all the layers and enter your
bloodstream the bloodb brain barrier
worse goes through it like it wasn't
even there and when that cologne enters
your bloodstream just breathing it in or
enters it through the skin it heads up
and crosses the bloodb brain
barrier there are many Pharmaceuticals
designed to pass through your bloodb
brain barrier morphine is one of them
it's one of the reasons why morphine can
kill you so easily it can cross through
blood vessels of the brain and spinal
fluid vessels fast remember this all
Pharmaceuticals have toxic heavy metals
in them so engineering Pharmaceuticals
to cross the blood brain barrier means
the toxic heavy metals in those
Pharmaceuticals also cross through the
bloodb brain barrier whether it's
Platinum titanium copper Mercury
aluminum were exposed via pharmaceutical
pills creams and liquids and more and it
all crosses the bloodb brain
barrier and what about all the oxidation
people having toxic heavy metals in
their organs their livers you know
medical medium information that got out
there all these years how metals are in
our organs and they're
oxidizing as they're oxidizing they're
leeching and that runoff which is the
oxidation coming off those Metals
travels through the body well that
runoff that oxidation can also travel
and cross the bloodb brain barrier
too science of research medical science
doctors none no one knew that the toxic
heavy metals stored in small amounts
throughout all the organs of the body
and that a blood test
taken doesn't catch that doesn't see
that so when you get your blood drawn
and they're looking for toxic heavy
metals in there and they're really low
you could still have a high amount of
toxic heavy metals in your brain your
liver your pancreas your spleen medical
research and science did not know that
they thought the blood test determined
how many metals you had in your body and
then the teachings of medical medium
information getting out there for
decades and the publishing of the books
has changed
everything now you'll see today when you
get a blood test a lot of blood labs are
actually putting a little disclaimer on
the document on the test saying we're
only seeing what we see in the blood but
you could have it in the organs and
tissue and the crazy thing is I can't
tell you how many people have battled
how many profess Professionals in health
throughout the years when I said look
the blood test doesn't show everything
with toxic heavy metals it could be
anywhere in your tissue your organs your
brain and the blood test doesn't
determine it same thing with hair
analysis I battled so many different
professionals on this and now the blood
Labs put it on their documents as
they're handing the documents out to
people their tests meanwhile science
hasn't studied or tested any of it where
did they get the information they didn't
do a study
they can't measure it they've never done
a study measuring it they're not
biopsying people they're not actually
sticking needles in people's tissue and
saying well your blood test says this
but we're actually doing biopsies on
your brain and your tissue and your
liver and your organs and your pancreas
and we're looking woo you got some heavy
metals in there still but the blood test
says you don't have any they're not
doing that at all where did they get it
it came out of thin air well I know
where it came from there's no study
behind it and there's no science behind
it it's a shame they don't site The
Source other things pass through the
blood brain barrier viruses and viral
toxins now viruses are small all in its
own can you imagine a neurotoxin coming
from a virus just think about how small
that really is a neurotoxin it goes
right through the blood brain barrier
fast and easy and neurotoxins coming
from viruses well that's medical meme
information as well
one of the reasons publicly known
medical research and science doesn't
even identify
neurotoxins is because they're so small
when neurotoxins are excreted from the
Epstein bar virus shingles virus hhv6
hhv7 simplex 1 Simplex 2 and so many
other viruses when they're
excreted they are excreted in a liquid
form and then that liquid slips right
through the blood brain
barrier if classified medical research
and science ever discovered neurotoxins
being released from viruses and they
told publicly known medical research and
science about it then science would be
completely halted on it publicly known
medical research and science would not
be allowed to do any more research on
neurotoxins involving viruses at all the
reason because it would lead to the disc
discovery that viruses actually eat and
go to bathroom and this information
about viruses releasing neurotoxins
would compromise the gene Theory where
medical science is trying to convince
everybody on the planet they're sick
because of their
genes there are certain varieties of
Epstein bar that can cross through the
bloodb brain barrier and there are
varieties that can't cross through the
bloodb brain barrier but their
neurotoxins still can either way way
that's what gilon Beret syndrome is
pathogens and pathogenic toxins and
waste Crossing through the bloodb brain
barrier the pathogens that can cross the
bloodb brain barrier do so by latching
onto the barrier itself and inflaming it
all the way through they slowly do
tissue damage to the barrier so the
pathogens can enter and cross eventually
permeating it and leaving microscopic
thick barrier
scars keep all of this in mind as easy
as it is to convince us that our blood
brain barrier is an impermeable presence
that makes us impenetrable to the
dangers that Industries release into our
world all we have to do is look around
us at the suffering on this planet to be
reminded that this doesn't add up if we
we want to save ourselves we can't take
advantage of our body's protective
mechanisms we can't take our bloodb
brain barrier for granted but we do we
have to protect our brain and body we
have to bring every chance we can to our
brain to protect it and that starts with
bringing awareness to the Daily
exposures in our Mists our brains and
body
have not betrayed us they've been
betrayed by industrial chemicals and
other contaminantes in our everyday
lives that have only accelerated in
development in recent
years original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing in years of
their life searching for answers like so
many have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our modern-day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium and information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion