how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William today we're talking about
tattoos now I'm not judging anyone who's
got a tattoo and I'm not judging anybody
who wants a tat and I'm not pulling that
old hey Sunny don't do the that too I
wouldn't do that if I were you to the
young people but there is something you
need to know hang on for the ride this
is lightning and I mean lightning and
you'll see
why yeah no sit down sit down you can
hang out while I'm getting this tattoo
right now ow oh okay no no it doesn't
hurt doesn't hurt what am I getting I'm
getting this crazy lady that's got like
she's like a Medusa
right and like snakes in her hair and um
she's got a rose wrapped wrapped around
her and then she's got like she's
holding she's holding a sword and it's
got a skull on the sword it's my design
I I you know I told the guy what I
wanted yeah and then on my thigh I'm
getting a viking but it's a viking
lady right and above her it says vajala
in red and orange with Fire in the Sky
and and there's a whole bunch of like
people's heads on Pikes all around and
there's just like crazy old tree and
tree trunk coming out of the ground and
then some gravestones all around it it's
just actually it's incredible and I love
it and my friend was like designing it
and yeah and then I'm oh I'm getting
something written across my rib cage
yeah yeah what kills
you doesn't make wait what is it it's
written it's it's I got it on paper it's
like what doesn't hurt you makes you
stronger or something like
that as of today there are no sources of
tattoo ink that are free of toxic heavy
metals and as of today there are no
tattoo inks free of metals but I know
there's some people out there that are
just going to say no way not my ink I
know cuz I got the assurance that my ink
was
crueltyfree crueltyfree and not to
mention my ink was vegan and crueltyfree
so there's no way that's not my ink I'm
going to listen to the show but this
isn't me I repeat there are no tattoo
inks available out there without metals
and there's something else you might
want to know there is a certain
percentage of ingredients inside the
tattoo ink
that do not have to be exposed and do
not have to be
disclosed just like in food products
they can have a certain small percentage
of ingredients chemicals and so forth
all kinds of different ingredients that
do not have to be disclosed and just
like
supplementation same thing you could
have a certain amount a certain
percentage of ingredients that are
hidden not disclosed to the public or
the consumer that are in there and
nobody knows about will tell tattoo ink
is the same these days there are people
out there that are really careful about
what they eat careful about what they
drink making sure that if they drink
coffee it's the best stuff out there
like they even know the Farms like there
are people out there that are crazy
about what's going on what they put on
their body they're concerned whatever
kind of cream whatever kind of facial
they get whatever it is they're all
about I don't put things in my body that
that shouldn't be there meanwhile
they'll be getting a tattoo and those
are the kind of people that if they want
a tattoo they're asking questions like
is this tattoo good is it clean is it
crueltyfree and the place they're
getting it be like yeah here's our best
inks here's what it is and it's like
great I feel good about this put it in
my body and that ink is not free of
heavy metals and that ink is not free of
toxins and that ink is not free of metal
s is that ink better than the ink 30
years ago probably is the ink better
than the ink they used 50 years ago yeah
definitely but how much better is it not
that much better and then there's the
people that are afraid to speak up no
judgment no anything like that but
they're afraid to speak up so they go
get a tattoo they don't want to tell
that tattoo artist anything they don't
want to say hey can you use this ink or
what's your ink made out of they're just
afraid they could have been recommended
to the place from a friend and there
could be a huge waiting list because the
tattoo artist is amazing really good at
what they do they could have traveled
across the country around the world
could be this one guy in
La this one person in La it could be
anybody and they go and they're there
and they're not going to say anything
just sign the dotted line just put it in
boom and then then there's the sanitary
issues the sanitary issues that are at
hand literally on the
hand now I know that tattoo artists they
change their gloves they're not using
the same pair of gloves each person and
you'll never see a tattoo artist wear
white gloves and you'll never see a
tattoo artist wear blue gloves they wear
black gloves the reason why it'll look
like a murder scene now blood is really
tricky tends to get everywhere
it's not even like water water doesn't
get everywhere that's how crazy it is
blood tends to get everywhere because
blood is slippery it's got a
viscosity and micro drops go everywhere
so when someone's getting a tattoo the
micro drops are flying you don't see
them it's hard to see them they don't
leave a stain but they fly now there's a
good chance your tattoo artist is just
going to change gloves between clients
and those gloves are laced with blood
the client's blood now you would think
it's Flawless nothing bad could happen
the guy or the girl takes off their
gloves throws them away in the
biowaste but if you took a blue light
over everything you would see blood in
weird places you would see it on the
table you'd see it on the floor you'd
see it on the chair you'd see it on the
box they're drawing new gloves from the
very box that has brand new gloves you
would see it even on that box but of
course you get a brand new set of
needles for your tattoo and years past
you wouldn't get a set of new needles it
would be the same needles it would just
be needles that went through a
sterilizer the guy would walk up to the
incubator sterilization machine open up
the door pull a brand new needle out not
a brand new needle out an old needle
that was used before 100 times take it
out say it was
sterilized attach it to the gun and get
to work there are millions of people
that had their tattoos done that way and
have transmitted a lot of different bugs
because of it
viruses bacteria but it's changed now
it's brand new needles in brand new
packages but what hasn't changed is
other forms of
contamination tiny blood smears tiny
blood drops everywhere any friends that
I have that want to get a tattoo or have
tattoos and want to get another tattoo I
tell them be the first client of the day
don't be the second don't be the last if
I was going to get a tattoo I would
bring a brand new set of gloves better
than that I would bring a box my own box
of gloves then I would make sure I was
the first person
and it was after the tattoo artist had a
day off this allows for any kind of germ
warfare any kind of pathogens viruses
bacteria that could be from other
people's blood that could be left
anywhere anywhere at all in the tattoo
parlor gives it a chance for there to be
a die off several years ago I was in a
tattoo parlor with a friend my friend
asked me to be there wanted me to be
there while he was getting a tattoo so I
was watching everything so the tattoo
artist grabbed some fresh gloves put
them on his hands looked at me and said
is this good he was being sarcastic cuz
he knew I was there to just keep an eye
on things cuz my friend said so so I was
watching everything he also grabbed some
new needles brand new needles he opened
them up and he made a joke too at the
same time but he grabbed the new needles
unpackaged them put them in the gun he
also told me how much he s paralyzed the
place he started to work on my friend he
was doing the tattoo everything was
going pretty good I was sitting there
okay not bad and then I saw him he took
his right hand and He adjusted his stool
there was a little handle on his stool
and because each client had a different
height different weight different size
person he would have to get himself
comfortable position himself just right
and he would have to adjust his stool
and then he had blood from this client
which was my friend on his glove and
then he reached over with the hand that
had my friend's blood on it and grabbed
the handle to the stool and then I said
wait a
minute hold on here wait a minute and I
had to give a
101 to a highly experienced tattoo
artist famous is in La who's worked on
everybody I said was that stool
sterilized and he said no I said was a
handle to that stool sterilized he said
no I said you touch that on every client
he said yeah I told my friend this is
why you got to be the first client of
the day and this is why it should be
after a day or two off that the tattoo
artist had maybe if the tattoo artist
took the weekend off then it's Monday
morning first client this way way you'll
have a better chance for whatever was on
that stool handle could have had time to
die off and this isn't Ironclad so the
artist sterilized the chair sterilized a
stool did some extra sterilizing
everywhere else did some alcohol rubs in
different places and then of course
changed out the gloves and changed out
the gun because he was touching the gun
after touching the stool then touching
the gun and put some new needles into my
friend he was happy with his Polar Bear
tattoo I have to admit came out freaking
amazing almost made me want to get one
but I didn't but I still told my friend
just because the ink was crty free and
vegan it didn't mean it was metal free
or hidden toxin free my friend was
bummed out to hear about the metal part
but he was happy it was crueltyfree and
I said you know that's good because they
didn't experiment or torture the animals
in the world to make your tattoo ink
what people don't know is that without
the toxic heavy metals or Metals at all
inside the tattoo ink you can't get the
pop the shine you need Metals inside the
ink so that when the sunlight hits your
skin it reflects off the metals without
Metals in the ink any light hitting your
skin your arm your body your back your
chest your face your neck you won't be
able to see the tattoo it won't be clear
it won't be fresh it won't pop it won't
have vibrancy you have to have Metals in
there so when light hits at any kind of
light the light inside your room the
light inside your car the light inside a
restaurant wherever the light is the
light in the sky it has to hit the metal
it has to reflect and then you see it
that's why a brand new tattoo really
pops it really showcases it really
exhibits itself the newer the tattoo the
better the display and then over time
the tattoo fades it could take years
it's very slow but it fades and as it's
fading the metals are leaving that could
be a good thing right the metals are
leaving but wait they're not leaving
they're staying they're just shifting
their location they're entering your
bloodstream they're entering your
lymphatic system they're entering both
and from there they take a nice little
trip into the liver they stay in there
as long as they can until they get
overloaded and they leave the liver and
they head to the brain as these Metals
leave the Derma and they leave your
tattoo it's the wild west some of the
metals may not even go to your liver
they'll just go straight to your brain
but they never ever leave your
bloodstream and leave your kidneys and
leave you unless you're doing something
proactive we'll talk about that later
having a tattoo and having that tattoo
ink in the Derma of your skin is
different than drinking something like
so say you drink something that has
toxic heavy metals in it there might be
a tiny percentage a small portion of
those metals that might leave your body
through your urine and the reason for
that is because those metals were never
in your body they never had a long time
to sit inside your body they've never
conformed they've never changed they've
never altered while in your body they're
fresh they're in the drink or something
you're eating they go in your body it's
brand new your body excretes some of it
out keeps most of it but still excretes
some of it out the metals in your
tattooing though that's sitting in you
for one year 5 years 10 years has
started to oxidize it's not the same
thing as it was when it went in you for
one it has a different weight to it for
two your body has identified it over the
years learn to live with it your body's
not in a rush to eliminate it it's not
thinking it needs to your immune system
has learned to coexist with it it's not
in a rush or any desire to eliminate it
or get rid of it or help carry it out
our immune systems are designed to
gobble up fresh threats fresh toxins
fresh Metals things that it sees as a
threat but the metals inside and the
toxins inside the ink that's in your arm
for a long time our immune system has
learned to cohabitate with it as these
oxidized Metals leech out of your Derma
into your bloodstream there isn't a bell
whistling there isn't a massive red flag
your body's not alarmed your body has
coexisted with it for a long time
there's no rush to push it out there's
no Avenue to send it out
it's Wild West it's free it's clear and
it's heading where it wants to go
another reason why your body's not in a
rush to get rid of the toxic heavy
metals from the tattoo ink that's
leeching out of your Derma into the
bloodstream and another reason why your
immune system isn't in a rush either is
because it's been time relased slow and
steady slow and steady and that's how it
goes every year every day every decade a
little bit at a time there's no alarm
Bells being rung just a little bit at a
time coming out and that's why the body
is not in any any emergency or rush to
rid it but as the years go by the tattoo
starts to fade maybe because you're
thinking well that's what it's supposed
to do right supposed to fade it was done
many years ago you grow older no it's
supposed to be just as shiny and nice as
the day you got it because it's not
supposed to have metal in there it's
supposed to have some new form of
technology that they'll discover 30
years down the road 50 years down the
road that never Fades that isn't a toxic
heavy metal something they'll create in
a lab somewhere but right now it's the
metals and they fade because they leave
time relased they dissipate they go away
as the years go on and you're left with
a faded tattoo and as the light from the
sun or light from the light in your room
or light from anywhere hits your arm
hits your leg hit your back hit your
neck it doesn't pop anymore the metals
are leaving it doesn't reflect against
the metal as much anymore if you already
have tattoos don't have to remove them
instead you can follow medical medium
protocols to stop up and expel the
metals as they're being time relased out
of your Derma into your blood and lymph
this way over time the metals don't keep
on building up inside your brain if
you're somebody that doesn't like their
tattoo anymore and they want it gone
they want to remove it I don't recommend
that because the procedure could release
more toxic heavy metals more toxins into
your blood and lymph faster heavier I
prefer just leaving them on people keep
them don't worry about it unless you
really want them removed and if you do
then really you should be following the
heavy metal detox Guidance the medical
medium books brain saver if anybody has
a tattoo remember the metals slowly
leech out of the Derma into your system
your blood your lymph your brain your
liver your spleen your pancreas your
bones so it's always best to do the
right
protocols
hey let we got under this hot dog stand
just in time yeah all right all right
just wait for the storms lightning bad
lightning yeah the Lightning's really
bad oh whoa you see that guy down at the
beach yeah that guy's totally Inked Up
he's got ink from his head down to his
toe man he doesn't know it but he's got
to be careful because that's metal and
that's lightning
yeah yeah cuz the metal it's
industrialized that's the kind of metal
they put in us it's different than the
minerals and trace minerals that are in
our body yeah oh totally he's like an
iron Rod right now for that lightning
bolt yeah someone's got to tell them but
I'm I I don't know should we go out
there let's go out there and tell them
think the guy will get mad I don't know
he might punch me out I don't know I'm
going head out there and tell them to
get get undercover
okay something to understand that when
we get tattoos we're putting a lot of
metal under our skin this isn't metal
like minerals trace minerals from the
plants we eat from the food that we eat
from the water we drink these are
manufactured metals that are inside the
tattoo inks they're destabilized they're
industrialized it's not like the plants
we eat the food wheat it's not the same
trace minerals inside our body it's not
the trace minerals that actually help us
function it's not the electrolytes that
are in our
bloodstream when you're playing a game
of golf and a thunderstorm comes and you
see some lightning bolts in the distance
you're holding a golf club you know you
have to put it away and head back it's
not that you have to be afraid or scared
of a lightning storm thunderstorm more
so than anybody else but it's something
to keep in mind
because the lightning tends to find
metal it looks for lamp posts it looks
for fence posts it looks for metal
objects it looks for metal lawn chairs
it looks for metal gates it looks for
all kinds of different varieties of
metal sticking out of the ground and it
looks for metal roofs lightning tends to
search and
seek just like someone doesn't want to
go into a lightning storm wrapped in
aluminum foil you just don't want to do
it someone doesn't want to go into a
lightning storm holding a golf club in
the air it's not about having fear it's
not about being scared it's just about
being proactive and careful lightning
storm coming your way Thunder's going
you see lightning bolts you got a ton of
Ink on you and in you just be careful
try to get cover protect yourself be
aware be smart about it that's all these
are just just some of the things to
consider if you have tattoos or you plan
on getting tattoos or you have tattoos
and you plan on getting more
tattoos I've been bringing awareness
about Metals being in tattoos for
decades now here's a recent clip of a
social media live stream I did in 2022
March 16th where I talk about tattoo ink
and metals inside of it so with brain
fog you can have metal sprinkled
about so you're what like where do I get
Mercury and all these metals like where
does it come from well I noticed a lot
of people like tattoos these days a lot
of people like ink these days and I'm
not against getting ink at all if you
got ink don't get it
removed you know I mean if you have ink
it's fine it's fine but what people
don't realize is that's a huge one for
toxic heavy metals that's why the heavy
metal detox cleanse is so important
that's why the heavy metal detox
smoothie is so important because it's
that there's no heavy metal free ink so
when you get when someone's like hey I
know this great tattoo parlor I know
this great tattoo artist they use
crueltyfree ink they use animal
crueltyfree ink it's vegan it's vegan
ink it's filled with metal you can't
have it any other way and I'll tell you
why when you get your
ink right and I'll show you this right
here you see this Rose you you can see
this rose up
close the reason why you can see the
rose on your arm when you get the ink or
you get on your wherever you got your
tattoo maybe you just got an inscription
maybe you just got some wise words you
know like some wise words written across
maybe you got like you know the name of
of something written somewhere whatever
it is that you choose to get you see the
rose it pops when light hits it right
when it's in your arm and the only way
that can happen is if that ink is filled
with metal that's the reflective nature
of the ink so what happens is when light
goes into your
Derma anything light any kind of light
not sunlight any kind of light goes
through your Derma it hits the ink and
it reflects back
out that's how you get that pop so when
you walk out of a tattoo parlor and the
dude there or whoever gave a
tattoo they said it was animal Cru
cruelty free ink maybe it was animal
cruelty free free ink but it's not heavy
metal free ink because the metals make
it so you can see it and so here's how
it works as the metals go into your
bloodstream every day from there on out
and they go to your brain over time as
the metals travel into your bloodstream
and get to your brain over time okay
your your tattoo f Fades it's not fading
because you're getting
older it's not fading because you've had
the tattoo for 10 years or 15 years 20
years it's fading because all the metal
is slowly leaving through your Derma
that pass through your Derma into your
bloodstream and ends up in your
liver and ends up in your brain that's
where it's going right and it's not
about getting them removed it's about
just being proactive and catching the
metals as they're
leaving I always tell people who are
Inked Up heavy metal detox smoothie for
Life Man heavy metal detox smoothie for
life because what you're going to do is
you're going to be catching the metals
as they're going to the brain you're
going to be catching
[Music]
[Applause]
them lately I've been feeling
subdued I'm in a strange mood I think I
want a
tattoo do I want color I'm feeling kind
of
blue what about red orange green can be
true life has been kind of hard I'm
going to head down to Hollywood
Boulevard get myself some ink regardless
of who is in my life that raises a stink
it's my ident ID it now I want ink
because it's good and don't hold back
give me plenty doesn't matter what
everyone says that I'm going to be bored
of what I got long before I'm dead I
want it now doesn't matter which parlor
and how give me some Basset tracin let
it heal fast I'm off to the races the
tattoo exhibit is around the corner so
others can Google and oole and St at my
faces all of this can be fine and dandy
as long as I'm mindful
proactive and I'm doing my heavy metal
detox because it's
handy original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
their life searching for answers like so
many have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together this rock know that the
information you hear on this podcast is
separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion