how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about coffee
enimas now I think you might want to
hear this episode because there's a
whole lot of people doing a whole lot of
bad to themselves but I don't blame them
one bit it's easy to fall in into an old
trendy trap that becomes a new trendy
trap all over again but this one sneaks
up the back door and chips away at your
true foundation and Constitution in a
nutshell if you're sick it could take
you
down hey guys welcome to my YouTube
channel we're doing the coffeea today if
you subscribe to my $44 pay wall you'll
be here a month and if you did the
course the deluxe course course for
$5,000 you'll be here too so we're going
to do the coffee an I'm going show you
what kind of coffee I'm using I have one
that's so great anyway you got to hold
the coffee in for like 3 minutes but it
can get really uncomfortable and that's
okay because you can put on something
relaxing like a podcast or something or
a meditation while we're doing this
whatever works for you like whatever
your truth is just do it anyway this is
going to be help ful for detoxification
of blood and the liver and bile and I'm
energetic after I do it and I feel
really good it's like so amazing anyway
let's get
started coffee Animas are popular
they're
longstanding theoretically the idea is
it cleanses toxins out of the liver
that's a great idea we want toxins out
of the liver we want our liver cleansed
and healthier why not so that's why
coffee enemas really sound good and then
if we get sick chronically sick we hear
about coffee animus being a Panacea like
an alltime fixer upper if we have a
problem a disease any kind of condition
if we're suffering in any way we're
going to hear from somebody somewhere
whether on social or online or at a
clinic do a coffee enema it will help
you it may even save you and coffee
enemas used to be just involved in
alternative medicine so it was an
alternative medicine thing it was never
conventional medicine but now it has
crossed over into conventional medicine
so both fields of medicine say coffee
enemas they're good for you and they all
are parting the same claim a perfectly
good reasonable claim detoxifying the
liver
does help you heal but there's a problem
the first problem here's where we get
into trouble coffee to begin with is
strong very strong but not in a good way
coffee is also harsh very harsh not in a
good way extremely
acidic
dehydrating highly
astringent and
overstimulating because coffee is a drug
and people love their drug people love
their drugs and coffee is one of those
addictive drugs that people don't want
to let go it's hard for them to let go
it's a massive industry and people love
their coffee and that's why the coffee
enema sounds so good there are two kinds
of people in the world one kind of
person will get an Ena any kind of Ena a
water enema some kind of Solution that's
pharmaceutical grade and then there's
the other kind of person in the world
that will never ever ever get an enema
even if they're on their dying breath in
a hospital bed somewhere and this is the
last time they're going to be here on
this planet they will never get an enema
but because everybody drinks coffee and
loves coffee so much that a bridge gets
put in between the two kinds of people
in the world and even some of the most
stubborn people that would never get an
enema will consider an enema only
because it's a coffee enema it's the
only way they'll ever even consider it
they may still not do it but there are
some people that break and they break
because they think about it and they're
like coffee I like coffee okay doctor or
practitioner or health coach I'm going
to do it now remember coffee is really
acidic extremely
astringent very harsh so what happens
when we drink coffee we have a buffer
our stomach is that poison control
Shield it buffers things that aren't
good for us it buffers things that are
really really harsh so our stomachs are
designed to actually try to withhold
poison as long as possible in Hope hopes
that we vomit the poison up or that we
get a chance to exit the poison up the
esophagus out of our mouth and out of
our body so our stomach is a buffer zone
it holds on to things not just for
digestion not just for
stimulation not just for enzymes to
start breaking things down our stomach
purposely holds things in there just
long enough in case something is toxic
or poisonous in case we ingested
something that's extremely bad for us
this doesn't mean coffee makes you
vomit that's not what this is it may
make somebody vomit out there I'm sure
somebody doesn't like coffee or they're
sensitive to it and they vomit it out if
they drink it but it's not meant to
happen that way but it nevertheless
it's a harsh toxic poison that sits
inside the stomach and the stomach
buffers it it buffers the
acidity which is extremely harsh it
buffers the
stringency and it buffers the caffeine
most importantly the caffeine our
stomachs hold on to the caffeine so when
we drink a cup of coffee our stomach is
holding on to the coffee as long as it
can because it's holding on to the
caffeine it identifies the caffeine
hangs on to it so it disperses in small
amounts into the
bloodstream it's holding the caffeine
back as much as possible and as long as
possible so only
increments of the caffeine enter into
the bloodstream not all at once because
when it enters all at once into the
bloodstream it attacks the heart our
stomachs have a two-step identification
process One Step the stomach knows
what's entering into it the tissue
itself is experiencing it and absorbing
it second step a signal from the brain
matches the stomach's understanding they
both connect the brain the nervous
system sends a signal telling the
stomach to hold on to that caffeine as
long as possible the stomach agrees
communicates with the brain and holds on
to the caffeine as long as possible and
one of the most important reasons this
communication happens to hold on to that
poison that caffeine as long as possible
inside the stomach is because if it was
released all at once there would be an
emergency the emergency would be
adrenaline being released on a large
scale a large release of adrenaline so
large it can injure and damage the brain
heart and liver and then there's the
communication between adrenals and the
stomach they have a lot in common they
protect each other adrenals protect the
stomach the stomach protects the
adrenals there's a reason for that too
much adrenaline released too many times
like adrenaline addiction which people
actually suffer from all the time in
different ways too much adrenaline
release damages the nerves in the lining
of the stomach and guess where those
nerves come from they come from the
Vegas nerves and when these nerves get
hypers sensitive from being adrenaline
injured then the person gets nauseous
and hypers sensitive
and can start to feel their food feel it
so much they get confused thinking
they're not digesting their food anymore
so they start saying things like well I
can't eat lettuce and kale and cilantro
and parsley I can't eat zucchinis I
can't eat raw broccoli I can't eat
cucumbers and tomatoes it's too harsh it
feels like it's bothering my stomach and
it's not
digesting what people don't realize the
food's digesting but it doesn't feel
like it's digesting because the nerves
have been irritated and injured the
nerves that align the stomach make no
mistake coffee has caffeine caffeine
ignites
adrenaline everybody's high on
adrenaline they're high in their coffee
they're high in their caffeine and that
caffeine enters the organs enters the
brain the kidneys the liver the spleen
the pancreas and the stomach and that
stomach has all those nerves and the
caffeine over time irritates those
nerves but the stomach holds on to the
caffeine as long as it can with the
communication it has with the brain to
stop an adrenaline release a
superpowered surge of adrenaline so the
stomach releases little spurts of
caffeine into the bloodstream which
ignites the adrenaline to only rise so
much and that's the high everybody runs
on all day long especially if they're
intermittent fasting or they're not
eating much and they're on coffee all
day and they're doing their errands and
their appointments and they're high on
little spurts of
adrenaline and that adrenaline even on
low low Amounts is still
hyper irritating to the nerves along
with the caffeine being irritating to
the nerves as well it's a double whammy
so many people are worried about aging
they're trying to do the whole
anti-aging thing and Longevity but
caffeine is the ultimate
Ager and everybody's on it almost
everybody they're living off of it many
of them women who are worried about
their skin and are worried about getting
older and worried about their looks and
how and their appearance are consuming
caffeine on a rate and on a scale it's
unimaginable at this point in history
and a lot of women nowadays are worried
about what they eat how they take care
of themselves what they're doing for
themselves their exercise routines and
the Spas they go to to get lymphatic
drainage and the saas and everything
else they're doing so what they're
essentially doing is
battling the bad that they're doing
they're hooked on the
caffeine and then they're trying to
counter it without realizing it with all
these other things they're doing so it's
a constant War it's like doing some
things that could be
helpful to support the thing that isn't
helpful while not even realizing this is
happening they need their coffee they
need their caffeine to function to do
their appointments to do anything at all
all day long and the coffe is aging them
the caffeine's Aging them and at the
same time they're using the caffine to
give them strength and energy and
fortitude to go and do all their Marriot
of appointments all day long that are
anti-aging and then there's the men the
new man not the old man in the past that
drank coffee in the morning during his
break time maybe one more at the end of
the day no talking about men that are in
the saas at the Spas every day doing
their exercise routines sitting there on
social all day long and they're hooked
on caffeine too and the caffeine is
giving them energy and giving them
fortitude to push through their day and
get all their appointments done they're
doing things that are aging them like
the coffee and the caffeine and the
energy drinks and that same time they're
trying to do other things that are
anti-aging
when coffee enters our stomach it
challenges our pH
environment it challenges our stomach's
environment our gastric
glands our gastric juices our
HCL but our stomachs can handle many
times strong Brew they can handle it
enough it hinders our stomachs it lowers
our HCL over time which breaks down
protein protein it destroys our gastric
glands throughout the years but
nevertheless our stomach is still
designed to handle a punch and to handle
that strong brew and then there's a
group of people who are
sensitive they've been sensitive their
whole lives or at least a part of their
life they have a pancreas issue
gallbladder problems weak stomachs maybe
Crohn's k or IBS maybe some kind of
digestive compromise or
distress maybe they have neurological
symptoms anxiety Tremors tingles
numbness brain fog aches and pains and
maybe even struggling with insomnia and
they know coffee doesn't sit right with
them and that leads us to another two
kinds of people in the world one doesn't
have a lot of neurological problems
neurological symptoms they're not
struggling with chronic illness they got
in the moment a stomach of
Steel and they can do fine with coffee
they can drink it all day long and every
day and then the other kind of person in
the world the chronically sick the
chronically ill somebody who's hypers
sensitive their nervous system is
challenged their immune systems are
challenged they're struggling they may
even be suffering and both these types
of people in the world get told to do a
coffee enema and that takes us to the
coffee enem itself because if you're
somebody who's chronically sick and you
have neurological symptoms and you get a
coffee
enema the damage the injuries the harm
could be much more serious than if
you're somebody that hey stomach of
Steel no neurological symptoms in the
moment in their life and they're getting
a coffee enema and there's a big
difference it's hurting them but they
can handle it better and then what about
dosages what kind of Eno are we talking
about what is the dosage because what
happens out there is you can take a
woman who's 5et tall 99 lb and they'll
stick the same amount of coffee in that
woman is a would a man that's
6'4 220 lb and is the woman sick with
chronic illness and neurological
problems versus the man who may not have
any neurological problems in the moment
at all and the same amount of coffee is
going into both of them once again
another huge flaw now there's a big
difference from drinking coffee to doing
a coffee enema when anything goes in the
stomach regardless if it's a can of soda
if it's something else if it's a food if
it's a glass of milk if it's a parasite
you picked up at a restaurant eating out
regardless of what it is the stomach is
built to deal with it but if it goes up
the rectum if it goes into the anus if
it goes up into the colon and it's
forced up there it's a different story
the stomach doesn't apply anymore the
stomach's ability to buffer to delegate
to protect to withhold all gone all of
it out the window it's an entirely
different thing we're talking about now
the hydrochloric acid in your colon is
much different than when it was when it
started in your stomach produced by your
stomach glands it was fired up it was
strong it had strength to it by the time
it gets to the colon and almost out of
the rectum that hydrochloric acid is
nothing to what it used used to be it
has no protective measures anymore it
has no ability to digest or break down
anything or pull apart anything it's
useless it just becomes part of your
elimination now so let's talk about what
happens when you insert coffee up your
anus so I just got back from the
drugstore let's see it says open up
here let's see undo wrapper pull tab um
connect it says unscrew unscrew I'm
going to unscrew this top
here then directions did you prepare
your coffee I have to figure this out I
do have my coffee here let me
see all right and I think I could fill
this up but I I can't do this without
some music I need a little music to
relax me a little bit let me
see all right all right
so take this pipe and um insert it it
says insert it into your
rectum okay all
right ooh ooh
ooh oh yeah all
right okay squeeze the
bag all right squeezing the
bag I'm trying
to oh ow I'm on the floor right now I
think I need some help um I just spilled
it everywhere on the floor and it came
out I think I have to reinsert it oh God
it's getting everywhere I have to get
some
towels our liver's protective buddy and
friend is its
stomach the stomach the liver's stomach
our stomach the body's stomach it is the
liver's best friend it buffers
everything and when it's not there and
it doesn't have the livers back and
something
enters up through the rectum into the
colon and into the bloodstream from
behind not in our mouth but from
underneath us behind it's an entirely
different story and our liver is not
protected anymore and our liver is very
vulnerable our livers are never meant to
take a direct hit a direct attack or a
direct punch it never gets a direct
slam everything that hits the liver has
always been buffered including alcohol
when somebody drinks a whole bunch of
alcohol which is going to affect the
liver in a bad way that alcohol sits in
the stomach and gets buffed Ed by the
stomach and time relased into the
bloodstream so the liver doesn't get the
first punch and our colon is not a
buffer it's not our stomach it has
nothing to do with our stomach as far as
how the layout works with the tissue the
thickness the design the cell
structures all of it is different the
colon is not a buffer for the liver on
any level the colon instead is a direct
passageway to the liver and that might
sound like a good thing because we're
trying to detoxify the liver with the
coffee but it's not a good thing anytime
anything enters the rectum and is
released into the colon it sets off an
adrenaline release an adrenaline
response
but it doesn't mean it's the end of the
world so if someone takes somebody's
temperature with a rectum thermometer
and it enters into the rectum some
adrenaline is going to be released your
adrenals are going to respond to
protection
method and if someone sticks the hose or
the pipe to an enema bag into the rectum
it's going to create an adrenaline
response and adrenaline is going to be
released it's not the end of the world
but it depends on what's being put into
the rectum into the body and into the
bloodstream when when it comes down to
coffee that adrenaline is responding and
those adrenals are responding to the
caffeine in the coffee so when caffeine
goes into the colon through the rectum
an Urgent Response occurs the emergency
the button is pressed the adrenals start
to react instantly
and the adrenals start to flood large
amounts of epinephrine large amounts of
adrenaline into the bloodstream
immediately and then the person's in
fight or flight so if the person's
laying on the bathroom floor and they're
doing an enema and they're sitting there
or they're laying there and they're in
their bathroom they're in fight or
flight they're in something they're not
supposed to be in they're in something
that's reserved for a real problem
an outside Invader some kind of other
emergency some kind of bad news it isn't
supposed to be happening this way but
yet their whole body is going into fight
or flight so as they're pumping innocent
coffee up their anus into their colon
into their small intestinal tract
because it can go that far and then all
that caffeine is surging through and
pushing through through the colon and
the small intestinal tract filling the
bloodstream getting to the brain the
brain's also reacting communicating with
the adrenals and now the adrenals are in
super high gear they're releasing even
more heavily heavily bombardment of
adrenaline into the bloodstream because
this is an urgent situation the body is
under great threat and then something
magical happens the person
starts to feel better because they're
high the person is feeling the effects
of an adrenaline High adrenaline is
pumping through the entire body it can
be
euphoric they're feeling something
they're feeling elevated they're feeling
energy they're feeling
strengthened they are jacked
up and this could be fine for someone
who is strong who can drink coffee no
problem they can do a coffee enema and
not get really sick from it yet and they
can sit there and feel that Euphoria
from that adrenaline high but there's
somebody that actually has a
neurological symptom or condition or
problem they're hypers sensitive maybe
they have Panic issues and anxiety
issues they're going to be feeling
something different they're going to be
high on their adrenaline but their
nerves are going to start going on fire
and
overreacting and then there's the
coffee's harshness acidic nature a
stringent nature that's entering the
bloodstream that's aggravating the colon
in the small intestinal tract that was
never buffered ever cuz it's going up
through the rectum into the
colon and that toxic coffee is now
wreaking
havoc and it's heading to the liver it's
heading through the bloodstream it
shouldn't be entering the bloodstream
without digestion and proper time
release it wasn't Time released at all
it was just shot up there pumped up
there and then it just entered where it
was going to enter and this is not a
good thing people would say well it's
detoxifying it's going to cleanse and
detoxify my liver but here's the
interesting thing the liver does not
like to be forced for
detoxification the liver detoxifies when
it wants to detoxify when the
environment is right not being forced to
purge liver has an automatic shutdown
process it's to protect the liver so it
protects you so if there's a threat of
any kind the liver shuts down its over
2,000 chemical functions goes into low
battery and
underdrive goes dormant shuts down and
it stops doing what it needs to do and
there's no coffee that's going to
cleanse it there's no anything that's
going to cleanse it in that moment the
opposite happens to what people believe
happens when they put coffee up the back
end they think that it's detoxifying the
liver but the opposite occurs where the
liver shuts down and becomes more
toxic the liver becomes abused
and it's being forced to do something it
doesn't want to do meanwhile what you
see on social is all these influencers
now they're all into self-love and self-
goodness and positive love and making
sure they take care of themselves and
not push things too hard and make sure
things are balanced and they're all
going into coffee anemas and they're
beating the crap out of their own
livers and it's the direct opposite of
what they preach and say they do so
instead of taking care of themselves
like they preach and say they do out
there all the time they're looking for
that quick High the quick fix the trendy
thing and they're being tricked into
doing something that's damaging their
liver hurting their nervous systems
forcing their liver into
shutdown thinking that they're forcing
their liver into
detoxification they're not caring for
their body's properly kind of reminds me
of cold plunging everybody's just doing
cold plunging without realizing the cold
plunging can damage the central nervous
system with somebody who's hypers
sensitive depending on the temperatures
and how long and that leads to the next
thing everybody being a superhero or
wanting to be a hero or
superhuman where they'll do the coffee
enema much longer they'll try to hold in
the coffee longer or they'll cold plunge
and they'll cold Plunge in colder water
much longer and everybody wants to be a
show off and everybody wants to say hey
look at me look what I can do and
they're injuring
themselves and as they're doing this
they're trying to sell you enema kits
enema information coffee enema
information and courses so they can make
money off of you or cold plunging
information and cold plunging equipment
so you can pay for that too meanwhile
they're selling an adrenaline High
they're selling an energy crisis in the
body they're selling an adrenal crisis a
brain crisis a heart crisis and a liver
crisis because What's Happening Here is
they're selling an adrenaline rush
because after you do a coffee enema you
are high three words you are high you're
high in caffeine and you're high on the
adrenaline and surge of the body under
attack because it was dangerous on the
body and the body saw it as a threat
unauthorized Rogue toxins coming from
coffee being forced into the bloodstream
at an accelerated
rate unlawfully into the body so once
you pass being a beginner of coffee
enimas
you start going into that let me hold
the coffee in me longer let me get more
effects so what influencers will do now
they're trying to sell the whole coffee
enema approach they're trying to show
off and tell their crowds that they tend
to hold it in longer that they tend to
squeeze it in kind of squeeze their legs
and try to keep it inside their colon
and small intestinal tract try to push
it as far up as they can to get all the
detoxification effects possible but what
they don't realize is they're putting a
drastic strain on their own Hearts
they're endangering their own heart
which could lead to some people having a
heart attack and dying from coffee
Animas and this strain on the heart
causes an adrenaline release that
surpasses a smaller adrenaline release
or even a smaller one this is a large
extreme large adrenaline release the
longer you hold the coffee in the longer
that caffeine is going into the
bloodstream Without A Time release the
longer the liver is under attack and
shut down going dormant so it's
functions aren't even working the longer
the adrenals are releasing poison which
is adrenaline cuz it's fight or flight
the longer the brain has to sit there
receiving that adrenaline and that
caffeine
all of it happening at once while the
person's holding in the coffee longer
being a
showof showing their crowd this is the
best way to do your coffee enimas
meanwhile putting their crowd Their
audience into danger and during this
process as the liver shut down the
liver's preparing itself to go into high
gear to have to accelerate its function
which means it will not detox at all
because it has to work because it has to
collect and absorb and soak up all that
lethal damaging
adrenaline that's completely being
ejected out of the adrenals which by the
way ages the person faster and faster
and faster the more coffee enemas the
quicker somebody ages because they're
they're deet eting their adrenal
strength the same adrenal strength women
need for their pregnancies for birthing
children the same adrenal strength they
need for having sex the same adrenal
strength they need to exercise daily
they're depleting it they're destroying
their adrenals for the future and
they're aging themselves faster so when
they hit their 50s or 40s they're going
to look like they're in their 60s unlike
regular enimas which are much safer and
very safe in many ways coffee enimas
have a boomerang effect what happens is
poisons that are actually leaving the
liver naturally before the enema are
gathered back up by chemical compounds
released by the liver to protect the
brain and the heart and the kidneys the
liver has to start shutting down but
then when it goes back to work it's
collecting as much poisons and toxins in
the bloodstream as possible so nothing
leaves it collects them to protect your
brain and other organs it's a boomerang
effect it does the opposite you can't
force the liver to cleanse you can only
give your liver the necessary tools but
coffee enemas are not a tool for the
liver to cleanse it's the opposite it
shocks the liver into protecting
becoming a mama bear and protecting the
brain and other
organs the true definition to coffee
enema is robbing Peter to pay Paul and
that's what's happening it's stealing
precious adrenaline so the person can
become euphoric and feel high after the
coffee enim is done and then feel like
something good happened when in the end
they got high off of a Dr adrenaline
that was tomorrow's
adrenaline tomorrow's reserves to
protect you it was adrenaline stolen for
a quick high with a bad Trend adrenaline
borrowed for a rainy day now adrenaline
borrowed used up and thrown away what
most people will notice when they do a
coffee enema is accelerated heart rate
that accelerated heart rate is the
epinephrine the adrenaline being
released into the
bloodstream but keep in mind that that
accelerated heart rate puts pressure on
guess what the heart it puts the strain
on the heart now some people who do a
coffee enema will get the accelerated
heart rate right at the beginning right
at the start and it'll push all the way
through some people it's a little
delayed The Accelerated heart rate goes
up but it's not is noticeable but after
the coffee ena's done the accelerated
heart rate goes much higher at that
point it's euphoric it feels good it
feels like an accomplishment and when
you think you're releasing all these
toxins and you're helping your liver
it's kind of twofold it's like I just
did something really good for my liver I
just helped myself and I feel great I'm
going to recommend this for somebody
else to do but keep in mind if you're
going to do a coffee anema anyway and
even listening to this you say to
yourself I'm not going to listen to this
guy I'm going to do one because the
health professionals are saying it's
good the influencers are saying it's
good I want to try it then take this
information very seriously do not hold
it in long if you're going to do one no
matter what you got your own free will
and you're going to do it do not hold
the coffee in long term
quick in and a quick out do not hold it
in there you can get really sick I've
seen people out there and I know that
you can get very very ill and even
damage your own central nervous system
doing it and consecutively if you're
doing it often or you're doing it a lot
and at the beginning things are going
okay but by the 10th time or the 50th
time it's eventually going to bite you
on the ass
and you're going to be highly reactive
to a coffee enema where your whole body
is going to shake and go into
convulsions and Tremors and the bad part
about that is even when the coffee enema
is done those shakes and those
convulsions and those Tremors could
always be there at a hairline trigger
that means they're hovering from behind
and something else can trigger them easy
meanwhile the coffee enemas were truly
the thing that really pushed over the
edge and if you're somebody that feels
you were harmed by coffee enemas or you
knew it was hurting you at the time or
you're concerned about it look into
medical medium information ask your
doctor if it's right for you what you'll
find is it doesn't promote adrenaline to
just be pouring out everywhere it
doesn't promote aging it doesn't promote
caffeine instead it doesn't give you a
high it restores the body so you don't
need stimulants at some point in your
life down the road cuz a lot of people
they're on stimulants every day they're
looking for that adrenaline high and
they do trends like cold plunging or
coffee enas where they're getting this
excessive adrenaline rush and they feel
like it's moving them forward but in the
end it's hurting them because it's
putting the body in fight or flight
because the body thinks it's in danger
the brain thinks it's in danger now for
the ones that feel that I didn't maybe
give enough information on the cold
plunging claim that it's not good for us
keep in mind when you stick yourself in
ice water the body is under threat and
the brain is under threat and the body
is looking to protect itself so it's
releasing adrenaline to keep the brain
from freezing and that becomes an
adrenaline High which makes people feel
like whoa they're super human or they
get that rush like it's incredible and
cold plunging is not for everyone I was
the first person to put that information
out there and now influencers are just
starting to talk about that too because
they know that if you push it too far
you can get hurt and they know the
medical medium information has been
talking about that for quite a while out
there so but the coffee enema same thing
if you pushed yourself too far with it
or you've been involved with it know
that there's healing you can do rest
restorative healing that doesn't require
robbing Peter to pay
Paul feels so much
better that's that's feels so much
better I feel like really
good I'm going to do another coffee anal
I got to get online and start talking
about
this all right let me just flush for a
second
so many mistakes made in the health
field experimenting on the sick without
a care in the
world every influence opportunist
jumping on
board maybe they can sell something that
never worked
before make it shiny and new and looking
above
board who cares who it
hurts what are you going to do about it
you're not my
Lord coffee enema another screw up for
the
Millennia got to keep your antenna tuned
in to the wannabe popular scene that's
Reviving every new old Trend cha-ching
cha-ching it's
obscene robbing Peter to pay Paul gives
you the energy you need for a shopping
Hall Meanwhile your health is
stalled it's all fun and games until the
roads you're on Falls your nervous
system hits a wall who do you
call let me guess it won't be the one
who influenced you to do a coffee
position just right with a long
straw always keep in mind
mind there's a way to recover from it
all heal and rebuild move forward and
not have to give in to the next round of
influencer making things look good while
showing off a booty call it's okay next
trend on its way in and
out original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher Source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion