how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about taste
everybody has a different taste
everybody likes different flavors
everybody has a different opinion to
what they like what they like to eat
what tastes good to them their taste has
a lot more control over them than they
even know and we get taught growing up
does that taste good Does that taste bad
taste this taste that get ready for a
reality check and fasten your seat belts
cuz what you're going to learn here
might leave a bad taste in your
mouth yeah not Grandma I love this
place um yeah I ordered a burrito
yeah let me just bite into
[Applause]
it these burritos aren't so bad but this
one's not as good as it usually is
Grandma what'd you get Beef
Wellington how is
it you like it no you like the buttered
noodles next to it okay that's
understandable you want me to try that
what you have a crab
cake okay I'll try
it Grandma it's
awful yeah yeah just excuse me uh ma'am
ma'am can you bring me a glass of water
I I have to rinse my mouth
out
yeah Grandpa what's wrong with the pizza
you have a face on you what's
wrong it's it's not as good as your your
favorite pizza place it it's a pizza
Grandpa
I mean it looks like it tastes
great you hear it out there all the time
I don't like this food I don't like the
taste of that food or the food tastes
better in Europe or the pizza is better
in New
York or this is too sour this is
Bland I don't like the texture it's all
about texture it's the
consistency I don't care
for I just don't like that that's too
tart that's too salty that's too sweet
oh I don't like sweets I never eat
sweets I don't like Savory I like
crunchy I need something to crunch
crunch crunch crunch I need something to
Crunch on all the time I need my crunch
fix I like to Crunch chips in my mouth I
love flavor spicy I want things really
really spicy I want things hot
I'm a foodie everybody's got their thing
they got their way to eat they got their
tastes they got their likes they sit
down and eat they stand up and eat they
eat laying down they watch TV and eat
they go to the movies and eat they eat
with people can't eat with anybody they
have to eat alone Everybody's Got A
Different Twist a different liking and a
different taste and a different flavor
profile in reality everyone wants to eat
what they want to eat eat if everybody
had their dream eats it would be eating
anything they ever wanted all the time
if somebody loves chocolate they wish
they can eat chocolate all day long if
someone loves chocolate cake they wish
they can eat chocolate cake all day long
if someone loves ice cream they wish
they can eat ice cream all day long
people have their favorite foods and
people want to eat their favorite foods
they they find comfort in their favorite
foods humans love to
indulge that's how it works on planet
Earth humans want to indulge in the
things they love it's called
addictions doesn't matter if it's food
doesn't matter if it's something else
doesn't matter if it's alcohol drugs sex
food or some other crazy thing out there
they love to indulge
and then so many of us have emotional
injuries around food whether being told
when they were a child not to eat a
certain food or being
force-fed a certain food or just being
told you have to eat this food or you
take food that was given to you to go to
school with and it's the only food you
have so you have to eat it and then
maybe you get sick of it so as you grow
up and get older you're like I'm never
going to eat that sandwich ever again
and then if somebody comes from a family
that didn't have enough money to buy
certain foods and they only had certain
foods to eat that were on the table and
that was what was there and you couldn't
do anything about it that can create an
emotional injury around food as well and
then if you're a teenager or young adult
and you want to eat differently because
you're witnessing a friend eat
differently and they're eating a little
bit healthier and you're young and you
want to eat healthier it could be seen
instantly by a family or friends or
somebody or School teachers as if you
have a bad eating disorder and then you
hear that phrase that famous Infamous
phrase the one that has Darkness behind
it at the same time wears your protein
you hear this when you're younger you
hear this when you're older you hear
this all the time it's out there where's
your protein the concern of protein
you're going to die if you don't get
enough
protein and as you try to pave your way
Forge ahead eating healthier in your
life or changing the course in the foods
you're choosing the protein phrase is in
your head so everything you do
everything you touch you're doubting how
much protein you're getting you're
concerned about the protein people are
telling you is there enough protein or
asking you is there enough protein and
that becomes something that sits inside
your Consciousness in your soul and it
doesn't leave it can stay in there
forever and alter how you think about
food and even your
tastes remember this everyone has issues
around eating there's no one out here
there's no one on planet Earth there's
no one probably in the Galaxy or even in
the universe that doesn't have an issue
around food there's never been a perfect
situation anywhere regarding food are
forebears waited in line during the
Depression for a loaf of bread and they
never forgot that they passed the
stories on and along those stories went
and even today we have wars and there's
concerns about food and there's famine
everywhere on this planet and then
there's people who just can't simply
afford food or people that are homeless
and they just don't even have a home to
even set up a meal and even when
everything is just great perfect there's
plenty of money plenty of affordability
someone can actually buy all the food
they want they can go to the best
restaurants they can eat in restaurants
every day the most highest priced
decadent restaurant food fair they can
have it it's there they still have
issues they still have issues around
Foods you see it on social you'll see
somebody with all the means in the world
they could buy what they want all the
food they want they can eat all these
decadent meals they can show it on their
social media feeds and you can see them
complaining they're complaining about
their food which food where they're
getting it what they're eating how they
feel meanwhile somebody on the other
side of the world is suffering suffering
all huddled together in some Dwelling my
bombs are going off or there's just no
way to get any food and they're really
struggling they have nothing to eat
maybe haven't eaten in weeks and then
you see it on social these people
they'll blame their fears they'll blame
their concerns they'll blame their
worries they'll blame their problems
they'll blame people they'll blame the
healthy diet they're eating they'll
blame anything and everything they'll
blame it all on their food and there are
endless variations of emotional wounds
that people have things that have
happened in their life things that have
happened in school things that have
happened because of their friends things
that have happened because of their
family experiences struggles hardships
it ends up making a massive amount of
combinations of issues that can all get
funneled into food in the end and not
only can someone have endless emotional
injuries they can also have something
physically going on different level of
toxins poisons exposures Pharmaceuticals
in their life all through their life
everything and anything from toxic heavy
metals other contamination that gets
into the brain in their body and that
can alter how they see food or even
taste food no two people are the same no
two people have the same experiences
emotionally physically there are endless
endless combinations of experiences and
this plays a role in how they taste and
seafood if you're with a friend or a
family member and you're eating the same
Pizza they're eating and both of you are
enjoying it
immensely your family member is saying
how much they love it they're eating it
it tastes so good it's a great pizza
place and you're agreeing saying it's
incredible this stuff is Bomb it is
delicious it is amazing I'm going to buy
another pizza here and both of you are
enjoying it both of you are not tasting
the same thing as you're eating it
you're connect it you know what you're
tasting you're enjoying it little sweet
little salty nice and doughy you're
tasting the sauce you taste the cheese
you can taste a little bit of Basil it's
hitting your
brain you're in love with this slice of
pizza as it's going down you're trying
to hold back you're trying not to shove
it all down at once you're trying to
take your time a little bit but you can
taste it and you know what you're
tasting to a degree you may not be an
expert at all all the flavor profiles
but you feel it and you know it and at
the same time the person that you're
eating with is experiencing the same
thing in that way they have a connection
they taste a little bit of the basil
they taste the sauce they taste the
sweetness of the sauce they taste the
cheese they like their crust they're
enjoying it they love it but what you're
tasting is not what they're tasting both
of you are tasting two different things
our brains control our experience they
control the flavor our tongues those are
just
tools our tongues as a tool could get
dirty and when they get dirty like if we
have a stick of gum or we smoke a
cigarette it can alter the taste buds
but still it's all deriving from our
brain yes we can saturate our tool which
is our tongue we can contaminate it it
can get dirty with other things and
toxins cigarette smoke different
artificial flavorings it can alter it as
far as as a tool but that's as far as it
goes the brain is where it's all
happening with flavor contamination
Place aside the controls and the
experience come from the brain central
nervous system signals travel back and
forth between the cranial nerves so if
there's any kind of interference in the
brain
like toxic heavy metals something toxic
inside the brain then it can alter how
we perceive flavors inside our mouth
because the cranial nerves either become
poisoned or neurons sending messages to
these nerves become poisoned so if the
brain has any kind of solvents MSG toxic
heavy metals petrochemicals pesticides
herbicides other toxic chemicals or
viral neurotoxins from hsv1 or any virus
stored up in brain tissue then that can
affect whether someone likes or dislikes
certain foods and drink and if someone
has an elevated amount of mercury inside
their brain and it's affecting their
cranial nerves in any way possible it
can change how cilantro tastes it can
make it so cilantro is not pleasing
doesn't have a good flavor doesn't taste
good doesn't feel feel good on the
pallet until the Mercury is going away
so as the Mercury is decreasing and the
metals are leaving the brain cilantro
starts to become pleasing agreeable this
can change and alter depending on where
the Mercury is but there are thousands
and thousands of testimonials from
people who are doing the medical medium
heavy metal detox and as they're doing
it they start out hating cilantro or
they always did hate cilantro and as
they go along and they're getting rid of
the Mercury the toxic heavy metals
what's happening is they all of a sudden
become in love with cilantro it's
pleasing it's agreeable they like it and
it becomes part of their life as if they
should have never had it out of their
diet to begin with they love it now
contaminants do other things inside
people's brains not just alter the
fever but Al alter things like
consistency issues like someone will be
like I don't like avocado cuz I don't
like the texture I don't like anything
mushy I can't do it I only like crunchy
things or I like to sink my teeth in
something and if I can't sink my teeth
into it then I'm not going to like it
these are messages coming from the brain
and a lot of those messages can be
derived from the toxic heavy metals
inside the brain rerouting electrical
impulses messing with
neurotransmitters and a combination of
emotional injuries throughout life
whether from childhood or adulthood but
the combination of emotional issues
emotional injuries combination of that
plus the toxic heavy metals and other
contaminants all put together make it so
there are millions and millions and
billions of combinations of how people
see food feel food taste food and enjoy
food back 2,000 years ago if you were an
emperor and you were given by your
medicine man a Mercury Elixir cuz that's
what happened back then to treat any
kind of issues and that mercury Elixir
altered your taste where you can taste
food differently and it's not the same
and your Chef who made you the same meal
that you like every day gives you that
same meal and you tasted it and it was
awful and tasted like poison you would
then then chop off that Chef's head
that's how serious people are about food
going all the way back dead serious here
on planet Earth taste can be the
ultimate controller it can determine how
you're going to heal what you're going
to do for yourself there are people in
the world that could have healed if they
can get past their
taste people naturally do not like leafy
greens people naturally do not like a
bitter leafy green people don't like
lettuce they have to have the lettuce
drowned out by a dressing or cheese or
eggs or some sort of oil vinegar lots of
salt some sugar dressings that aren't
good for them people can't just eat a
leafy green on its own it's not easy
it's not desirable a piece of kale a
collared green most people have trouble
just eating a piece of fruit an apple a
berry sure they'll eat it if you give it
to them it's in their hand they'll eat
it they'll chew it but in the end they
don't want to sit there and eat apples
all day and they don't want to sit there
and eat raspberries all day they don't
want to sit there and eat melons all day
they don't want to eat really any fruit
and if they eat a piece of fruit they
want to offset it pretty shortly after
with something like chicken salad or
something else a hamburger or something
else it's not something people really
want to do it's eat a leafy green or eat
a piece of fruit a plum an apple a
cherry a berry for example if somebody
drinks a smoothie they want milk in that
smoothie they want peanut butter in that
smoothie they want kefir and that
smoothie yogurt they want something in
there something that kind of brings the
temperature down brings their worries
down the worry of tasting something like
an astringent fruit or a bitter green
that's the worry it becomes a smoothie
where it's just a protein based smoothie
with something in there like milk and
dairy and yogurt and nut Butters and
oils and they want to wash down the
medicine away with all of that fat and
all of that Dairy and then when you say
hey how about a sweet potato if you had
one of those and they would say I don't
like the texture I hate yams I can't eat
a sweet potato can I put something on it
can I eat it with something or how about
a potato a plain potato I can't eat a
potato plain I need to have sour cream
on it some cheese some other things on
there some yogurt or something hey how
about a avocado I'm like I don't like
the mushy texture I don't like the
consistency I can't stand guacamole I've
heard so many different things from so
many different people and it gets in
their way of healing and I call it the
taste demon and one of the reasons why I
call it the taste demon is because of
the trickery that goes on with it you
tell somebody why don't you try some
avocado they say it's too mushy they
don't like the texture but then later on
at night they're eating an ice cream in
front of the TV someone will say they
like crunch they like crunchy things
they like chips and they can't get off
their chips they need it it's like their
therapy and I'll say why don't we do
some dehydrated apple chips they're
crunchy they're delicious and they'll
say no I'll say to somebody are you
eating that salad every day that I was
tell telling you about are you making
that salad they'll say yes I'm having my
salad every single day and I still don't
feel good aw how come and I'll sit there
and I'll scratch my head and then s so
will say because their salad has changed
it's got pieces of ham in there pieces
of egg in there and I'll ask them what
happened to your salad what's in there
and they'll be like well I just feel
like I need more protein so I'm just
switching the chickpeas instead of the
garbanza beans she told me about I'm now
putting ham in there and um and I have
croutons in there too and I'll be like
well the croutons are the gluten
remember the gluten was bothering you
and be like yeah I can't help it I can't
eat the salad any other way The Taste
demon I'll say to someone you can have
your celery juice in the morning you can
have your hmds in the morning morning
you can have some steamed potatoes for
lunch if you really want or a later
lunch in the afternoon and they'll say
oh no I can't eat that much in the
morning I can't eat anything in the
morning ever I need to be not eating it
doesn't make me feel good I can't eat
like that say okay okay I respect that
let's figure something else out a week
later I'm just not doing good I'm not
feeling good I'll be like what you been
doing lately well I've been just eating
a lot of stuff like in in the morning
and early afternoon I'm like what are
you eating well I had pizza out for
lunch with a friend in the morning I had
like four coffees and decided to eat a
Danish I thought you didn't eat though I
thought you weren't eating in the
morning so you're not going to do the
celery juice or the hmds but 3 days
later you're going to eat a pizza at
noon and you're going to eat a whole
bunch of danishes and so forth this is
the workings of The Taste demon and then
I'm talking to somebody and they're like
has to be grass-fed beef aw that's what
I only eat it's only grass-fed beef aw
and free range pasture raised chickens
it's the only thing I eat it's those
things right there week later you talk
to him and you're like okay give me the
whole rundown what you've been eating
every day like well been eating my usual
doing pretty good and then they say well
went to a restaurant with a friend like
what' you order chicken was it free
range is it pasturised uh I don't really
know I I actually didn't ask you know
we're just out and whatever The Taste
demon could go on and on forever so many
different variables variations so many
different Antics and so much trickery
and that's how the taste demon works and
this can get in the way of people
heading to the Finish Line to heal
people who just can't get past it the
taste demon takes over and they gobble
down that chocolate bar they gobble down
that chocolate cake they drink their
coffee every single day they eat
something that isn't helping them they
do something that's not helping them in
health they take something that's not
helping them and that same taste demon
will even turn that person against
somebody because they want to protect
their food
or their
addictions or their
indulgences they want to protect it till
the cows come home and they'll blame
somebody else or something else is
causing their problems and causing their
sickness and causing their poor health
and their poor mental health it's the
taste
demon I eat here all the time this place
is amazing yeah I got my chicken salad
coming waiter is it it's on the way I've
been waiting all right here here it is
the best chicken salad I've ever had
this is amazing thank you thank you
great all right get my napkin ready
here yeah what is this oh this isn't my
chicken salad uh waiter waiter I come
here every day this is not the chicken
salad that I eat every day what do you
mean calm down I I'm telling you
whatever this is it isn't it I I need to
talk to the chef please get the chef out
here immediately I'm a customer here
okay Chef what do you think what are you
thinking what are you saying it it's the
same thing same ingredients I don't
believe you it can't be this tastes
terrible it tastes God awful what does
it taste like um I don't know like it
just I I don't know maybe it's bland I
can't tell I'm not sure what I'm tasting
I just know that this isn't it it's the
same I'm walking out of here I'm not
paying for this I'm never eating here
again
goodbye that tastes good as it should
I'm
addicted it doesn't taste bad I think my
taste buds have been had don't make my
Foods
restrictive what do you think how's it
vibe in your mouth mouth watering or
does it go South I point my Fork at you
I'm thrilled at how good this meal is
I'm made for you wait why do you look so
blue what's gotten into you you're
pointing your butter knife at me you're
disappointed because the meal is too
soggy and
overdone just because you can't cut the
kiche and the knife is bending you're
done what Have We Become overrun by our
taste buds and their elected taste fun
doesn't matter if the meal was
Homespun a bad meal has been known in
history to make a person take out a gun
in olden times if the king queen Emperor
had a bad meal the chef would not just
be fired the chef would be burned at the
stake by fire the next one hired a year
later would also expire and around and
around it would go food becomes death
defying and treacherous but the same
time because the taste demons already
exist in everyone's mind we protect our
ways of eating and almost never give up
our favorite feedings until one day
we're too sick enough to learn how to
refeed ourselves so our bodies reverse
the hands of
time original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from Medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more ing stories of real people
not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion