how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about recovery
Faith
healing rising out of the ashes so many
people have been there before and they
know it well why because they lived it
or should I also say lived through it
what's it one more time what's it it's
when you thought all was lost and you're
on your hands and knees praying to God
to anyone that will listen and then it
happens a miracle
happens you find a path a healing path
after all this time you stuck to your
guns
and then the hand of shimmering light
grabs your hand and you rose out of your
suffering you have risen out of the
ashes yeah I thought I told you yeah I'm
so
tired yeah I can't even function and my
arms feel like
sandbags yeah the doctor's coming in
yeah okay okay just
just
yep so
doc doctor hi so did you look at my test
results um why am I so deathly
tired I'm
lazy
huh what do you mean I'm
lazy my tests look good everything's
fine I'm just like e he uh um wait no
wait hold on hold on wait no I only I
only watch TV because I can't do
anything else so that's why I'm on the
couch watching TV or in my bed yeah I
can't even function or
move no it's not because I'm
lazy this for the 100th time I've
already been through this already I'm
really that tired I I can't even keep my
eyes open but I can't sleep when they're
shut it's so
bad unless You' been there really really
been there been really down really sick
will you ever really know will you ever
really see what it's like the feeling of
what do I do how do I get out of this
where do I go from
here how am I going to push
through and how am I going to make it
like another day and get past this or
how how am I going to make it another
hour or another minute even I've heard
it before thousands of times throughout
the years I have tried everything
researched everything been to every heal
and every Health Pro had every test I've
been exhausted I've exhausted everything
money energy time friends family and I
have nowhere else to go nowhere else to
look for or look to and then those
powerful
words you know them the words that are
almost like Supernatural
your body loves you
unconditionally your body will never
turn against you your body is working
hard for you every day it's fighting for
you not fighting against you you can
heal your immune system is not attacking
your organs and
glands it's not your fault that you are
sick it's not your fault you're not a
bad person you're not a terrible person
you didn't do anything wrong you're not
faulty you're not sick because you want
to be sick you don't have a fear of
healing you're not lazy you're not
trying to trick anyone you're not trying
to trick everyone you're not pretending
to be sick you're not doing this on
purpose and you're not doing it to try
to get attention you're not a weak
person you're the opposite you're the
opposite of a weak person you are truly
a strong person you have a strong light
inside of you one that can never be
taken away from you you Harbor a life
force you have a soul it is more
powerful than you know know and no one
can ever take that power away from you
not even
sickness there weren't answers out there
for chronic illness all these decades
before and because there weren't any
answers one of the cornerstones people
were told was people had a fear of
healing they were sick because they did
not want to heal because they were
afraid let's face it there is no one I
repeat no one who is sick physically
emotionally or mentally that doesn't
heal because they are afraid to get
better that they're scared to
heal they could be afraid of something
else they could be nervous or scared
about the path the journey what it may
entail and what it may be about the
process or how they may be feeling
through the time they are healing but
there is no world where they are afraid
to heal and that's why they are sick or
chronically ill because they're scared
there's no place for that people want to
heal they want to feel good or at least
just good enough any equality of life is
sacred and people know this how many
people who got sick were told that they
were lazy that their fatigue wasn't real
they were just struggling with a lack of
motivation they had no passion for life
their fatigue and tiredness was a lack
of
Interest a lack of caring and maybe just
depression Meanwhile your legs they felt
like sandbags and your arms they felt
like lead and your body felt so heavy
even lifeless like gravity was pulling
you down it was not just you being lazy
and just plain tired or
unmotivated your fatigue was real and is
real and you are a warrior to push
through each and every day no one
realizes that because you are so strong
they just don't realize it and they take
for granted what you're going through
and there are real reasons why you are
so sick you're not a weak person instead
you are a strong person no matter what
you're ailing with when we get sick here
on planet Earth we default to thinking
we are a bad person it can automatically
happen because we feel we aren't as
useful sometimes many people feel they
are in the way they lost their purpose
we are a burden and something is wrong
with our body so we start believing that
we are a bad person but this is so far
from the truth just because we get sick
isn't any reason to believe that you or
anyone are a bad
person when people get sick they've
heard this before at some point on their
Journey your body has turned against you
that's the words that have rolled off of
many tongues an answer that brings
people no relief it brings people into a
darker Place how is it ever possible to
really heal believing that your body has
betrayed you and won't let you heal and
instead is making the opposite happen
your body is making you sick the
powerful truth is your body will never
turn against you instead it's working
for you every day and it wants to
thrive maybe you know somebody maybe
you've been through it yourself people
who care for others that are really sick
can understand pain and suffering too
they see it and they can realize it they
watch the person suffer and struggle
they watch it and they know how hard it
must really be on their friend their
loved one their family member they may
not be sick themselves or struggling or
struggling is bad but they witness it
they see it there's something you need
to know everyone has the god-given right
to heal healing is etched and carved
deep within their soul and so many have
access their healing powers they just
need to learn
information that changed everything for
them it's possible for all and never
doubt your healing strength and healing
wisdom because all can heal and never
forget you deserve to heal so many
people believe they don't deserve to
heal and that they never deserved to
heal ever but that's not true they do
deserve to heal you deserve to heal and
live free of sickness you did not miss
out on your chance because it's more
than just a chance chance comes and goes
in life you never lost your chance
though healing is always there and
awaits
you it's a roller coaster ride you go up
and around you go high and then down
getting better seems possible when your
hopes are up when your hopes are down
It seems
impossible feels like your time is up
but it's not not true you have time no
one can take that from you God is good
God can be kind there is a way to heal
just like you knew all along how it
should be you feel that spark your
healing isn't stuck in park it's in
drive there is a button somewhere in you
that will get you to a place to thrive
there's a switch in you that is turned
on and you will stay alive you won't
fail you won't fall grab on to the light
rail the Angels sent for you so your
healing doesn't stall you hear that it's
a call from above
the angel of Joy will ignite your core
and you will laugh first time in years
laughter because you know nothing is
going to stop you from rising out of the
ashes no evil no darkness no fear no
cold Frost it's your time to heal
negativity and the demons from hell can
get lost you're not stupid you've been
around before you've been around the
block you know the drill just need to
clean up a toxic spill you're not a pill
your soul knows better your immune
system will make the proper kill against
the bugs body thugs never give up your
time is now your time has come we can
rise out of the ashes together batten
down the hatches feel it
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
bot research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and enter ing
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion