how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about adrenals we
live in a world where we don't realize
it but we get our kicks from adrenaline
our adrenaline we get high and for many
it's how we get by but who pays the
price is it your adrenals or you or both
or even everyone around you adrenaline
is liquid gold precious resource but are
we taught to throw it away yes we are
and certainly not taught to preserve it
hang on to your britches in this episode
you're going to be looking at things a
lot different and we will try to keep
the excitement to a minimum to keep a
nice easy adrenaline
release woo that was crazy C you see
that guy are you ready to do it I'm
bracing myself man I heard this was the
most crazy water slide yeah some girl
she was thrown off the side and died a
few years ago yeah you know the sick
part about it was everyone was so pumped
up that they cheered her on they thought
she did it on purpose but then people
started to realize there was no water
down there and she landed on cement all
right it's your turn all right get ready
I think we're 700 ft up up up on this
hill my heart is racing it really is oh
whoa do you ever hear that old saying
whatever floats your boat someone likes
to do something they're into something
somebody says to them I don't know
whatever floats your boat man whatever
your boat what it really means is and
what it really boils down to is where
and how do you get your adrenaline High
your adrenaline fix where does it come
from what turns you on what are you into
people don't realize it but they have
adrenaline addictions and we take our
adrenals for granted every day our
adrenals they do so so much for us and
in return we don't do a lot for them
most people don't do anything for their
adrenals that's right nothing NADA we're
not talking about hey we respect our
adrenals and that's what we're taught
every day we're taught the opposite
we're taught to destroy them in many
situations we're taught to annihilate
them but by default we sometimes look
out for our adrenals but we don't
realize it meditation yoga reading a
book watching something cing sitting
down to eat sitting in nature sleeping
but the good we do can easily get
cancelled by the bad get offset by The
Bad Coffee green tea chocolate cold
plunging hot yoga high fat foods extreme
exercising recreational drugs
psychedelics alcohol intense triggering
movies we will get into some of these
later do you like getting up in the
morning do you like taking a shower
brushing your teeth do you like brushing
your hair do you like walking to the
kitchen opening up the refrigerator do
you like checking the mail do you like
hopping on your computer
do you like using your phone do you like
hopping in your car do you like driving
all that is done because of adrenaline
without it you can't do it what else do
you like to do do you like to exercise
do you like hopping on the treadmill
hopping on your bicycle do you like
doing some stretches do you like doing
some yoga do you like having sex do you
like doing anything else do you like
getting on the phone do you like talking
to friends do you like going down to the
Park all of that is adrenaline and it
can't be done without adrenaline and we
don't tell ourselves when we're doing
anything this is because of adrenaline
without my adrenals I don't know what I
would do wait I'm opening up my car door
I'm getting in I'm starting my car
that's because of
adrenaline wow it's got a dawn on me
okay let's keep on going I got to stop
here and do an appointment oh I'm
getting a massage today I can't do that
without adrenaline only adrenaline
allows you to actually do that I got to
talk to my therapist today I got to sit
down at her office talk for about an
hour I got to just unload talk about my
hardships I got to just let out some
tears and it can only happen because of
adrenaline every basic normal task every
single
chore any
project anything work rated play related
life related is adrenaline based and our
adrenals help us battle and handle
stress any kind of bad news any kind of
stress put on us it takes adrenaline to
help defend us from that stress to help
protect this so when you get given bad
news or you're up against a challenge
that adrenaline being released is
helping you power through it's there to
help you make quick decisions what to do
where to go and there's different levels
of adrenaline running through your
system and being released if you're
under a little bit of stress that's one
level adrenaline's being released it's
helping you to move quick it's helping
you to think fast and then there might
be something else more challenging in
that moment more adrenaline's being
released and that's helping you to get
on the move to get out of the way to do
something and then there's adrenaline
for everyday projects and jobs chores
things that you're doing so you can
think about what you're doing stay
focused get things done and then there's
fight or flight it's either run or fight
something happens there's a fire you
need to hustle you need to think fast
it's an emergency adrenaline's being
released into your bloodstream it's
flooding your central nervous system do
I jump out of this window or do I take
the staircase how do I get out of here
and then you go to the beach you're in
the ocean you're in the water playing in
the waves and then you get stung by a
jellyfish you feel an overwhelming
burning stinging pain on your leg you
don't know what it is at first and then
you realize it's jellyfish and you start
yelling and frantically trying to swim
out of the ocean it takes a large amount
of adrenaline to service Us in that
moment to help bolster us so we can move
and we can think and we can react and we
can feel and a lot of us have a storage
bin of adrenaline just for this occasion
just in case something happens a fight
ORF flight moment or a moment when we
have to become
superhuman like if somebody is changing
their Tire on the side of the road and a
car falls on them you got to be there
and that superhuman strength kicks in
that adrenaline you hear them screaming
while the car is on their torso and then
you go and you lift up the car so they
can slide out so let's gain some
perspective here if that happens a car
falls on someone and the person that's
going to rescue them is a guy who's
about 6'4 has a lot of muscle or just a
guy that's really strong has a lot of
muscle he's got to have a lot of
adrenaline storage he has to have strong
reserves adrenaline reserves and there's
a good chance he can lift up the car or
the back of a small car just enough for
somebody to be able to get out but what
if it's a strong muscly guy he looks
good he's got a lot of muscle and he's
there and he tries to lift the car and
he has weak adrenals weak adrenaline
reserves it's just not there he just
doesn't have it in him and he's trying
to lift a car he's not going to be able
to do the job that needs to be done it's
that lack of adrenaline that lack of
adrenal strength that can get you in
trouble so if a crisis comes and you're
needed it's that lack of adrenal
strength that can get in the way and
make it so that you don't perform like
say somebody else can perform if their
adrenals are strong I've seen this
happen with bodybuilders they got a
routine they're doing it for years
they're building a lot of muscle they
know what kind of weight they can lift
they know what kind of ground they can
move and then they get severe adrenal
fatigue they get adrenal issues their
adrenals are wasted and then they can't
do the workouts they used to do they're
dragging they're suffering they're
struggling they're going to the doctors
they don't know what it is they don't
know if it's fatigue chronic fatigue
they don't know if it's depression or
anxiety and the guy is struggling and
slowly they start losing muscle they
can't do what they used to do adrenal
issues are getting in the way and it
takes a little time for them to lose the
muscle because at first they have the
muscle it's there but they just don't
have that inner strength because they
have adrenal issues and then over time
if they can't keep the muscle on by
using them enough to the capacity of
what they were doing before and that
adrenal issue gets in the way they start
to slowly waste away wasting muscle away
it's partly why if you've ever heard
this before that sometimes a skinny
Scrappy person tends to be able to do a
lot lift a lot it's like that group of
firefighters there's one that's skinny
and lanky but the guy can lift a heavy
burning log or that construction crew
where you got a skinny lanky guy he's
got muscle he's toned the guy looks good
he can lift a lot of bricks he's known
for it and then there's a couple of guys
on that same crew one is really built
he's always wondering how that skinny
lanky guy that Scrappy guy can lift all
those bricks when he can't really lift
them as much or as good a reason
adrenaline plays a role in this and then
you ask the skinny Scrappy guy how do
you do it and the guy would be like I
just have a strong back but really it's
more than that it's adrenal reserves
adrenaline strength and we need
adrenaline reserves for that special
moment like giving birth that's when
fight ORF flight happens for a woman
having a baby the baby has to come out
the body knows this the central nervous
system knows this it's time the
reproductive system knows this and
adrenaline is needed when the water
breaks people around a woman will say
stay calm stay calm everybody stay calm
let's get in the car let's get moving
let's get going to the hospital or if
it's a birth at home okay let's get
things ready because everybody's
freaking out adrenaline is Flowing the
woman's adrenal strength means
everything adrenaline reserves and
adrenal strength can determine if it's
going to be an easy birth or a very
arduous labor when the woman pushes with
all her might
pushes really hard with everything she
has every bit of inner strength every
cell in her body every single piece of
her existence is in into that one big
huge push and then that other big huge
push to get the baby to move it's
adrenaline behind it adrenaline reserves
can determine if it's going to be a
strong push a very productive push or a
weak push an unproductive push a lot of
emergency C-sections are because of weak
adrenals if the labor really long it's
not the woman that's giving up or it's
not her real physical muscles or
physical body just giving up it's the
lack of adrenaline it's the adrenals
giving up during that child birth which
could lead to an emergency C-section
there are many different reasons why
women can have complicated childbirth
situations but one of the most common is
weak adrenals but women aren't being
taught to protect their adrenals
strengthen their adrenals and preserve
their adrenals and prepare them prepare
them for childbirth but it's the
opposite women are taught to actually
destroy their adrenal glands caffeine
chocolate coffee tea intermittent
fasting high fat diets cold plunging
restricting calories low sugar diets low
carb diets long-term water fasting
long-term juice fasting extreme
exercising Hot Yoga recreational drugs
psychedelics drinking alcohol laying in
the hot sun for hours and hours watching
intense triggering movies and the list
goes on and it's not about judging
anybody that's not it at all people can
do what they want they can do what they
like to do remember it's whatever floats
your boat because one day if you hit the
wall if something happens it's good to
know you can do something about it it's
good to have the knowledge in case
there's something that you're doing that
could be backed off a bit or something
you could do that could really help you
through it to realize hey my adrenals
might be wasted here for example a lot a
lot of people with adrenal fatigue right
now are doing cold plunging and what's
happening is they're feeling like woo
something was refreshed in them
something happened and they feel good
for the moment when they come out but
what's happening is they're on an
adrenaline High what this means is when
you dipping into that cold Icy water
your body started to fight for its life
because of the temperature dropping and
your adrenals released a lot of
adrenaline because it was fight or
flight your adrenals are releasing that
adrenaline to keep your temperature up
your core temperature up because you're
making your core temperature colder what
do you think happened when the Titanic
was going down and everybody was
floating around in that icy cold water
they were freezing to death within
minutes now of course they didn't have
the option to get out of the water and
say hey our cold plunge is done but a
lot of people now are in competitions
and they're trying to stay in there as
long as they can and they're putting
their bodies into severe crisis which
means they're putting their adrenals
into severe crisis is it can become an
addiction you're getting an adrenaline
High the irony nobody knows they're
getting an adrenaline High when they're
doing cold plunging they have no idea
that that's actually what's happening
but a year down the road or two years
down the road when your adrenals decide
to say see you and you're hitting the
wall and you don't know why you can't
even take 10 steps you're going to be
like what happened what was it you're
never going to blame the Cal plunging
ever but you'll blame that piece of
spinach you ate one day and if you're a
woman and you had a really difficult
childbirth really incredibly difficult
childbirth and you don't know why and
you don't know why you're so exhausted
afterwards where for months you just
can't get back to where you were you
won't blame it on all the cold plunging
you were taught to do for the last
couple years you'll blame it on
something entirely different one thing
that chips away at our adrenal glands
over time is high fat diets the more fat
we eat the more overt fat we eat the
more adrenaline is released the more
fats we gobble down and eat in our meals
the more adrenaline's getting into our
bloodstream and released this is why
when someone goes lowfat for a little
while a healthy lowfat regimen of some
kind they start rebuilding their
adrenals they start getting stronger
over time they start getting replenished
and then they go and eat a lot of fat
like whatever diet they choose whether
it's animal protein or it's plant-based
fat and they end up gobbling down a lot
of fat and they get this euphoric
feeling like whoa like a rush they feel
this energy they feel this Surge and
what they don't realize is they just
felt their adrenal glands go explode of
adrenaline to try to help save them from
the amount of fat that's floating in
their bloodstream so they don't have a
heart attack or interrupt the brain
chemistry at all they're feeling that
strength that Euphoria they're feeling
that adrenaline surge because their
adrenals over time restored it restored
and then now the adrenaline's being
released a lot of it the reason why
adrenaline's released into the
bloodstream when you're on a high fat
diet or eating High fats all the time
it's to thin out the blood it's to
protect the heart and before that person
did a lowfat healthy regimen of some
kind there were dog in it they didn't
feel good they felt sick all the time
they felt weak they had low energy they
were struggling with some kind of
condition and then they were slowly
rebuilding back their adrenal glands
getting them stronger so then when they
finally did that pizza whether it was a
vegan pizza or some other kind of pizza
that was loaded with just fat all in and
on top of it they were like wow I can't
believe how good I feel eating these
three slices of pizza I feel good I feel
strong I feel euphoric what am I doing I
don't have to eat that lowfat anymore I
don't have to do this or that or try to
be healthy I could just go back to this
I was restricted I guess now I can eat
what I want and they take it for granted
they don't know they just restored their
adrenal glands all those weeks or all
those months and then over time they'll
decline their adrenals will decline
again they'll start losing adrenaline
reserves their adrenals will start
losing strength they'll just be eating
anything they want for quite some time
and then when they're hitting the wall
are starting to drag again whether it's
2 years later one year later 3 years
later they're going to be like oh no I
have to do something for myself and they
won't even realize what restored their
adrenals to begin with excessive
high-fat diets whether it's plant-based
high-fat diets animal protein high-fat
diets will eventually weaken the adrenal
glands so many people walk around with
undiagnosed adrenal problems and
undiagnosed adrenal fatigue and their
symptoms getting shakes and Tremors or
their symptoms of feeling very weak at
different times of day or brain fog will
be blamed on blood sugar problems
meanwhile if somebody has blood sugar
problems their hypoglycemic hypoglycemic
or any kind of diabetes situation
pre-diabetic and they have adrenal
fatigue both those problems can meld
together causing a lot of confusion and
causing a bigger problem if somebody's
pre-diabetic or they got blood sugar
issues or they're hypoglycemic it's
critical to keep strong a adrenals it's
critical to make sure they restore and
replenish their adrenals and protect
them because if they don't protect their
adrenals and they don't keep them safe
and strong and build up that adrenaline
Reserve then they're going to be
confused all the time they're going to
not know what's causing what and what is
this and what is that they just won't
know the brain and body needs blood
sugar glucose that's how we function we
run on sugar without it the brain starts
to die and we can't can't do anything we
can't function we can't live sugar is
what makes the world go around but if we
lose our sugar or glucose if we go
glucose deficient in the bloodstream
guess what takes over
adrenaline people who are intermittent
fasting or on low low carb diets they're
not getting enough sugar enough glucose
to their brain to their body what do
they do they exist on caffeine they rely
on caffeine in all kinds of different
forms to get them through the day while
they're not eating while they're not
getting enough glucose to survive on so
what they're doing is they are taking
from Peter to pay Paul they are actually
using their own adrenaline to compensate
for the lack of sugar the lack of
glucose they're stealing adrenaline from
their adrenals that should have never
been released that should stay in those
adrenals to keep those adrenals strong
they're stealing that adrenaline to
actually work with whatever thing
they're doing that means not eating
enough food enough glucose to get by
instead they're relying on caffeine to
shoot those adrenals to blow out that
adrenaline so they can function do their
appointments and live their life and why
are they low carb or why are they
intermittent fasting because the
high-fat diet didn't work for them to
begin with so they're cutting their
high-fat diet that never worked they're
cutting it in half or cutting it down to
just a quarter they're starving
themselves for most of the day and still
doing their high-fat diet but only doing
it partially versus doing it every day
all day and they're relying on the
caffeine to get them by to do it and
guess who pays the price your adrenals
their adrenals everybody's adrenals our
adrenals need a lot of things to
preserve to restore to replenish a
couple of things that are adrenals need
is glucose sodium and potassium
electrolyte and glucose if you don't
have the glucose and electrolytes in
your bloodstream floating around in your
brain then your adrenals are going to
know about it and they're going to
release adrenaline to compensate and the
more adrenaline released the more
problems we get down the road so we're
not freed just because we're doing
intermittent fasting for years or we're
doing cold plunging for years and we're
going to just be healthy great have
longevity and live forever instead we're
going to have long-term a adrenal and
adrenaline damage that means adrenaline
going into the brain and burning out
neurotransmitter chemicals over time so
all the different adrenaline addictions
many of them we've already mentioned in
this episode over time push the adrenals
over the edge releasing lots of
adrenaline and that adrenaline floating
through the body and the Brain burning
out neurotransmitter chemicals burning
out neurons weakening the nerve sheath
of all the central nervous system and
creating a problem with cranial nerves
and the Vegas nerves upping anxiety as
the years go by creating issues all
throughout the body including the liver
and even the stomach glands inside the
stomach that creates your gastric acid
your hydrochloric acid adrenaline
addictions weaken the central nervous
system bringing people to new types of
symptoms in their lives new confusion
they get lost they don't know why
they're sick they don't know what's
wrong and
long-term adrenaline wastage was behind
a part of it so let's talk a little bit
about restoring your adrenals sleep does
help to restore adrenals but a lot of
people that are under stress they're
under termoil they're under challenges
can't sleep good so it's kind of not
fair to them sleeping would help their
adrenals would help them fend off what
they're up against help protect them but
they can't sleep because of the stress
and challenges so one thing that can
help restore adrenals is resting doesn't
mean you're sleeping it could just mean
you're resting you're laying there with
your eyes closed even if it's for 10
minutes every hour or 10 minutes in the
afternoon or 15 minutes at the end of
the day or midm morning just laying
there resting the nerves also rests the
adrenals and helps to restore them
another way to help restore the adrenals
is lowering your overt fats so if you're
an animal protein person find a way to
lower some of your fats it could be
lowering animal protein a little bit or
lowering plant fats that you're also
eating at the same time lowering your
nuts and seeds lowering your oils
lowering your animal protein bringing
your fat down same thing if you're
plant-based or vegan lowering your oils
your plant-based oils lowering your nuts
and seeds lowering your avoc
bringing it down a little bit Bringing
Down the overt fats helps to restore the
adrenal glands another way to actually
restore your adrenals is having adrenal
snacks medical medium adrenal snacks
they have a balance of glucose sodium
and pottassium those three things are
critical to protect your adrenals and
help restore them and to balance your
blood sugar a lot of people their blood
sugar drops really quickly and then
their adrenaline sets off and then boom
they're having all this adrenaline
floating through the bloodstream instead
of having glucose sodium and pottassium
floating in their
bloodstream another powerful tool that
helps restore adrenal glands is celery
juice every single day having celery
juice try to have it on an empty stomach
try to have it a half an hour away from
food having celery juice every single
morning on an empty stomach is really
helpful to help restore adrenal glands
another powerful way way to protect your
adrenal glands and help replenish and
restore them is not going long without
eating making sure that you're having
snacks in between your meals or having
snacks all day long eating every hour
and a half to 2 hours will protect your
adrenals so they're not releasing
unnecessary wastage of adrenaline into
your bloodstream and if somebody can't
snack and they have a lot of digestive
stress or some kind of digestive problem
they could try a little bit of coconut
water or maybe some apple cucumber
celery juice they can have that in
between meals some other helpful tools
for the adrenals are licorice root
ashwaganda lemon balm and b12 the B12
should be a dooil cobalamin and methyl
cobalamin for more information check out
medical medium.com check out the medical
medium book series there's a tremendous
amount of adrenaline and adrenal
information in the medical medium book
series that can really help somebody
navigate and move
forward I love paddle boarding it's like
so relaxing what do you think you like
it too I know I know oh my God it's like
smell the air the Ocean
Air this is like rejuvenating my
soul yeah what is
that that's a
dolphin yeah that's a dolphin fin you
see how how the fin is curved in a wait
a minute that's not a dolphin fin oh my
God you nope two sharks I see two sharks
stay calm stay calm take a deep breath
take a deep breath okay um you know what
we do in yoga class right just okay just
stay still Yep they're going around the
paddle boards oh oh all right okay that
one the fin hit the paddle board no no
what look out okay all right we got to
we got to figure this
out
okay great job honey now we have to
restore your adrenals I'm going to get
the medical medium book get some adrenal
snacks
going this is wonderful twins
too it's not fair never was never will
be the world isn't kind to our adrenals
the world
may have been kind but evil doesn't make
life easy down here there are endless
obstacles in the way so that people live
in fear living free and safe and happy
is
obtainable but the roller coaster rides
make it so that peace here on Earth
isn't always
sustainable there's always a worry and
always a concern
but that's okay we have our adrenals to
lean on every day they are a
Powerhouse no one can doubt the role
they play they're there for when we see
a mouse in the middle of the night our
heart skips a beat we hear a noise and
our mind races as our adrenals stop
snoring and awaken to help us figure out
it was just a Creek in a board and the
mouse ran across the floor it's never
too late to bring our little adrenals
back to the Starting Gate we can help
them come back no matter what people
taught us that attack them to no end we
always have a chance and a choice to
revive a precious resource
[Music]
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for Medical
Science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research while lobbyists
internal Kickbacks persuaded belief
systems private panels of influencers
health field payoffs trendy traps or
gathered bits and pieces of gimmicky
confusion because chronic illness is
exploding like never before in our
Modern Day history it takes a greater
force than us down here it takes a
helping hand from above medical medium
information has street cred it's an
organic movement of countless people
around the world healing more healing
stories of real people not being paid to
tell their life-changing experiences of
rising out of the ashes of sickness and
entering into the light of full recovery
getting their lives back and finally
healing when nothing else in the world
of Health could move the needle and get
them better the information on this
podcast is not man-made it comes from
above from a higher source whatever you
believe in whether God the universe the
light or the Creator or if you believe
in nothing at all that we're just
floating through space together on this
rock know that the information you hear
on this podcast is separate from all the
other noise out there it comes from a
different place a pure untampered with
Advanced Clean uncorrupted original Prim
primary source a higher source Spirit of
compassion