how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about avoiding
certain foods or eating what you want
don't eat this don't eat that watch out
for this watch out for that that can
give you cancer that can gain you lots
of weight and make you fat that can hurt
your baby that can age you fast that can
make you lose your libido what is it now
the world has caught on to shock and awe
don't eat this don't eat that fear fear
fear you better intermittent fast you
better stop sugar you better avoid the
medical system you better avoid carbs
they say now you should even avoid the
doctor the doctor's going to kill you
pharma's out to get you you better do a
fast you better try to fast you you
better try this product you better try
that product it can be an insane asylum
out there and who's right and who's
wrong and most important where's the
substance to it all seems like a lot of
empty quick ideas shouting out with no
Foundation at all empty noise and
my plane was delayed oh no yeah
yeah what about yours oh you're on the
same flight right oh this is awful I'm
just going to sit down try to kill
sometime yeah I um let me just look at
some articles here online
um four foods that will destroy your
life in under 10 minutes all right see
here's this one here the 10 forever
chemicals to avoid like the plague all
right all right what's this article here
experts warn that garlic may cause colon
cancer really I like
garlic that's weird
scientists say that if you eat twice
your stomach size you will get stomach
cancer oo I don't want
that influencer warns that the
contraception she used made her sick all
right what about this article here
fitness trainer with 72,000 followers
dies eating a package of
tuna all right all right here's some one
right here uh maybe I'll read this one
restaurant sued because of peanuts in
the
dressing oh yeah well I've heard about
peanuts being a problem how about this
one um you have an 8% chance of dying
early if you eat too fast oh
man my God when's my plane taking off
you see it every day out there now
shocking all shocking all that's what
it's all about clickbait Fe fear chaos
concerns discernment worry it's all out
there everybody's trying to create a fly
trap trying to get you to click that
button to read that article to look at
that video and everything's like die die
die you're going to die you're going to
get sick something terrible is going to
happen until you click this button here
and then suddenly lately there's all
these food experts now and the food
expert expts are everything from
dietitians to scientists to food experts
who knows where what how but they're
just in every article now they're like
top five foods to help you age less top
five foods that will actually age you
it's endless now but it's still fear and
there's really nothing behind it nothing
really behind the information no
substance sometimes just a random
citation to somebody else's article with
a whole bunch of theories in there but
nothing really really
substantial and then the influencers who
discovered food they discovered food
it's like they woke up one day from
their college dorm and realized that
food is important now an entire movement
of influencers that discover that food
actually makes a difference when you
change it something can happen with your
health with your mental state with your
mindfulness with your life in general
and then people are noticing that if you
say something good about food people are
interested people are also noticing if
you say something bad about food people
are interested because let's face it if
you don't eat you won't exist we have to
eat in order to sustain ourselves to
stay here to live to breathe to feed our
brain to feed our heart we have to
consume food of some kind regardless of
what it is food makes a difference and
so influencers are seeing that now and
wo and most everybody has that aha
moment that come to Jesus moment it's I
can't eat myself sick of processed food
anymore I know it's not helping me and I
have to back down one way or another I
can cheat I could have some I could
limit it I could play games all I want
but I have to be careful now I can't
just eat everything I want and anytime I
want all I can I can't just pull into
that fast food restaurant and order four
hot dogs with bacon and cheese two
double bacon
cheeseburgers three tacos with all the
fixen onion rings whole bunch of fries
gobble it all down and think that that's
a good thing the age of bliss is
disappearing right in front of us
everybody and their grandmother and
their cousin and their uncle and their
best friend and anybody else including
their pet dog and their pet monkey and
their pet cat knows better now or almost
knows better now or is on the edge of
knowing better either way something's
changing out there we can't just always
eat what we want a big chocolate cake
have it every single night right a big
juicy steak with butter on top have it
every single night whole bunch of
lobster with butter have it every single
night big bowl of mac and cheese every
single night sure every single night we
can't just do that we can't just eat a
dozen eggs every day yeah dozen eggs
every day I know there's a few people
out there're doing it and trying it or
saying that they swear by it but it'll
kill them in the end one way or another
to eat a dozen eggs every day we just
can't eat grilled cheese sandwiches all
day long every day and I'm talking about
Quan
large amounts of this because in the end
people would love to eat lots and lots
of this there are people out there that
do they eat lots of this same food I'm
not just talking about a little slice of
pizza and one egg a day I'm not talking
about small helping of mac and cheese
sure people they're careful with their
portions when they eat different foods
they're always worried they're always
looking out but they know they can't
just eat a whole gig antic chocolate
cake every single day because even
somebody's conventional doctor would say
whoa put on the brakes put on the brakes
the most conventional doctor you can
ever Stamp Out out of a conventional
medical school would say whoa I don't
advise you to eat a large chocolate cake
every single day hold your horses we got
to cut that back that's not good for you
and the world has changed right now the
food police is out there they're out
there every everywhere every how the
media is talking about it influencers
are talking about it no one can just
walk down the street and eat what they
want anymore someone's going to say
something someone somewhere somehow is
going to make you feel like they're
going to make you feel like you're doing
something wrong that you're eating
yourself to death you're eating the
wrong food you're eating the wrong way
it's going to kill you you should change
you should be ashamed of yourself you
should feel guilty and you need to
change and then there's the attack
haacks out there influencers are
attacking food companies food brands out
there they're holding packages of food
with the name of the company right there
on their feed and they're saying this is
going to kill you this is going to
poison you here's the forever chemicals
here's the toxic chemicals here this
Foods the worst thing in the world you
can't eat this look at all the chemicals
in here and they're doing that every day
right now and why are they doing it
because they care about you are they
doing it because they care that you got
chronic illness are they doing this
because they're really caring about your
well-being they don't care about you
they care about themselves and about
getting somewhere becoming somebody on
social and using any kind of shock and
all they can to get you spooked and
scared they care if you're sucking it
out and struggling down on your luck not
feeling good been to 20 doctors you're
really struggling they care do they care
if you have vertigo and tontis and
you're sick and have chronic fatigue
syndrome and anything else and
everything else do they really care
they're just sitting there thinking
about how to cash in the chi-ching how
to develop their brand how to make it so
they're actually you know making some
money and doing good and living it up I
don't think they really care about the
chronically ill they're not holding a
packaged food item that's filled with
chemicals because they're really
concerned that you're going to get that
chemical in your body and it's going to
make you sick like they really care and
it's all fun out there it's all fun in
games when you're you're not that sick
when you're hardly sick and it's kind of
fun just getting rid of some processed
foods eating better doing some
meditation doing some yoga changing your
lifestyle for the better and if you're
not so sick and you only have some mild
symptoms that come and go or go away
completely because you got rid of the
processed foods and you're taking care
of yourself you're sleeping a little bit
more you're living a better lifestyle in
some way a healthier way and you're
getting rid of some symptoms now you're
an expert total expert now but are you
really an expert because there's a big
difference a very big difference from
being not so sick and being really sick
and being seasoned with that trying
everything been there done that lots of
doctors been sick a long time tried
virtually almost everything and being
not so sick getting rid of One symptom
eating better taking care of yourself in
general symptom comes and goes you feel
stronger more confident feel like you
know health and wellness big big
difference right there two different
worlds two different worlds completely
The Not So Sick and the very very sick a
sick person who's been around the block
knows a thing or two they know what
works for them what doesn't work for
them at that point especially if they've
been in it for years and they also know
when they find something that makes
sense and actually works and they can
feel it and they're moving forward in
their life and they're getting rid of
some symptoms shedding me maybe even 10
symptoms they know they got something
it's gold and they've been on a search
long and hard for many years so when
they find that thing they hold on to it
they hold on to it with conviction
because they know it is saving them and
then they're not so sick that are
playing around with all kinds of
different foods they're looking out for
some of the bad stuff they're looking
out for some of the good stuff they're
trying different things they feel
something might be helping them they
feel something might not be helping them
but until they're really sick will they
ever have that conviction will they ever
really know and have that inner truth
what happens is The Not So Sick will
just play games try this and try that do
this and do that and they'll just EB and
flow and they'll go along for the ride
they're not that sick they can do it
until the scale tips someday and they go
downward and then they're like oh my God
those things aren't helping me anymore
but until that downfall happens until
they hit that rock bottom or head down
to that direction they sit up here way
up and they're just like yeah I know
what I'm doing I'm going to tell you how
to heal I'm going to tell you how to
take care of yourself the thing is I've
seen this thousands and thousands and
thousands of times I've seen people play
around up there being not so sick and
then the scale tip and then they go
downwards and they're getting humbled
takes a little time doesn't happen fast
depends on the entitlement or who they
are or where they come from or their
resources and when they start heading
down and they're like weit a minute
something isn't changing I'm really
stuck down here I don't feel good then
The Humbling starts to happen and then
they come knocking on a door cuz they
already knocked on 50 other doors and
they're still sick they knock on a door
and they're like you know what I like
what you're talking about I need some
answers these look like real answers so
let's Jump Ahead let's put aside food
chemicals let's put aside fast food and
greasy fried foods let's put aside
processed foods say you're somebody and
you're already pass that you're not
doing any of that or you believe you're
not doing any of that maybe some slips
in by default but you're trying to
really avoid that in your life you're
wise but you're still sick and you're
not getting fully better and you're
avoiding virtually
most of that or all of that and whatever
your sickness is inflammation is playing
a role you've heard that before inflamed
inflammation and the other thing that's
playing a role is immune system weakened
immune system and
inflammation but what does that mean in
the end if you go to a practitioner or
healthc care provider or a medical
professional and they say you're
inflamed or you have some form of
inflammation or markers are up and
you're inflamed in some way and they say
well you either got autoimmune or you
have some form of inflammation
something's going on here your Ana is
high your markers are high whatever it
may be whatever test you did what's the
answer in the end where's the
answers because it comes down to this
pathogens and metals bugs and
toxins viruses bacteria and poisons
toxins and metals
pathogens create this inflammation
that's inside of people's bodies mystery
chronic illness pathogens love toxins
and metals and feed off of toxins and
metals and then that also Spurs on lots
of
inflammation pathogens eat the toxins
and the poisons and the metals and then
they excrete the poison out of their
little viral cells and pathogen cells
but pathogens also eat other things they
eat Foods because this is one of the
biggest and most important missing links
here it's what feeds pathogens food that
pathogens like so it's not about being
the food police out there don't eat this
and don't eat that it's about having
real reason to not eat this or that when
you have a chronic illness there's a
reason to avoid a certain food it's not
just about shaming somebody about a food
or saying you shouldn't eat all that you
shouldn't eat a loaf of bread and a
stick of butter every day it's not about
that because there's people out there
that can eat a loaf of bread every day
and a stick of butter and they may not
have the same inflammation as somebody
else who's eating pretty good because
they may not have the pathogens that
somebody else has they may not have the
viruses and the bacteria so when they're
eating a loaf of bread and a stick of
butter it may not be feeding the same
pathogens that someone else has and
let's face it if anybody's trying to eat
healthy that's because something's wrong
because why would they just give up all
the pizza they wanted and all the
macaroni and cheese and all the
cheeseburgers and all the ice cream and
all the milkshakes why would they just
give that up they're either sick or they
want to look a certain way it's either
one or the other and looking a certain
way may not be enough motivation because
you'll still have your cheat days and so
forth as time goes on and pathogens
don't discriminate pathogens don't say
well those are children those are
teenagers those are young adults those
are people in their 30s those are people
in their 40s hm let's see let's not be a
pathogen in an 8-year-old let's only be
a pathogen in a 50-year-old it doesn't
work that way that's why there's a lot
of sick kids pathogens all kinds of
different bugs pathogens like viruses
and bacteria will be in children they'll
be in teenagers they'll be in young
adults they'll be in anybody anywhere
anyhow there's no discrimination they're
just in everyone at any time and the
same thing happens pathogens and toxins
creating inflammation pathogens and
metals creating inflammation so when it
comes down to avoiding a food there
needs to be a reason like seriously a
very important reason to avoid a certain
food and that important reason is to not
feed a bug because foods can feed bugs
pathogens viruses and bacteria Epstein
bar shingles hhv6
hhv7 undiscovered hhv 10 through 16 hsv1
hsv2 the herpes simplexes sedam virus
and many more many mutations many
different strains strep staff CI hpylori
anything and different bugs have
different appetites they like different
foods for different reasons for one
thing a bug might have been in somebody
else before you caught that bug a bug
might have been sitting in somebody else
and then eating a diet that that
somebody else fed that bug and that bug
has been used to that very diet and then
that bug gets contracted into somebody
else someone actually gets that bug
maybe they drank off of somebody's glass
maybe they shared a bodily fluid or
maybe off of a shopping cart handle you
touch the handle then you put your
finger in your eyee and then you got a
bug and that bug has a history it has a
past bugs have a past when they come
from other people they had a different
diet different foods so maybe you were
fine eating corn you've been eating corn
every year you eat corn in different
ways corn flour tortilla chips corn off
the cob you eat frozen corn any kind of
corn cornbread and everything's fine and
then then a bug you picked up recently
some exposure that had a corn diet from
another person is now in you and now
you're eating corn and you're eating
corn and you're eating corn and
something's changing you're not feeling
good you're getting sicker something's
wrong and you don't even know it but
that bug is feasting off of that corn
and eliminating toxins growing
proliferating getting stronger and
you're getting weaker you might be a
person that always did good with glut
you saw everybody else wasn't doing good
with gluten you hear about it all the
time you see gluten-free products
everywhere and you could eat plain old
straight Pizza glutened in bread anytime
you want and everything's fine and then
one day all of a sudden you get a bug
you catch somebody else's bug maybe it's
a strap you catch that strap loves to
Feast on gluten and that strap was in
somebody else's body and it was feasting
on gluten all the time and reproducing
itself and wreaking havoc UTI all the
time bladder infections kidney
infections St conjunctivitis lung
infections sore throats ear infections
all kinds of different headaches and so
forth and that strep was flying high and
it was feeding off of that gluten and
now that strep bug got into you somehow
maybe you kissed somebody maybe you just
caught it somewhere somehow on a public
toilet seat but you have it in you and
it's feasting on gluten and that was
never a problem before before instead
now you're like wait a minute
something's wrong I feel a little bit
better getting off of gluten am I one of
those people now where I have to be off
of gluten and yeah you have to be off of
gluten and maybe you're somebody that
does great with eggs can eat eggs every
day two eggs every single day could have
them boiled fried you could have them on
your salads you can have them scrambled
you can have any form of egg you can
have it in bread you can have it
anywhere anyhow you do good with eggs
you've been eating them for years and
then you're getting sick and sick and
sicker because you caught a bug maybe
you caught an Epstein bar virus maybe
it's your Epstein bar virus that
suddenly was awakened because your
immune system just broke down and some
triggers occurred and other exposures
and then boom immune system weakened and
then an Epstein bar came out of a dormy
that's been there forever and as it gets
up and strong and grows it's feeding off
those eggs for the first time in all
these years and something starts to
change and then you're in a public
bathroom you sit on a toilet seat you
actually eliminate in the toilet the
splash goes right up into the rectum and
in that Splash was a different Epstein
bar virus got into you it's now in you
it's not going to leave you it's going
to percolate it's going to do its thing
and you start getting sick and that
Epstein bar virus had a different diet
it loved dairy products milk cheese and
butter and that Epstein bar virus that
was in another person that was eating a
lot of milk cheese and butter wasn't
used to or eating goat's milk or goat's
cheese and that person that has this
virus now that's feeding off of milk
cheese and butter is shying away over
time from milk cheese and butter and
starting to gravitate to other options
because they're hearing people say well
if you don't feel good get off the milk
get off the dairy and you should try
goats milk or goats cheese and they end
up feeling a little bit better they do
okay and they're like wo I like goat
cheese that's what I eat and that's what
I like and I seem to do better with it
until that epine bar over time says I'm
hungry and I need some Dairy so it
starts to actually go towards the goat
cheese and the goat milk and then you're
somebody with a shingles virus maybe it
was dormant for years maybe you picked
up a shingles virus very easily from
somebody else somehow and that shingles
virus had a diet in somebody else that
was actually eggs somebody else ate a
lot of eggs they had a shingles flare up
continuously they had maybe multiple
shingles viruses and those shingles
viruses were used to eating eggs for a
long time and maybe you ate eggs and
everything was fine but this other
person they got away from eggs they got
away from other things too because they
were kind of figuring out whoo this
doesn't work for me this does work for
me because they were so inflamed for so
long with these shingles viruses but
you've been eating eggs all this time
and you've been doing okay with them and
you feel confident that the eggs work
for you and then you get this new
shingles virus it's in you now and it's
feeding on the eggs same goes with soy
soy can feed pathogens too genetically
altered soy can actually feed some
pathogens so if somebody's loaded with
some kind of pathogen and they're eating
a lot of soy same thing can happen or
they get a pathogen from somebody else
who ate a lot of soy GMO soy and then
boom they were eating soy too that
pathogen's like whoa this is the food I
like this is the food I want and when
someone gets extra inflamed out of
nowhere because they're eating that soy
if they could line it up and match it up
cuz a lot of people can some people
don't know what's bothering them they
don't know what food's triggering them
but some people do and they're like whoa
I think I'm going to back down the soy
for a while and now they're feeling a
little bit better but what's really
happening is they're starving the
pathogen they're starving the virus
medical medium information is about
customizing a protocol for you taking
your health as far as you want to go so
when you learn that gluten feeds bugs
say you got an H pylori say you have or
two streps and they eat gluten and that
gluten is feeding them creating
inflammation then you could rid that
gluten and see what happens and you're
starving one or two varieties of bugs
same thing if you take eggs out of your
diet you're taking the eggs away from
the pathogens viruses like shingles and
Epstein bar love eggs so when you remove
the eggs those bugs don't have a food
that they love and eat every day
essentially you're starving the bugs
starving them out of your body they die
if they don't have the food they need
it's a great way of getting rid of so
many bugs many people use the medical
medum information to clean up all the
pathogens they learn about the foods
they get rid of the pathogens and then
they bring those Foods back in the eggs
or the gluten or dairy as time goes on
and they notice that they're actually
able to eat it they're not getting
inflamed and they're okay but
everybody's different so many people
have different toxins poisons metals and
different bugs and pathogens some people
have two or three different viruses some
people will have 10 different strains of
viruses some people will have five
different viruses or they'll have
bacteria as well and there'll be
different levels of bugs some aggressive
some very mild so they have to customize
protocol for what they need because
they're different than somebody else
who's sick they have the option of
taking out one of the foods that feeds
bugs or take all of them out the
difference with medical medium
information then what's out there is
that it's not one siiz fits-all it's one
siiz fits-all out there in so many
different ways in the end it comes down
to just one size fits-all but with
medical medium information you can
customize it to what you need for where
you are at you can take it as far as you
need to go to work on your healing
process if you get a chance check out
the medical meeting book series you can
even go to the library to look for a
book see what's right for you in the
books customize something for yourself
ask your doctor what's right for
you yeah the plane is just not arriving
yet I'm so bored let's take a look at
this article here what's this one 10
ways you can make yourself live forever
all right let's see what this
is eat out of cast iron pans that's
number one number two two breathe deep
breaths of fresh air outside okay number
three do yoga twice a day okay number
four meditate twice a day okay number
five do a steam bath um okay number six
do a cold plunge all right number
seven um yeah no thank you no that's
great I'll take another one of those all
right thanks number seven stay away from
processed foods number eight eat more
vegetables number nine stay away from
all fruit number
10 bring salt back in to your
diet I
guess yeah I don't know some of these
things might be okay or not I think some
are okay I just I'm so
confused Health has become a game yo
a game of here's a new shiny
thing always tricks the ones that are
still green you know same old same old
for many Health has become nothing but a
pain in the
a-hole how lame how lame it's all become
hard to know if you're up or down when
sickness comes and the bioh hacks don't
resolve it's hard to stay sane meanwhile
you didn't know that they were all
clowns here we go the ones involved
didn't know been down to not eat what I
want been told to never eat what I
shouldn't want got sold on eating what
everyone else does don't know what's up
don't know what's down see that person
selling their dietary program that's
renowned I'm sick of the one size fits
all and I'm looking for a way to move
forward y'all need to get this ghost
ship to the dock and deboard my tired
body on the shore it's time to take my
healing to the next level and someday
after a healthy life stay on Earth while
my soul is in heaven knowing I did what
I needed to do down here until it
happens again
on another trip down from heaven into a
body that may need help again the wiser
Soul filled with leftover past knowledge
you can heal you can get through this
life out of pain and get yourself back
to the beginning
Again original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place
appear untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion