how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about chemical
sensitivities you know what I'm talking
about if you know what I'm talking about
certain smells bother you certain
ingredients bother you like MSG for
example or you feel sick from smelling
gasoline at the gas pump could be
anything symptoms arise you feel sick
walking down the toilet tree aisle in
the grocery store you don't like walking
down the chemical fertilizer aisle in
the hardware store do you and maybe this
is not your flavor or your Kryptonite
maybe yours it's just that you're
sensitive to everything and anything and
it's constantly playing with your head
and it's hard to say what even caused
any of your problems either way strap
yourself in we're going on the chemical
sensitivity
train hey yeah no I've been working here
two years you just got hired oh
congratulations man yeah oh no oh no
somebody's coming up to me it's a
customer ah I hate this all right
ma'am hey ma'am no I can't go down that
aisle no and I can't I can't walk you
down that aisle you want to know where
the pesticides are it's down that aisle
go down that aisle and just look on your
left you want me to show you I can't you
don't understand I'm chemical
sensitive yeah excuse me I should be
fired that's not nice ma'am there's this
guy just got a job here today he's going
to help you down that aisle um what do
you mean your chemal sensitive too no
you're not you're just saying that cuz
I'm chemical sensitive no no you can't
be using that as excuse if you're not
chemical sensitive dude no ma'am he's
going to take you down you're not I'm
not taking you down ma'am I'm not taking
down either every time I go around those
chemicals I get lightheaded and I almost
throw up ma'am do you want me to throw
up on you because I will if you take me
down that aisle yeah yeah cuz I start to
Hive out and I get nauseous and I get
sensitive yeah you don't get it I my
hand soap has to be a certain kind of
hand soap for my skin or my hand rips
apart and my dentist knows I'm latex
sensitive too where my mouth reacts and
I get this weird flavor in my mouth and
I get tightness in the chest and I get
short of breath yeah do you have any of
that no you don't exactly but I do this
this is serious I'm not going down that
aisle you're going to talk to the
manager good luck you're not the only
ma'am that talked to the manager about
me not taking anybody down that aisle he
already knows I won't go down that aisle
yeah he's got a cousin that's chemical
sensitive and his wife is slightly
chemical sensitive too so he's actually
cool with it the fertilizer is on the
right all the way down and the
pesticides are on the left yep good
luck people are told they're crazy
yes thousands and thousands and
thousands of them over the years people
have suffered with chemical
sensitivities and they've been told
they're crazy and then there's people
that don't know their chemical sensitive
and they're told they're crazy why are
they told they're crazy because of they
crazy symptoms the symptoms they have
are crazy to other people Tremors
vibrations through the body ticks and
spasms anxiety aches and pains that
revolve all around the body and move and
shift mystery rashes that pop up mystery
hives that appear out of nowhere
shortness of breath out of nowhere
tightness of the chest pain in the neck
and throat spasms all around the body
restless legs at night swollen hands
puffy skin red patches
rashes itchy bumps feeling like you're
overheated little tingles on the end of
your
fingers unexplainable little tickle in
your throat that makes you cough out of
nowhere
lightheadedness nausea and uneasiness in
the stomach and the pit of the stomach
and the list goes on and people they're
told they're crazy at least years ago
now it's more accepted now it's like oh
you're one of them chemical sensitive
person okay and doctors now when they
see their patients and their patients
come in and their patient says I'm
chemical sensitive I react to everything
doctors now go oh okay you're one of
them I understand I can try to talk you
through this instead years ago it's like
oh you're one of them there needs to be
like millions of apologies issued to all
these people that went through hell
living hell because they were chem
chemical sensitive all these years 10
years ago 15 years ago 20 years ago
people good-hearted people good-hearted
Souls that were suffering from all kinds
of strange weird symptoms and they were
chemical sensitive and they got treated
like crap they got stepped on they got
told they were crazy making it up they
were
hypochondriacs that they had Phantom
issues that they were fabricating out of
nowhere they were told all these things
and they suffered through it and all
these apologies should be issued to all
of them but it'll never happen it's like
it never existed it's not like it's all
been fixed like a chemical sensitive
person gets put on a pedestal or they
actually get treated with respect or
someone says oh my God you're chemical
sensitive sure let's figure this out
let's put you over here let's help you
with this let's solve your problems
let's talk about it no it's not like
that people are still told they're crazy
it's better than it ever was that's true
it's better than it was many years ago
but people still have a hard time with
their family the people around them with
their friends with their co-workers they
still have a very hard time there are
people that work in an office they're
sitting next to somebody who has all
that Fabrics off and are just whoosing
off of them and it's giving them a hard
time they're getting symptoms they don't
feel good but they have to live with it
it's better than it was people do
understand a a little bit doctors are
looking out for people in a better way
but it's still hard it's still difficult
many situations people do things on
spite when somebody's chemical sensitive
and they complain a little too much
because they're trying to protect
themselves let's face it because they
need help and they're looking for some
kind of relief so they can function and
then somebody on spite does something to
them purposely to make their situation
worse like wearing more cologne or even
more perfume on spite someone working
with them will say hey can you dial it
down I'm really sensitive to your
perfume then that person sprays two more
sprays of perfume on them purposely when
someone's not chemical sensitive they'll
never understand they just can't cuz
it's not bothering them it's hard to
connect with that person who's chemical
sensitive because they're smelling
things but it's not bugging them at all
they're wearing perfumes cologn they got
the air fresheners they don't care about
gasoline they don't care about exhaust
fumes they don't care about smoke in the
air they'll sit in front of a fire pit
while the fire pit is burning treated
wood with chemicals in it so they can't
relate it's not possible while that
other person who's chemically sensitive
that knows they're chemically sensitive
though cuz there's two different
chemical sensitives out there there's
one that don't know and have no idea
it's affecting them in any way and ones
that do know and the ones that do know
know that the fire pits bothering their
sinuses making their chest all tight
making them not feel good they know the
air fresheners are making them sick they
know the Colones and perfumes are waking
out their nervous systems they know
these things and to the other person
they sound like they're hypochondriacs
and that they're crazy but they're not
this doesn't mean the person who can
handle all that smoke from treated wood
burning or handle all that perfume on
their body is
indestructible they can just get cancer
and die they can have a heart attack
tomorrow they can be going along
everything's great they smell everything
they're happy they got chemicals all on
their body they're breathing in
pesticides in their yard as they're
spraying their flowers They're doing all
that they look indestructible they're
fine they don't smell anything all is
good they're not reacting and then they
go drop dead 10 years later and it also
doesn't mean that they're never going to
become chemical sensitive in their life
see that's not true either they could
become chemical sensitive down the road
in fact they could become chemical
sensitive and not even know it so as
they got that fabric softener cooking in
the dryer and they got that detergent
and they got all kinds of chemicals
cleaning products that are actually
dangerous in their house and they're
breathing it all in while they're trying
to kill a spider with a can of toxic
pesticide while they're doing all of
this and breathing in all kinds of crazy
stuff they can become chemical sensitive
get symptoms from it run to a 100
doctors and not realize all those
chemicals are pushing their body over
the edge now what does chemical
sensitive even mean what's really
happening why is one person reacting to
a chemical or some type of agent or
solvent or some kind of toxic stuff
that's in the air or on their skin when
another person isn't because their scale
is tipped someone becomes chemical
sensitive because they're being
triggered the chemicals whatever form or
shape they're in are triggering them
they're lowering their immune system
which is already lowered they're
antagonizing their nervous system which
is already inflamed they're
overburdening the liver which is already
overburdened and the chemicals are
acting as a trigger which is feeding
pathogens and bugs which were already
being fed by other chemicals in the
person's body because the scale has been
tipped earlier on and the person who
isn't chemical sensitive isn't having a
situation where their liver is
overflowing with toxins they're not
quite there yet with all the triggers
now they may have some of these things
going on a pathogen or two in their body
creating all kinds of stuff Underneath
It All they may have sensitivities but
they're not quite showing themselves yet
and they may have inflammation and it's
not quite fully there yet but they're on
their way they're just not totally
spilled over and tipped over like the
other person is by medical medium
standards information that was released
in Liver Rescue and in other places
through medical medium information when
someone's chemically sensitive their
liver is overburdened stagnant and
sluggish and overworked
this is when the liver becomes a fatty
liver even if non-diagnosed not
diagnosed as a fatty liver the liver's
not functioning good it's stagnant it's
sluggish it's not awake it's dense it's
overburdened it's hardening up why does
this happened because of a lifestyle in
combination of pathogens such as viruses
like Epstein bar shingles Cirus herplex
1 herplex 2 hhv6 hhv7
viruses inside the liver trapped in
there living in there working on tissue
making it more dense making it more
problematic and weakening the immune
system inside the liver along with
toxins poisons like fragrances other
toxins and poisons and heavy metals
Mercury aluminum copper cadmium lead
arsenic nickel and even toxic calcium
along with a thousand other chemicals
that found their way into the filter
your filter the liver it's there
filtering your blood filtering what's
going into your intestinal tract and up
the stream of blood into the liver and
that filter your liver can have 10,000
chemicals that are foreign to the human
body 10,000 chemicals from chemical
companies from the chemical industry
just sitting inside the liver and when
your liver gets tired stagnant and
sluggish and it's not working as good as
it should then something goes wrong then
conversion doesn't happen like it needs
to the conversion of nutrients
methylation becomes stagnant and
sluggish when nutrients enter your body
from Foods they get to the liver and
they're supposed to be blessed by the
liver converted and they can't so
methylation starts to go downhill and
the person starts to become nutrient
deficient while this is happening though
a lot of different symptoms can occur
and a lot of different conditions can
happen like pre-diabetes type 2
diabetes blood sugar inconsistencies
hypoglycemia
hypoglycemia and then cholesterol
problems as well but when the liver is
stagnant sluggish tired overburdened and
overworked something else can happen
especially if the liver is filled with
pathogens and toxins and toxic heavy
metals when it's f filled with all of
those something not great occurs a
spillover the liver can't hold on to all
the garbage dump stuff anymore it has to
release some it has to let go and when
it lets go it's a spill and what does
that spill contain pathogens release out
of their viral cells and bacterial cells
lots of different neurotoxins and
poisons and garbage and junk and then
toxic heavy metals that are sitting in
the liver for a life time start to
oxidize start to gas out start to pocket
out and that debris starts to spread and
leave the liver too and then depending
on the pathogens that are sitting inside
the liver some of those pathogens like
Epstein bar will feed off of copper feed
off of aluminum and mercury and release
all kinds of toxic heavy metal
neurotoxins out of the viral cells and
into the bloodstream and then the liver
can't filter like it's supposed to
anymore it's not being a good filter
it's trying to be a good filter but it's
overflowing there's a spill and that
spill can be random at any time it can
be when you eat something one day it can
be when you wake up one morning it can
be in the middle of the day sometime
when you're exercising it could be when
you're walking but these spills are
random they happen at any time and when
there's a spill the concoction is
different in every single person one
person may have more heavy metals one
person may have one variety of a heavy
metal more so than other varieties of
heavy metals another person might have
one virus another person could have a
100 viruses another person can have
solvents and all kinds of different
pharmaceutical compounds when someone
else might have a whole bunch of
recreational drugs inside their liver
and somebody else may have all kinds of
different fossil fuels and all kinds of
other different toxins and
petrochemicals everybody's blend of
toxins is different and those toxins
bother the central nervous system most
of chemical sensitivity symptoms are
central nervous system based nerve based
when somebody's spill is filled with all
kinds of different toxins from toxic C
metals and from pathogens and other
chemicals and they actually leave the
liver they attack themselves to the
nerves so most symptoms in the chemical
sensitivity world are from nervous
system symptoms nervous systems that are
inflamed and hypers sensitive and then
another portion of symptoms in the
chemical sensitivity World those are
skin issues and swelling issues this is
when the spill is a different recipe of
chemicals and toxins and pathogen debris
and somebody's skin can react
hives different kind of red blotches
different kind of spots itchy bumps all
kinds of different skin conditions and
then swelling swelling in the knuckles
stiffness in the knuckles swelling in
the hands swelling in the elbows
lymphatic swelling lymphadema all
through the body all kinds of different
water retention all these symptoms can
really perplex people complicate their
lives and confuse their doctor their
practitioners their healthc care
providers their health coaches their
therapists their
psychiatrists all of them can get
confused by these symptoms and people
get diagnosed with all kinds of
different mental conditions because of
chemical sensitivities people will tell
them well we think we have OCD right
here or ADHD or add or we have bipolar
or some other condition they get
diagnosed with because they're sitting
there worried and they have anxiety
they're worried about the carpet being
hold from underneath them they're
worried about going down they're worried
about can't get in their car they have
panic attacks anxiety conditions all
kinds of different symptoms and they're
nervous and they're living their life
extra nervous because of it and it's
like a snowball going down a mountain
side where it's just going down and
Gathering all this debris and getting
larger and larger and larger until it
finally just spills onto a village it's
that concerning that difficult and that
complex one of the biggest fears that
people who have chemical sensitivities
have is the dentist chair if a dentist
wears latex gloves and the hygienist
wears latex gloves that's a big concern
for people who are chemical sensitive if
the dentist is using fluoride or wants
to offer fluoride treatment that's
another big concern and then it's the
numbing agents people who are chemical
sensitive are concerned about the
numbing agents lidocaine Novocaine
carbocaine septian all the different
numbing agents they're worried including
the numbing gels so what happens is
they'll take a Q-tip they'll stick it
into some numbing gel they'll put it
around a gum line and that's a big
concern for people who are chemical
sensitive another thing is getting
fillings removed or fillings put in if
it's old fillings whether they're
composits of some kind or Mercury
fillings that are old people who are
chemical sensitive either react or
they're really concerned and they're
telling their dentist this their dentist
if they know them as a patient their
dentist is wise to it many dentists are
worried because it could be like Russian
Roulette they don't know what's going to
happen in that moment how the person's
going to react what's going to happen is
a symptom going to develop it's very
hard for the patient and for dentists
often what happens with chemical
sensitive people is they're reacting but
yet they're blaming something that did
not cause the reaction many times
somebody could be eating something and
then they get a reaction but what they
ate did not cause the reaction they were
going to have a spill anyway or they had
a spill an hour before they ate
something and it took time for that
spill to create a reaction and it's
possible that what they were eating was
only helpful to their problem and not
hurtful but they wouldn't know that
because they had a spill long before and
now they're reacting and they think it
was that strawberry they ate or they'll
blame the wrong food mixed in with a
whole bunch of foods like they'll have a
piece of chocolate cake that had a
strawberry on top after they eat the
chocolate cake they get a reaction half
hour later or 45 minutes later and then
they blame the strawberry that was on
top of the cake I can say a thousand
examples we can go on and on all day
about this there's a lot of confusion
people don't know what creates the
reactions the problem is Foods aren't
the only thing that caus reactions in
fact foods cause the least amount of
reactions it's other stuff happening
inside the body it's a liver intoxicated
with so many chemical compounds so many
different pathogenic chemicals and
neurotoxins and all of that is actually
going through the bloodstream hitting
other organs and creating problems and
hitting nerves as well and creating
nervous system symptoms so in the end
it's not really the food that's why
somebody else can eat whatever food they
want and they don't have any kind of
chemical
sensitivities often times when people
are chemical sensitive they'll blame the
food no matter what they'll be triggered
left and right and food will always get
the blame when in the end it's much
bigger than food it's much more than
that in another episode coming up we're
going to go deep into food sensitivities
people who are chemical sensitive start
reacting to everything though they react
to air they react to water they react to
food they react to chemicals they react
to just about everything and the problem
is with that is if you take a healing
food like a lemon water where you
squeeze a half a lemon in a glass of
water and drink that every morning to
clean the liver flush the liver flush
the kidneys of toxins what happens is
that when someone does that and they're
chemical sensitive and they're having
any kind of reactions they're going to
be like nope I got to stay away from
lemon water I can't do it I can't go
near it and then they get in trouble
what kind of trouble they're stuck in a
catch 22 they're stuck in a vicious
cycle where they need something to heal
but they're afraid of using it because
they're confused when someone got to the
point where they're really chemical
sensitive they got past the point of
dumbing everything down and numbing
everything out that means using foods to
suppress they can't do that anymore
successfully they can't suppress the
toxins suppress the poisons and suppress
the emotions anymore because at any
random time at any moment a spill out of
the liver can occur and fill the
bloodstream at any time that means
whatever they're suppressing themselves
with and holding down and bogging down
emotions whatever they're trying to do
to use food as comfort it doesn't mean
it will work it will always be a random
moment a random time where something
goes KY where nothing they try works
anymore now it's just Blind Faith
chemical sensitive people are right for
the picking they're lwh hanging fruit
four people who are selling detox is
selling the hole you're detoxing too
much that's why you're having reactions
you're detoxing too much that's why
you're sick try this concoction try
these ensures your Pathways aren't open
your detox Pathways aren't working which
is ridiculous because there's no science
or ability to see if their detox pathway
is working science still doesn't even
know what the detox pathway actually
really is it's all a theory but they'll
still sell that to you and detox sellers
will use the default mechanism it's you
and you're detoxing that's what it is
but overloaded livers and liver spills
does not mean you're detoxing you could
be sick and you're having spills your
liver is overloaded stagnant and
sluggish and stuff is coming out of the
liver it's filling your bloodstream but
that still doesn't mean you are detoxing
because all of that spill all of those
toxins is still going back into the
liver it's not leaving the body because
because whoever is offering the detox or
the program or whatever they're selling
is not properly getting the metals and
the poisons and the toxins and the
pathogens out of the body so what's
happening instead of it leaving the body
it's circulating and going right back
into the liver and making the person
sick and then they're telling the person
you're detoxing and our thing is working
proper detoxing is when it leaves the
liver and then leaves the body because
the person is doing the right things in
order for that to happen and when you're
properly detoxing and it's leaping the
body less reactions are occurring over
time it's riding out the storm when you
do the right things you could ride out
the storm and get to the other side and
it's hard to ride out the storm with all
the different stuff out there getting in
the way all the sharks selling all their
crap all the detox programs that have
stuff in there that cause problems with
the liver and all the Malarkey that's
going on it's hard to ride out the storm
when you don't know where you are in the
storm you're on a boat in the middle of
the ocean there's a hurricane and you
don't know which way is North South West
and East and even when you're doing the
right things to cleanse to heal you can
still get a brand new exposure that tips
the scale for a moment sends somebody
backwards a little bit scares them to
death and here we are right back into
the Catch 22 and the fear and the chaos
where we have to ride out the storm
because there are new Expos exposures
people get every single day and it adds
on to things while they're trying to
heal there are people out there who are
chemical sensitive who aren't doing
anybody's detox whatsoever and they're
having the same symptoms every day as
people who are doing somebody's detox
out there and the chemical sensitive
person who's doing somebody's detox out
there is being told that they're
detoxing and that's why they're having
reactions here are some quick tips if
you're somebody that's chemical
sensitive and you're struggling with all
kinds of different symptoms you want to
kill pathogens taking away foods that
feed pathogens that's a great gentle way
to start remove gluten remove eggs
remove dairy products remove corn look
into the anti-bug cleans in cleanse to
heal the medical medium book in the book
series cleanse to heal that's a great
place to start the next place to start
bringing in a little bit of lemon water
half squeezed lemon in a nice big glass
of water every single morning you can
gently start there you can even start
with 4 oz of lemon water or 2 oz of
lemon water as you're going through that
and that's successful over time because
it will be it's very healing it's very
gentle then move into some celery juice
after that start with 2 ounces of celery
juice if you like or 4 oz and you can
build yourself up to eventually drinking
32 o of celery juice every single
morning another option is keeping overt
fats out of the diet in the morning no
peanut butter no nuts no oils no eggs
and dairy products no meat or chicken or
fish no avocado until after noon in the
morning keep over at fats out of the way
you can bring in steam potatoes in the
morning if you want something that feels
satiating you can bring in fruit you can
do the celery juice and the lemon water
you can do some raw honey if you like
but keep the overt fats out check out
cleans of heel the morning cleanse
there's a lot of different options in
there and there's even a chemical and
food sensitivity section in that book
with a protocol another option if your
chemical sensitive is to bring in the
heavy metal detox if you're somebody
that's concerned and you're looking at
the ingredients and the heavy metal
detox you can always reduce and lower
the amounts you can also lower the
amount of heavy metal detox that you
actually consume you take it one step at
a time same goes with celery juice same
goes with lemon water ask your doctor
what's right for you yeah I mean I I
really like this job I do I know you're
here for your first day you know you
like it too already yeah I've been here
2 years okay oh H oh oh here she comes
again sorry ma'am I I can't walk you
down the toilet tree aisle no I can't
because there's all kinds of crazy
products that smell really bad down that
aisle like fragrances and stuff huh look
I'm doing the best I can it's just that
there's two aisles I won't walk down I
won't walk down the one that has all the
pesticides and the chemicals and all
that and I won't walk down the one with
the toilet trees you know the toilet
trees all those stinky items and
deodorants and all kinds of other stuff
I won't walk down that aisle you can't
make me do it I'm a bad worker well
that's not nice you talked to the
manager what did he
say he said what he said that getting
fired that's not true I told you he's
got a cousin that's chemical sensitive
there's no way all right well good luck
go down the toilet trees look for your
favorite brand I got to talk to the
manager let's go over there now hey uh
hey Jack hey did you talk to did you
talk to the lady over there what
happened what she wants me fired what
did you tell her you told her you're
going to fire me are you serious oh
you're not going to fire me you're just
making the customer happy in the moment
oh thanks man I really love this job
it's the best
place people say I'm crazy no one gets
me they don't
understand they think I'm
overreacting was called a hyper contract
woman and
man one person said my system is just
out of way
whack I spent the last 10 years trying
to get my system back on track no one
knows how hard it really is when you
can't do the same things and run with
the
pack been Solo in this life defending
for myself have to protect my body in
the world that's gone
Loco I see people living
how they want out there until it happens
to them one by one they
fall why would us humans create so much
toxin down here under the sun in this
world so their bodies start to
rust does God bless the chemical
industry for what they have done or does
God punish them in the end for all that
they have ruined and how they try to
destroy everything wholesome and
Homespun is this what they did on Mars
the war machines and the toxic bombs
blew it all to hell and before they did
that everyone became chemical sensitive
like they are becoming here on Earth
with no
Prevail it's a spill but you got to have
Blind Faith you can get to the other
side we can get past it all and heal
[Music]
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compass passion