holy [ __ ] we need to get this guy off
the internet like we need to just take
it all down it's like evil runs through
all of us
and I don't know it's just like to me
that sums up the whole cuz I I'm not
over here trying to pretend I'm a
s go you it
that's of course I've committed horrible
acts but you know you didn't even have
to do anything bad in your
ha he's Conant
watching Anthony
and just grabbing every little bit of
information that he thinks could be
helpful to take him down and I remember
one time you know I had this kind of
like a I've talked about a little bit
before so my my kind of my dark dark
days um I felt this voice and it was
like you know if you nothing else has
been working for you you should kind of
like thought maybe maybe you need to
come work on my side it's a long story
but in the nutshell
there was a voice that was like you
should come work for leave the light
come work for the other side and I
remember falling on the floor and in
tears being like I will never never work
for the dark like I I don't care if I'm
in a wheelchair or a bed bound or die I
will never switch TS and I'm telling you
that moment something lifted off my
chest like and then I knew I knew I was
like you demon whatever is in my body I
don't know what Megan's told you but it
will be interesting to see what the
response when this comes out you know
yeah what do you think is going to
happen I think there will be a parting
of the Red
Seas initially and I think that it will
definitely ruffle some feathers and I
think that there will be a large
community of people who share it um I
think me it's coming out VY fair so it
will be widely will be widely shared
yeah no matter what Amber and Anthony
have no idea what's in store for them in
the coming
years years ago a group of people
secretly teamed up and did everything
they could to try to knock me out of the
health space they formed a multi-step
long-term plan to create a quote
post-medical medium era by feeding false
information to mainstream media
companies anonymously like they did to
Vanity Fair last year using a false
story about a woman named Stephanie who
passed away from cancer years ago this
group thought they could destroy my
reputation with a series of hitpiece
Articles against me without anybody
knowing who was behind it all so that
they couldn't be held accountable until
they reached their goal they ultimately
wanted the hit pieces to lead to
securing themselves a deal for an
anti-ed medium documentary on Netflix
and would then bring Fame and other
benefits to them this group had been
working on their plan for a long time
secretly recruiting more people to join
them along the way using false
information and false stories about me
but their plan was thored last year when
this group tried to recruit a woman
named Amber visicaro an alternative
medicine practitioner who's been a part
of the medical medium Community for over
7 years Amber decided to legally record
her phone calls with the leaders of this
group for her own protection and safy
because she immediately felt that
something was off she ended up capturing
evidence of the identities of the main
individuals behind this Sinister plot
and sadly all of them no exaggeration
are people who have been helped by
medical medium information and even some
by me personally in their Darkest Hours
whether it was with their health or
their career or both Amber captured
evidence of this massive betrayal proof
that this group is Rife with ulterior
motives and has been led by individuals
with Platforms in the health industry
who want to take me out and a documented
record of the verifiably false stories
and Flatout lies they've been telling
people about me to try to get them on
their side her recordings serve as a
record of the entire recruitment process
and the recruitment tactics for example
they tried to to sell Amber on the idea
that she could be made famous by Vanity
Fair if she turned against me and let
the journalists position her as the
leader of the post-medical medium era
mean I I've been thinking about this for
a long time like you definitely have an
opportunity to be a leader in what I
would call the postmed medium era and
having him put you on a platform and be
like a leader of this era would could be
good for you Amber knew that what was
happening was very wrong and instead of
joining them she came on four episodes
of the medical medium podcast last year
and used her recordings facts and
evidence to expose this group the
details of their multi-step plot their
malevolent and ulterior motives and the
verifiably false information they'd been
trying to spread and publish in order to
take medical medium and the community
down what we covered was appalling and
shock so many of you to the core and yet
there is so much more to the story this
is truly one of the biggest scandals
that has ever happened in the health
industry as you'll see it's also one of
the biggest instances of capturing
corruption within the mainstream media
this episode is the first in what's
going to be a full-blown expose Amber
vakaro is back on here with me today and
she's going to be joining me in an
ongoing series series of many podcast
episodes in which we are going to be
thoroughly exposing this group that we
refer to as the plotters and dismantling
their Web of Lies alterative motives and
much more some of the evidence we're
presenting in these episodes includes
original written content such as text
messages and social media posts that
have been produced by the plotters and
will be reenacted for greater ease in
following along those who are listening
to the podcast can find video versions
of these episodes on the medical medium
YouTube and Rumble channels that will be
displaying screenshots photos videos and
more Amber thank you for being here
again can you start by explaining why
we're back here doing this
again thanks Anthony it's crazy that
it's been over a year since we released
the first round of podcast episodes
about this group and part of me is
pained by the fact that we're back here
addressing this again because I know
that what we all want more than anything
is to be able to move on from this
deranged plot and all of this group's
just really dark and nasty attacks but
we're back here again because even after
being exposed and proven wrong last year
the plotters did not stop
plotting in fact they escalated their
behavior significantly to the point that
it's become allout expressions of
Senseless hatred they took to social
media and put their true intentions on
display as they began terrorizing
publicly attacking bullying harassing
shaming and humiliating chronically ill
people in the medical medium Community
who are just minding their own business
trying to
heal this hateful group has disturbingly
targeted and attacked moms and even
children if someone in the community
tried to defend themselves against these
attacks the plotters would Gaslight them
flip it around portray them eles to be
the victims and label medical medium
community members as being bullies when
the plotters were in fact the
aggressors throughout the past year this
organized hateful group has issued
threats toward Anthony and myself
they've repeatedly expressed clear
intent to harm medical medium and the
community they've deliberately tried to
stop Anthony from doing a free event to
support and raise money for the
community they've posted videos of
themselves burning medical media books
and they've incited for others to do the
same okay all these medical medium books
are going to be burned
today it's
happening this is going in first celery
juice
one I took out the insides cuz it's
going to take forever to
burn this is not a joke this organized
hateful group has even gone as far as to
issue a public statement calling for
Anthony himself to be exterminated by
fire if you're watching the video
version of this episode you'll see a
social media graphic titled Pest Control
cheat sheet that has a list of options
that you can use to repel or kill pests
like ants and spiders you'll see that
someone who has been involved with the
plotters rehar it and added medical
medium
fire you don't have to like Anthony you
don't have to like medical medium
information medical medium information
is always has gotten plenty of criticism
because anything Leading Edge always
does and there's a lot of spiritual
discrimination out there this is
different this is just objectively wrong
and unacceptable Behavior this is a
barrage of baseless attacks that are
completely devoid of rationality Truth
and
Sanity the plotters have spent the
entire past year still desperately
trying to create something that doesn't
exist they have pivoted so many times
shifting narratives and saying anything
to get a rise out of people and they've
manufactured and spread an unimaginable
number of New Lies they're still out
there trying to get attention from media
companies by playing dirty with lies and
verifiably false information which is
going to be thoroughly exposed in this
series they continue to use and exploit
deceased individuals and others in the
process of trying to get what they want
they continue to ignore reality they
thought that they had a meal ticket
because they had text messages from
Anthony that they took from a deceased
person's phone and manipulated to try to
frame a public figure to serve their own
agenda but it's too bad for them that we
have all of the text and other evidence
they're hiding that proves them wrong
and their admissions on recording and
more and we will use it all to set the
record straight as many times as we need
to and because their attempt to take
Anthony out using their false Stephanie
story was a failure and didn't get them
where they wanted to be they've had to
Pivot and manufacture entirely new
outrageously false
narratives that is why we're back here
doing this again but it's all coming out
this time around as you said Anthony
there is so much more to this story in
our previous episodes we held back on a
lot out of respect for Stephanie and the
family we only released what was
necessary to address the false
accusations at the time we also held
back on a lot about the plotter
purely as courtesy to them in hopes that
after being proven wrong they would at
the very least just
stop that is very much not what has
happened this organized hateful group is
still trying to rewrite history they are
spreading verifiably false information
they are flat out lying and they are
withholding and altering evidence as
they try to perpetuate their false
narratives so that courtesy is no longer
going to be
extended at at the time of my calls with
the plotters I knew enough to know that
what they were telling me was wrong but
I have now spent the entire past year of
my life thoroughly studying every detail
for myself every text thread every
communication with every one of the many
individuals who were involved every
audio every photo every video every
social media post every piece of data
that was submitted to us every
Everything organizing it all into
timelines forensically analyzing it
scrutinizing the facts and running it
all through fact checker and a legal
team this group is in for a rude
awakening we're going to be exposing
everything there's a lot that's coming
in these episodes and we want to prepare
everyone for it by first issuing a
trigger
warning we understand that content about
the activities of this organized hateful
group can be triggering for those who
have experienced serious betrayal
bullying harassment emotional trauma
manipulation and abuse so please take
care of yourself as you listen you might
want to have some lemon bomb tea or a
medical medium adrenal healing snack
with
you next to further prepare everyone
listening for what's to come I'm going
to provide some shocking updates of
occurrences since our last series of
podcast episodes about this group as
well as some important context as to how
we got here today and I'm going to start
by officially releasing the names of the
plotters for the first time right now at
this point everyone deserves to know
exactly who and what they're really
dealing with the number one person
responsible for this plot a mountain of
Lies upon lies and all of the
chronically ill people who have been
harmed by all of it is a woman named
Ashley
Foster Ashley Foster is the one you
heard telling the original verifiably
false story about Stephanie Ashley is
the one you heard talking about how she
was hoping that a director or a producer
that her husband works with would be
interested in doing a negative
documentary about Anthony
and she's the one you heard saying that
because Anthony has such a presence that
a Netflix documentary is her goal
because then there would be no coming
back from that for
him um oh my
um yeah we're hopeful that once the
article's out um one of the directors or
producers that Britain works with
will uh you know become interested in
telling the story really well I think
it's going to take that because Anthony
is so um he has such a presence and if
it just stops at the article I'm
guessing that like there would be some
buzz in the medical medium Community for
a few months but like really I think
then it would kind of die down
ultimately the
way to really get the word out is like
would be like a Netflix documentary you
know
so um once you hit that
level of like being exposed there's kind
of no there's no coming back from
that Ashley is the ring leader of this
organized hateful group Ashley's
original false story about Stephanie is
the story that was given to Vanity Fair
as was reflected in the questions that
were asked of Anthony the questions
literally mirrored Ashley's very
distinct false story and we are going to
be reading those questions off in this
series Ashley's story was first posted
on social media in 2020 Ashley told more
than 15 verifiable falsities in the
comment section of that post Ashley told
more than 15 additional verifiable
falsities the next day Ashley posted an
adapted story to her blog at the time
and that version contained more than 20
verifiable falsities Ashley was sent a
legal letter informing her of the facts
and what she was wrong about Ashley was
asked to preserve a record of what she
had posted but instead Ashley decided to
delete all of it
immediately Ashley then spent years
plotting and scheming lying to people
around her trying to get them on her
side and against Anthony in 2022 Ashley
tried to get away with taking that same
false story about Stephanie from 2020 to
the media so that she could hide behind
anonymity as a source and therefore not
be held accountable for being wrong too
bad for her I CT captured her and her
hateful group exposing themselves on
recording last year since the article
and our podcast came out last year
Ashley has spearheaded a whole ongoing
smear campaign against Anthony and
medical medium information in addition
to all of the attacks the new lies
Ashley's been spreading all of the
pivoting she's done and the bullying
Ashley has also been childishly ACC
costing people in the medical medium
Community via DM intentionally trying to
break them down and convince them to
stop applying medical medium
information hey I um just wanted to
slide into your DMs as a little
troublemaker after having spent years
littering lies and false information
about Stephanie everywhere every chance
she could get and claiming Stephanie to
be the reason why she started attacking
Anthony in the first place Ashley's now
very recently pivoted almost entirely
away from Stephan
and has conjured up new narratives about
medical medium information in general
that are even more verifiably wrong than
her fake story about Stephanie
throughout this series we will be
exposing a tremendous amount of
information about Ashley you're going to
learn all about Ashley's true motives
behind her desperate desire to want to
take Anthony down and the true history
that she's been hiding from everyone all
this time the pathological lies Ashley
has told all all while she's claimed to
be perfectly honest and morally Superior
are going to be put on display the
fabricated stor she's been telling for
years are going to unravel you'll learn
about individuals who have been
personally victimized attacked and
belied by Ashley Ashley's clearly
documented track record of being
dishonest and highly inaccurate and then
simply pivoting to the next false claim
when caught that has been playing out
for years is going to be uncovered
you're going to learn just how far
Ashley has gone with her lies what she
had to do to get Vanity Fair to run with
and publish their HIIT piece on Anthony
and much
more the number two person responsible
for this plot and all of the chronically
ill people who have been harmed by it as
many of you have figured out is Robbie
Barbaro Robbie has a health business he
was Anthony's friend Anthony helped him
a lot with his career and Robbie was
also my friend Robbie St us both in the
back Robbie lied to my face while he was
secretly plotting to destroy medical
medium in the community for over a year
during our friendship all while he was
actively using medical medium protocols
like the heavy metal detox celery juice
and specific medical medium recommended
supplements himself and even asking me
repeatedly for health advice when he was
very clear on the fact that it was
medical medium
information so here he is plotting to to
take down the medical medium Community
while he's using the medical medium
heavy metal detox celery juice and
supplement protocol information to
achieve better health for himself then
asking Amber for help while lying to her
and this is one of Ashley's closest
friends and Ashley said on a recording
that she believes there's like no one
more trustworthy than
Robbie but there's like no one more
trustworthy than Robie so I know that
whatever he shared with you it's like
spot on Amazing prime example of who the
plotters
are Robbie is the one you heard
detailing the plot and multi-step plan
using the infamous phrase postm medal
medium era stating that the plotter
vision is to create a negative
documentary about Anthony that would be
a quote [ __ ] hit on Netflix
describing how he had to give the
journalist the plotter sought out a lot
of direction for the hit piece how he
had to hammer their narrative into the
journalist's head how he had to point
the journalist here and point him there
and how he ultimately had to threaten
the journalist to get him to move
forward with the
article I connected with a lot of people
to it he really appreciated Ash and I
and then just gave him a lot of
direction for this piece we gave him a
lot of clarity sort of Tor like he he
was having a hard time wrapping his head
around a lot of it
like really Hammer his head like what's
going on and like explain the details
and point him towards this point him
towards that but I I was upset I said
Dam like he you are scared you're scared
like what's going on what's the delay
like you you have everything it's on the
[ __ ] you have all this stuff what do
you need and then I Bally
threaten there is a whole lot more to
the story with Robbie as well that again
I held back on because I was really
trying to avoid having to fully go there
with all of this publicly I only shared
what was necessary at the time but
because Robbie instigated and enabled
Ashley to get to where she is now that
she uses her platform to relentlessly
inflict harm upon the chronically ill
because Ashley won't stop even after
being caught lying and proven wrong with
facts and evidence because Ashley has
lied and lied and lied and lied some
more and even gone as far as to portray
Robbie as somehow being a victim in this
situation when that could not be any
further from reality it has become
necessary for me to fully set the record
straight on Robbie and I'm not holding
back on anything in this
series as you'll see and hear Robbie
could not find a fact about what
happened with Stephanie to save his life
Robbie has exhibited zero regard for the
actual truth in this matter Robbie
simply used an exploit Ed Stephanie just
like the rest of this group Robbie went
to Great Lengths to try to take Anthony
down for ulterior reasons which are
going to be exposed for the first time
and you're going to get to learn more
about who Robbie really is behind the
facade he portrays including his
documented track record of disrespecting
women and just being a shady person in
General Robbie has deeply hurt betrayed
and inflicted harm upon me as well as
Anthony and this community and it's time
for him to be held
accountable another person who I am
extremely disappointed to announce as
having been involved with this plot is
Christina cillo bugam raw Christina with
a K from Hawaii she just like Robbie has
a competitive Health business which can
lend to ulterior motives Christina is
the one you heard calling people in the
medical medium Community vampires and
spreading insane false rumors that she
admittedly didn't have accurate
information on and couldn't have cared
any less but to spread them
anyway Anthony that's not even his real
name by the way I'm not sure if you know
that it's not um it's not no it's not
what is
it um I don't even know I don't care
anymore that's not his real name
though Christina is also the one who
said that she believed there would be a
parting of the Red Seas after the
hitpiece that was fed by the plotters
about Anthony to Vanity Fair came
out I don't know what Megan told you but
it will be interesting to see what the
response is when this comes out you know
yeah what do you think is gonna
happen I think they will be a parting of
the Red
Seas initially and I think that it will
definitely ruffle some feathers and I
think that there will be a large
community of people who share it um I
mean it's coming out B be fair so will
be beely shared no matter
what Christina spent the entirety of my
call with her gossiping about Anthony
and sharing a bunch of absurd rumors
about him with me she admitted that
she'd engaged in name calling and
spreading rumors about Anthony around
the island that she lives on Christina
only said a little bit about Stephanie
and yet every single thing she told me
about Stephanie is provably wrong let's
just say a lot more is going to be
revealed in these
episodes it was very disconcerting for
me as I studied the recording of This
call and compared it with all of the
records of what actually happened with
Stephanie in 2017 to learn that
Christina had absolutely no clue what
happened just like the rest of these
people but that didn't stop Christina
from just saying whatever terrible
things she felt like saying about
Anthony that didn't stop her from
spreading rumors or from wanting to see
him smeared in the media
there are other individuals with health
businesses who are behind this plot to
take Anthony out including a woman named
Taylor call Taylor is the one you heard
in the previous episodes referring to
herself and the other members of this
hateful group as an elite category of
people but I'm letting you know
like we are an elite group of people we
we're in in Elite category
you Taylor is also the one who you heard
saying that she had to commit horrible
acts to get into the inner Inner Circle
of their
group
so well you're not a part of it Amber
you're in the inner Inner
Circle and you know you have to earn
your right to get in that Circle so
there you go you've earned it then
that's a rare spot to me and of course
I've committed horrible acts but you
know you didn't even have to do anything
bad in your ha
that recording gives me PTSD every time
I hear it Taylor was Stephanie's
caretaker that independently took charge
of many of Stephanie's medical decisions
when Stephanie was sick Taylor had
significant influence over Stephanie's
care for example when Stephanie would
get medical testing or
not interestingly Taylor has been
entirely hidden and omitted from the
stories that are told by Ashley
Stephanie's brother and the other
plotters about Stephanie Taylor was also
entirely hidden and omitted from the
Vanity Fair article even though she was
a source that the journalists spoke to
but now in this series you will get to
hear the truth the facts and the
evidence of Taylor's role in what was
happening with Stephanie that alone
makes the narrative the plotters tried
to run with
impossible when Taylor tried to tell me
what happened with Stephanie from her
perspective not only have I now studied
all of the evidence that proves her
wrong which is going to be exposed in
this series but the number of times
Taylor said to me on recording in
regards to the facts of the story I
don't know it's all a blur I can't
remember or it doesn't matter is
appalling I had multiple calls with
Robbie and Taylor individually and
together and what you're about to hear
is just a few examples from just one of
those calls when Taylor was explaining
her version of the Stephanie story me
and Robbie was chiming
in she she' come for some kind of
program that I can't remember as I told
you I was looking or maybe I didn't tell
you this I can't remember somehow I
can't remember how um and so he called
Stephanie and asked her if she would
handle all that or maybe Anthony's wife
did I can't remember there was something
a dis I can't remember exactly what he
said but the bottom line was he told her
she need to light lay flat and not move
so somehow I managed which I can't even
remember how I had to get a nurse there
to give her blood test and the blood
didn't show up I can't remember but
there was things that were off um I
maybe it was the liver enzymes and you
know I don't know but I don't remember
it's all blur so
um and a lot of it is a blur for me and
I don't remember exactly what you wrote
but at some point you know I was in
touch with him um directly and I don't
know the timeline like again I don't
know the time this is all just a blur to
me what the [ __ ] was it doesn't even
matter all right well whatever but you
know whatever you know whatever fine
whatever she had the L okay you know
these things Escape me sometimes um well
escapes me at the moment yeah there was
something
else is it a week I
can't when you take a story to a
mainstream Media company about somebody
who died with the expressed intent of
causing harm to somebody else's
reputation it's all a blur I don't know
I don't know the timeline these things
Escape me sometimes it doesn't matter is
all completely and entirely
unacceptable on calls that I had with
Robbie and Taylor together they were
even arguing with each other about
critical details that they couldn't even
keep straight and that neither one of
them ended up being accurate
about also pause real quick that there
PR all this there was
also where her health was what happened
in this last month was developing for
years okay and there was a time when she
was in LA and you can hear this from Ash
when when you talk to Ash Amber
hopefully you do um her her nipples were
bleeding no no her nipples didn't start
bleeding until she had a lump and she
asked Anthony about the lump and he said
it was okay yeah but this is this is
long before long before exactly but they
didn't start bleeding until she was in
Pennsylvania so she was I don't know ask
whatever fine whatever she had the lump
okay she had the lump
okay there is so much to unpack in just
this audio alone that we're going to do
more thoroughly later on in this series
but basically they're talking about
Stephanie's breast lump Robbie is trying
to claim that Stephanie's nipples
started bleeding a year before Stephanie
discovered her breast lump in 2017 and
instead during a time that Stephanie
stayed nights with Ashley in LA in 2016
which doesn't even make sense and is
provably wrong as we unpacked in a
previous episode one of Stephanie's
nipples not both started bleeding on
October 15th of 2017 it's documented in
text messages it happened 6 months after
Stephanie discovered her breast lump 6
months after Anthony and his wife
immediately told Stephanie to get her
lump assessed by her physician 6 months
after Stephanie had been telling the
both of them that she was under the care
of a doctor for her breast lump but in
fact was
not Robbie said this though because
Ashley's original false story about
Stephanie included reference to that
short time in
2016 Ashley's told so many fake stories
about Stephanie that he's getting them
confused and has no idea what he's
talking about that's why he's saying ask
Ash I hope you talk to Ash Taylor tries
to correct Robbie and says no no no
Stephanie's nipples didn't start
bleeding until after after she had the
lump a year after the timeline you're
talking about she was in Pennsylvania
not la which is true but then Taylor
added in a huge falsity that comes
directly and exactly from Ashley's
original false story about Stephanie
that is a lie that we've addressed and
that we're going to debunk even further
in this
series Robbie gets palpably upset that
he was challenged by Taylor when he was
literally wrong about one of the most
basic facts
of the timeline and then they both just
resort to I don't know ask Ash they're
also both saying nipples as in plural
just like Ashley did in her original
false story when really it was only one
nipple that bled even the article
accurately described it as only being
one
nipple Taylor and Robbie are both wrong
very wrong they're both referencing
Ashley's story they're both confused
they're deferring to Ashley and Ashley
is more wrong than any of them this is
why Ashley's original false story about
Stephanie from 2020 still matters
greatly it is what all of these people
have clearly been brainwashed with all
these years and it is what they're still
going off of to this day in these
upcoming episodes you're going to see
that they've had to manipulate and mold
cherry-picked and otherwise altered
messages to fit what they could try to
piece together from Ashley's original
false storyline while they've hidden all
of the evidence that proves her and them
wrong somehow Ashley has been positioned
by this group as the leader and the
ultimate Authority on
Stephanie as will become extensively
clear in these episodes Ashley is far
from a valid Authority on Stephanie or
really much else for that
matter another individual with a health
business involved with this group is a
woman named Gretchen manzer Gretchen is
the one who you heard saying that there
were statements she had made to the
journalist that she didn't fully stand
behind
100% Gretchen is also the one who you
heard commenting on how strange it was
that what suddenly turned Robbie against
Anthony years and years after Stephanie
passed away was when he suddenly watched
the documentary that Ashley's husband
was the cinematographer for which was
about a fugitive and an ex con who
committed actual crimes and had nothing
to do with
Anthony it was funny when Robbie had
like the realization after she met we're
like welcome Robbie like where have you
been you know but yeah it's so weird how
for him it just like it's like the Click
of a finger you know did you watch that
documentary I did yeah yeah um but I I
heard that like Sarma feels really
misrepresented like she doesn't feel
like that it was
how she wanted her story to be told yeah
interesting um yeah but it's so funny
how he watched that and
then like it just all clicked into
place as you just heard again this was a
documentary they expressed using as a
model for what they wanted to do to
Anthony and Gretchen says here that the
very documentary they revered as a model
is one that a main subject feels really
misrepresented by as Gretchen was
telling me her version of the Stephanie
story she admitted that it was hard for
her to keep all of the facts and
timelines
straight and
um it just it just took me so long and
sorry the story is kind of it's just so
many layers and components and timelines
and it's hard to get it all
straight during my calls with this group
that Robbie organized and prompted me to
engage him by the way not the other way
around Robbie was so boastful about this
plot and what he had done that he was
just spewing information and divulging
details to me left and right completely
unprovoked one of the details he
divulged was a ranked list he spouted
off of who in the group was most
responsible for the Vanity Fair hit
piece I I will definitely take
responsibility for one I've been one of
the people that's been pushing for this
if you want to take the list people of
why this article's coming out and why
it's coming out in a um mainstream
publication is number one Ash is the
number one responsible I would be number
two Tony would be number three and Megan
would be number four it was us four who
like decided this needs to
happen as you just heard Robbie named
Tony as the number three person
responsible for the plot Tony is
Stephanie's brother Tony has admitted
that he's in charge of Stephanie's phone
and he's therefore responsible for all
of the content that has been manipulated
Twisted hidden and otherwise distorted
to try to frame Anthony and coordinate
with Ashley's original false
story for example you're going to learn
in this series that Dan Adler the
journalist spent an entire year writing
about Stephanie based on what was said
and provided to him by Tony and the
other plotters yet Dan did not know that
Anthony and his wife had texted
Stephanie and said that she should
always see a physician for her breast
lump right away the very next day right
after Stephanie first discovered her
lump in March of
2017 Dan remains completely unaware of
this critical text message that in and
of itself disproved the narrative the
plotter sold him on all throughout his
writing process as was reflected in
Dan's initial questions to Anthony there
is documented evidence that Dan was
entirely unaware of this critical text
message as well as a lot of other
critical evidence that should have been
on Stephanie's phone for a whole year
all the way up until Dan first reached
out to Anthony about the article and
Anthony had to be the one to inform him
but Dan didn't reach out for Anthony's
side until right before Dan was planning
on publishing his hit piece and had
already formed the story Anthony had to
be the one to inform Dan that he had the
entire narrative wrong and was missing
critical evidence but only had the
opportunity to do so in response to Dan
sending Anthony hundreds and hundreds of
clearly biased questions with a deadline
of five days to respond to after Dan had
already invested a year of his time into
the other side and their false
story there's a good chance that most
likely Dan would have dropped the
article if he knew earlier on that the
day after Stephanie found the breast
lump that my wife and I told Stephanie
that she should always see a physician
if Dan knew this it would have been a
shocker because he was also told the
same old Ashley lie which was that I
never told Steph to see a doctor but Dan
was too deep into the article too much
time and money had been invested and Dan
was buried in Ashley Foster's falsities
and lies and everybody had a save face
and just put an article
out and that doesn't even scratch the
surface of what Tony is culpable for
hiding and distorting in efforts to
rewrite history portray a narrative that
doesn't exist in reality and frame
Anthony to get a documentary deal all of
which is going to be thoroughly exposed
in this series Tony is the one you heard
Robbie insulting and describing as being
lowc
conscious Tony might be tough because
he's he's a he's not a he's not a uh
conscious I wouldn't say as an involved
Soul as we
are Robbie also describe Tony as not
being
levelheaded Tony Tony could be a little
bit more on the edge he might not be so
levelheaded but everybody else have
levelheaded if the plotters are saying
that Tony is not levelheaded that's
really saying
something next up is a woman named Megan
Elizabeth who Robbie identified as being
the number four person most responsible
for this plot Megan outed Tony for
having multiple fake accounts that he
uses to stalk and spy on the medical
medium
Community it's interesting to see how
his inner circle handles it too like I'm
not always paying attention to that
stuff but Tony has
like other profiles that he's in these
groups and he watches what they're
saying we have since observed this group
using fake accounts to try to influence
public opinion spread lies across the
internet and make it look like they have
more support than they actually do this
is far from the behavior of honest
people with an honest story to tell
Megan also outed Tony for constantly
watching Anthony and wanting to take
Anthony
down I mean
there
yeah I mean Tony's like
he's been Relentless about this like
since stuff passed like just you know we
have to do something about this and he's
constantly watching Anthony
and just grabbing every little bit of
information that he thinks could be
helpful to take him
down and Megan is also the one you heard
in previous episodes saying we need to
get this guy off the internet and just
take it all
down holy [ __ ] we need to get this guy
off the internet like we need to just
take it all
down Megan has been working with Tony on
this for a long time trying to use
cherry-picked contents on a deceased
person's phone who's no longer here to
speak for herself so that they can craft
false story lines that frame Anthony
when we spoke last year Megan claimed to
have seen everything on Stephanie's
phone I've listened to her entire phone
listen to all their voice messages back
and
forth yet when Megan described her
version of the Stephanie story to me I
really listened with an open mind and
wanted to understand where she was
coming from but it quickly became
abundantly clear that Megan just like
the rest of this hateful group had no
idea what she was talking about she was
wishy-washy and confused about every
detail and she even got the most basic
key facts of the story
wrong I can't remember if it was skin
stuff or what it was yeah um I don't
know that she really ever went to see a
doctor when she started working with
Anthony
see I can't remember if he recommended
the chiropractor or if she suggested it
and then it never turned out or
something
um I'm trying to
remember I think so when it was just a
back
injury
um I'm trying to remember if there was
like any push for a doctor at that point
um I can't remember if it was the same
um can't remember the other people okay
so I can't remember this woman's name um
but I don't I don't remember exactly
what it was um definitely Taylor all the
time I don't know how much she was
keeping up with Robie at the time Taylor
like I don't know if she flew out there
right away or what happened but I didn't
know what that name I didn't know
recognize the name and I don't know if
stuff was on that call I don't know if
she was saying he's saying it's not true
or she was saying it was not true as
you're going through the timeline
of of everyone's story there's so much
happening and it's hard to keep track of
what happened
when there is so much wrong with all of
this too it's ridiculous Stephanie was
not working with Anthony as a client
first of all the most concerning thing
here is Megan saying that she doesn't
know if Stephanie saw a doctor when
there is evidence all over Stephanie's
text threads demonstrating that while
Stephanie made the decision to avoid
seeing a doctor for her breast lump even
after Anthony and his wife repeatedly
encouraged her to do so Stephanie was
seeing multiple doctors for her back
injury and other concurrent health
problems it's one of the most key facts
of the entire story for somebody who
said that they've seen everything on
Stephanie's phone that level of
ignorance is highly problematic IC as a
reminder my recorded call with Megan and
my recorded calls with the other sources
for the article took place after the
article had already been written and
right before it was
published at that stage the article was
already done and they still couldn't get
anything right they got every key fact
so painfully and provably wrong Megan
like Gretchen at least admitted that she
was confused and that all of the
different text threads and timelines
were hard for her to keep track of how
dare you be that uncertain on what
happened with Stephanie yet so sure that
all the work that Anthony has done to
help and support the chronically ill for
decades should be taken down how dare
you take a story that you're that
uncertain about and text messages that
you admittedly don't even understand or
have organized to a media company to
smear someone a story that they
admittedly had to hammer into the head
of the journalist because even he was
having a hard time wrapping his head
around a lot of it as Robbie said a
story that they had to biasedly shape by
pointing him here and pointing him there
and that they had to threaten him to get
him to publish Megan was right about one
thing though there is a lot going on
with all of Stephanie's text threads
that document what was happening and
that is why we're going to be here for a
long time unpacking it all factually and
all of the other data that we have Tony
has had access to Stephanie's phone
since before she passed away in 2018 and
now for nearly 6 years since Megan has
been a part of this with Tony and has
had access to the phone again for a long
long time there is no excuse for any of
the plotters being as ignorant as they
are still to this day to the facts and
the evidence we've now spent the past
year doing the homework that this group
was not willing to do to get it right
it's so quick and easy to hurl out lies
and misinformation to cherry-pick and
misappropriate text messages and to say
what you feel like about somebody
whereas it takes a lot of time and
energy to be factually correct to get it
right and to prove this unbelievably
diluted hateful group wrong with
evidence but we are going to do it time
and time again as often as we need
to of course when people pass away
sometimes there are loved ones who have
a hard time accepting what really
happened and want to find someone to
blame in fact there's a documented
record of one of the plotters admitting
in years past that they believed this
whole thing to stem from Tony looking
for someone to blame but there's no
excuse for manipulating and hiding
evidence to try to rewrite history frame
someone and smear them online and in the
media and none of this would have played
out this way or have been taken this far
if it weren't for Ashley and
Robbie so let me to
you and to be honest um again 100%
transparent Ash and I in being the two
people that taught like Tony and Megan
had with the [ __ ] right the whole
podcast thing was just dumb so dumb um
we had to kind of like educate them and
convince them he this is a better route
to go and then just text with us four
kind of funny back in the day but
anyways um the intention and action I
had is that it's going a Netflix series
like bad vegan will be made about
Anthony and it will be a [ __ ] hit
because what he pulled off is
unbelievable I the celebrity angle like
this thing this Netflix version is gonna
go boners it's gonna take many many
years to get there I mean I mean to to
produce like that tastes years but it'll
still be just like the bad Deegan thing
like how many years ago did that whole
thing actually happened versus like when
the the movie came out or the or the
Netflix came out like this is this gonna
happen holy
[ __ ] there's going to be a documentary
about it all that's our vision I mean
it's not we first get to publish the
article and then once the article is
published then people start bidding on
the piece so just you know again um I
guess um The Hills article I just sent
you yeah is being made into a
documentary okay so Dan Adler and this
whole whole Vanity Fair people they have
a history of producing something that is
you know well done you know done well
enough to um be turned into um a
documentary of some sort holy [ __ ] he's
GNA look real bad it's going to look
real
bad this is what they tried to recruit
me with the promise of a big Netflix
documentary
deal these main plotters have recruited
others to join them over the years and
there are other individuals involved
that will be exposed throughout this
series and then we have Dan Adler who
really should be called a plotter too at
this point because we have so much
evidence that we're going to release of
just how deeply he was in cahoots with
this group Dan is the writer at Vanity
Fair that the plotter specifically
sought out to do this hit piece with the
premeditated goal from day one of It
ultimately leading to a documentary deal
for them on June 1st of last year a
couple weeks after the article and our
podcast episodes came out Dan Adler did
a very unusual very brief 21-minute
interview as a guest on a small podcast
that sole Focus us is criticizing and
disparaging people in the health and
wellness industry further proving Dan's
bias shockingly again after the article
was published Dan admitted in this
interview that he was confused about
everything he had written about
regarding
Anthony but I think one thing that also
came across in the text messages that I
reported on and many of the
conversations I had with sources is that
a lot of it is just very confusing
there's a lot of information being
conveyed there's a lot of jargon being
used there are lots of supplements
talking to sources about their
interpretation of the information more
than anything else I think there's just
a lot of confusion there's a lot of the
sense of if I could just understand
what's being conveyed through this
figure who's portraying himself as as I
say in the story just under God I could
just understand what the message is that
would help me but when you try to look
at what the message is it's very very
murky
that is
something from a journalist first I from
a journalist exactly from the journalist
that had already written the piece he's
confused about everything and first I
have to address what Dan said in here
about how he wrote in his hit piece that
Anthony portrays himself to be just
under God Anthony has absolutely never
said that he is just under God and he
does not portray himself in that way
that is an Ashley Foster talking point
that she has been misappropriating and
mischaracterizing Anthony with for years
to serve her own agenda clearly that
must have been one of the many things
that Ashley and Robbie had to give Dan
Direction on and Hammer into his head as
that is not something that Anthony has
ever said or published not once
apparently Dan didn't properly research
or fact check his work and just adopted
provably false narratives from this
group
secondly he said that what he was
reporting on was just very confusing and
he thinks there's just a lot of
confusion yeah Dan your sources were
confused and that's why it was confusing
to you too and they were confused
because they didn't know the story of
what really happened and because Ashley
Foster has been lying about it so much
since day one and if what was being
presented to Dan seemed that murky and
was really all that confusing why on
Earth would he go through with
publishing an article on a story that he
was that unclear on or at least why on
Earth spend a whole year writing a story
you're uncertain about and then only
reach out to Anthony after it's already
been
formed I would imagine that to be
because Dan like many journalists these
days was not really interested in the
truth so you've got this crazy toxic and
unprecedented combination of a brother
who's looking for someone to blame
sources who don't even know what
happened admittedly can't keep track of
the timeline and don't have their fact
straight you've got a journalist who's
admittedly confused and still to this
day doesn't even understand the subject
matter he wrote about sources and a
journalist that are all relying on
Ashley Foster as the ultimate Authority
on Stephanie when Ashley as you'll learn
in the series was not around for what
happened with Stephanie at all
admittedly barely even spoke to
Stephanie during the time period that
this is all about in 2017 has been
caught flat out lying about Stephanie
and the original conjured up story
Ashley posted that they're all still
running with to this day had dozens of
verifiable falsities in it including the
one you heard Robbie and Taylor repeat
and that's why Ashley scrubbed it from
the internet when she got a legal letter
in
2020 you've got a journalist who was
somehow conveniently unaware of the text
messages that were on Stephanie's phone
that disproved the entire narrative he
was sold on for the whole year he spent
writing his story you've got sources
that expressly want to take Anthony down
have a vested interest in being part of
getting a Netflix documentary deal
sources that also have other documented
ulterior motives that are going to be
uncovered for the first time in these
episodes a journalist that has a vested
interest in securing a big Netflix
documentary deal using his story sources
who admitted to shaping the article
themselves by giving the journalist a
lot of direction for the piece having to
hammer their narrative into his head
Point him here and point him there and
threaten him to get him to publish it if
there were ever a perfect recipe for
corruption and dishonesty this would be
it again this is one of the biggest
scandals that has ever happened in the
health industry this group has been
using abusing and exploiting Stephanie's
name and Legacy as a means to an end
this was certainly never about the truth
for them if you're confused you do not
get to fill in the gaps as you want to
if you can't get the facts or the
timeline straight you're not in a valid
position to tell a story let alone to
take it to a media company if you're
unaware of even the most basic key facts
of what really happened you have
absolutely no business perpetuating a
story that you don't understand
they tried to get away with lying and
getting it wrong using Anthony's name
they try to get away with lying and
getting it wrong using Stephanie's name
to serve their own agenda because she's
not here to speak for herself they try
to get away with grossly misrepresenting
medical medium and the community to
serve their own agenda and none of it is
going to stand lies inaccurate
information plotting and scheming will
only ever get you so far
and the full actual truth is coming out
in this
series so Dan the journalist published
his hit piece we came out with our first
few podcast episodes that began the
process of exposing the corruption and
collusion that took place between the
media company and the plotters an we
began to expose the plotter ulterior
motives their goal from the beginning
was not to Simply put their version of a
story out there that they beli to be
true their goal was categorically to
take medical medium and the community
down the response to the podcasts was
massive and I just want to issue a huge
thank you to everyone for all of the
support we have received through all of
the craziness so many people were
devastated by the fact that the plotters
could be so intentionally poisonous to
go so low as to use a manipulated story
of a deceased woman to try to injure a
community of people who were just trying
to heal I read through many comments
from people who were shocked and
outraged by the voices they recognized
as being behind this the fact that
something so dark is coming from people
who portray themselves to be very
different there were also a lot of
people who came forward to share their
own experiences with the plotters one of
them is a woman named Melody Pence who
has been applying medical medium
information for several years and knew
some of the plotters personally
following the release of our first ever
podcast about this group Melody took to
her Instagram stories to share about
attempts that were made to recruit her
including even before Ashley came out
with her original false story in
2020 so when I listened to the podcast I
could not believe what I was hearing as
you guys could not believe what you were
hearing either and what I recognized
right away was Robbie barbaro's voice so
clear I mean it's a voice that
um if you know him if you talk to him if
you've been around him you're going to
pick up on his voice it's a very
distinctive voice and what I knew Robbie
as is someone who is very charismatic on
the outside seemed like a pure genuine
soul to me I looked up to him I thought
he was an amazing person um and so when
I heard him talking like that on the
medical
medium uh podcast that Anthony just
released I I saw his true colors and it
was shocking it was shocking to realize
that someone that you thought um was a
good person and had so much Prisma on
the outside and portrayed that they
wanted to help others is not like that
honestly it was it was so shocking that
it took me like a full day to like
recover from that and and um and and and
what's interesting about Robbie is he
comes off as such a positive vibe been
wanting to help people but something
that I brought up um in my last stories
was when I met Robbie in gosh 2016 I'm
not sure when it was when Anthony did
his event in LA and um and I uh I was
there I got interviewed by Robbie and I
remember he told me at one point he said
um you know just focus on the food focus
on the food and it's like when he said
that I felt a lack of compassion because
I he had just interviewed me about my
story the strugg struggles I'd been
through um and you know I had a lot of
failures a lot of heartbreak and then to
hear just focus on the food to just
focus on the food for my Instagram right
that I pretty sure that's that's exactly
what he was saying like he didn't he
didn't really just he didn't want to
hear about like someone's struggles or
pain exactly was just like yeah focus on
the food which is crazy cuz that's not
even what the chronically ill is about
and he does help chronically ill people
he helps people with diabetes you know
and so right there is just a red flag of
lacking compass and also speaking of um
this Elite group right um and being
recruited that they talk about in the
video my nose is just so bad right now
but um um I I remember right let's see
when shortly after he moved to Miami in
2020 when Co happened I all of a sudden
like noticed that he was watching my
stories and I was like why like that's
weird like we follow each other but um
he never communicates with me I don't
communicate with him and then all of a
sudden one day he was just watching my
stories a lot then I get a DM from him
completely unexpected and it basically
is inviting me to go to Miami and stay
at his house that he has a guest bedroom
blah blah blah um this and that and I
was just like hm that's weird and in my
gut feeling at that time I was like well
this isn't a romantic interest like what
does he want you know what I mean and
and now looking back it all makes sense
it all makes sense that they were
recruiting people um someone dm' me
yesterday and said that uh they did his
program and that they've been around him
before and that he always has females
coming in and out of his house he's
always surrounded by females and it's
that's odd right thank God I didn't go
and um but now I realize it it could
have been because he was trying to
recruit me and turn me against mm which
would never happen so I found out about
Ashley Foster through um one I just I
knew that things were getting weird with
this group and I'm about to go into this
um Ashley's
group and like a couple years ago um
gosh in 2018 when I moved back to Hawaii
um Gretchen lived there she invited me
over um I didn't I don't think I
realized before I went to her house how
against mm she was I was just going
there to like meet a familiar face cuz
Gretchen was a part of reclaimers of
Health in 2016
17 so I still thought maybe oh maybe
like she's still doing mm you know
whatever so anyways I go to her house
and she tries to she talks to me about
how bad Anthony is how bad mm is and
basically trying to turn me against mm
well I never saw her again after that we
lived on the same island I I never
contacted her nothing it was just such a
turn off to me and the other thing that
she was talking about was Ashley and
basically referring to Ashley as if
she's some type of idol some type of God
because Gretchen worshiped her I mean
she did sorry Gretchen if you're seeing
this but you did and like everything
Ashley did was amazing and and and
Ashley was the one that had a heavy
influence on
Gretchen and made Gretchen like really
not like mm so much so what does that
say and here now we're seeing her
resurface and a couple years ago
Ashley's Instagram got shut down because
she was blaming Anthony for her friend's
death um verbally announcing it on
Instagram and everything and and now she
is and what's crazy is Ashley um was at
the um the mm event in La the same T
place I met Robbie I knew they were good
friends cuz they just stuck to each
other and hung out together the entire
time Ashley's husband was doing the
video for interviewing people he was the
cameraman when he when Robbie
interviewed me okay and so this is just
comes full circle you know what I mean
um o my blood's starting to boil so
anyways um also in the p real quick in
the podcast they talk about how they
have someone that can do the video well
guess who you think that is I mean I'm
just speaking for my own intuition here
but come on like I'm sure it's her
husband recording for the documentary I
don't know but that's thing and I
remember when I saw Ashley I was excited
to meet her cuz she had a lot of what
seemed like light about her she was
Smiley happy just seemed so like nice
but then what I realized is when I met
her excuse me um she like really didn't
hardly even say hi to me anything I mean
and then I realized she's like that with
her friends she's like that with her
friends cuz I was like Oh I thought she
was so nice like okay and then I just
see her with her circle of friends and I
was like hm and that was my f that was
my first
impression but she will play the victim
card very well very well so don't get
fooled by who knows who the three
younger recruits are h M so who knows
but um I wanted to share everything with
y'all and I'm not done yet but I wanted
to share everything with y'all so you
could gather the information too and
just see like okay what's going on here
you know
and and uh during that time is just when
I started realizing there was a whole
bunch of group of people against mm um
simply because who knows why they're not
happy
so Robbie's in the on the podcast and
then of course ra
Christina um she says The Parting of the
Red Seas that is
disgusting that is disgusting she is
someone who preaches spiritualism who
preaches peace and love and happiness
and healing and health and then she's
behind this directly orchestrating how
she's going to take down mm are you
kidding me and the reason I know this is
because if you have followed her if you
have watched many of her YouTube videos
if you were a follower of her trying to
heal then you will recognize her voice
when you listen closely so baffling to
me is these people right that
are have high high following numbers
who's supposed to be what they come off
as to help people get healthy and well
they want to wipe out the chronically
ill
community so you want to wipe out people
that you are actually pretending that
you help so if you're about green juices
and fruits and vegetables and people
getting their health back you don't
really care if you're going to try to
take down an entire
community that is Sinister I've also
gotten um so many messages from you guys
and some of you guys have said Taylor is
in the video the one that says oh I have
to do really really bad things to get
here that's three people Robbie
Christina five and either Taylor Britney
or someone else and again this is just
from what I've seen in my personal
experience who I've talked to personally
how it evolved for me was through
Gretchen um and and yeah since then it's
just I've had a huge a awareness about
people trying to take down mm because of
what's happened so I hope this clears is
clears things up and I'm super tired cuz
I have so much brain fog but let me know
okay you guys want to know like what
else I think is so um Sinister about
this people that are called first of all
they call themselves Elite so what does
that tell you you know what I mean the
only person that Elite is Elite to me is
God um in Jesus Christ the Holy Spirit
and that is a huge red flag number one
that they're calling themselves Elite
that's just that should be enough that's
enough for me right there and then the
thing is is that they're saying oh I had
to do you have to do bad things to get
into this group and then she's talking
to Amber oh but you didn't have to do
anything and you're here hah and it's
like what does that sound like yeah that
sounds like a cult to me that sounds
like um something that you have to be a
part of that's Elite that you have to do
bad things to join and it sounds very
very dark to me what about you you guys
you know honestly what that made me
think of once I got over the shock of
I'm still in shock of Who's involved
honestly but it's it's just so crystal
clear that um yeah I mean now I know who
these people are so the shock is lifting
and then a couple days later after our
second episode came out Melody posted
this but I've been online um and seen
some people like just really talking
crap about medical medium and it's just
really not cool it's it's really not
cool it's
like I'm going to be straight up and
because I'm exhausted and I'm just a
person that doesn't have really a lot of
filter these days cuz I am working my
ass off and I'm fried so here I go um
but you know people that want to talk
[ __ ] and talk like bad about somebody
who's doing something amazing have
nothing going on in their lives there's
a lack of faith on this planet that is
so massive that and so many people have
trauma and like things that have
happened to them that they want to blame
someone for and instead of looking
within and like you know fixing their
own life they have to like try to bring
someone else
down later on in this series more is
going to be shared about Melody's
experiences which very much align with
my own experiences with this
group as the content and evidence from
all the upcoming episodes unfolds you're
going to see just how spot-on Melody is
especially about the dynamic of this
group how they worship and idolize
Ashley Foster and the influence that
Ashley specifically has had upon them
turning against medical medium over the
years and the other thing that she was
talking about was Ashley and basically
referring to Ashley as if she's some
type of idol some type of God because
Gretchen worshiped her I mean she did
sorry Gretchen if you're seeing this but
you did and like everything Ashley did
was amazing and and and Ashley was the
one that had a heavy influence on
Gretchen and made Gretchen like really
not like mm so
much you're going to see that Ashley has
been lying and plotting and scheming for
years for ulterior reasons while
pretending to be a
whistleblower Ashley so badly wanted to
position herself as a leader and a guru
and get attention for that under the
guise of being an advocate on top of the
lies and falsi she's already been caught
telling as well as the many more lies
and falsities of hers that are going to
be exposed in these episodes one of the
biggest giveaways that Ashley is
completely disingenuous is the fact that
she has now spent the entire past year
relentlessly belittling harassing body
shaming name calling and attacking the
very people she claims to be advocating
for the chronically ill
Ashley got sloppy and put her true
character and intentions on public
display which is purely to cause harm to
Anthony and the medical medium community
and there is no low that she won't stoop
to in her
efforts any journalist or Media company
that takes Ashley Foster and her
organized hateful group seriously is a
joke and a sham anyone who platforms a
group that is lying spewing hatred
burning books and calling for another
human being to be exterminated by fire
is
Despicable and Melody wasn't the only
one with the story to share a lot of
people have come forward with all kinds
of information and evidence which will
be discussed throughout these upcoming
episodes last year following the release
of the previous podcast episodes there
was also something really suspicious
that occurred immediately after the
episodes were released my computer which
of course had the recordings on it was
hacked I have never in my life had
anything like that happened prior but
all of the sudden right after our
podcast started coming out one night I
was sitting at my desk about a foot away
from the computer using my phone while
my desktop computer screen was idle
suddenly out of the corner of my eye I
noticed that something had taken over my
computer and a bunch of my files were
being pulled up at lightning speed I
realized that somebody had hacked into
my computer and was looking through my
files extremely rapidly my gut reaction
was to just shut down and unplug the
computer immediately and thankfully I
learned later that that's exactly what
you're supposed to do in that situation
as it removes a hacker's access I was
able to catch and interrupt the attempt
right
away now hacking into someone's computer
is obviously not only a privacy
violation but it's also massively
illegal and it says everything about the
character and the desperation of the
person who did it or had someone do it
for them I had to get a new computer and
I had to replace other devices like my
phone that were compromised by the
Hacked Wi-Fi and I had to move because I
no longer felt comfortable living where
I was living I consulted with some
experts and I was told that you have to
know someone's location in order to hack
them like that so it easily could have
happened again can't say for sure who
did it yet but one of the plotters knew
where I lived
I've had Specialists investigating the
situation and supporting me with
security on my new devices it seems to
me like someone wanted those recordings
really
badly the recordings serve as critical
evidence of the identity of the plotters
because their whole plan was to go
through with this anonymously and
conceal their identities so that they
couldn't be held accountable for the
false information they were using the
media to spread they serve as critical
evidence of the plot's own ranking
system of the top people who are most
responsible for the plot and the
recordings serve as critical evidence of
the malicious intentions behind the
plotters the verifiably false
information that they've tried to use to
recruit people the recruitment tactics
the verifiably false information they
fed to the media
as well as a very serious corruption and
collusion between the plotters and the
media company that they sold false
stories too and there's so much more
from the recordings that we are going to
be
releasing yes and as such Ashley and the
other plotters did everything that they
could to try to discredit the recordings
and the podcast episodes but it's really
hard to walk yourself out of what you
said in your own
words after the podcast came out Ashley
started behaving very erratically she
kept frantically changing her profile
over and over again she called Anthony
and I both obnoxious names she kept
posting and deleting things she issued a
statement that she was quote proud to be
a plotter and then she deleted it Ashley
then continued on with her pattern of
Simply pivoting when proven wrong she
started spreading new versions of false
stories about about Stephanie and other
plotters followed suit they combined
their pivoted new and updated false
narratives about Stephanie with other
types of false information about medical
medium and the community absolutely
anything they could piece together and
fabricate to try to disparage medical
medium Robbie and Christina were both
reportedly caught deleting comments and
blocking anyone who recognized their
voices and asked them about their
involvement with this plot to take
Anthony and the community down numerous
other individuals have been caught lying
about their involvement which is going
to be exposed Ashley even tried to
Gaslight people by claiming that things
everyone heard the plotter say very
clearly that can't mean anything else in
any other context were not said and then
a couple months after the attempt to
hack into my computer was unsuccessful
another suspicious event occurred some
of you may have noticed that our
previous four podcast episodes came down
from Apple in the fall of last year
Ashley Foster instantly started
spreading rumors that they were taken
down because they contained illegal
recordings this became her favorite
deflection tactic and false
claim once Ashley posted a screenshot of
a message she had gotten that says the
plot thickens the plotter podcasts from
this year are gone not sure if you knew
that and Ashley
replied I did yes
they were removed by Apple because they
contained illegal
recordings this is not true and I'm
happy to report that the podcast
episodes became available again on Apple
in January of this year ironically
shortly after Ashley posted this falsity
it's important for everyone to know what
really happened a law firm whose client
was kept Anonymous filed a strange vague
claim with apple demanding the podcast
be taken down Apple sent my team an
email just to alert us of the claim and
to give us the ability to dispute it
unfortunately this email somehow went to
spam so my team did not see it in time
we found out later that Apple has a
policy that they only give you 5 days to
respond otherwise they just
automatically remove the content by
default because my team didn't see the
email that is what happened they were
removed by default after 5 days had
passed but this whole time they've
always remained up on every other
platform because nothing was actually
wrong with the episodes it was just a
fluke that the email alert went to spam
so we couldn't dispute it in time
anybody can file a claim even if it's
unfounded and inaccurate and if my team
would have seen the email we would have
been able to provide evidence to refute
the claim
immediately we were very upset when we
realized that the podcast episodes were
unjustly removed from Apple due to a m
fluke Apple told us we needed to first
try and deal with the law firm that
requested the podcast to be taken down
but that law firm refused to engage with
us and ignored our Outreach we informed
apple and then Apple ended up
investigating the claim after this
thorough investigation Apple concluded
that there is absolutely nothing wrong
with the podcast episodes and that the
recordings are in fact legal the
episodes were restored to Apple in
January and they all still remain up on
every other
platform as I've said all along the
recordings were legally obtained and
that has now been confirmed by Apple
itself in its restoration of our
episodes once again Ashley Foster is
wrong and her claims are false even
Apple itself has now proved Ashley wrong
Anthony posted about this ridiculous
ordeal in January and one commenter said
hm so who was the anonymous person this
Law Firm acted on behalf of that's what
I want to know but there are not many
options are there kind of obvious who
would go to such lengths to get it taken
down it seems as though the claim that
was filed with apple was another attempt
to suppress our ability to defend the
truth and disprove the attacks and the
false narrative this organized hateful
group is responsible for for but such
attempts are not going to stand we are
going to continue unraveling their
contrived stories lies tactics
disinformation and more the behavior
this organized hateful group has
exhibited which we've only just
scratched the surface of in this episode
is beyond scandalous I've never
experienced such little regard for the
truth in my life from any individual let
alone a coordinated group of people or
such little regard for how one's
Behavior impacts other
people unfortunately Ashley Foster and
her hateful group have caused very real
harm to many people's real lives in
their pursuit of a documentary deal and
all of the benefits that would come
along with that for them at all costs
and their willingness to just say
anything to get a rise out of people
using Anthony's name it matters greatly
to bring attention to this it matters
greatly for everyone to know what's
really going on here there are many
episodes to come and they're not going
to be able to stop us from defending the
truth some of you may be unaware that
this has even been happening but many of
you have been tremendously injured and
harmed by what this organized hateful
group has done the record needs to be
set straight and they need to be called
out for what they've done and are still
doing the medical medium Community does
not deserve to be attacked like this and
we are going to set the record straight
as many times as we need to we invite
you to have an open mind listen to the
facts learn how they manipulated and
altered data and created falsities and
lies it's a story for the history books
that is truly
unprecedented if you have been harmed
deterred from your healing process
bullied shamed emotionally upset or
physically hurt by flareups of your
conditions from the stress induced by
the plotters attacks like hundreds of
others have been reported please go to
medicalmedium.com
SLS safespace to submit your report and
share your story if you've been
contacted by anyone who's tried to deter
you from using medical medium
information please take screenshots and
Screen recordings and submit them to the
same place medicalmedium.com
safe space