The Following episode is part of a
series dedicated to exposing an
organized hateful group that has been on
a Relentless pursuit to destroy the
medical medium community and that has
been attacking bullying harassing and
preying upon the chronically ill joining
me in the series is a guest named Amber
bakaro she's an alternative medicine
practitioner who became a whistleblower
after she witnessed this hateful group
in action when they tried to recruit her
to join them last year Amber caught the
main members of this group on legally
recorded calls describing their
premeditated multi-step plan to create a
quote postm medal medium era by feeding
false stories and claims about me and
about medical medium information to
Major media outlets in hopes that it
would lead to securing themselves a deal
for an anti-ed medium documentary on
Netflix that would bring Fame and other
benefits to them now known infamously
instead for their malicious plot that
was caught on recording and exposed we
refer to this hateful group as the
plotters their entire smear campaign is
spearheaded by one woman who comes from
an extremely wealthy family didn't get
what she wanted from me years ago and is
now seeking re Revenge she's made it her
mission to gather a bunch of plotters
with ulterior motives and AES to grind
including competitors in the health
industry to try to frame medical medium
and take down the community what this
organized hateful group has done is
unprecedented it's one of the biggest
scandals that's ever happened in the
health industry as you'll see it's also
one of the biggest instances of
capturing corruption within the
mainstream media so prepare yourself for
lots of details and nuances as we are
going to be thoroughly untangling the
massive Web of Lies they have spun and
we're going to be releasing a lot of
disturbing new information new
recordings and mind-blowing evidence of
just how far they are going to lie to
try to get what they want some of the
evidence we're presenting in these
episodes in includes original written
content such as text messages social
media posts that have been produced by
the plots and will be reenacted for
greater ease in following along those
who are listening along to the podcast
can find video versions of these
episodes on the medical medium YouTube
and Rumble channels that will be
displaying screenshots photos videos and
more some of you may be unaware that
this has even been happening but many of
you have been tremendously injured and
harmed by what they have done the record
needs to be set straight and they need
to be called out for what they've done
and are still doing the medical medium
Community does not deserve to be
attacked like this and we are going to
set the record straight as many times as
we need to
[Music]
people who lie are liars if you're
willing to lie about one thing you might
be willing to lie about everything One
Lie calls into question the entirety of
someone's character what about two three
4 100
lies these are words from Ashley Foster
words that she is soon going to eat
because as I've said from the very
beginning what Ashley projects and tries
to accuse other people of being and
doing is usually what she herself is
guilty of being and
doing Ashley is the ring leader of an
organized anti-ed medium hateful group
that she created on a mountain of Lies
Ashley has been lying and attacking
Anthony for years and she has now
incited a group of people that are out
there attacking harassing and bullying
the medical medium community and even
going as far as to make videos of them
eles burning medical medium books okay
all these medical medium books are going
to be burned
today it's
happening this is going in first celery
juice
one I took out the insides because it's
going to take forever to burn why is
Ashley really doing this many have asked
in response to the activities of the
plotters one online commenter said it's
clear there are other motives behind all
this
a different commenter said it's just
full-on Reckless ruthless attacks that
seems like it doesn't have anything to
do with the realities nor facts of our
community just attacks simply to bring
us down utterly nonsensical and
infuriating and another commenter said
it's so clear that there's an agenda I
don't see why anyone would listen to all
their
n so what are Ashley's ulterior motives
what is this really about for her what
type of person is capable of harboring
so much hatred towards someone who does
nothing but help the chronically ill
even long after the madeup story they
tried to use to slander him was proven
to be
false what type of person could be so
painfully entitled and careless so as to
spend years plotting and obsessively
trying to bring Anthony and the entire
medical medium community of chronically
ill people who are already struggling
down
today we're going to be answering these
questions Ashley's true motives are
going to be exposed for the first time
we're going to be revealing some
shocking new facts that are wildly
inconsistent with Ashley's Proclamation
that she's doing this smear campaign
quote #for step to Zone and we're going
to begin exposing some of the many many
more lies that Ashley has told since the
release of our podcast episodes last
year you may recall that in our previous
episodes we played the following
recording of Taylor call and Robbie
Barbaro describing their friend and the
number one plotter Ashley
Foster and by the way Ash do need to
work Ash ever ever the woman is she
family money a lot of it you know
private jet and
plus Ashley has since responded to this
part of our podcasts somebody said to
her you are independently wealthy what
is the source of your family's wealth
I'm suspicious because of that and
Ashley
replied my dad grew up without shoes or
electricity his first job was knocking
the cement off off all Briggs for a
penny a brick he worked incredibly hard
harder than anyone else I have ever met
eventually he was able to buy one of the
houses he built for $700
he sold it later for a few thousand he
built another house by hand and sold
that by the time he died at 83 he had
been working in real estate for 60 years
he built and sold houses and eventually
apartment buildings he was able to leave
an amazing Legacy for our family I'm
incredibly proud of him and
grateful that said we don't own a plane
like they said in the podcast we aren't
able to spend money without thinking
about it we don't have vacation homes
like Anthony does we don't have the
ability to pay indefinitely for
aggressive lawyers like Anthony does
we're just able to live a comfortable
life where I can stay home with my kids
and homeschool them my husband works
incredibly hard there's nothing crazy
here we're just blessed and I'm really
really
grateful so Ashley's claiming
specifically that quote we don't have a
plane and quote we don't have vacation
homes she's trying to portray herself as
a victim of Anthony's lawyers saying
that she can't afford ongoing legal
representation of her own and she's
depicting herself as having a simple
humble life just to give you an idea of
how absurd these statements and
characterizations are I'm going to
reference some of the many news articles
that have been published about Ashley's
family a July 2021 article in the Daily
Mail is headlined son of late
billionaire real estate developer Jean
Phillips wages legal battle against his
father's mistress over $6.3 million gift
she claims is
hers the article States in reference to
Ashley's father Jean
Phillips born in South Carolina he
relocated to Dallas buying a 16 acre
property next to George W bush and
making a
$3.5 billion fortune in real estate and
energy The Daily Beast
reported Ashley the number one plotter
as you just heard is the daughter of a
multi-billionaire with a
B Not only was Ashley dishonest about
her family's wealth but she also said
that her father was able to leave an
amazing Legacy for her family and that
she is incredibly proud of of him in
2001 The Wall Street Journal however
described Ashley's father Jean Phillips
using the following
terms Mr Phillips has long been one of
the most controversial figures in
publicly traded real estate which in
that famously eccentric industry is
saying
something according to court documents
and multiple news outlets including the
BBC and the New York Times Ashley's
father was indicted with members of the
mafia in the year
2000 reporting conducted by the BBC
states that members of the five mafia
families in New York are among 120
people who have been charged in the
largest Crackdown on Securities fraud in
US history the defendants were arrested
for their alleged part in Nationwide
stock fraud schemes that caused losses
of more than $50 million over a 5-year
period they used bribery extortion and
even murder threats to pursue the frauds
that reaped millions of dollars in
illegal profits prosecutors said the
defendants include Jean
Phillips the New York Times states that
a familiar name popped up among the
relative unknowns charged with a raft of
misdeeds that included stock
manipulation money laundering and
pension fund fraud Jean Phillips former
head of the South Mark
Corporation in their indictment of Mr
Philips last week prosecutors said he
had caused American realy to issue
preferred stock where 20% of the
proceeds was to be secretly kicked back
to what prosecutors called a criminal
organization Lori Bailey a special agent
for the Federal Bureau of Investigation
in Dallas said that while he awaits
trial Mr Phillips must wear an
electronic monitor his house is so large
however that agents had to install three
monitoring stations where typically one
is needed
Jean did not end up being convicted
however news Outlet records and
litigation documents show that Ashley's
father has been the subject of class
action lawsuits many scandals and many
other types of lawsuits even still to
this day in 2001 The Wall Street Journal
described Ashley's father as being best
remembered as the head of southark Corp
the Dallas real estate conglomerate that
collapsed in 1989 in a swirl of lawsuits
Mr Phillips now presides over a $2
billion
Empire Forbes once reported that
Philip's name does not shine brightly in
real estate circles with his record of
mismanagement South Mark was one of the
largest bankruptcies in US history and
his pension for using public companies
he controls to enrich
himself Forbes also states that Phillips
wo a tangled web bankrupt in 1989 South
markk left more than $1 billion doll in
investor losses his investors lost
heavily Phillips lived lavishly in
Texas just a few weeks ago in this
current year of 2024 d magazine covered
another Scandal involving Ashley's
father in an article titled behind the
$22 million verdict against Jean
Phillips Company the article reports
that Daniel moose the former president
and CEO of pillar income Asset
Management SU sued his former employer
after he was fired and claimed the
company refused to pay him what he was
owed the first Serious Sign of Daniel
Moose's trouble at Pillar income Asset
Management arrived with a document he
had never seen it was a two-page
contract that said moose had signed his
2% stake in a $1.8 billion real estate
deal back to his employer the document
had Dallas real estate executive Jean
Phillips signature and his own but there
was one big problem moose said he had
never signed the contract the allegedly
forged contract was key evidence in a
trial where a jury recently awarded
moose more than $22 million in salary
and real estate compensation after he
sued his former
employer the plaintiff's petition calls
the document in which moose allegedly
signed over his rights to vaa the
doctored letter and says it was created
by taking the signature from a different
document and combining it with a new
cover page
It also says the document was altered by
a typewriter after the fact to reflect
that pillar was a third party to the
agreement with Phillips and moose the
pillar signature lines font differs from
the rest of the
document as it turns out it's an awfully
fragile glass mansion that Ashley is
trying to throw stones from can we play
that last audio
again and by the way Ash didn't need to
work Ash
ever ever the woman is she family money
a lot of it you know private jet and
plus Ashley's closest friends said that
she doesn't have to work and that she
has a lot of family money like private
jet
plus and then Ashley denied their claims
after the podcast came
out that said we don't own a plane like
they said in the podcast we aren't able
to spend money without thinking about it
we don't have vacation homes like
Anthony
does this part is hilarious because
Ashley has always been an aspiring
writer and she had written a piece about
her own life years ago she sent it to
multiple people who have since submitted
evidence to us in this piece in
reference to her family Ashley had said
this
my mother was gorgeous my father was
brilliant and Rich they had cars and
planes and houses all over the
globe brilliant and rich cars and planes
plural and homes all over the globe
furthermore in 2018 Ashley's childhood
home was listed in an article by D
Magazine titled the 100 most expensive
homes in Dallas Alice her family's home
ranked number six at a value at the time
of
29,5 56,0
$320 the house Ashley currently lives in
and posts about on social media in
Colorado is an 80 acre property worth
$10
million Ashley's previous home in
California sold for $73 million and we
know people who have visited multiple
different properties of Ashley's in
different places around the country some
of which are worth close to $13
million once in the process of trying to
purchase a property Ashley had sent a
text to a friend that says the
following our first loan didn't close 2
days before closing the board of the
bank had approved the loan when our
broker got a random call they were
cancelling
it the friend asked was your dad a
backer and Ashley
replied I was in tears and so confused
and he was so pissed off and
Confused my dad looks at the paperwork
and goes oh this Bank never would have
made you alone I sued them for $70
million last year # thanks
Dad the friend said holy LOL
so Ashley's dad a late billionaire had
sued a bank for $70
million but Ashley wants you to believe
that she can't afford a lawyer and that
she is somehow a victim of Anthony's
legal representation because she has
simply been notified that she is
repeatedly spreading verifiably false
information about Anthony and about
medical medium information and she
continues to ignore the facts that have
been presented to her in a different
text Ashley wrote
this we bought an apartment building in
Texas with the help of my
dad Ashley and her husband bought an
apartment building with the help of her
dad a lot of people rent apartments not
many people can buy apartment buildings
as investment
properties and we have another text from
Ashley to a
friend a lot of huge huge things going
on over here 100 plus million doll deals
Etc it's a lot to get my mind around and
I feel easily overwhelmed if I don't
just focus on listening for what God has
for
me so she's involved with a 100 plus
million doll
deals 100 plus million dollar deals but
remember everybody Ashley just lives a
simple humble life she can't even afford
legal representation and again she's the
victim when she gets called out for the
falsities that she originated and took
to the media with the expressed intent
of harming Anthony and the
community um oh my
um yeah we're hopeful that once the
article's out um one of the directors or
producers that Britain works with
will uh you know become interested in
telling the story really well I think
it's going to take that because Anthony
is so um he has such a presence and if
it just stops at the article I'm
guessing that like there would be some
buzz in the medical medium Community for
a few months but like really I think
then it would kind of die down
ultimately the
way to really get the word out is like
would be like a Netflix documentary you
know
so um once you hit that level of like
being exposed there's kind of no there's
no coming back from
that there's kind of no coming back from
that that's what Ashley wants for
Anthony and let me be clear that nobody
over here cares if Ashley has money or
not that's not the problem it's the fact
that she's being ridiculously dishonest
about it and even publicly rebutting
with her own close friends who know her
situation personally said about her
wealth at the same time as Ashley's
trying to convince everyone that she's
so perfectly honest and morally
Superior the truth is that Ashley will
throw anybody under the bus even her own
friends who threaten The Masks she's
wearing as she's trying to portray
herself to be an everyday innocent Mommy
so that people are more likely to
believe her
lies Ashley's misrepresenting herself
just like she's misrepresented the
entire Stephanie story and just like she
continues to misrepresent Medical medium
information with every lie and every
falsity she's out there
pedling here is again Ashley's response
to what Taylor and Robbie said about
her that said we don't own a plane like
they said in the
podcast they don't own a plane hm maybe
Ashley doesn't have a plane but her
family does or at least they did there's
obviously a reason why Robbie and Taylor
said what they did and Ashley's being
dishonest again just a minute ago you
heard what we read from Ashley from
another time in which she said
explicitly that her family has homes and
cars and planes all over the globe if
that wasn't enough there's also an
article on businesswire.com from 2017
about Ashley's father that
reads Dallas real estate entrepreneur
and philanthropist Jean e Phillips
offered his private plane for a
humanitarian flight to St Thomas and the
US Virgin Islands last
week her father offered up his plane not
a plane his plane there are also
multiple currently public posts on
Ashley's mother's Instagram account in
which the family can be seen on a
private jet like in this
video Ming with the
dogs look at those dogs trying to bite
me
crazy dogs
right
more you wants to do it
[Music]
again if you're listening to the podcast
version of this episode what you just
heard is the sound to a video of
Ashley's family on a private jet that
seems to be on its way to the location
tagged of CIO Hawaii it appears as
though Ashley's mother is recording the
video while Ashley's dad is holding
Ashley's daughter on his lap as he's
showing her something on his phone and
Ashley herself is in plain view talking
to someone behind him on the private jet
it was posted on June 25th of 2019 with
the caption quot memories Priceless as
if from a trip they had taken in
previous years it gets even crazier
there are two posts one from July 7th of
2018 and one from July 15th of 2018 with
photos of Ashley's kids on a private
plane with Ashley's dad the July 7th
2018 post is captioned quote we are
headed to
Pennsylvania this was four months before
Stephanie passed away and Pennsylvania
is where Stephanie lived
Ashley's family took the private jet
that Ashley's now claiming that they
don't have or have access to to the very
state in which Stephanie lived just four
months before Stephanie died and
yet Ashley did not visit Stephanie once
during the entire time she was sick we
know this because in a blog post Ashley
wrote on March 7th of 2020 she said this
Steph went back home after a few months
and a relationship turned into texts and
occasional phone calls she was the kind
of friend I didn't talk to every day but
I never worried about it because I knew
the second I saw her again it would be
like we hadn't missed a day
unfortunately I wouldn't have that
chance here Ashley is referring to a
Time when Stephanie stayed with her in
2016 Ashley is saying in this post that
she never saw Stephanie again after that
time Stephanie passed away on November
13th of 2018 over two years later in an
Instagram post from March 6th of 2020
Ashley said something similar Steph went
back home to Pennsylvania a few months
later and a relationship turned into
texts and occasional calls she was the
kind of friend I didn't talk to every
day but who I knew I would never miss a
beat with the second I saw her again
unfortunately I never
would Ashley saying she would never get
the chance as if Stephanie had died
right after that but Ashley had over two
years of a
chance for someone who claims to have
cared so much about Stephanie that
Stephanie is the reason why she is so
determined to blatantly harm Anthony and
the medical medium Community it seems
just a little strange that Ashley did
not visit Stephanie once while Stephanie
was sick for 2 years Ashley clearly has
the means her family according to her
own words has quote cars and planes and
houses all over the globe and Ashley
appears to even have been on one of said
private planes with her family to
Pennsylvania just a few months before
Stephanie died in Pennsylvania and yet
Ashley still did not visit her instead
during that time that Stephanie was sick
Ashley was traveling to run Retreats
with her friends here is a text that
co-plot Taylor call had sent to a friend
on November 6th of
2018 I'm good just now back from
California the retreat was wonderful but
loads of work gret and was sick and in
the hospital the whole time so it was me
Ash and Mel full
on that text was sent just seven days
before Stephanie passed away so for over
two years despite Ashley taking multiple
trips despite her having the time to run
Retreats despite the family using a
private jet to visit Pennsylvania where
Stephanie lived all while Stephanie was
sick Ashley didn't visit Stephanie once
in instead Ashley was using that time
trying to become something in the health
industry using the medical medium name
in Ashley's blog post from 2020 where
she began pedaling her original false
storyline about what happened with
Stephanie she told a massive additional
falsity I have absolutely no agenda I
don't make money off clients or my
Instagram I intentionally never have and
the reason for that is because of how
how highly I value the truth I know it's
hard to trust people in the current
climate of social media and no one is
perfect but I want you guys to be able
to trust me as much as you choose
to As Nice And as trusting as that might
sound it's far from the truth and it's
incredibly manipulative Ashley clearly
had an agenda all along and Ashley has
very much made money off of her
Instagram or at least she's tried to and
she had every intention to do so I'm
going to go through some examples first
of all Ashley once had a platform on
Instagram of around 20,000 followers she
had this platform mostly because the
medical medium account was reposting her
and that's largely how her account grew
to what it was at the time Ashley then
used that platform built from the
medical medium Community to sell a
myriad of different digital products and
inperson
events one type of digital product
Ashley made money from was her ebooks
that she marketed on her Instagram
account there were three different
ebooks and we have receipts that were
submitted To Us by people who had
purchased them from Ashley in 2018 2019
and
2020 two of them were $7 each for PDF
copies and $15 each for hard copies and
one of them was $20 for a PDF copy and
$25 for a hard copy in 2018 through 2020
Ashley was promoting her offerings a lot
on social media Ashley shared
screenshots directly on her Instagram
stories that customers had taken of
their receipts from purchasing Ashley's
ebooks at the time of course Ashley
would share these receipts to try to
encourage more people to buy her ebooks
through her Instagram Ashley promoted
her ebooks constantly on her Instagram
page there were so many promotional
posts but we're going to read off the
captions for just a few of them in one
post Ashley made during that time period
She said
January 1st is coming and I know a lot
of us will use the momentum of a new
year to jump start our health goals so
I'm offering my nourish ebook for half
off on my website now until January 2nd
grab your copy for just $10 at the link
in my
bio in another promotional post Ashley
did a giveaway to try to reach more
people this one
said the recipe for these potato cakes
with roasted garlic cream sauce is in my
potatoes recipe book and one of you has
a final chance to win a hard copy of
that and my sweet potatoes recipe book
as well to enter tag as many people as
you can below the person who tags the
most people gets the books it's that
easy I've always preferred games where
your faith was in your own hands this
will be
hilarious ready
set go PS you can also buy the books
yourself at the link in my profile the
ebooks are $7 each and the hard copies
are
$15 this was obviously a tactic for
Ashley to get as many comments and tags
as possible so that she could get her
name out there more and to get her
ebooks to sell to more people in another
promotional post on January 10th of 19
Ashley
said this recipe for buttermilk mashed
potatoes uses cashews and it's low fat
oilfree you can find it in my potatoes
ebook Link in my profile and grab a copy
for just
$7 in a May 14th 2019 post Ashley said
this you can find the recipe in my
potatoes ebook by visiting the link in
my profile and checking out the books
section
there Ashley did another giveaway
promotional post for her eBooks on May
23rd of 2019 six months after Stephanie
passed away this one
said I'm giving away another hard copy
of each of my recipe books to enter tag
your food bestie and tell me one of your
favorite things to eat together P.S if
you are are naturally a sort of
impatient person like me and you just
got to have them they're available for
purchase on my website now at the link
in my profile May the odds be ever in
your
favor but what takes the cake out of all
of this is that Ashley actually released
her second ebook the day after Stephanie
passed away in her November 14th 2018
promotional post Ashley even casually
mentioned in the caption that a friend
of hers had died last night but that she
felt like it was still the right thing
to do to launch and start selling her
next ebook anyway Ashley is the daughter
of a billionaire it's not like she
needed the money she had no publisher
and no deadline this was an ebook Ashley
self-published she had the freedom to
release it at any time of her choosing
and she decided that the day after
Stephanie died was the right time and
then in the caption of the promotional
host Ashley said
this I could use your help getting the
word out about this little book I just
didn't have the energy to do the
giveaways and the hype stuff to build
momentum for it but that's the way life
goes Ashley offered to donate some of
the proceeds of her book sales to relief
efforts for the Wy fires that were going
on and affecting Ashley personally at
the time but not all of the proceeds and
again Ashley is the daughter of a
billionaire she doesn't need sales from
the medical medium Community to donate
to a cause what a bizarre time to try to
make money not even 24 hours after
Stephanie died that's the kind of thing
you do when you don't care about the
person who died but to each their
own so not only did Ashley lie about
never making money or trying to make
money off of her Instagram clearly she
did but Ashley even tried to make money
off of her Instagram the very next day
after Stephanie passed away and Ashley
was not only making money on Instagram
with her ebooks but she was also trying
desperately to make a name and a brand
for herself Ashley used the name of her
weight loss ebook and made a separate
Instagram account for it she did
Instagram lives promoting it she made a
Facebook group for it she created an
Instagram hashtag for it and she used
the hashtag in a bunch of her posts and
encouraged other people to use the
hashtag too
and Ashley wanted to do a retreat in
2020 centered around this brand she
created one Instagram post she had made
a few years ago said
this I'm over here dreaming up holding
some Retreats this year based on my meal
plan Ashley also participated in a vegan
bundle with one of her ebooks another
Avenue of Ashley making money off of her
Instagram we have a receipt that was
submitted to us from someone who
purchased the bundle without Ashley's
ebook in it for $50 from Ashley on
February 7th of 2020 which was just 4
days before Ashley started coming out
against medical medium and publicly
spreading false stories about
Stephanie think about this Ashley was
making money off of the medical medium
community Through Instagram 4 days
before coming out with her false
story for anyone who doesn't know how
bundle companies work I'll give you an
example I was asked to be an affiliate
for a bundle company multiple times over
the past year I chose not to participate
but I was sent all of the information
about how the commission structure works
the vegan bundle that Ashley
participated in was a different type of
bundle than the one I was asked to be a
part of but the structure for all of
them is very similar so I'm going to
read off parts of the pitch that I
received to give you a peek into how
much money Ashley could have made from
being a digital product contributor in
the vegan bundle and selling and
marketing it directly from her Instagram
account the pitch I received ceed said
this in short we have over 100 creators
come together and each ad their book or
course as an affiliate you would make
$19 per bundle you sell I sold 800
bundles our last
launch in the bundle companies Creator
section of their website participating
in the bundle is marketed to have the
following benefits it says why should I
join one high earnings two huge exposure
three followers love it and then in the
the commission breakdown section it says
if you contribute with one or several of
your digital products in the bundle you
get 70% Commission of the net profit
which is $33 per bundle sold as somebody
contributing an ebook Ashley could have
gotten a similar commission making
around $33 per bundle she sold through
promoting it on her Instagram the person
who reached out to me with this proposal
said that they sold 800 bundles during
one 10day launch as an example so just
to piece all this together for everyone
if Ashley with her 20,000 followers at
the time would have sold even half of
the example amount that I was given for
a similar bundle and therefore made 400
sales at $33 commission per bundle sold
Ashley would have made
$13,200 in 10
days and again all of this is done
through marketing the bundles on
Instagram meaning that Ashley in fact
made money or tried to make money off of
her Instagram
once again Ashley misled
people we not only have proof that
Ashley did in fact make money or try to
make money off of her Instagram but we
also have proof that she got new
customers and likely made more money
after she started pedaling her false
storyline about
Stephanie here's a comment somebody made
to Ashley on Instagram on February 11th
of 2020 it says hi Ash I had no idea who
you were until today when your post
about your dear friend started
circulating social media first I'm so
sorry for the losses that you've
experienced and I'm hopeful that by
sharing this that it will help those of
us who follow Anthony make those hard
decisions about the intersection of
holistic wellness and life-saving modern
medicine so many of us have been so sick
for so long and we are vulnerable to a
message of healing even if it's tainted
or imperfect in some way thank you for
sharing your truth I think it's so
important to not follow anything or
anyone blindly although so many have
experienced healing with Anthony and I
was super excited to order all of your
books sending you lots of
love to begin with that person believed
I did what Ashley said I did Ashley
created a false story and that person
believed it and now that person believes
Ashley is doing a justifiable action
most likely that person will never hear
the truth and they're probably just gone
they left thinking that I hurt somebody
second she purchased all of Ashley's
books so Ashley made money selling books
on a platform that was built off of
medical medium and then at the same time
using a false story to do so in that
instance oh yeah and Ashley claimed that
she never made money on her Instagram
and here it is little old honest Ashley
once again being
dishonest even better than that Ashley's
ebooks are still still available for
purchase to this day multiple people
submitted receipts to us from their
purchases of Ashley's ebooks in December
of
2023 and Ashley wanted to make a whole
lot more money off of the medical medium
community Through many different Avenues
this was what she wanted one
money-making Avenue was through running
big Retreats first in 2016 Ashley began
by sending an email to let Anthony and
his wife know that she wanted to host a
retreat in Santa Monica California and
she asked them if they would give her
and her Retreat a shout out then later
on in 2016 Ashley submitted a business
proposal to Anthony Ashley wanted to do
medical medium Retreats with Anthony
using the medical medium name in the
summer of
2017 in the business proposal which I
have in front of me Ashley included a
cost analysis and financial forecast for
150 attendees with a cost of attendance
of $33,000 per person and a total
Revenue amount of
$450,000 it's worth noting that in this
2016 business proposal Ashley listed
Robbie Barbaro on the retreat itinerary
as someone who would have been teaching
classes at the medical medium Retreat
that she wanted to run and profit from
Ashley also stated in her business
proposal that quote by looking ahead to
2018 the quote event could grow up to
250 people if desired this shows was
that Ashley's desire was to do medical
medium Retreats for years to come and to
make even more money with more people at
$3,000 per person with 250 people like
Ashley desired the revenue would have
been
$750,000 and then came a pivotal moment
in history Anthony turned it all down
and said no to Ashley's big Retreat
proposal I've always felt Ashley was not
looking out for the community and The
Chronic ill so much she was more into
what can Ashley get out of this and that
concerned
me Ashley got turned down and then
Ashley still had Her Mind Set On Doing
Retreats so she went forward with trying
to do them on her own we have a
screenshot from Ashley's old website in
which she had a spot she was using to
Market upcoming Retreats under upcoming
events it says summer Retreat 2017 check
back for more information
soon Ashley was trying to Market her own
retreat but it seems as though this
Retreat never ended up taking place
however Ashley still kept trying to move
forward to make her big Retreat business
plans happen here is the text Ashley
sent to someone on April 29th of
2018 would be fun to buy a small house
there and just set it up to do Retreats
let comfy bunk beds in each room and
make it hold 10 to 12 people and then I
could fly into lead Retreats once a
month and make like 30 grand house would
pay for
itself and here is another text she sent
to the same person 3 days
later it would make even more sense for
me to just do like a full month of
Retreats twice a year and bring in
240k less with cost of course how much
cashh do I need in the bank do you think
to get a loan on these houses I'd want
to do it without my
trust she's the daughter of a
billionaire family she has a trust fund
and she was trying to use medical medium
to make it big in the health industry
and she didn't want to dip into her
trust and I can promise you this her
trust fund doesn't just have $220,000 in
it
I'm sure it
doesn't we've got the daughter of a
billionaire with a trust fund who's
trying to act like she can't even afford
a lawyer but she does have a lawyer by
the way everybody should know that and
she was trying to do medical medium
Retreats so that she could make
$240,000 a year from the chronically ill
only have to show up for two months out
of the year and she didn't want to dip
into her trust fund
amazing next I'm going to play voice
text that Ashley sent to Anthony around
that same time in 2018 asking him again
about doing Retreats note that we are
redacting the name of her child for
privacy as you'll hear in the audios the
Retreats were her and her friend's ideas
Ashley reached out multiple times over
the course of 17 days trying to get me
on the phone trying to get me involved
and still trying to use the medical
medium name on them and get me to
promote them and I was not interested
and told her no this was many months
after Stephanie was diagnosed with
cancer and Ashley was trying to do
business with
me hey it's Ash I
know sorry got too
bigle it's okay Budd um okay I know you
talked to gret about this that she and I
are trying to get some Retreat stuff
going and she's doing one in Hawaii that
I'm going to help her do the food for
which will be really fun but we've also
been talking about this main idea and um
we're getting a proposal from them to do
a retreat for a smaller group like you
and I talked about of about 30 people
this coming September and I just wanted
to get a feel from you because I wasn't
sure I kind of felt like you weren't
really wanting to be involved in that
which is totally fine I just wanted to
make sure before we go ahead and see
like is that something that you would
want to do through medical medium at all
and um if not we're going to just Market
it as like a family Retreat where like
the food happens to follow medical
medium healing um guidelines and you
know we'll be we'll run all our
marketing by you guys just to make sure
it's like on the up and up but um it
wouldn't be like we would make sure to
make it clear it's not like affiliated
with medical medium so that's kind of
what I'm thinking because I sort of got
the vibe of like you're not sure about
that yet but correct me if I'm wrong
okay if you guys would like to
be like have medical medium be the SP of
something like that the idea I mean the
retreat is just on a beautiful Retreat
facility and there's hiking and beaches
and a lake and we're not going to plan
like too much for people it's mostly
about you know a chance to get together
with other people and all the food you
know have the food done for you and just
to rest and maybe there'll be like a
cooking demo and some like guided
meditations or something something like
that but nothing nothing super
structured nothing real um formal it'll
just be an opportunity for people to
come take advantage of the
location all I have to say just let me
know if it's something you guys did do
end up feeling like you want to be more
through the mm Banner or if you're if
you'd rather us just kind of Take the
Lead and run with it and like I said
we'll be well you know you know I'll
check with you in case to make sure all
our marketing is really clear in that
case that it's not through you guys and
and we won't we'll be careful with the
wording and
everything that first audio was sent on
April 27th in 2018 Ashley did not get a
response from Anthony and then Ashley
sent another one nudging him further on
May
14th hello good morning good afternoon I
don't know where you are
um this is the week we have to make a
decision about the main Retreat we got a
proposal back from Catherine at Point
Lookout it suggests a cost of about
41,000
and that's with an estimate of 30 people
30 adults and 10 children so the cost
per person comes down to a little like
around
$1,100 per
person so
I think it has the potential to be a
pretty good little test trial you know
if we are thinking of a retreat cost of
around
$3,000
um and it's really cool because if it
did work next year we could do the same
thing for 150 people and all of a sudden
then it would really be generating some
income let me know your thoughts it's
obviously no pressure but we just are
going to have to make some decisions
about it this week so so um any insight
into what you're thinking and whether
you guys would want to be involved would
be awesome okay love you
bye Ashley's saying here that the
retreat she had been planning would just
be a test trial she said that she wants
to charge people $3,000 for the retreat
and ultimately at some point host 150
people which if you do the math would
bring in almost half a million dollar
half a million dollar for one
Retreat Anthony how did you respond to
this prodding from Ashley I turned her
down
again right and then after you turned
her down Ashley still tried to pursue
doing Retreats on her own to whomever
she could sell them to Ashley did end up
posting a retreat later on with now co-
plotters Taylor and Gretchen and they
had a total of 12 attendees
I'm sure that 12 attendees made Ashley a
lot less money than the 150 to 250
attendees that Ashley was hoping to get
from doing Retreats with Anthony using
his name and
likeness Ashley's retreat with Taylor
and Gretchen took place in aahu Hawaii
from October 15th through the 21st in
2018 this Retreat ended just three and a
half weeks before Stephanie passed away
in the marketing that was done to
promoted on Instagram the details of the
retreat included quote all organic
plant-based grain-free meals in line
with the medical medium protocol and
quote cooking classes led by
Ashley so again Ashley was too busy to
visit Stephanie once while she was sick
but she certainly wasn't too busy to
travel from where she was living in
California to Hawaii and run Retreats
using medical medium
information and then even over a year
after Stephanie passed away Ashley was
still trying to run medical medium
Retreats Ashley ended up trying to sell
a retreat that she would have hosted
along with Gretchen in
2020 initially The Retreat dates were
going to be August 31st to September 5th
of 2020 initially Ashley had said that
she wanted to add a second week to that
but then she changed her mind Ashley
marketed this Retreat all over her
Instagram in early 2020 just literal
weeks before she came out with her false
Stephanie story in one Instagram post
Ashley started describing the retreat by
saying
this cost is
$3,800 for the week all meals daily
hiking and yoga and celery juice
included in that same Instagram story
post Ashley included a blurry photo of
random people swimming in the ocean she
Drew an arrow pointing to two of them
and said
this I recognize that these are random
some people but this could be you and
me in the next Instagram story Ashley
said this I know it's expensive but if
you find a Budd and save $10 a day
between now and then you can both
come Ashley then did a series of
promotional Instagram stories for the
retreat one said
this OMG you guys I booked it I'm
freaking out who will come eat dinner at
this table with
me she also included a poll in this post
with one option being yes and the other
option being yes also next to a photo of
an outdoor table overlooking the beach
then Ashley posted a very blurry photo
of a bed and said
this there are so few spaces six each
week is this your
bed Ashley did many other promotional
posts for this Retreat on her Instagram
and then she said
this and for those of you who feel like
you're missing out don't worry I'll do
something here in LA in May more on that
after I fill up
Hawaii so Ashley planned to continue on
doing Retreats and making money Ashley
then had two long-standing story
highlights lights up on her Instagram in
2020 one was for marketing her Retreat
and the other was for marketing one of
her ebooks in addition to those Retreats
on her former website Ashley marketed a
variety of different offerings a dinner
party she hosted in
2018 a wellness week private retreat for
two people in
2019 a cooking class and meal planning
workshop that Ashley charged $150 per
person for in 2018 and a virtual meal
planning workshop that Ashley char Char
$60 per person for in
2018 Ashley also had an Amazon
storefront she linked products like VI's
barleygrass juice powder which Ashley
described by saying
this one of the supplements I take every
single day I filed it under Beauty
because it has helped my hair grow in so
thick and
shiny Ashley had plenty of plans for
making money off of the medical medium
community Through many other avenues as
well
in 2016 Ashley submitted a proposal to
Anthony's wife in which Ashley offered
to invest in getting a YouTube channel
going for medical medium Ashley proposed
doing a 5050 Revenue split Ashley wanted
50% of all of the medical medium YouTube
earnings this is something that never
ended up panning out and so just so
everyone is clear to this day I do not
accept money from YouTube this was
Ashley calculating and planning some
kind of financial Endeavor that she
wanted to do with me that wasn't about
money going back into the community with
more free resources instead it was
Ashley hoping to make money for herself
classic
Ashley we also have texts that Ashley
sent to a health practitioner friend on
November 7th of 2017 they said
this what if we did an ebook
specifically for the postpartum period
and if we kept it short and sweet we
could release it for like $10 or
[Music]
something we could possibly talk to an
and rage and see if they want to do it
through medical medium like we could
design the whole thing but they could
release it as an MMA ebook or something
so much more reach that
way again this was taking place during
the time that Stephanie was sick instead
of visiting Stephanie Ashley was using
that time trying to become something in
the health industry using the medical
medium name another text she sent to the
same friend on March 27th of 2018
reads I know I wrote a whole book last
year and then realized I had to do a
proposal and still haven't started
lol on May 15th of 2018 the friend asked
when is your ebook launch so exciting
and Ashley
replied hm probably in another two weeks
or so I know so much exciting stuff
these days I'm cooking for Gretchen's
retreat in October I decided to host the
one-day cooking class of my very own
this August and the
ebook I'm talking to an agent today
about doing my own cookbook we're
remodeling the playroom and the yard my
head is
spinning around this time Ashley had
asked me to co-author a medical medium
recipe book with her and I said no and
turned her
down it looks like after Ashley got
turned down on co-authoring a medical
medium book Ashley then went around
trying to pursue a book deal on her
own and Ashley was desperately trying to
grow a following on social media here is
a text she sent to a friend in
2017 had a meeting with a marketing
consultant
yesterday the friend responded by asking
is this for your brand for your book and
Ashley
replied I basically just have to get my
numbers up before I post all the random
baby photos and stuff yeah every time I
post something other than food I lose
about 10 followers which adds up so I
have to sort of streamline and
focus in the same text thread Ashley
said up for a little friendly
competition I just want to like I don't
know I need some inspiration to get
serious about growing my insta so I
thought you might be down for a little
challenge like first one to gain 10K or
something we can put some fun Stakes on
Ashley was regularly asking this person
for advice on how to grow her social
media following in another text she
asked question did your IG growth slow
down so much because your only posting
less frequently how many times do you
think one needs to post to
grow after receiving advice Ashley said
this okay I've been trying to post once
a day
and I like lose followers at that rate
LOL it seems like if you start a YouTube
channel you get way more followers
without posting as
much after receiving advice again a
couple days later Ashley said
this I finally have been consistent
enough with insta where I'm not losing
followers at least once a day posting
results in like super slow growth like
10 new a day or
so on a later date frustrated with not
seeing the growth she so desired Ashley
sent this
text I'm posting twice a day on IG
really top quality photos and seeing no
growth she got some more advice from
this person on Switching up her hashtags
and then several hours later Ashley
texted back
okay I changed them up to see if it
helps got a little boost from switching
them
up okay so Ashley had a meeting with an
agent about getting herself a book deal
Ashley had a meeting with a marketing
consultant and then she was trying
really hard to grow her social media
following Anthony can you explain for
listeners how book deals work and why
this was so important to her it was a
different world back in 2018 it was
before influencers could become famous
on social media you either got somewhere
on television acting music getting
signed in a record deal something in
sports or in publishing getting a book
deal maybe it was before the time period
we living in now where someone hits
their grandmother over the head with a
2x4 and gets 20 million views and the
person who hit the grandmother over the
head with a 2x4 has endorsement deals
the world has changed Ashley was
desperate to to get a book deal
desperate to become somebody Ashley
wanted to co-author a book with me she
was very entitled and raised that way
and she expected to co-author a book
with me she expected it I said no for a
multitude of reasons and I'm so glad I
said no because this is the kind of
person she is back then I noticed that
when I spoke to Ashley she would say
something and then the second time she
said said it it would be different I
didn't trust her I said no so Ashley
tried to get a book deal on her own and
in order to get a book deal on her own
she needed a certain number of followers
so Ashley was trying to learn from
people like Robbie her best friend one
of the other plotters how to build
followers on her Instagram
Facebook that makes sense so clearly
Ashley was trying to make a name for
herself and build a platform for herself
she ultimately wanted to be famous she
was definitely also trying to make money
the claims Ashley made when she was
trying to get people to trust her with
her fake Stephanie story that she never
made money off of her Instagram and
intentionally never did because of how
much she quote values the truth are
Flatout lies Ashley was using Instagram
to sell ebooks Retreats bundles and more
and let's be clear making money off of
Instagram is fine that's not the problem
but why did Ashley feel the need to lie
about about it furthermore Ashley even
tried to pursue another Avenue for
profit by offering to invest in a brand
that Anthony endorses here is the text
she had sent to the owner of that
company also bear this in mind if you
ever decide you want to do a big push
with vimergy and take on some investment
and try and grow it up quick let me know
I do it with y'all in a
heartbeat there you have it Ashley got
turned down on this proposal as
well Ashley Foster always gets her way
no one's allowed to tell Ashley no if
they do Ashley will turn on them anyone
who tells her no will pay the price it's
who she
is not only did Ashley eagerly want to
invest in vimergy but this is also a
company that has products that before
Ashley got upset and turned on everyone
Ashley said she used every day and that
helped her hair quote grow in so thick
and
shiny now after being turned down by
them years ago Ashley and her hateful
group repeatedly attacked this company
along with Anthony and the medical
medium Community after we released the
plotter podcast episodes last year in
another post Ashley made as she was
trying to say face she said this
something that really bothers me is how
Anthony claimed in his podcast that we
were doing this for money but at the
same time claims that we must be part of
some evil plot because we have money
which one is
it this is inaccurate if you listen back
this instead is what was actually said
in our first podcast
episode what I learned is that the
strategy of this group is to try to
capture people like those young women
with a manipulated story
of a deceased person who isn't here
anymore to speak for herself or to
defend the truth of what actually
happened they might throw in some other
random misinformation to add to their
story of why you shouldn't trust medical
medium because they try to act like they
have some special information that you
just don't know even though all these
people still admitted to applying
medical medium information into their
own lives yet they say that they don't
trust you they just don't they they
explicitly say that they don't credit
the source they use it and don't credit
the source and I literally heard them
out on all of their points for a total
of over 17 hours and I can tell you that
everything that they think they have is
a bunch of Twisted
misinformation their false narrative
story is the guys that they're using but
what these calls also made clear to me
is that some of these sources are part
of this plan because they're actually
being driven by some of it is misplaced
grief some of it is is people being
driven by guilt but most of them
disturbingly are being driven by
self-interests and what they would stand
to gain financially and otherwise from
the impact of a medical medium
takedown I stand by all of that Ashley
always gets it wrong first as you can
hear it was me who said this not Anthony
hi Ashley I did not say that you were a
part of a plot because you have money
your friend Taylor called you out for
having a lot of money like private jet
plus her words I said that I suspected
that the plotters had mixed motives we
didn't mention the fact that some of
them have money and some of them don't
have money and there are plenty of
extremely wealthy people out there
including billionaires and Daughters of
billionaires who never stop wanting to
make more money what Ashley said is a
false dichotomy in fact Ashley knows
that this is a false dichotomy in text
messages she sent to a friend in 2017
Ashley used the following words to
describe her own father who had long
since been a billionaire and his
business
dealings he's trying to build something
bigger and bigger and bigger I think
he's just addicted to the game he's a
real true addict the rush of the
gambling element is so addictive to
him while Ashley was applying medical
medium information she wanted to do
high-profit retreats without dipping
into her trust fund admitting in that
very text that she has money but that
she wants to make more Ashley was
selling eBooks she was working with
bundle companies she wanted to be an
author she was meeting with marketing
consultants she wanted to grow a
following she wanted to run the medical
medium YouTube channel for 50% of the
earnings she wanted to have a stake in a
company endorsed by medical medium and
more Ashley also talked about wanting to
do a positive medical medium documentary
on Me on the light blast years ago she
had her sight set on it she was obsessed
with
it okay so this is going to be shocking
for people listening to hear to hear
that so Ashley has wanted to make a
documentary in some way shape or form
about you for a long time this goes way
back one of the most interesting things
I've seen from Ashley is that one of her
longest standing goals has been to
become successful specifically in the
film industry in a blog post Ashley
wrote in 2010 she described a rule book
she had for herself one of her rules was
this right did you write
today right and the writing you do today
must eventually lead to a successful
career in the film
industry as you just heard Ashley has
always wanted to be successful in the
film industry Ashley's husband is also a
documentary cinematographer I'm sure
that he wants to be well known for that
can you describe for everyone Anthony
what the proposal that Ashley made to
you years ago for a positive medical
medium documentary was
like Ashley was so fixated I wanting to
do a documentary she asked me about it
first on the phone she asked a mutual
friend about it over and over again that
mutual friend brought it up to my wife
and I again and was in conversation with
Ashley about it Ashley wanted to write
and control the content of the
documentary she wanted her husband to
film it and she wanted her sister to
edit it over the years I've been
approached many times by big producers
media companies and networks about doing
a medical medium documentary or TV show
my wife and I thought it'd be great to
get people's healing stories and more
information out there to help the
chronically ill at some point but we
wouldn't have have gone to Ashley to do
a documentary we entertained Ashley's
ideas but then we quickly became
concerned about what Ashley was
saying so I have that text thread in
front of me your wife initiates a
conversation with Ashley about it after
Ashley had been prodding about doing a
documentary for a while Ashley says that
she had thought about doing the
documentary idea a lot and then she gets
into her proposal she starts describing
some of her ideas
I like the idea of following a new
client we could even fake that part of
it
LOL it can be an actor that recreates a
storyline that is true that's frequently
done for
documentaries this sounds super sketchy
very weird of Ashley to suggest being
dishonest and to say that that's
frequently done in
documentaries after your wife politely
responds interesting Ashley right away
changes her mind on the idea that she
herself just presented the actor idea is
no good if someone got wind of it it
would be real bad but it is common
LOL these were more signs we saw
firsthand of Ashley being manipulative
and dishonest it made us really really
uncomfortable right after Ashley's last
message your wife changed es the subject
and ends the documentary conversation so
I'm guessing you guys had turned her
down on that sketchy proposal as well
yeah in the nicest way possible she kept
asking about it and prodding and it's
something we were never going to do with
her we didn't want to disappoint Ashley
but we just were not on the same page
about it at all for Ashley to suggest
altering a documentary so it becomes
dishonest was unimaginable for a medical
medium documentary we were sitting there
wondering why on Earth is Ashley telling
us this is how you do a documentary you
fabricated in a dishonest way this was a
shocker to
us yeah so Ashley wanted her hand in
every pot with you I'm sure that she saw
you as a ticket to success everybody
knows that you're one of the biggest
Health authors in the world Ashley was
trying to use the medical medium name to
get her herself and her husband
somewhere and she ended up getting
turned down from basically every angle
Ashley had spent years trying to pursue
all these different Avenues and they
were unsuccessful Ashley was struggling
to grow a following she got turned down
on co-authoring a book with you getting
a book deal on her own evidently didn't
work out she got turned down on
investing in a company endorsed by you
the medical medium YouTube channel deal
that Ashley proposed didn't work out for
her she got turned down on her proposal
to partner with you to do medical medium
Retreats her independent Retreat only
filled 12 spots Ashley never made it in
the film industry like she wanted to she
got turned down on her proposal to do an
inspirational documentary about medical
medium that she wanted her husband to
film and her sister to
edit was Ashley upset with you I mean
how did she respond to all of this
rejection at the time she was
disappointed and frustrated Ashley
wanted desperately to have a hand in
Everything Medical medium everything she
wanted a piece of everything I was doing
and now look what she's doing because
she didn't get her way Ashley's not used
to being told no it's an entitlement and
an ego thing when Ashley realized she
wasn't going to be able to get all of
these high-profile business deals with
me she flipped the switch was flipped
and she started making things up that
didn't exist she started Ed working on
her false storylines and any
communication she had with me of any
kind or anybody I was associated with
she started to try to twist and rewrite
history so she could tell people a
disturbing story that never existed and
then she decided to take her stories to
the media to try to hurt me and the
community and you turned her down on
these deals years ago because you had
concerns about her intentions I turned
her down for multiple reasons first of
all every time someone I knew would talk
to Ashley they would be left shaking
their heads because it seemed that
nothing that came out of Ashley's mouth
was totally accurate she was 50/50 at
best 50% mixed in accurate things with
50% mixed in completely wrong inaccurate
information and it was obvious to me
that Ashley was only wanting to be
involved with medical medium because of
her wanting to start a business invol
olving me or use me to launch her
business and I knew this about Ashley
it's not that I'm saying it's bad she
wants to become somebody it's bad that
her desire was to become somebody using
me and then when I said no afterwards
trying to destroy the medical medium
community and me because she didn't get
her way even if there was a world where
I was naive enough to give Ashley all
that she wanted a book deal with me big
Retreats with my name on them $750,000
like pop documentaries for her and her
husband money made from those Ventures
which could have equated to Millions
would have been taken from the community
and not invested back into the community
on any level it would have been selfs
serving as we'll cover later on Ashley
is so cheap she wouldn't buy Stephanie a
coach plane ticket to help Stephanie get
out to Ashley's family is Pebble Beach
mansion and money that I've made from
working around the clock a big portion
of that money goes back into producing
free everything for the community if
there was a world where I was naive
enough to let Ashley go into multiple
business deals with me all that money
would have been
squandered Penny pinched and
self-serving for her children and her
lifestyle so that she can have expensive
vacations and grandiose dinners with
friends all all while I will still be
standing in my kitchen eating a steamed
potato standing up working 20 hours a
day to get the next book out so people
can heal an example of how Ashley works
is that she wanted to make all this
money from you the community that
doesn't have money so she's didn't have
to touch her trust fund a trust fund
with an exorbitant amount of money in it
it would have been unfair to the
community that Ashley was making a
killing off their backs I could not live
with that so I chose not to do a
documentry with her I chose not to let
her co-author books with me and I chose
not to go into the retreat business with
her using my name Ashley would have made
a killing so that she could avoid using
her trust fund from her billionaire
father now after I turned her down and
she didn't get what she wanted Ashley is
trying to become famous
through pretending to be a whistleblower
spreading lies false claims and
disinformation and trying to frame me
along with her partner Tony tazone
Stephanie's brother who as one of the
plotters said is just looking for
someone to blame according to another
plotter Tony has multiple fake accounts
on social media platforms and he may not
realize it but he's doing Ashley's
bidding
she's stoking the Flames of his grief
and anger and Tony doesn't know why
Ashley's really on this Mission she's
using him Ashley has recruited other
people to spread her lies for her we
have Insider information that she's
promising the people who are supporting
her a spot in a documentary ultimately
Ashley's goal is now to make it
somewhere in the film industry by trying
to get a deal for negative hitpiece
documentary about me and to take the
medical mum Community down in the
process I also want to ask you this
because I know that there will be people
out there wondering about spirit and if
Ashley was capable of all of this
spinning stories and lying to harm you
and attacking the medical medium
Community then can you explain why why
did spirit let you engage with her at
all Spirit told me not to engage with
Ashley
and I voiced that to my friends Ashley
was a friend of a friend I communicated
with Ashley very little I kept her at
arms length when I got off the phone
after one of my first calls with her I
said to my wife no she is not a good
person she seems empty and soulless and
not genuine and spirit's given me a
warning but I gave it a chance because I
always keep faith that people will heal
their mental state Spirit gave me the
potential that Ashley could be an
ill-intentioned person but you can only
hope that someone uses their free will
to do good things and not harmful things
despicable things abusive things and I
didn't want to let a mutual friend down
who was wanting me to connect with
Ashley for somebody that said I saved
her and her sister's life and to turn so
dark and to lie so much really brings me
a new understanding of what people can
be I mean you expect out there in the
world for things to go wrong but you
never expect a mom to be so conniving
and just plain evil she built the whole
thing off of originally I never told
Stephanie to see a doctor which was a
lie that alone is sick if you think or
falsities lies and fabricated stories
about me are harmful and ridiculous now
what would have happened if I didn't
keep Ashley at arms
length I mean just in what we've exposed
in this episode alone Ashley has been
wildly dishonest about her wealth she
said quote there's nothing crazy going
on over here when she is in fact the
daughter of a late multibillionaire with
cars and homes and planes all over the
world and she grew up in a mansion
according to the Daily Beast next door
to former US President George W
bush just a good old humble nextdoor
neighbor nothing crazy going on over
here she lied about not having a private
jet she lied about not having vacation
homes she lied about not making money
off of Instagram she lied about never
having the intention to make money off
of Instagram Ashley in fact had every
intention to make money off of per
Instagram and also specifically to
repeatedly make 200 $40,000 off of the
medical medium Community without dipping
into her trust fund by doing Retreats
two months out of the year plus to gain
a whole lot more money and fame off of
other Ventures she wanted you to set up
for her Ashley lied about having No
Agenda her agenda is Despicable and
Crystal Clear for everyone to see
Stephanie was sick for two whole years
and despite Ashley having all of the
means in the world the convenience of a
private jet that even went directly to
Pennsylvania where Stephanie lived and
somehow the time to be able to travel
for other purposes like to host Retreats
that she was trying to make money off
of Ashley did not visit Stephanie
once what Ashley's doing is not about
Stephanie Ashley has exploited and used
Stephanie now along with multiple others
as well and because her Twisted
Stephanie story didn't do the damage she
desperately wanted it to Ashley's now
twisting and manipulating and spinning
more stories whatever she can do to harm
you and the
community Ashley has a vendetta against
you because she didn't get what she
wanted from you that's clear she didn't
get the success the fame The Retreat
deal the book deal the followers or the
positive documentary deal that she
wanted and now that she didn't get what
she wanted from you she's running a
smear campaign against you and still out
there obsessively now wanting to do a
negative hitpiece documentary about you
so that she can become famous and
successful that
way this isn't some whistleblower who
walked away because of Integrity Ashley
is trying hard to convince her followers
that she is such an honest and
transparent person yet Ashley has not
publicly disclosed the fact that she had
every desire to make money and become
somebody using medical medium Ashley has
not disclosed the fact that she made all
of these business proposals to Anthony
and that she got turned down all right
around the same time as what was
happening with
Stephanie Ashley has not disclosed that
she was still marketing and trying to
sell Retreats using medical medium
information to the community for over a
year after Stephanie passed away and all
the way up until literal weeks before
she came out with her false story about
Stephanie it's hard to think that Ashley
is this motive driven person when she's
breastfeeding or acting like she's this
well-to-do authentic or honest mom
it's really a good cover like she's just
a whistleblower to stop a mean man the
story she's telling people never
happened but a mom who seems so honest
in every sense it can win somebody over
it can win a journalist over it can win
other people over especially people who
are looking for reason to not like me
her cloak in Disguise is this wholesome
mother with seemingly so much wisdom who
cares so deeply about the world from the
outside raises her children with the
best of values and then she seeks out
journalists they see this she puts on
this front how can she be wrong
influencers who weren't friends of mine
but were acquaintances she would
befriend them purposely to try to sell
them these stories that I'm a fraud and
she's worked really hard at it for years
now and in reality the truth she has a
condition
either born out of jealousy and hatred
towards me or just a different illness
where she just can't help but to lie and
makeup stories as you'll learn in these
episodes to come Ashley can't get
anything right or anything straight not
just her own madeup stories but factual
worldly understandings that can actually
be fact checked and she'll still be
completely off the
mark we've only Only Just Begun exposing
Ashley and her group so buckle your seat
bels everybody and stay tuned for the
next episode in this
series as we are in the process of
exposing Ashley and her organized
hateful group for who and what they
really are it's important to take note
of their tactics and patterns that are
likely to follow the plotters have a
documented history of initiating attacks
using lies and misinformation and then
upon getting called out and corrected
trying to flip it and play victim that
is not going to work here all this group
has done is spread verifiable lies and
falsities they've carelessly attacked
and harmed many innocent people they've
used and exploited deceased individuals
and others in the process of trying to
get what they want they've repeatedly
explicitly expressed the intent to harm
medical medium and they've even
deliberately tried to stop Anthony from
doing a free event to support and raise
money for the community we have every
right to set the record straight and to
defend the truth with facts and evidence
and to defend the chronically ill
against the malicious attacks of this
group and we are going to continue to do
so we expect the plotters to evade and
ignore what they have done wrong we
expect them to continue to lie and
spread falsities we expect them to Pivot
onto something new they'll make up and
we expect them to skew and alter data
and to hide critical pie pieces of
evidence that undermines their entire
campaign we also expect the plotters to
fabricate explanations as they do
everything they can to try to discredit
what we're exposing them for having done
and said in their own
words but we are using their own text
messages voice messages social media
posts words that they spoke on recorded
calls and other published materials
there's no use of any AI in any of these
episodes and never will be all of the
information was fact checked and
forensically investigated if youve been
harmed deterred from your healing
process bullied shamed emotionally upset
or physically hurt by flareups of your
conditions from the stress induced by
the plotters attacks like hundreds of
others have reported please go to
medicalmedium.com
slsa space to submit your report and
share your story
if you've been contacted by anyone who's
tried to deter you from using medical
medium information please take
screenshots and Screen recordings and
submit them to the same place
medicalmedium.com
slsa space