The Following episode is part of a
series dedicated to exposing an
organized hateful group that has been on
a Relentless pursuit to destroy the
medical medium community and that has
been attacking bullying harassing and
preying upon the chronically ill joining
me in this series is a guest named Amber
bakaro she's an alternative medicine
practitioner who became a whistleblower
after she witnessed this hateful group
in action when they tried to recruit her
to join them last year Amber caught the
main members of this group on legally
recorded calls describing their
premeditated multi-step plan to create a
quote post-medical medium era by feeding
false stories and claims about me and
about medical medium information to
Major media outlets in hopes that it
would lead to securing themselves a deal
for an anti-ed medium documentary on
Netflix that would bring Fame and other
benefits to them now known infamously
instead for their malicious plot that
was caught on recording and exposed we
refer to this hateful group as the
plotters their entire smear campaign is
spearheaded by one woman who comes from
an extremely wealthy family didn't get
what she wanted from me years ago and is
now seeking Rev venge she's made it her
mission to gather a bunch of plotters
with ulterior motives and aess to grind
including competitors in the health
industry to try to frame medical medium
and take down the community what this
organized hateful group has done is
unprecedented it's one of the biggest
scandals that's ever happened in the
health industry as you'll see it's also
one of the biggest instances of
capturing corruption within the
mainstream media so prepare yourself for
lots of details and nuances as we are
going to be thoroughly untangling the
massive Web of Lies they have spun and
we're going to be releasing a lot of
disturbing new information new
recordings and mindblowing evidence of
just how far they are going to lie to
try to get what they want some of the
evidence we're presenting in these
episodes in includes original written
content such as text messages social
media posts that have been produced by
the plots and will be reenacted for
greater ease in following along those
who are listening along to the podcast
can find video versions of these
episodes on the medical medium YouTube
and Rumble channels that will be
displaying screenshots photos videos and
more some of you may be unaware that
this has even been happening but many of
you have been tremendously injured and
harmed by what they have done the record
needs to be set straight and they need
to be called out for what they've done
and are still doing the medical medium
Community does not deserve to be
attacked like this and we are going to
set the record straight as many times as
we need to
[Music]
we have a guest here with us today who
is a highly respected holistic health
practitioner and speech pathologist and
was a friend of Stephanie's her name is
Dr Kimberly spare Kim and her husband
supported Stephanie at the time of her
illness back in 2020 Ashley posted her
original false story about Stephanie
which she made more than 15 false claims
in one vers version of and told more
than 20 falsehoods in another version of
Kimberly's husband corrected Ashley in
the comments on something she had gotten
very wrong and Ashley had to adjust her
false story because of it Kimberly made
a statement to her own small private
Community to calm fears and Chaos that
Ashley had created with her false story
Ashley was not happy about this and she
responded by attacking Kim and trying to
intimidate her to this day Ashley has
continued to publicly attack Kimberly
and her family Kimberly thank you for
coming on to share your story I know
that this situation has been extremely
upsetting thank you Amber this is a
really sad situation a dear friend that
I cared about is being used for an
agenda that seems to have been created
years after her passing I would have
never shared the intimate details of her
story because Stephanie's privacy is my
number one concern however the plotters
have shared very intimate details of
Stephanie's story and even delicate
unnecessary details about her life I was
recently attacked and have been
continually attacked since 2020 the
attacks were sudden they were out of the
blue I was actually really shocked when
they began I felt it was really
necessary for me to set a few things
straight here
today yeah could you start Kim by
telling us first about your relationship
with Stephanie and how you were
supporting her when she was
sick yeah so we met actually at Ashley's
home during the LA medical medium event
Stephanie and I became instant friends
we realized that we lived just one state
over from each other and that she had a
nephew that was very close in age to my
son we started texting and voice texting
a lot Stephanie was sweet she was funny
she was loving and she was always
looking for advice but she was also
always offering to help in any way that
she could I would meet up with Stephanie
for lunch at the grocery store juice
bars and I met up with her the night
that her niece was born at the hospital
to arm her with the things that she
wanted to support her sister-in-law
through
Labor a few months later I met her
sister-in-law niece and nephew for a
lunch date and we bounced together along
with her family and my family at her
nephew's birthday party
Stephanie was so so proud of her niece
and nephew and wanted me to be friends
with her sister-in-law because she
thought we had so much in common and we
had kids that were really close in
age I adored Stephanie and the
friendship that we shared I soon became
pregnant with my second child and
Stephanie volunteered to help me
postpartum with my 2-year-old son the
same way that she supported her
sister-in-law and her nephew because she
told me I helped to support her and her
brother and her brother's family
postpartum and that I also needed that
same help she was always so gentle so
kind and always questioned how I was
working full-time how I was pregnant and
also caring for a two-year-old she got
it and it meant so much to
me when Stephanie got sick I remember
discussing doctors with her and offering
to go with her into the City and hold
her hand but Stephanie was not receptive
to the idea of seeing a doctor at that
time wow and then what was happening and
what were things like after Stephanie
got
sick so this was really hard when
Stephanie took a turn for the worst I
was getting ready to birth my baby I was
planning a vack birth as my first birth
was a traumatic emergency birth and the
stress of what I'm about to explain was
impacting my ability to birth my baby I
was under so much pressure and I was
having such a hard time shifting into
birth mode as I was on constant group
messages with then friends colleagues
medical doctors consultants and
personally with Stephanie to support her
as best I could the pressure was never
ever from Stephanie it was coming from
several of the plotters mostly Ashley
who lived across the country they were
looking at a map and telling me that I
live an hour and 20 minutes from
Stephanie but in reality with City
traffic this often times could take up
to 4 hours each way this is why when
Stephanie and I did meet up before she
was sick we were always extremely
strategic about our planning the city
traffic where we live is
horrendous and the driving around here
during the city traffic it's it's just
crazy so back to my birth I was
literally in the birthing tub birthing
my baby on text threads with Stephanie
and with her supporters several of which
are now involved in trying to take this
community down when I finally birthed my
baby I was back on the text threads
within minutes planning how I could best
support Stephanie this was before my
family or my son had even met my new
daughter I was under so much pressure
before I was even cleared to drive by my
midwives I was back on my feet caring
for my newborn caring for my 2-year-old
and driving food and teas and
supplements that Stephanie wanted to her
whenever I
could Stephanie herself did not want me
doing this but the plotters continued to
push me like I was some type of robot
that should birth a baby and then be
back to running around I also opened up
my home to a house guest when I was only
a few weeks postpartum a friend Gretchen
she came to my house and stayed with me
so that she could support
Stephanie my husband and I gave up a car
we ran errands on no sleep we also
opened our home to
illness as greten was in and out of the
hospital and then back in our home
around my newborn we all came down with
a flu when my baby was just a few weeks
old my 2-year-old was also sick it was
one of the hardest experiences of my
life being postpartum having a baby
being exposed to a
flu on one trip to pick up Gretchen
again before I was cleared to drive I
was so tired that I went to pump gas
near Stephanie's
home the gas station was old and the
pump was malfunctioning and I was
exhausted I grabbed the noble nozzle and
I pressed it a few times before it
turned on soaking me in gasoline my hair
was soaked my clothes were soaked I was
drenched from head to toe I was sprayed
in the eyes and I felt like I couldn't
breathe I was shaking from the freezing
temperatures my newborn she was in the
back seat breathing in all the
fumes I rushed to Stephanie's house with
my windows down freezing
shaking and I had to shower and wear
someone else's clothes
home the whole time period it was
totally
insane I had a baby a baby a newborn
that was just a few weeks old and a
2-year-old son and I was being pushed by
women across the country mostly Ashley
to do more and more I had already been
supporting Stephanie in every way that I
could I had given her money I had
purchased supplements that she wanted
and couldn't afford I was cooking her
meals when I could bringing her teas
when I could my husband even took food
to the hospital at one point just days
after my daughter was
born he felt extremely uncomfortable in
the hospital as Stephanie wanted to talk
to him and welcome the food but he felt
so mixed up in a situation where some of
the plotters were screaming at her
family one of the plotters Taylor was
attacking Stephanie's father having a
heated discussion while disagreeing with
Stephanie's father about her
treatment my husband during those days
was rushing home from work so that he or
I could run things we could move cars we
could run errands we can manage house
guests cook meals run guests back and
forth with a baby and a 2-year-old I
wanted to do everything for
Stephanie but Ashley was creating a
pressure on me that almost broke me
during that
time
wow there's so much to unpack here from
this story and it sounds like such an
unbelievably stressful and traumatic
time having gasoline sprayed all over
your body like that when your body's
already compromised from having just
given birth let alone when you're
breastfeeding it's a
tremendous exposure I can't even imagine
I would have been devastated and despite
having just given birth you and your
husband were both doing the best that
you could to help Stephanie while she
was sick you weren't cleared to even
drive yet and you did it anyway the
drive wasn't short I want to bring in a
text that we have from Stephanie she had
sent it to a friend this was from before
she had gotten sick and she was talking
about some items that she was thinking
about picking up from you and she says
okay cool she isn't super close so may
not get it unless it's super
important this text corroborates this
text from Stephanie corroborates the
fact that you were far enough away from
her that it would have been a hassle for
her to pick up items from your house if
they weren't super
important you said that your husband
brought food to the hospital and spent
time around the family you both were
actually there and you got to witness
what was going on in person when
Stephanie was sick as Ashley mainly was
putting all of this pressure on you to
do more and more I'm wondering where was
Ashley and what was Ashley doing during
the year and a half that Stephanie was
sick I have actually been to Ashley's
family home in Pebble Beach California
but at the time I didn't know how well
off she was she was actually in Malibu
while Stephanie was sick she kept saying
she was very far away I now wonder why
she didn't offer Stephanie more support
or come to see her she very well had the
means to do it instead Ashley put
incredible pressure on me knowing that I
didn't have postpartum support I didn't
have anyone there helping me supporting
me Ashley and Gretchen were both
marketing and running Retreats during
the time of Stephanie's illness and
after she passed the Retreats were out
of state and they had to travel to get
to them somehow Ashley could travel for
the Retreats but she never made it to
see
Stephanie yeah so while Ashley was busy
running Retreats with Gretchen in Hawaii
and trying to make money off of the
medical medium community she was bossing
you around and putting pressure on you
to help even more than you already were
you and your husband were there with
Stephanie and you showed up to help but
Ashley on the other hand we now know
that Ashley wasn't physically present
for any part of Stephanie's breast lump
Discovery she wasn't around for any part
of Stephanie's back injury she didn't
visit Stephanie in the hospital
once as we covered earlier on in these
podcasts Ashley the daughter of a
billionaire family with a private jet
was on a private jet headed to
Pennsylvania where Stephanie was just a
few months before Stephanie died and
Ashley still didn't visit
her yeah I know that Stephanie's family
didn't even like Ashley or any of the
Potters at the time they didn't like the
way that she lived they didn't like the
way that Steph ate which by the way
wasn't exactly medical median she did so
many
things so the family didn't like Ashley
Ashley wasn't around at all and somehow
for some reason Ashley has tried to
position herself as an authority on
Stephanie I want to bring us back to
when Ashley posted her original false
story online in
2020 Ashley made more than 15 false
claims in one verse version and more
than 20 false claims in another version
your husband however having firsthand
knowledge of what had occurred corrected
Ashley in the comments of one of her
posts he said but you're missing the
critical part when Anthony at Medical
medium told her she needed to see a
doctor and have the lump dealt with oh I
forgot that doesn't fit your
agenda Ashley replied to this by
saying Anthony didn't tell her to see a
doctor until she was bleeding from her
nipples the same point at which he
stopped communicating with
her at this point in the plotter podcast
series we all know that this is far from
the truth to this your husband responded
by saying I don't know the whole story
nor claim to but if you are going to
claim the truth needs to be out there at
least do such a thing in its entirety
the above is one case in point which you
just acknowledge you skipped over and
I'm sure there are others kind of
calling the kettle black when you want
to make allegations of people being
Liars your husband called Ashley out for
being inaccurate and falsely narrating
the story the way that it served her
agenda even people who didn't know what
happened with Stephanie found Ashley's
story to be alarmingly inconsistent with
what they know of Anthony and medical
medium information one person commented
and said
doesn't he always say to see a doctor
and see what the diagnosis is and go
from
there another person added I listen to
Anthony's podcasts and have never heard
him suggest not to see a doctor
conventional or otherwise I find it hard
to believe your claim that Anthony
explicitly told her not to see a
doctor after all of the push back and
being corrected by your husband Ashley
commented this I tried to add it to my
post but Instagram won't let me but if
IG will allow me later I will add
it initially Ashley left out any mention
of any doctors being involved then here
because of your husband's correction and
the push back she was getting she
changed her story and went on from there
to say Anthony told Stephanie to see a
doctor but not until it was too late
which is still very far from the truth
and with all of her blatant false claims
Ashley caused a lot of damage one
comment on this post read he should have
told her to see a doctor the moment she
found the lump and told him it should be
a lesson for him and any healer I've
heard similar stories many times with
other healers I'm just so so sorry again
to hear
this we hope that this person has now
listened to our podcasts to learn the
truth even though they probably didn't
because they're probably long gone since
being scared by Ashley's false claims if
they have been listening they would have
learned that this is exactly in fact
what Anthony did exactly one day after
Stephanie reached out about her breast
lump Discovery Anthony and his wife
texted that you should always see a
physician even after being corrected by
her husband Ashley continued on with
more falsities she commented this
he told her to see a doctor when it was
too late for them to do anything and
when he clearly realized he had screwed
up it was at this point that he also cut
off communication with her it doesn't
feel very relevant to me that after
years of telling her not to see a doctor
and that she would be fine he changed
his tune when she was incredibly ill
there are so many false things in here
it's disturbing not a single sentence is
accurate as we've covered Anthony told
Stephanie to see a doctor from the very
beginning he didn't screw up Anthony was
consistent in his messaging to Stephanie
all throughout the time of her illness
that doctor should be involved he never
changed his tune and Anthony was not the
one who cut off communication with
Stephanie we'll get to that more in a
bit but my gosh Kim no wonder you had to
make a statement I mean can you just
describe for us what was going on in the
community at the time after she did this
I know that many people had reached out
to me and I know that many people were
reaching out to you too what was the
impression that they had gotten from
Ashley's post Ashley compared Stephanie
to her own father who she said did
everything his fancy doctors told him to
do but summarized that none of them
actually had any idea what they were
doing she said her dad did everything
the conventional doctors told him to do
and he died Stephanie also followed
conventional treatment yet Ashley
insinuated that Stephanie followed a
protocol designed by Anthony and died
this isn't true Stephanie received
conventional
treatment as for the community it was a
mess it became so divided the fear was
unbelievable what Ashley did was instill
fear in so many people it was like they
started thinking their spinach salad or
their spinach soup was harming them and
they went back to a standard American
diet or went back to eating
McDonald's it's horrifying and it's all
so far from the truth all based on
complete completely false claims I've
seen from the data that Stephanie
received conventional cancer treatment
for almost a year and because you unlike
Ashley were directly involved with
Stephanie's situation you were there in
person you had the ability to set the
record straight so you and another
practitioner who was also directly
involved sent letters out to each of
your private communities I remember
those letters I remember the volatile
situation that Ashley had created with
her
disinformation you and the other
practitioner handled this with a
tremendous amount of care Grace and a
lot of respect while protecting
Stephanie and her private information
after Ashley had exploited her to serve
her own
agenda I have your letter in front of me
and here are some of the critical
clarifications that you
made Stephanie was not under Anthony's
care for
cancer Anthony did not provide
supplementation or food protocols for
her Cancer all cancer related medical
decisions were being made by Stephanie's
family and a few close
friends Stephanie received chemotherapy
and many other conventional Medical
Treatments you also shared in here about
how devastating it was for you to have
lost a friend and about how unhappy you
knew it would make Stephanie that
Anthony was being inaccurately blamed
for such a terrible
tragedy you had every right to send this
letter you had every right to make those
clarifications and we now know those
clarifications to be true as proven by
the evidence that has been presented in
these podcast
episodes but Ashley obviously didn't
like that so can you explain what
happened after these letters were sent
out yeah Ashley started attacking me on
text on audio messages while I was
driving in the pouring rain and then she
took the letters we sent to a very small
private
Community these were not public
communities and she made a retaliation
post posting these letters public public
and then calling me and the other
practitioner
Liars okay so let's unpack that in the
retaliation post Ashley made she said
this some women I know were really upset
by my post they knew Steph personally
though I wouldn't call them good friends
of
hers though we've got a false claim
right at the beginning now I think that
Ashley tried to discount count your
friendship with Stephanie to make you
appear less credible Ashley also did an
Instagram live on April 1st of 2020 in
which she took it even
further
um what about the response of other
practitioners defending him and putting
others
down man that's so hard to talk about
[Music]
um I mean first of all they called
themselves Stu's friends which was
really hard because they were not her
friends like they knew her they weren't
friends with
her
um it's it was amazing to me frankly if
I'm being totally honest it was like it
was kind of just shocking and for them
to see and walk through that experience
um the only thing I keep coming back to
is they didn't know stuff that well
so here she went as far as to say
publicly that you and the other
practitioner weren't friends with
Stephanie at
all I know that this is false first of
all because Ashley told me the exact
opposite on the phone several months ago
as a reminder to everyone I recorded
that call and it appeared in our podcast
episodes and previous episodes and just
so everyone also knows and understands
that reporting was completely legal
Ashley has made false claims about that
as well but here is what Ashley told me
in that call and I said this to Kimberly
then and I Kimberly is the only person I
really lost my temper with because I
felt like she was Steph's friend and she
saw what
happened Ashley said to me privately on
the phone that you were Stephanie's
friend and that you saw what
happened why is this the opposite of
what Ashley shared in her 2020 blog post
because it sounds to me like she was
trying to deceive the public in Ashley's
live she also told this
falsity they weren't there at the
beginning of her journey they kind of
came in at the very end when Anthony
ghosted this one is even more ridiculous
I've seen
from all the text records that the other
practitioner Ashley is referring to
became friends with and started texting
with Stephanie in June of 2016 a year
before Stephanie's health really took a
turn and you met Stephanie at the live
event in 2016 and became friends with
her at that point as well I've seen so
much evidence of both of you having been
there for her and offering your support
to Stephanie early on in her illness
Journey as we've talked about before
Ashley loves to to say that Anthony
ghosted Stephanie to get people riled up
it's a tactic but it's completely false
Stephanie's family cut off communication
between them and told Anthony in a very
aggressive way to stay away so Ashley
made plenty of false claims
here yeah so Stephanie sent me hundreds
of voice notes many of them were a long
voice notes that's the kind of
relationship I had with Steph I got many
times the daily update from her I knew
what she did from the moment she woke up
she would take me through her morning
morning routine and how she spent many
of her days her messages were personal
like really really personal they were
family they were about friendships she
asked for help supporting the ones that
she loved she always asked for advice I
know the very intimate details of some
of the closest family members to her she
shared it all she offered to stay in my
home when I was postpartum to care for
my son and to care for me the way that
she did for her own nephew I don't think
you share that much and offer so much
with someone who is not your
friend yeah it sounds like the two of
you were close friends to me we also
know that Ashley's claims are false
because we have audios that Stephanie
had sent to a friend talking about how
close she was with you
and him just become good friends really
sweet women and really great
people and about trips she had taken
with you tomorrow I'm actually going
away with um Kim you know Canim really
spare and to see Gretchen because she's
in Pennsylvania right now I remember I
told you about that we're just going to
go for like a couple days and spend some
time with her and then again in a couple
weeks I'm going to go up again for a few
days
we also have a text that Stephanie had
sent to a friend about you that reads
she lives by my brother which is
convenient I introduced her to my
sis-in-law and fam and they have become
friends as well so that's been
nice and we have a long audio from
Stephanie talking about how you were
there for part of her back injury which
was months and months before Anthony was
told by Stephanie's family to stay away
hi well I hurt my back in the beginning
of
June I you know I hadn't been doing yoga
for a while or Pilates and I ended up
just by fluke coincidence I ended up
doing them both in the same week and by
the end of that week my lower back felt
kind of
weird
um weird enough where literally it was
hurting to go on the rebounder so I kind
of had to stop that uh and then I went
to the caropractor and everything was
better like a day later but I only
waited like a few days to start
exercising again you know I started like
light you know I just went on the
rebounder for the first couple days and
walked and did pocket gym but then after
a few days I was back into yoga fully
and I was like doing yoga every day and
pilates every day or almost every day
um and I was just feeling so good and I
just like wanted to do all these things
and it was so stupid in hindsight I'm
like what am I thinking you know we know
better than to do that um just too much
at once like that especially since I
hadn't been doing it I mean I felt fine
doing it I felt I got right back into it
I was doing like intense stuff and it
was like great but clearly my body
wasn't right ready there and so I went
to the chiropractor again but then it
never it got a little bit better but
then I was carrying all these heavy
watermelons which were killing me but
like I was hanging out with scratching
and Kim and like when I went up there I
just brought all these watermelons like
seeed huge watermelons
and I just from there it got worse and
worse and I was with Gretchen for like
almost a week when I came home at the
beginning of i as I came home the 4th of
July it got it was like horrendous like
it got really bad
excruciating like super super bad like
crazy spasming and neres like shooting
pains like and literally I've been home
doing nothing for the whole month of
July all of that goes to show that you
were around and there to see a lot of
what happened including that Stephanie
injured her back by doing all of the
physical things she just described which
again proves Ashley's original false
story line wrong in which Ashley had
said this on March 7th of 2020 about
Stephanie in the spring of
2017 her back began to ache we talked a
little bit during her back injury she
told me Anthony said it was a yoga
injury I really don't remember hurting
it in yoga she
said Ashley claimed that Stephanie had
said she didn't remember hurting back in
yoga but we have several audios from
Stephanie like the one we just played in
which Stephanie explains to various
different people all about how she
injured her back doing yoga and pilates
so obviously Stephanie was aware and
remembered because as we covered
previously
Anthony didn't tell Stephanie that her
back problems were due to a yoga injury
Stephanie told people that she had
injured her back doing yoga and
pilates and then she was doing things
like carrying heavy watermelons with an
already injured back that you witnessed
which made things worse so now I just
want to bring it back to Ashley's
retaliation post once more again she had
said this some women I know were really
upset by my post
they knew Steph personally though I
wouldn't call them good friends of
hers and Ashley's April 1st 2020 live in
which she said
this
um I mean first of all they called
themselves Steph's friends which was
really hard because they were not her
friends like they knew her they weren't
friends with
her we've shown the you Kim were indeed
a good friend of Stephanie's we also
have text and audio messages showing
that the other practitioner Ashley was
referring to was also in fact a good
friend of
Stephanie's on June 29th of 2016
Stephanie texted the
practitioner you're so sweet I love you
dear
friend in a text from November 11th of
2016 Stephanie says to her I love you
dearly
in a text from December 29th of 2016
Stephanie said to her hey sweet friend
in a text from July 8th of 2016
Stephanie said to her it's also
validating when sharing with a trusted
friend and we have audios from Stephanie
discussing how much this practitioner
had helped Stephanie Stephanie's
sister-in-law and Stephanie's brother
who is now a plotter trying to take down
the medical medium Community during an
extremely troubling time for them Tony
and Megan my brother's Tony his wife
Megan they wanted me to be there for the
birth I'm here supporting them you know
they um it's just been kind of intense
there's a lot of stuff that was going on
to the hospital thank God man us was
with us the entire time like you know
over the phone and and she was always
just so supportive and there for me the
whole time and anything we needed and
supporting tuny and Megan
there are hundreds and hundreds of text
messages that I've read going back and
forth between Stephanie and this
practitioner mostly of Stephanie asking
the practitioner for advice the
practitioner also helped Stephanie's
family in a very significant way during
a very dark time for them Stephanie
regularly expressed tremendous gratitude
for the positive impact this
practitioner had in her life and in
her's
lives we've got all of this evidence of
Stephanie calling this practitioner a
dear friend referring to you Kim
specifically as a good friend and
talking about all the time that you had
spent together including during the time
of Stephanie's back injury clearly this
practitioner and you were both very
important people in Stephanie's life and
Ashley told another big falsity to the
public I was even invited to Stephanie's
celebration of life I was around when
Stephanie injured her back I remember
her jumping on that trampoline with her
injury I supported Stephanie and met up
with her at the hospital the night that
her niece was born it's a strange thing
strange thing to have to qualify a
friendship but what Ashley said was so
hurtful because Stephanie was someone
that I really cared
about yeah I'm sure it was really
hurtful and it's a very it's a very um
it's a low blow it was very low for her
to go there and so following the false
friendship claims Ashley's retaliation
post continued on to say this these two
women sent out letters about my post to
their entire communities they
essentially made it seem like I was
lying this was a really impactful
experience for me because something I've
never realized before is just how much
you can use facts and distort them to
create what's actually a lie
and there's nothing I hate more than
lying so Ashley is saying that what you
shared was
factual but she's still calling you a
liar and the irony of all is that she's
calling you a liar in a post that she
Ashley herself told more than 15 false
claims in one version of and more than
20 in another version of Kim how
frustrating was it for you to watch
Ashley do this
publicly it has been so heartbreaking
it's been extremely traumatizing for me
for my family the amount of stress that
Ashley has created with her false
stories is just
unbelievable
yeah and sadly she didn't stop there
Ashley tried calling you while you were
driving in the pouring rain and because
you didn't answer Ashley sent you a
barrage of textt messages and I want to
walk us through that
conversation in the very first text
Ashley tries to rewrite history by
retelling her false version of what had
happened with Stephanie she tried to
sell this narrative to you Kim when you
were actually there for Stephanie and
witnessing things that had happened
firsthand in person and Ashley was
not the text says this hey girl I just
can't not not say something to you Steph
was personally Guided by Anthony for
years she did every single thing he ever
told her to do she laid on her back for
months while her spine literally
crumbled because he told her she had a
yoga injury that later he ended up
staying with shingles and then when she
started bleeding from her nipples after
telling her she would never have cancer
his response to cut her off completely
and never speak to her again after days
before Steph died she was texting
Anthony begging him just to talk to her
for you to write that letter and
knowingly mislead people about their
relationship is so absolutely disgusting
to me and just frankly
unimaginable this text has six false
things in it six critical things that
are completely wrong and it seems as
though Ashley thinks if she just repeats
them enough she'll be able to get
everyone to just go along with it I'm
going to walk us through the false
Claims One Stephanie did not do
everything Anthony ever told her to do
Anthony's consistent message from the
beginning was that Stephanie should see
a doctor for her breast lump and
Stephanie made the decision to wait too
long to follow that
advice two Stephanie did not lay on her
back for months because Anthony told her
she had an
injury three Stephanie got stuck laying
on her back because Stephanie said
herself she had injured her back doing
yoga and pilates and it was made worse
by Stephanie carrying heavy watermelons
and jumping on the trampoline which you
were actually around to see Stephanie
got stuck laying on her back because her
doctor diagnosed her with a disc injury
and because she was on a small old
childhood mattress on the floor that was
terrible for her back and made it too
difficult for her to get up four
Stephanie did not bleed from both
nipples she only bled from one and five
Anthony never ever told Stephanie that
she would never have
cancer and six Anthony did not cut
Stephanie off Stephanie's family told
Anthony to stay
away Stephanie did not text Anthony
begging him to talk to
her Ashley was so wrong about all of it
from the beginning and yet she continued
to berate you Kim for the factual letter
you had sent out to your small private
Community further text messages in this
thread from Ashley to you said this she
found a lump in her breast three years
before she died and he told her it would
never be cancerous does that bother you
at all does it like hello is this hting
home I get that you weren't there when
that happened but I was does that I mean
come on that series of texts from Ashley
is not only incredibly condescending but
also has three more false things in it
the first one Stephanie did not discover
her breast lump when she was living with
Ashley in
2016 Stephanie in fact discovered the
lump a year later when Ashley was not
around the second false thing Anthony
never told Stephanie that the lump would
never become cancerous he repeatedly
encouraged her to get it looked at by a
physician and here Ashley's putting you
down by claiming that she was around
when you were not which is the exact
opposite of the truth that's the third
falsehood our data shows that Ashley
wasn't around for any single part of
Stephanie's experience with her breast
lump her back injury her her cancer or
her passing and yet you were physically
there helping Stephanie as much as you
could after just having a baby during
Stephanie's
illness you responded to Ashley by
saying in all caps I'm driving in the
pouring
rain which sounds to me like you were
begging her to stop attacking you and
then Ashley replied to you by saying
this I'm not there to see it so maybe
it's not actually happening
later
cim and then she sends three IR roll
emojis what Ashley is again
condescendingly implying to you is that
you don't believe in Ashley's story
which we know is
false she's saying it's because you
weren't there to see it and that's why
you don't believe her Ashley is saying
that Ashley was there to see it and you
weren't but in reality it's the exact
opposite the real truth is that you were
there and Ashley wasn't the truth you
were
there Ashley wasn't if Ashley wants to
play the comparison game and use
physical proximity as a measure of
someone's authority to speak on
Stephanie then in reality based on facts
Ashley loses at her own
game however Ashley ends up going on to
say this to you I know that you can see
what you did I know
it I don't know how you can live with it
but I know you can see it and I hope it
haunts you bye
Kim and then you replied by saying no
Ash we all tried to help with all we had
when it was going on I know you don't
realize that but it's the truth I was
barely paying my own bills and was
buying her supplements at one point and
doing everything I could with a brand
new baby nobody saw that make me a
monster
though and then Ashley sent you some
voice messages that we're going to play
now Kim I don't think that you're a
monster I think that what you did in
your letter is you isolated facts and
you painted an untrue picture of what
happened it's just not
true for you to use the facts that you
do have and manipulate them in such a
way I just I mean come
on and honestly I don't even care about
all the people that it impacted because
they will have their chance to hear the
truth I can't even call it lying because
of the way that you used facts but you
used them so articulately to distort the
truth that it ended up being a lie and I
hate that I can't stand liars
wow wow just unreal
Wow first of
all I want to oh
sorry it still gives me Goose Goosebumps
hearing that
yeah yeah yeah yeah I can imagine it's
she first of all I want to point out
that Ashley said here that she doesn't
care about all the people who her post
impacted because she's saying that they
will have their chance to hear the truth
in fact the people Ashley impacted with
her false 2020 posts didn't get a chance
to hear the truth before these podcasts
if they're even still around and
listening Ashley has impacted many
people and hurt many people with her
disinformation secondly Ashley's being
incredibly manipulative in these
messages she's twisted everything around
so much it's actually scary she's
attacking you relentlessly while you're
driving in the pouring rain her
information is all wrong she wasn't
actually there and you were yet she's
putting you down demeaning you and
admitting that you used facts so she
can't actually call it lying but at the
same time she's calling you a liar with
all those falsities in her text at the
same
time how did it feel to have a grown
woman act like this and treat you like
this
honestly Amber I have PTSD from what
Ashley did to me that night I was
driving to my sister-in-law's wedding
festivities I was alone it was dark it
was pouring down rain Ashley would not
stop she wouldn't stop I had to call my
husband on the phone because I was
shaking at the time I was doing my best
to protect Stephanie's privacy and to
not let her be exploited by Ashley it's
really sad that Ashley has it this far
I've now been attacked personally
professionally my family has been
attacked Ashley is actually the most
intimidating person I've ever
met yeah I'm so sorry Kim that you've
had to go through all that and it's
really not okay that she's that she
attacked you like this and it's really
Brave of you to come on here and talk
about it because I'm sure that
everything we're discussing you know
brings up a lot of emotion and what's
even worse is that Ashley didn't stop
there that exchange that we just went
through was in
2020 now 3 years later several months
ago after I caught Ashley and the other
plotters for what they were trying to do
to Anthony and the medical medium
community and we exposed them in our
podcast episodes Ashley went on a
rampage on social media rather than
addressing any of her false claims we
had corrected her on with evidence she
pivoted onto other points of focus she
began bullying and making fun of Anthony
she made fun of the light blast and the
collecting Stones meditation she made
fun of the medical medium Community many
of its members one of her targets was
you and shockingly your
kids on August 17th Ashley posted this
this is not enough fuel for a child to
thrive
if you watch closely you will see that
the children of influencers who promote
extremely restricted diets are often
incredibly small just like Kim's
kids in this she tagged you along with a
screenshot of a photo of your three kids
plates that you had posted that You'
captioned Beach
snacks the plates all have a lot of
avocado a bunch of cucumber sticks a
bunch of strawberries and a pile of
cooked cassaba flour tortilla
chips Ashley continues on in the next
story post switching back to the priate
convo for a second many of you are
sharing more accounts of raw vegan
children and it's really sad a few of
you have made the point that some kids
are just small and that's true some kids
are just small but all ra vegan kids are
noticeably small in a significant way
I've never seen a single example
otherwise bu would welcome being
challenged on that
point and then just a little bit later
after Ashley must have gotten some
serious push back on this she deleted
the first story and then posted this one
I did remove that repost of the lunch
trays though because it didn't sit right
with me I don't want to tear down moms
on here however I still think it is sad
and abusive to raise your kids on a
severely restricted diet how about
y'all when I first read this I was sick
to my stomach this is truly despicable
behavior from Ashley and I would ask any
mom out there how would you feel if
somebody did this to you and your kids
everyone is entitled of course to their
own dietary belief system but it is
unacceptable to shame and attack moms
publicly for how you think they feed
their kids like
this next I have to walk us through and
point out the falsehoods and
inconsistencies here because it's
insane Ashley attacked yuk Kim for
supposedly Mal nourishing your children
referring to a photo of your kids plates
as lunch trays when in the exact
screenshot Ashley used from you you
literally captioned it Beach snacks and
she has that in the photo that she
reposted how much sense does it make to
judge what somebody feeds their kids as
a snack as if it were a meal first of
all and then the snack plates in the
photo have plenty of food on them there
are piles of cooked cassava flow chips
with guacamole there are plenty of
strawberries and cucumber sticks as I
said they were Beach snacks they weren't
intended to be a Thanksgiving dinner
they were
snacks once again Ashley got it
wrong all of your posts online show your
fridge being loaded with huge amounts of
food and your kids eating plenty of food
with tons of variety your kids are
obviously far from restricted and it's
clear that Ashley was just trying to
hurt you and I'm
sorry thank you yeah she definitely got
me with that one um it first made me
really mad I cried a lot and then I
actually started to laugh because it's
just so insane we were traveling when I
posted those trays it was my husband's
40th birthday those trays don't belong
to me but I can tell you they were giant
man-sized trays my baby was one at the
time my daughter in preschool and my son
is eight they're little young children
you are correct Amber these were snacks
to take to the
beach as for the insults about my kids I
was so sick years ago before medical
medium and these kids were raised with
the principles that healed my body none
of them have ever had a cavity they
rarely catch colds and flu and when they
get something they bounce right back I
attribute that to the way that we live
and I would never call that restrictive
illness is
restrictive Wellness is freedom and I
know so many of you would agree with
that
yes yes really well said and I also want
to point out how Ashley conflates
medical medium information with raw
veganism yet again I know that your kids
are not raw
vegan yeah Amber my kids are not raw
vegan they never have been I have no
idea why Ashley would put me in that
category there's nothing wrong with raw
vegans but my kids are not and they
never have been my son has consumed
cooked soup that Ashley herself made
while I was staying with
her um that was when we went to visit
her family's home in Pepple Beach my son
was also one of the first ones to trial
her cooked bread recipe and some of the
cooked potato recipe in Ashley's ebooks
that I always supported one scroll back
will let all of you see that my kids eat
loads of produce yes they do and they
enjoy it but they also consumed cooked
foods and they eat plenty of treats
they're kids you guys once again Ashley
got it
wrong yeah once again very wrong it's so
upsetting
and I'm sure I'm sure it's so upsetting
I can't imagine having my kids attacked
like that um it's so Ashley has actually
seen your kids eat cooked food that she
made
herself and she still called them raw
vegan it's it's mind-blowing correct and
correct what what's so insane and what
also speaks to how carelessly Ashley
just hurdles out attacks with paying
such little attention to facts and
details is that in the exact screenshot
Ashley took from you and displayed in
her post it clearly shows cooked chips
on all of your kids plates you even
tagged the brand of the cooked chips you
gave your kids as a snack with guacamole
anybody could figure out that they are
cooked chips and obviously if you're
feeding your kids cooked chips they're
not raw vegan and what Ashley's saying
doesn't make any
sense Ashley got all of these things so
wrong anybody who's viewing these
stories can catch the inconsistencies
for themselves but this is how Ashley is
sloppy Ashley never has the details
right makes mistakes constantly and
leaves a trail of falsities
everywhere and then in this series of
attacks on your kids Ashley had the
audacity to call your children
small Kim your kids are objectively some
of the healthiest and strongest looking
kids that I've ever seen it's ridiculous
thank
you I'm super blessed in that department
and if you followed along with my
journey you've likely seen the pictures
of my son that I've shared over the past
year I'm pretty proud of him he's a head
taller than most of the kids in this
grade he's 90th percentile for height
he's a travel and All-Star baseball
player in fact he was on three baseball
teams this year he's strong he's fast
he's unbelievable and I know that sounds
ridiculous because he's my son but I
have every right to be proud after I
went through what I went through with
his birth and postpartum with him and
just being so unwell years ago before
finding Anthony
he's not small at all it's quite the
opposite my middle daughter and there's
been a lot of commenting about her in
the community because I've shared her
too she's a gymnast she's an All-Star
cheerleader who has literally abs of
steel um if you've seen videos of her
you've likely seen a lot of you have
commented she's literally jacked the
girl has muscles that I didn't have when
I was training during some of the most
intense training periods of my life
she's muscle and my baby who is now two
is literally a tub she's got a couple
chin rolls um so while this does make me
angry and you know she did attack my
children I really think that one simple
photo tells it all it's time for me to
speak out because actually Ashley is a
bully she bullied my children who does
that really who does that these are lies
she has no business commenting on my
children she has no idea how big or
small they are
she has no idea what they
eat I'm still laughing at the
accusations from the chips and guacamole
plate that was my husband's
40th birthday it was a party at the
beach this is just one example of how my
life has been disrupted for years now
because of Ashley her social media post
ruined that trip for me and my husband's
40th birthday because they changed my
mood completely they were hurtful and
they brought a tremendous amount of
stress by publicly attacking me and my
kids yeah it's terrible and it's
ridiculous Ashley never should have
stooped that low she never should have
done that then after Ashley clearly must
have gotten called out Ashley said she
removed that post because she doesn't
want to tear down moms on here but she
still left another story post up in
which she attacked a different mom and
her kid for their diet it's obvious that
the whole point of these posts was to
put down moms for how Ashley thinks they
feed their kids in the way that their
kids look and like you said Kim who does
that Ashley literally used the word
abuse and applied that you were abusing
your kids by what you're feeding them
when she wasn't even accurate with any
of her
claims there's nothing more egregious
Ashley just didn't get away with it and
after receiving push back that's when
she deleted some of it your kids are not
even raw
vegan some of it yeah she deleted only
some of it and left other parts up
yeah your kids are not even raw vegan
medical medium information is not the
same thing as raw veganism her posts
don't make logical sense Ashley's raw
vegan attacks are also especially
baffling to me considering the fact that
many of her own best friends and co-plot
are actually raw vegans yeah I wonder
how Ashley's raw vegan co- plotters and
best friends feel now about how they
have supported Ashley and getting to
where she is now that she uses her
platform to viciously criticize the diet
that they follow and promote in their
businesses going as far as to call moms
who feed their kids raw vegan food
abusive plus what Ashley said in this
Rampage is wildly contradictive to what
Ashley has said self in the past in an
Instagram story post that Ashley made at
the end of 2019 to sell her own ebook
she said this you deserve to nourish
your body in whatever way you choose
without fear of
condemnation you deserve unquestioned
authority over what your children are
fed
unreal wild
contradiction this is another prime
example
of sloppy Ashley it's a prime example of
someone who is always changing to fit a
narrative that suits her agenda of the
moment Kim this was absolutely
reprehensible of Ashley to- do to your
to you and your family and I'm so sorry
that you were the target of this attack
and that your kids were the target of
this
attack it's been a lot it's impacted my
husband in a big way too it's been
completely
unnecessary stress and from mother to
mother all I think about every time she
puts these posts out there is that this
is time and energy away from our kids
and away from our families we're not
getting this time
back like I said so many trips so many
family events so many holidays so many
birthdays have been ruined for me
because of unnecessary abuse from
Ashley Kim I can't imagine being being a
mom and then being publicly shamed for
feeding your kids healthy
snacks and being shamed in a way that
confuses people into thinking that you
must be some kind of terrible Mom that's
abusively starving your kids it's
uncons sadly Ashley has so many things
wrong another exhibit on how Ashley
makes mistakes it makes sense as to how
Ashley got everything wrong to begin
with with the Stephanie story when you
look at how many things how many details
and how many claims are twisted
discombobulated and just straight out
factually
incorrect exactly exactly and now Kim I
want to just bring us back to 2020 for a
moment I know that Ashley was attacking
you in a similar way in the comments of
her retaliation post back then and
implying that you hadn't done enough for
Stephanie when she was sick your husband
defended you in a comment in which he
said this to Ashley can't sleep because
your comment of expecting Kimberly to go
in a hospital right after having a child
is ridiculous postpartum mothers are
supposed to be resting she wasn't
resting as she was making food and other
stuff to send to Steph on top of driving
it to her before she was cleared to
actually drive all of this led to the
issues you mentioned of an enlarged
uterus from not resting and taking care
of herself clearly wasn't enough for you
I guess and for the record I was the one
that held her back and didn't want her
to do even more than she already did and
kept her out of the hospital which is no
place for a new mother if it can be
avoided so I guess I'm the bad guy here
for trying to protect
Kimberly all of this was playing out
online at the same time as Ashley was
attacking you in the written and audio
texts we went through
previously and then there was an email
you'd sent to someone who was your
friend at the time the next
morning I have that email in front of me
and it says thank you for the email last
night Ashley started sending me terrible
text messages voice messages and then
that post I'm not sure what prompted all
of it honestly I didn't even read it as
I was at a family event honoring my soon
Tobe sister-in-law my poor husband was
defending our side of the story as she
put my personal information right in
that post and failed to mention that I
had a baby who was just weeks old as we
were still running around and trying to
do what we could on No Sleep our lives
are very different and I don't think Ash
can understand a family that has to work
for a living and care for their children
without help and servants I'm not being
condescending but realistic the
statements she made about me were
appalling I was driving things to Steph
before I was even cleared to drive a car
after birth these girls put that
pressure on me my husband was so upset
that he took on as much as he could I'm
really really hurt by the twists and
lies it's a different lifestyle and she
can't wrap her head around a mother
working and caring for two children
without a nanny or understand that
husbands leave and go to work all of
this on no sleep with a newborn and a
2-year-old but somehow I didn't do
enough for her I had Gretchen staying at
my home during such a sacred time of
having a newborn not to mention my fear
of her being in and out of the hospital
and around my tiny new baby I don't know
what the answer is here but she is
pointing a lot of fingers and there is
no truth to so much of what she's saying
I feel awful harsh and heavy energy from
her she has an agenda to spread fear and
make herself look like a hero I wish she
would spread Steph's life and her love
and her beautiful spirit this is just
upsetting anyway I'm pretty exhausted
from all of this I hope you are resting
today as I can barely move from all the
stress last night
Kimberly can you share more with us Kim
about why why it was that Ashley and
Gretchen were putting so much pressure
on you to help Stephanie more and more
when you just had a baby there was so
much going on and it was up to a 4-Hour
drive one way for you why did Stephanie
need so help with food poor Stephanie
wouldn't eat the hospital food she was
relying on friends to bring her food
when she couldn't get enough help from
friends or family she just wouldn't eat
looking back I asked myself why wouldn't
an extremely wealthy friend send food a
chef support something instead I was
pushed to the max I opened up my home
postpartum to Gretchen who came to care
for Stuff Gretchen was also met at the
airport with a hot tea and a home-cooked
meal that my husband and I prepared for
her I wanted to support the situation as
best I could at the time but nothing I'm
telling you nothing that I did was good
enough nothing I don't get that time
back with my newborn I don't get to do
it again I don't get to hold her again
as a newborn I don't get to be there
again with my two-year-old son I I went
through all of this and that time is
just it's gone it's passed and now I
live with Ash trashing me whenever she
chooses and continuing to disrupt your
family time and it just seems really odd
to me that you were the object of blame
here and especially when you and your
husband did as much as you could for
Stephanie after just having a baby and
not living that close to her it seems
like over and over again throughout the
whole Stephanie situation the plotters
Ashley Robbie Taylor Christina Megan
Tony Gretchen have tried to place blame
on people who were actually trying to
help yeah many of Stephanie's friends
were just doing the best they could to
help her when it was possible and that
was all acceptable they were happy if
someone donated some time or some energy
or some food or whatever it was but
somehow I was definitely a Target in the
whole thing I was being pushed to do
more and more and more and whatever I
did it was not good enough I did what I
could in the situation I was in with a
brand new baby somehow the 2-year-old
little boy and the several week old
little girl that I had in my arms while
my husband was away at work was
completely overlooked they just kept
looking at me like I was some kind of
robot that was supposed to go and do and
do more and more it was
horrible wow yeah wow and in reality I
mean you were trying so hard to help
Stephanie in an impossible situation on
no sleep that you actually had gasoline
sprayed all over you to the point that
your hair was drenched and Ashley who
was putting all this pressure on you was
nowhere to be found and an exposure like
that of getting straight gasoline
sprayed all over your head all on your
hair all over your body it's treacherous
that much gasoline all on your body
soaked on you like that gets absorbed
into your breast milk you just had a
baby
and then your immune system is already
comp compromised because you had a baby
and then you yourself Kim were sick
years ago this is a major exposure which
could trigger your system and then if
you were sitting in your car right after
you just had gasoline dumped all over
you if you had accidentally hit the car
lighter with your elbow or your hand or
your phone just by putting your phone
down you could have gone up and Flames
all it would take is just one spark from
an electrical wire from just the
ignition of the car starting and you
would have burned up and died along with
your baby in the car all because you're
helping out a friend Stephanie while
Ashley was sitting in Malibu in her
multi-million dollar house and then
spreading rumors and false claims about
how you and Stephanie weren't even
friends yeah
not
friends it actually haunts me Anthony
the whole situation haunts me it was
traumatic like truly traumatic for me
and to have to live with the constant
social media insults threats and stress
it just brings it all up over and over
and over again every single time I see
her starting posting it's like the antic
start and I just it it all comes up over
and over again for
me I'm so sorry him thanks Amber
and yeah you you
also awful yeah it's
aw you also ended up unfortunately with
an enlarged uterus because you were
standing up constantly making food
driving long distances before you were
cleared to and bringing food to
Stephanie instead of resting postpartum
and at the same time Ashley was nowhere
to be
found while you were going so far out of
your way to help Stephanie that you
risked your own life and your baby's
life and sacrificed your body literally
to help you did all of this because
Stephanie was a close friend of
yours and Ashley was nowhere to be found
yet Ashley has the nerve and entitlement
to imply that you weren't doing enough
for Steph and that you weren't even a
friend of hers at
all Yeah Ashley always communicated as a
very entitled manipulative woman I just
didn't know to what extent back then
that she was
entitled um when we all flew out to
Pebble Beach to stay in her family's
home Stephanie actually didn't have the
money to go and it was a really touchy
subject but meanwhile Ashley the
daughter of a billionaire family didn't
offer support to her then I look back at
those emails wondering why did Ashley
not just buy her a ticket if they were
such good
friends yeah it's a really great
question and I looked through those
emails there are a few I want to read
off for everyone the first one was from
Stephanie to everyone on the email
thread that Ashley had invited to a
weekend getaway
it was sent on January 11th of 2017 just
a few months before Stephanie discovered
her breast lump and it says hey I'm
still in the unknown territory if I can
come or not financially at the moment
not best however things could turn
around and make it possible very quickly
flight prices are low so that's a plus
so I may have to wait as it gets closer
to make a move is that
okay this question question was directed
to Ashley and Stephanie said that flight
prices are low but still too much for
her to afford at the
moment then on January 22nd of 2017
Ashley sends an email to everyone in the
group with a status update and some
background information about each person
for her friends who hadn't met each
other before Ashley's update to everyone
about Stephanie says this Stephanie
possible step is trying to make it work
work financially I so want her to be
there Steph is a wealth of information
and a bright positive Shining Light in
any group she's part of for dinner she
likes to eat heads of Roma lettuce
dipped in kind pepper and lemon if
that's not next level I don't know what
is I was shocked by this email because
here Ashley is actually praising
Stephanie for eating only lettuce with
cayenne and lemon for
dinner as we've covered a lot obviously
a head of lettuce as a meal let alone
for dinner is not enough it is not
MediCal medium information this is
something Anthony absolutely advises
against it was Stephanie's pre-existing
approach to food that here we see Ashley
praising and calling next level like
restricting yourself is something that
everyone should aspire to do
and Ashley said in this email that she
so wants Stephanie to be there Stephanie
had said herself that flight prices were
low at the time in 2017 flight prices
were quite a bit cheaper than they are
today I'm sure that she could have
gotten a flight from Philly to La where
Ashley suggested everyone to fly into
from a Budget Airline for 99 to
$150 Ashley is the daughter of a
billionaire family and has a trust fund
as you said if Ashley was truly such
great friends with Stephanie and really
wanted Stephanie there why wouldn't
Ashley have just gotten her the plane
ticket yeah looking back I really do not
understand it especially with all the
finger pointing Ashley has done Ashley
let her miss out because Stephanie
couldn't afford it and then Ashley even
asked everyone in the group who was
coming to her family's multi-million
dollar home for a weekend for a cleaning
fee
I saw that in the email
thread unbelievable a cleaning
fee so after the Pebble Beach thing just
a few months later Stephanie discovers
her breast lump in March and then she
injures her back and then she gets sick
during the time that Stephanie was Ill
how would you describe Ashley's
relationship with Stephanie's family do
you know if they interacted were they
close what was that like Ashley actually
talked negatively about Stephanie's
family there was this constant thing
where the family wanted Stephanie to
receive conventional Cancer Care and the
plotters were not in agreement with the
family's wishes Stephanie's personal
wishes were pushed completely to the
side at the time the plotters and the
family were not on the same page at all
so it's so unbelievably strange to me
that now they've come together to BL and
attack Anthony who wasn't even involved
in Stephanie's Cancer Care because the
family cut off communication with him it
was a lot for me birthing a baby and
trying to simultaneously support a
friend who was not well and listening to
Stephanie stress literally stress about
her support people closest to her not
getting along I was dealing with the
text threads with the plotters that were
trashing and fighting with her family it
was horrendous seeing those plotters who
were disagreeing with and arguing with
Stephanie's family now representing and
advocating for them or with them is very
confusing to me my own data clearly
shows that there was a major issue
between the plotters and Stephanie's
family my husband witnessed this in
person when he went into the hospital to
visit Stephanie the plotters and the
family were not on the same
page that's extremely interesting and is
something that's very it's very
confusing to think about that as well
and how things somehow changed and
flipped in that way and then what
happened when your husband went to the
hospital to visit and bring food to
Stephanie what what did he
see so my husband observed an argument
between Taylor Stephanie and Stephanie's
family Stephanie didn't want the
treatment at the hospital that was being
offered at that moment she was crying
it's heartbreaking Taylor was on her
team and she was fighting with the
family Stephanie wanted to go to Mexico
for an alternative treatment but her
family didn't agree to this my husband
just wanted to have a genuine
conversation with Stephanie the way that
he had so many times in the past but it
was uncomfortable and impossible because
of this conflict that was going on while
he was there instead he tried to be
helpful and find creative ways to keep
the food cold and be sure that juices
were kept fresh for her but the family
they always hated the way that she ate
dating back years before Stephanie even
knew Anthony the family did not like the
way that she ate the family made my
husband feel like he was a villain for
bringing food to
Stephanie
wow so there was this massive ongoing
battle between the plotters and the
family completely independent of Anthony
and just to bring this all together for
everyone all Anthony ever did in this
whole situation as we've shown was
encourage Stephanie to see a doctor
offer emotional support and try to get
her up off the floor she got stuck on
due to her injury so that she could get
in for proper Medical Care Anthony was
not Stephanie's health practitioner
Anthony is not an oncologist in order to
get diagnosed with cancer you need to
see a board certified oncologist ologist
from the moment Stephanie discovered her
breast lump she was repeatedly told by
Anthony to see a physician if Stephanie
had listened to Anthony's advice to see
a doctor from the
beginning outcomes probably would have
been entirely different and we probably
wouldn't need to be sitting here today
to talk about this and you Kim you even
talked with Stephanie early on about
doctors she could see in the area that
were near her and you said earlier on
that Stephanie wasn't receptive to that
at the
time and so then Stephanie's battle with
cancer ended up going on for about a
year after Anthony was told aggressively
to stay away during that time again
independent of Anthony the plotters were
fighting for Stephanie to get some kind
of alternative treatment for her cancer
while the family on the other hand
wanted her to do conventional
treatment while Stephanie was SI sick
the plotters and the family were at odds
Waring with each other and then when did
things change when did you see the
plotter start coming around and and
coming together with the family to try
to blame
Anthony I honestly didn't see things
change until years after Stephanie
passed away months after Stephanie
passed away I was invited to her
celebration of life the plotters were
offering Retreats yeah they were
offering retreats to the medical medium
community and then all of a sudden the
pters changed their tune it was
literally overnight and to me that seems
so clear that an agenda was
born yeah it's pretty crazy and then I
want to bring it back to when Stephanie
was Ill when you went to go bring
Stephanie food at the time that she was
living in her family's home what was
that experience like for you I went to
Stephanie's family's home to pick
Gretchen up who was going to stay in my
home Gretchen was using my husband's car
but on that day he had to travel for
work so I drove to pick her up I was
drenched And Gasoline by the time that I
got there and needed to take a shower
and rinse off as quickly as possible I
showered in one of Stephanie's family's
bathrooms it was a really scary time for
me I had my newborn baby and I brought
her in her little car seat because
Stephanie wanted to meet her she
actually wasn't able to hold the the
baby due to the drugs that she was on I
dropped off some food for her and was
just in shocked from all that happened
with the gasoline and all that was
happening around me in that moment it
was around the same time when I was told
by Gretchen that she had observed
Stephanie with dust bunnies on her head
and face and that Gretchen had to dust
her off when she arrived in her home my
heart was broken and honestly it's still
is
Amber that is horrifying and and the
fact that it was Gretchen who is now a
plotter who saw the dust situation is
especially
interesting yeah it was horrible all of
it the the whole situation was horrible
it was so hard to see it was hard to
hear it was hard to experience and all
at the same time with everything that I
had going on I felt so terrible for
Stephanie and I couldn't understand why
and everything that she was going
through that she would be covered in
dust
yeah yeah that's something that's really
hard for me to wrap my head around as
well
and so then it's some point when
Stephanie was sick Taylor Who's now also
a plotter stepped in could you explain
what your experience was like with her
and what role Taylor
played so Taylor was one of the ones
arguing at the hospital she basically
took over but she also was not fond of
the family and they were not F of her
Taylor was in charge though or at least
she thought she was in charge of the
whole situation she was so manipulative
and so bossy on the text messages and on
the phone I had never even met her in
person like have never met this woman
ever yet she was calling me out and
saying I needed to do more even though I
had a newborn and I remember thinking
that she was really insensitive and mean
and I didn't and and she just didn't
realize I'm like does this woman realize
I have a newborn right now she she just
didn't
understand yeah that that description
especially the bossiness matches a lot
of the experiences that I had with
Taylor several months ago in person um
so so Stephanie was in a vulnerable
position her back injury prevented her
from being able to do much herself she
was having a hard time getting the food
that she needed you said earlier that
she wasn't really making her own
decisions Taylor who was acting you know
as her caretaker and Stephanie's family
were making a lot of decisions for her
you were being supportive and trying to
help out as best as you could did you
and Stephanie stay in touch throughout
the course of her illness or how did
that go so for a long time we were in
Daily communication personally and also
in group chats with various different
plotters that were discussing
Stephanie's situation all of a sudden
out of the blue Stephanie stopped
responding to me I was told by Gretchen
that her brother took her phone away and
I never heard from her again I was also
removed from the group chats it was very
very weird because Stephanie normally
would text a lot and send a lot of audio
messages and all of that I was again
newly postpartum so swallowing this was
all really hard and I was just trying to
survive and feeling completely
heartbroken at the same
time wow yeah so you were told by
Gretchen that Stephanie's brother took
Stephanie's phone
away wow and we actually have text
messages and audio recordings
corroborating what you just said that
we'll be sharing in another episode it's
really sad that you had the same
experience as other friends of
Stephanie's who were either cut off
without explanation or were told that
they were not allowed to speak with her
yeah and then I'm also curious about
experience with Stephanie before she got
sick what were Stephanie's eating habits
like before she got
sick so actually shocking to me as
someone that eats a very clean diet
which has reversed my own symptoms years
ago I I was actually shocked when I met
Stephanie for lunch or at a juice bar
she wouldn't eat it was very rare that
she would eat something she mostly
wouldn't eat at all not even at a
completely organic juice bar one time I
actually had a car full of fresh organic
produce like wholesale produce fresh and
she wouldn't touch any of the fruit and
she would eat only the lettuce and I
just always felt like she was starving
and it just it just broke my
heart yeah so you experienced Stephanie
having some pre-existing problems with
food just eating lettuce is definitely
not MediCal medium information and it's
really sad frankly yeah and
yeah this goes along with so much
evidence that we have of what Stephanie
was eating and not eating which is the
exact opposite of the story Ashley tried
to tell starting in 2020 about Stephanie
following medical medium information to
a
te so Ashley's told many false stories
about Stephanie and many other things
and now you've heard all the different
iterations of the infamous cat story we
shared earlier on in this podcast series
Ashley told me directly in my calls with
her that Anthony had put her on a
fat-free raw diet and completely missed
the cat
allergy however one of the true
versions of that cat story came from a
text conversation Ashley had with you on
September 14th of 2018 which was months
after she had given away their pet cat
because in fact Anthony had said that
the cat was part of the problem in
Ashley's text to you Ashley said that
Anthony told her to cut out nuts and
seeds specifically for her son's eczema
but that fats like olive oil were
okay she also said to you that Anthony
had recommended lots of squash which is
something that would be cooked of course
not raw so Ashley obviously was not put
in a fat-free raw
diet yeah this one is really crazy to
hear so versions of this story Ashley
and I were actually talking about this
because my daughter had skin issues
temporarily directly following my
exposure to all the gasoline that I was
sprayed with while I was breastfeeding
her I have texts from Ashley saying that
Anthony told her to cut out nuts and
seeds specifically because of the
Arginine and that other fats like olive
oil were okay and cooked squashes were
okay and that he suggested bringing in
cooked squashes again along with
bringing in lots of green
juices yeah okay
so now I'm
wondering it's I mean years ago Ashley
in all all these false stories I'm sure
Ashley years ago told you a lot of the
false stories that we've debunked in
these podcasts like the origin of the
breast lump Discovery and the infamous
cat story and it's got to feel really
weird to look back and realize that you
too were told so many untrue stories
that were Ashley's foundational building
blocks to get Robbie and the others on
board to try to take down the medical
medium Community it has been really
upsetting to see this story evolve after
seeing Ashley tell her healing story at
the medical medium live event I know
some of you remember it or you remember
hearing about it Ashley herself was
suffering and I mean really suffering
and hearing her words firsthand and
seeing her life turn around and now for
her to do this it doesn't make much
sense to me the very information that
saved her life and these are her words
not mine and saved my life and several
of the other practitioners were
plotters and now to twist it and to
trash it and to manipulate it into an
article and into an agenda is just
upsetting she has been trying so hard to
convince everyone out there of things
that are simply not true about Anthony
and about this situation she tried to
Corner me and make me believe things
that are not true Anthony saved my life
and I've watched thousands of Miracles
over the years thanks to this
information there is such a clear agenda
here and I actually feel really bad for
everyone who has been swallowed up by
this so many of them have been saved by
this same information thanks to Anthony
and I know very personally that he has
helped most of these plotters some of
them in their Darkest Hour even after
Stephanie's death even when they have
walked away from the information but
that just tells you who Anthony
is
yeah
wow I just have to say how sorry I am
again that Ashley targeted you and your
family came the way that she did in so
many different instances she clearly
didn't know the facts about the
Stephanie story she just felt entitled
apparently to say whatever she wanted
she said herself in her text to you that
she didn't care about any of the people
in the medical medium Community who she
hurt with her 2020 posts if Ashley had
genuine questions or concerns about what
had happened with Stephanie if she had
any real interest in pursuing the truth
she could have asked Anthony about
anything she never did she could have
asked you she never did she decided to
take it public only a few months after
still trying to sell the medical medium
community on her self-proclaimed
expensive Retreats with celery juice and
a weight loss plan she tried to act like
some kind of hero or whistleblower when
she used a completely false story Ashley
exploited Stephanie and her private
information which is the saddest part
yeah she caused outrage and Chaos in the
medical medium Community with her false
stories she put you and others in a
situation where you'd have to defend the
truth and then she had the nerve to
attack you for
it yeah she attacked my family my
children my profession and I just want
to talk about her weight loss book for a
second twisting the information and
claiming to be an expert Beyond
Anthony's books I don't quite understand
it Amber but I can tell you that it
confused a lot of people Ashley's ebook
was targeting postpartum women and it
was a weight loss plan with portion
sizes in ounce amounts I consulted with
a lot of postpartum women who were
influenced by Ashley's ebook to eat less
food and restrict their calories as a
means of rapid weight loss they were
under the impression that they were
still following medical medium
information when medical medium
information does not restrict calories
they were just following Ashley's
Twisted
information a lot of these women had
their supply of breast milk drop because
they were not eating enough and some of
them even blamed medical medium
information for that when it it wasn't
medical medium information it was
Ashley's portion controlled information
that she was marketing to the community
and it was so
irresponsible Ashley has done a lot of
damage I'm hurt I'm lost I'm traumatized
by all of it and I just wanted to
stop yeah yeah that's crazy that you've
had that you had those direct
experiences and uh with the impact that
Ashley's that her weight loss ebook had
on women particularly postpartum women
in the community that's extremely sad
and Ashley really is the original of
twisting medical medium information and
um she's had a lot of influence on how
that's happened in more recent times
even you know with other people in other
cases and it's all really sad and Ashley
has indeed done a lot of damage and
that's why it's so important that we're
here you know to set the record straight
to help stop Ashley and the plotters
from misleading deceiving hurting or
taking the chance to heal away
from anyone else so thank you very much
Kim for coming on I know that you're a
busy mom of three little ones and that
this wasn't easy to do I really
appreciate you being here and sharing a
lot of these really difficult
experiences and I appreciate both of you
very much it's unfortunate that we had
to get together for something like this
setting the record straight I'm sure the
medical medium community and anyone even
outside of the medical medium Community
truly appreciates your caring and
willingness to get the truth out there
thank you Kim thank you guys I
appreciate you
both thanks
than as we are in the process of
exposing Ashley and her organized
hateful group for who and what they
really are it's important to take note
of their tactics and patterns that are
likely to follow the plotters have a
documented history of initiating attacks
using lies and misinformation and then
upon getting called out and corrected
trying to flip it and play victim that
is not going to work here all this group
has done is spread verifiable lies and
falsities they've carelessly attacked
and harmed many innocent people they've
used and exploited deceased individuals
and others in the process of trying to
get what they want they've repeatedly
explicitly expressed the intent to harm
medical medium and they've even
deliberately tried to stop Anthony from
doing a free event to support and raise
money for the community we have every
right to set the record straight and to
defend the truth with facts and evidence
and to defend the chronically ill
against the malicious attacks of this
group and we are going to continue to do
so we expect the plotters to evade and
ignore what they have done wrong we
expect them to continue to lie and
spread falsities we expect them to Pivot
onto something new they'll make up and
we expect them to skew and alter d data
and to hide critical pieces of evidence
that undermines their entire campaign we
also expect the plotters to fabricate
explanations as they do everything they
can to try to discredit what we're
exposing them for having done and said
in their own words but we are using
their own text messages voice messages
social media posts words that they spoke
on recorded calls and other published
materials there's no use of any AI in
any of these episodes and never will be
all of the information was fact checked
and forensically investigated if you've
been harmed deterred from your healing
process bullied shamed emotionally upset
or physically hurt by flareups of your
conditions from the stress induced by
the plotters attacks like hundreds of
others have reported please go to
medicalmedium.com
safespace to submit your report and
share your story if you've been
contacted by anyone who's tried to deter
you from using medical medium
information please take screenshots and
Screen recordings and submit them to the
same place Medical medium.com fors
safespace