The Following episode is part of a
series dedicated to exposing an
organized hateful group that has been on
a Relentless pursuit to destroy the
medical medium community and that has
been attacking bullying harassing and
preying upon the chronically ill joining
me in the series is a guest named Amber
bakaro she's an alternative medicine
practitioner who became a whistleblower
after she witnessed this hateful group
in action when they tried to recruit her
to join them last year Amber caught the
main members of this group on legally
recorded calls describing their
premeditated multi-step plan to create a
quote postm medal medium era by feeding
false stories and claims about me and
about medical medium information to
Major media outlets in hopes that it
would lead to securing themselves a deal
for an anti-ed medium documentary on
Netflix that would bring Fame and other
benefits to them now known infamously
instead for their malicious plot that
was caught on recording and exposed we
refer to this hateful group as the
plotters their entire smear campaign is
spearheaded by one woman who comes from
an extremely wealthy family didn't get
what she wanted from me years ago and is
now seeking re Revenge she's made it her
mission to gather a bunch of plotters
with ulterior motives and AES to grind
including competitors in the health
industry to try to frame medical medium
and take down the community what this
organized hateful group has done is
unprecedented it's one of the biggest
scandals that's ever happened in the
health industry as you'll see it's also
one of the biggest instances of
capturing corruption within the
mainstream media so prepare yourself for
lots of details and nuances as we are
going to be thoroughly untangling the
massive Web of Lies they have spun and
we're going to be releasing a lot of
disturbing new information new
recordings and mind-blowing evidence of
just how far they are going to lie to
try to get what they want some of the
evidence we're presenting in these
episodes in includes original written
content such as text messages social
media posts that have been produced by
the plots and will be reenacted for
greater ease in following along those
who are listening along to the podcast
can find video versions of these
episodes on the medical medium YouTube
and Rumble channels that will be
displaying screenshots photos videos and
more some of you may be unaware that
this has even been happening but many of
you have been tremendously injured and
harmed by what they have done the record
needs to be set straight and they need
to be called out for what they've done
and are still doing the medical medium
Community does not deserve to be
attacked like this and we are going to
set the record straight as many times as
we need to
[Music]
we have a guest here with us today who
is a highly respected holistic health
practitioner and speech pathologist and
was a friend of Stephanie's her name is
Dr Kimberly spare Kim and her husband
supported Stephanie at the time of her
illness back in 2020 Ashley posted her
original false story about Stephanie
which she made more than 15 false claims
in one version of and told more than 20
falsehoods in another version of
Kimberly's husband corrected Ashley in
the comments on something she'd gotten
very wrong and Ashley had to adjust her
false story because of it Kimberly made
a statement to her own small private
Community to calm fears and Chaos that
Ashley had created with her false story
Ashley was not happy about this and she
responded by attacking Kim and trying to
intimidate her to this day Ashley has
continued to publicly attack Kimberly
and and her family Kimberly thank you
for coming on to share your story I know
that the situation has been extremely
upsetting thank you Amber this is a
really sad situation a dear friend that
I cared about is being used for an
agenda that seems to have been created
years after her passing I would have
never shared the intimate details of her
story because Stephanie's privacy is my
number one concern however the plotters
have shared very intimate details of
Stephanie's story and even delic get
unnecessary details about her life I was
recently attacked and have been
continually attacked since 2020 the
attacks were sudden they were out of the
blue I was actually really shocked when
they began I felt it was really
necessary for me to set a few things
straight here
today yeah could you start Kim by
telling us first about your relationship
with Stephanie and how you were
supporting her when she was SI
yeah so we met actually at Ashley's home
during the LA medical medium event
Stephanie and I became instant friends
we realized that we lived just one state
over from each other and that she had a
nephew that was very close and age to my
son we started texting and voice texting
a lot Stephanie was sweet she was funny
she was loving and she was always
looking for advice but she was also
always offering to help in any way that
she could I would meet up with Stephanie
for lunch at the grocery store juice
bars and I met up with her the night
that her niece was born at the hospital
to arm her with the things that she
wanted to support her sister-in-law
through
Labor a few months later I met her
sister-in-law niece and nephew for a
lunch date and we bounced together along
with her family and my family at her
nephew's birthday party Stephanie was so
so proud of rise and nephew
and wanted me to be friends with her
sister-in-law because she thought we had
so much in common and we had kids that
were really close in age I adored
Stephanie and the friendship that we
shared I soon became pregnant with my
second child and Stephanie volunteered
to help me postpartum with my 2-year-old
son the same way that she supported her
sister-in-law and her nephew because she
told me I helped to support her and her
brother and her brother's family
postpartum and that I also needed that
same help she was always so gentle so
kind and always questioned how I was
working full-time how I was pregnant and
also caring for a 2-year-old she got it
and it meant so much to
me when Stephanie got sick I remember
discussing doctors with her and offering
to go with her into the City and hold
her hand but Stephanie was not receptive
to the idea of seeing a doctor at that
time wow and then what was was happening
and what were things like after
Stephanie got sick so this was really
hard when Stephanie took a turn for the
worst I was getting ready to birth my
baby I was planning a vack birth as my
first birth was a traumatic emergency
birth and the stress of what I'm about
to explain was impacting my ability to
birth my baby I was under so much
pressure and I was having such a hard
time shifting into birth mode as I was
on constant group messages with then
friends colleagues medical doctors
consultants and personally with
Stephanie to support her as best I could
the pressure was never ever from
Stephanie it was coming from several of
the plotters mostly Ashley who lived
across the country they were looking at
a map and telling me that I live an hour
and 20 minutes from Stephanie but in
reality with City traffic this
oftentimes could take up to four hours
each way this is why when Stephanie and
I did meet up before she was sick we
were always extremely strategic about
our planning the city traffic where we
live is
horrendous and the driving around here
during the city traffic it's it's just
crazy so back to my birth I was
literally in the birthing tub birthing
my baby on text threads with Stephanie
and with her supporters several of which
are now involved in trying to take this
community down when I finally birthed my
baby I was back on the text threads
within minutes planning how I could best
support Stephanie this was before my
family or my son had even met my new
daughter I was under so much pressure
before I was even cleared to drive by my
midwives I was back on my feet caring
for my newborn caring for my 2-year-old
and driving food and teas and
supplements that Stephanie wanted to her
whenever I could Stephanie herself did
not want me doing this but the platters
continued to push me like I was some
type of robot that should birth a baby
and then be back to running around I
also opened up my home to a house guest
when I was only a few weeks postpartum a
friend Gretchen she came to my house and
stayed with me so that she could support
Stephanie my husband and I gave up a car
we ran arands on no sleep we also opened
our home to
illness as Gretchen was in and out of
the hospital and then back in our home
around my newborn we all came down with
a flu when my baby was just a few weeks
old my two-year-old was also sick it was
one of the hardest experiences of my
life being postpartum having a baby
being exposed to a flu on one trip to
pick up Gretchen again before I was
cleared to drive I was so tired that I
went to pump gas near Stephanie's home
the gas station was old and the pump was
malfunctioning and I was
exhausted I grabbed the noob nozzle and
I pressed it a few times before it
turned on soaking me in gasoline my hair
was soaked my clothes were soaked I was
drenched from head to toe I was sprayed
in the eyes and I felt like I couldn't
breathe I was shaking from the freezing
temperatures my newborn she was in the
back seat breathing in all the
fumes I rushed to Stephanie's house with
my windows down freezing
shaking and I had to shower and wear
someone else's clothes home the whole
time period it was totally
insane I had a baby a baby a newborn
that was just a few weeks old and a
2-year-old son and I was being pushed by
women across the country mostly at asley
to do more and more I had already been
supporting Stephanie in every way that I
could I had given her money I had
purchased supplements that she wanted
and couldn't afford I was cooking her
meals when I could bringing her teas
when I could my husband even took food
to the hospital at one point just days
after my daughter was
born he felt extremely uncomfortable in
the hospital as Stephanie wanted to talk
to him and welcome the food but he felt
so mixed up in a situation where some of
the plotters were screaming at at her
family one of the platters Taylor was
attacking Stephanie's father having a
heated discussion while disagreeing with
Stephanie's father about her
treatment my husband during those days
was rushing home from work so that he or
I could run things we could move cars we
could run errands we could manage house
guests cook meals run guests back and
forth with a baby and a two-year-old I
wanted to do everything for
Stephanie but Ashley was creating a
pressure on that almost broke me during
that
time
wow there's so much to unpack here from
this story and it sounds like such an
unbelievably stressful and traumatic
time having gasoline sprayed all over
your body like that when your body's
already compromised from having just
given birth let alone when your
breastfeeding it's a
tremendous exposure I can't even imagine
I would have been
devastated and despite having just given
birth you and your husband were both
doing the best that you could to help
Stephanie while she was sick you weren't
cleared to even drive yet and you did it
anyway the drive wasn't short I want to
bring in a text that we have from
Stephanie she had sent it to a friend
this was from before she had gotten sick
and she was talking about some items
that she was thinking about picking up
from you and she says okay cool she
isn't super close so may not get it
unless it's super
important this text corroborates this
text from Stephanie corroborates the
fact that you were far enough away from
her that it would have been a hassle for
her to pick up items from your house if
they weren't super
important you said that your husband
brought food to the hospital and spent
time around the family you both were
actually there and you got to witness
what was going on in person when
Stephanie was sick as Ashley mainly was
putting all of this pressure on you to
do more and more I'm wondering where was
Ashley and what was Ashley doing during
the year and a half that Stephanie was
sick I have actually been to Ashley's
family home in Pebble Beach California
but at the time I didn't know how well
off she was she was actually in Malibu
while Stephanie was sick she kept saying
she was very far away
I now wonder why she didn't offer
Stephanie more support or come to see
her she very well had the means to do it
instead Ashley put incredible pressure
on me knowing that I didn't have
postpartum support I didn't have anyone
there helping me supporting me Ashley
and Gretchen were both marketing and
running Retreats during the time of
Stephan's illness and after she passed
the Retreats were out of state and they
had to travel to get to them somehow
Ashley could travel for the Retreats but
she never made it to see
Stephanie yeah so while Ashley was busy
running Retreats with Gretchen in Hawaii
and trying to make money off of the
medical medium Community she was bossing
you around and putting pressure on you
to help even more than you already were
you and your husband were there with
Stephanie and you showed up to help but
Ashley on the other hand we now know
that Ashley wasn't physically present
for any part of Stephanie's breast lump
Discovery she wasn't around for any part
of Stephanie's back injury she didn't
visit Stephanie in the hospital
once as we covered earlier on in these
podcasts Ashley the daughter of a
billionaire family with a private jet
was on a private jet headed to
Pennsylvania where Stephanie was just a
few months before Stephanie died and
Ashley still didn't visit her
yeah I know that Stephanie's family
didn't even like Ashley or any of the
plotters at the time they didn't like
the way that she lived they didn't like
the way that Steph ate which by the way
wasn't exactly medical median she did so
many
things so the family didn't like Ashley
Ashley wasn't around at all and somehow
for some reason Ashley has tried to
position herself as an authority on
Stephanie I want to bring us back to
when Ashley posted her original false
story online in
2020 Ashley made more than 15 false
claims in one version and more than 20
false claims in another version your
husband however having firsthand
knowledge of what had occurred corrected
Ashley in the comments of one of her
posts he said but you're missing the
critical part when Anthony at Medical
medium told told her she needed to see a
doctor and have the lump dealt with oh I
forgot that doesn't fit your
agenda Ashley replied to this by
saying Anthony didn't tell her to see a
doctor until she was bleeding from her
nipples the same point at which he
stopped communicating with
her at this point in the plotter podcast
series we all know that this is far from
the truth to this your husband responded
by saying I don't know the whole story
nor claim to but if you are going to
claim the truth needs to be out there at
least do such a thing in its entirety
the above is one case in point which you
just acknowledge you skipped over and
I'm sure there are others kind of
calling the kettle black when you want
to make allegations of people being
Liars your husband called Ashley out for
being inaccurate and falsely narrating
the story the way that it served her
agenda even people people who didn't
know what happened with Stephanie found
Ashley's story to be alarmingly
inconsistent with what they know of
Anthony and medical medium information
one person commented and said doesn't he
always say to see a doctor and see what
the diagnosis is and go from
there another person added I listen to
Anthony's podcasts and have never heard
him suggest not to see a doctor
conventional or otherwise I find it hard
to believe your claim that Anthony
explicitly told her not to see a
doctor after all of the push back and
being corrected by your husband Ashley
commented this I tried to add it to my
post but Instagram won't let me but if
IG will allow me later I will add
it initially Ashley left out any mention
of any doctors being involved then here
because of your husband's correction and
the push back she was getting she
changed her story and went on from there
to say Anthony told Stephanie to see a
doctor but not until it was too late
which is still very far from the truth
and with all of her blatant false claims
Ashley caused a lot of damage one
comment on this post read he should have
told her to see a doctor the moment she
found the lump and told him it should be
a lesson for him and any healer I've
heard similar stories many times with
other healers I'm just so so sorry again
to hear this we hope that this person
has now listened to our podcasts to
learn the truth even though they
probably didn't because they're probably
long gone since being scared by Ashley's
false claims if they have been listening
they would have learned that this is
exactly in fact what Anthony did exactly
one day after Stephanie reached out
about her breast lump Discovery Anthony
and his wife texted that you should
always c a
physician even after being corrected by
your husband Ashley continued on with
more falsities she commented this he
told her to see a doctor when it was too
late for them to do anything and when he
clearly realized he had screwed up it
was at this point that he also cut off
communication with her it doesn't feel
very relevant to me that after years of
telling her not to see a doctor and that
she would be fine he changed his tune
when she was incredibly ill there are so
many false things in here it's
disturbing not a single sentence is
accurate as we've covered Anthony told
Stephanie to see a doctor from the very
beginning he didn't screw up Anthony was
consistent in his messaging to Stephanie
all throughout the time of her illness
that doctors should be involved he never
changed his tune and Anthony was not the
one who cut off communication with
Stephanie we'll get to that more in a
bit but my gosh Kim no wonder you had to
make a statement I mean can you just
describe for us what was going on in the
community at the time after she did this
I know that many people had reached out
to me and I know that many people were
reaching out to you too what was the
impression that they had gotten from
Ashley's post Ashley compared Stephanie
to her own father who she said did
everything his fancy doctors told him to
do but summarized that none of them
actually had any idea what they were
doing she said her dad did everything
the conventional doctors told him to do
and he died Stephanie also followed
conventional treatment yet Ashley
insinuated that Stephanie followed a
protocol designed by Anthony and died
this isn't true Stephanie received
conventional
treatment as for the community it was a
mess it became so divided the fear was
unbelievable what Ashley did was instill
fear in so many people it was like they
started thinking their spinach salad or
their spinach soup was harming them and
they went back to a standard American
diet or went back to eating
McDonald's it's horrifying and it's all
so far from the truth all based on
complete completely false claims I've
seen from the data that Stephanie
received conventional cancer treatment
for almost a year here and because you
unlike Ashley were directly involved
with Stephanie's situation you were
there in person you had the ability to
set the record straight so you and
another practitioner who was also
directly involved sent letters out to
each of your private communities I
remember those letters I remember the
volatile situation that Ashley had
created with her
disinformation you and the other
practitioner handled this with a
tremendous amount of care care Grace and
a lot of respect while protecting
Stephanie and her private information
after Ashley had exploited her to serve
her own
agenda I have your letter in front of me
and here are some of the critical
clarifications that you
made Stephanie was not under Anthony's
care for
cancer Anthony did not provide
supplementation or food protocols for
her Cancer all cancer related medical
decisions were being made by Stephanie's
family and a few close
friends Stephanie received chemotherapy
and many other conventional Medical
Treatments you also shared in here about
how devastating it was for you to have
lost a friend and about how unhappy you
knew it would make Stephanie that
Anthony was being inaccurately blamed
for such a terrible
tragedy you had every right to send this
letter letter you had every right to
make those
clarifications and we now know those
clarifications to be true as proven by
the evidence that has been presented in
these podcast
episodes but Ashley obviously didn't
like that so can you explain what
happened after these letters were sent
out yeah Ashley started attacking me on
texts on audio messages while I was
driving in the pouring rain and then she
took the letters we sent to a very small
private
Community these were not public
communities and she made a retaliation
post posting these letters publicly and
then calling me and the other
practitioner
Liars okay so let's unpack that in the
retaliation post Ashley made she said
this some women I know were really upset
by my post they knew Stu personally
though I wouldn't call them good friends
of
hers though we've got a false claim
right at the beginning now I think that
Ashley tried to Discount your friendship
with Stephanie to make you appear less
credible Ashley also did an Instagram
live on April 1st of 2020 in which she
took it even
further
um what about the response of other
practitioners defending him and putting
others
down man that's so hard to talk about um
I mean first of all they called
themselves Steph's friends which was
really hard because they were not her
friends like they knew her they weren't
friends with
her
um it's it was amazing to me frankly if
I'm being totally honest it was like it
was kind of just shocking and for them
to see and walk through that experience
um the only thing I keep coming back to
is they didn't know stuff that
well so here she went as far as to say
publicly that you and the other
practitioner weren't friends with
Stephanie at
all I know that this is false first of
all because Ashley told me the exact
opposite on the phone several months ago
as a reminder to everyone I recorded
that call and it appeared in our podcast
episodes in previous episodes and just
so everyone also knows and understand
stands that recording was completely
legal Ashley has made false claims about
that as well but here is what Ashley
told me in that call and I said this to
Kimberly then and I Kimberly is the only
person I really lost my temper with
because I felt like she was Steph's
friend and she saw what
happened Ashley said to me privately on
the phone that you were Stephanie's
friend and that you saw what happened
why is this the opposite of what Ashley
shared in her 2020 blog post because it
sounds to me like she was trying to
deceive the public in Ashley's live she
also told this
falsity they weren't there at the
beginning of her journey they kind of
came in at the very end when Anthony
ghosted this one is even more ridiculous
I've seen from all the text records that
the other practitioner ashle is
referring to became friends with and
started texting with Stephanie in June
of 2016 a year before Stephanie's health
really took a turn and you met Stephanie
at the live event in 2016 and became
friends with her at that point as well
I've seen so much evidence of both of
you having been there for her and
offering your support to Stephanie early
on in her illness Journey as we've
talked about before Ashley loves to say
that Anthony ghosted Stephanie to get
people riled up it's a tactic but it's
completely false Stephanie's family cut
off communication between them and told
Anthony in a very aggressive way to stay
away so Ashley made plenty of false
claims here yeah so Stephanie sent me
hundreds of voice notes many of them
were a long voice notes that's the kind
of relationship I had with Steph I got
many times the daily update from her I
knew what she did from the moment she
woke up she would take me through her
morning morning morning routine and how
she spent many of her days her messages
were personal like really really
personal they were family they were
about friendships she asked for help
supporting the ones that she loved she
always asked for advice I know the very
intimate details of some of the closest
family members to her she shared it all
she offered to stay in my home when I
was postpartum to care for my son and to
care for me the way that she did for her
own nephew I don't think you share that
much and offer so much with someone who
is not your
friend yeah it sounds like the two of
you were close friends to me we also
know that Ashley's claims are false
because we have audios that Stephanie
had sent to a friend talking about how
close she was with you Gretchen and Kim
just become good friends really sweet
women and really
people and about trips she had taken
with you tomorrow I'm actually going
away with um Kim you know Kim really
spare Anda SEC cor because she's in
Pennsylvania right now remember I told
you about that we're just going to go
for like a couple days and spend some
time with her and then again in a couple
weeks I'm going to go up again for a few
days we also have a text that Stephanie
had sent to a friend about you that
reads she lives by my brother which is
convenient I introduced her to my
sis-in-law and fam and they have become
friends as well so that's been
nice and we have a long audio from
Stephanie talking about how you were
there for part of her back injury which
was months and months before Anthony was
told by Stephanie's family to stay
away hi well I hurt my back in the
beginning of
June I you know I hadn't been doing yoga
for a while or Pilates and I ended up
just by fluke coincidence I ended up
doing them both in the same week and by
the end of that week my lower back felt
kind of
weird
um weird enough where I literally it was
hurting to go on the rebounder so I kind
of had to stop that uh and then I went
to the caropractor and everything was
better like a day later but I only
waited like a few days to start
exercising again you know I started like
light I just went on the rebounder for
the first couple days and walked and did
pocket gym but then after a few days I
was back into yoga fully and I was like
doing yoga every day and pilates every
day or almost every day
um and I was just feeling so good and I
just like wanted to do all these things
and it was so stupid on hindsight I'm
like what am I thinking you know we know
better than to do that um just too much
at once like that especially since I
hadn't been doing it I mean I felt fine
doing it I felt I got right back into it
I was doing like intense stuff and it
was like great but clearly my body
wasn't right ready there and so I went
to the chiropractor again but then it
never it got a little bit better but
then I was carrying all these heavy
watermelons which were killing me but
like I was hanging out with scretchen
and Kim and like when I went up there I
just brought all these watermelons ex
seeed huge watermelons
and it just from there it got worse and
worse and I was with Gretchen for like
almost a week when I came home at the
beginning of I as I came home the Fourth
of July it got it was like horrendous
like it got really bad
excruciating like super super bad like
crazy spasming and nerves like shooting
pains like and literally I've been home
doing nothing for the whole month of
July all of that goes to show that you
were around and there to see a lot of
what happened including that Stephanie
injured her back by doing all of the
physical things she just described which
again proves Ashley's original false
storyline wrong in which Ashley had said
this on March 7th of 2020 about
Stephanie in the spring of
2017 her back began to eche we talked a
little bit during her back injury she
told me Anthony said it was a yoga
injury I really don't remember hurting
it in yoga she
said Ashley claimed that Stephanie had
said she didn't remember hurting back in
yoga but we have several audios from
Stephanie like the one we just played in
which Stephanie explains to various
different people all about how she
injured her back doing yoga and pilates
so obviously Stephanie was aware and
remembered because as we covered
previously Anthony didn't tell Stephanie
that her back problems were due to a
yoga injury Stephanie told people that
she had injured her back doing yoga and
pilates
and then she was doing things like
carrying heavy watermelons with an
already injured back that you witnessed
which made things
worse so now I just want to bring it
back to Ashley's retaliation post once
more again she had said this some women
I know were really upset by my post they
knew Stu personally though I wouldn't
call them good friends of
hers and Ashley's April 1st 2021 live in
which she said
this
um I mean first of all they called
themselves Steph's friends which was
really hard because they were not her
friends like they knew her they weren't
friends with
her we've shown that you Kim were indeed
a good friend of Stephanie's we also
have text and audio messages showing
that the other practitioner Ashley was
referring to was also in fact that a
good friend of
Stephanie's on June 29th of 2016
Stephanie texted the
practitioner you're so sweet I love you
dear
friend in a text from November 11th of
2016 Stephanie says to her I love you
dearly in a text from December 29th of
2016 Stephanie said to her hey sweet
friend in a text from July 8th of 2016
Stephanie said to her it's also
validating when sharing with a trusted
friend and we have audios from Stephanie
discussing how much this practitioner
had helped Stephanie Stephanie's
sister-in-law and Stephanie's brother
who is now a plotter trying to take down
the medical medium Community during an
extremely troubling time for them Tony
and Megan my brother's Tony his wife
Megan they wanted me to be there for the
birth I'm here supporting them you know
they're um it's just been kind of
intense there's a lot of stuff that was
going on to the hospital thank God man
was with us the entire time like you
know over the phone and any she was
always so supportive and there for me
the whole time and anything we needed
and supporting tun and
Megan there are hundreds and hundreds of
text messages that I've read going back
and forth between Stephanie and this
practitioner mostly of Stephanie asking
the practitioner for advice the
practitioner also helped Stephanie's
family in a very significant way during
a very dark time for them Stephanie
regularly expressed tremendous gratitude
for the positive impact this
practitioner had in her life and in
her's
lives we've got all of this evidence of
Stephanie calling this practitioner a
dear friend referring to you Kim
specifically as a good friend and
talking about all the time that you had
spent together including during the time
of Stephanie's back injury clearly this
practition and you were both very
important people in Stephanie's life and
Ashley told another big falsity to the
public I was even invited to Stephanie's
celebration of life I was around when
Stephanie injured her back I remember
her jumping on that trampoline with her
injury I supported Stephanie and met up
with her at the hospital the night that
her niece was born it's a strange thing
strange thing to have to qualify a
friendship but what Ashley said was so
hurtful because Stephanie was someone
that I really cared
about yeah I'm sure it was really
hurtful and it's a very it's a very um
it's a low blow it was very low for her
to go there and so following the false
friendship claims Ashley's retaliation
post continued on to say this these two
women sent out letters about my post to
their entire communities they
essentially made it seem like I was
lying this was a really impactful
experience for me because something I've
never realized before is just how much
you can use facts and distort them to
create what's actually a lie and there's
nothing I hate more than
lying so Ashley is saying that what you
shared was
factual but she's still calling you a
liar and the irony of all
is that she's calling you a liar in a
post that she Ashley herself told more
than 15 false claims in one version of
and more than 20 in another version of
Kim how frustrating was it for you to
watch Ashley do this
publicly it has been so heartbreaking
it's been extremely traumatizing for me
for my family the amount of stress that
Ashley has created with their false
stories is just
unbelievable
yeah and sadly she didn't stop there
Ashley tried calling you while you were
driving in the pouring rain and because
you didn't answer Ashley sent you a
barrage of text messages and I want to
walk us through that
conversation in the very first text
Ashley tries to rewrite history by
retelling her false version of what had
happened with Stephanie she tried to
sell this narrative to you Kim when you
were actually there there for Stephanie
and witnessing things that had happened
firsthand in person and Ashley was
not the text says this hey girl I just
can't not say something to you Steph was
personally Guided by Anthony for years
she did every single thing he ever told
her to do she laid on her back for
months while her spine literally
crumbled because he told her she had a
yoga in iny that later he ended up
staying with shingles and then when she
started bleeding from her nipples after
telling her she would never have cancer
his response to cut her off completely
and never speak to her again up to days
before Steph died she was texting
Anthony begging him just to talk to her
for you to write that letter and
knowingly mislead people about their
relationship is so Absol disgusting to
me and just frankly
unimaginable this text has six false
things in it six critical things that
are completely wrong and it seems as
though Ashley thinks if she just repeats
them enough she'll be able to get
everyone to just go along with it I'm
going to walk us through the false
Claims One Stephanie did not do
everything Anthony ever told her to do
Anthony consistent message from the
beginning was that Stephanie should see
a doctor for her breast lump and
Stephanie made the decision to wait too
long to follow that
advice two Stephanie did not lay on her
back for months because Anthony told her
she had an
injury three Stephanie got stuck laying
on her back because Stephanie said
herself she had injured her back doing
yoga and lates and it was made worse by
Stephanie carrying heavy watermelons and
jumping on the trampoline
which you were actually around to see
Stephanie got stuck laying on her back
because her doctor diagnosed her with a
dis injury and because she was on a
small old childhood mattress on the
floor that was terrible for her back and
made it too difficult for her to get up
four Stephanie did not bleed from both
nipples she only bled from one and five
Anthony never ever told Stephanie that
she would never have
cancer and sck
Anthony did not cut Stephanie off
Stephanie's family told Anthony to stay
away Stephanie did not text Anthony
begging him to talk to
her Ashley was so wrong about all of it
from the beginning and yet she continued
to berate you Kim for the factual letter
you had sent out to your small private
Community further text messages in this
thread from Ashley to you said this she
found a lump in her breast 3 years
before she died and he told her it would
never be cancerous does that bother you
at all does it like hello is this hiding
home I get that you weren't there when
that happened but I was does that I mean
come
on that series of texts from Ashley is
not only incredibly condescending but
also has three more false things in it
the the first one Stephanie did not
discover her breast lump when she was
living with Ashley in
2016 Stephanie in fact discovered the
lump a year later when Ashley was not
around the second false thing Anthony
never told Stephanie that the lump would
never become cancerous he repeatedly
encouraged her to get it looked at by a
physician and here Ashley's putting you
down by claiming that she was around
when you were not which is the ex exact
opposite of the truth that's the third
falsehood our data shows that Ashley
wasn't around for any single part of
Stephanie's experience with her breast
lump her back injury her cancer or her
passing and yet you were physically
there helping Stephanie as much as you
could after just having a baby during
Stephanie's
illness you responded to Ashley by
saying in all caps I'm driving in the
pouring
rain which sounds to me like you were
begging her to stop attacking you and
then Ashley replied to you by saying
this I'm not there to see it so maybe
it's not actually
happening later
Kim and then she sends three ey roll
emojis what Ashley is again
condescendingly implying to you is that
you don't believe in Ashley's story
which we know is
false she's saying it's because you
weren't there to see it and that's why
you don't believe her Ashley is saying
that Ashley was there to see it and you
weren't but in reality it's the exact
opposite the real truth is that you were
there and Ashley wasn't the truth you
were
there Ashley wasn't if Ashley wants to
play the comparison game and use
physical proximity as a measure of
someone's authority to speak on
Stephanie then in reality based on facts
Ashley loses at her own
game however Ashley ends up going on to
say this to you I know that you can see
what you did I know
it I don't know how you can live with it
but I know you can see it and I hope it
haunts you bye
Kim and then you replied by saying
saying no Ash we all tried to help with
all we had when it was going on I know
you don't realize that but it's the
truth I was barely paying my own bills
and was buying her supplements at one
point and doing everything I could with
a brand new baby nobody saw that make me
a monster
though and then Ashley sent you some
voice messages that we're going to play
now Kim I don't think that you're a
monster I think that what you did in
your letter is you isolate facts and you
painted an untrue picture of what
happened it's just not
true for you to use the facts that you
do have and manipulate them in such a
way I just I mean come
on and honestly I don't even care about
all the people that it impacted because
they will have their chance to hear the
truth I can't even call it lying because
of the way that you used facts but you
used them so articulately to distort the
truth that it ended up being a lie and I
hate that I can't stand
liars wow wow just unre
wow first of
all I want to oh
sorry it still gives me Goose Goosebumps
hearing that
yeah yeah yeah
yeah I can imagine it's she first of all
I want to point out that Ashley said
here that she doesn't care about all the
people who her post impacted because
she's saying that they will have their
chance to hear the truth in fact the
people Ashley impacted with her false
2020 posts didn't get a chance to hear
the truth before these
podcasts if they're even still around
and listening Ashley has impacted many
people and hurt many people with her
disinformation secondly Ashley's being
incredibly manipulative in these
messages she's twisted everything around
so much it's actually scary she's
attacking you relentlessly while you're
driving in the pouring rain her
information is all wrong she wasn't
actually there and you were yet she's
putting you down demeaning you and
admitting that you used facts so she can
actually call it lying but at the same
time she's calling you a liar with all
those falsities in her text at the same
time how did it feel to have a grown
woman act like this and treat you like
this honestly Amber I have PTSD from
what Ashley did to me that night I was
driving to my sister-in-law's wedding
festivities I was alone it was dark it
was pouring down rain Ashley would not
stop she wouldn't stop I had to call my
husband on the phone because I was
shaking at the time I was doing my best
to protect Stephanie's privacy and to
not let her be exploited by Ashley it's
really sad that Ashley has taken it this
far I've now been attacked personally
professionally my family has been
attacked Ashley is actually the most
intimidating person I've ever
met yeah I'm so sorry Kim that you've
had to go through all that and it's
really not okay that she's that she
attacked like this and it's really Brave
of you to come on here and talk about it
because I'm sure that everything were
discussing you know brings up a lot of
emotion and what's even worse is that
Ashley didn't stop
there that exchange that we just went
through was in
2020 now 3 years later several months
ago after I caught Ashley and the other
plotters for what they were trying to do
to Anthony and the medical medium
community
and we exposed them in our podcast
episodes Ashley went on a rampage on
social media rather than addressing any
of her false claims we had corrected her
on with evidence she pivoted onto other
points of focus she began bullying and
making fun of Anthony she made fun of
the light blast and the collecting
Stones meditation she made fun of the
medical medium Community many of its
members one of her targets was you and
shockingly your kids
on August 17th Ashley posted this this
is not enough fuel for a child to thrive
if you watch closely you will see that
the children of influencers who promote
extremely restricted diets are often
incredibly small just like Kim's
kids in this she tagged you along with a
screenshot of a pH photo of your three
kids plates that you had posted that
you'd captioned Beach
snacks the plates all have a lot of
avocado a bunch of cucumber sticks a
bunch of strawberries and a pile of
cooked cassava flour tortilla
chips Ashley continues on in the next
story post switching back to the priate
convo for a second many of you are
sharing more accounts of raw vegan
children and it's really sad a few of
you have made the point point that some
kids are just small and that's true some
kids are just small but all of RA vegan
kids are noticeably small in a
significant way I've never seen a single
example otherwise Bud would welcome
being challenged on that
point and then just a little bit later
after Ashley must have gotten some
serious push back on this she deleted
the first story and then posted this one
I did remove that repost of the lunch
trays though because it didn't sit right
with me I don't want to tear down moms
on here however I still think it is sad
and abusive to raise your kids on a
severely restricted diet how about
y'all when I first read this I was sick
to my stomach this is truly despicable
behavior from Ashley and I would ask any
mom out there how would you feel if
somebody did this to you and your kids
everyone is entitled of course to their
own dietary belief system but it is
unacceptable to shame and attack moms
publicly for how you think they feed
their kids like
this next I have to walk us through and
point out the falsehoods and
inconsistencies here because it's
insane Ashley attacked yuk Kim for
supposedly Mal nourishing your children
referring to photo of your kids plates
as lunch trays when in the exact
screenshot as used from you you
literally captioned it Beach snacks and
she has that in the photo that she
reposted how much sense does it make to
judge what somebody feeds their kids as
a snack as if it were a meal first of
all and then the snack plates in the
photo have plenty of food on them there
are piles of cooked cassava flower chips
with guacamole there are plenty of
strawberries and cucumber sticks as I
said they were Beach snacks they weren't
intended to be a Thanksgiving dinner
they were
snacks once again Ashley got it
wrong all of your posts online show your
fridge being loaded with huge amounts of
food and your kids eating plenty of food
with tons of variety your kids are
obviously far from restricted and it's
clear that Ashley was just trying to
hurt you and I'm
sorry thank you yeah she definitely got
me with that one um it first made me
really mad I cried a lot and then I
actually started to laugh because it's
just so insane we were traveling when I
posted those trays it was my husband's
40th birthday those trays don't belong
to me but I can tell you they were giant
man-sized trays my baby was one at the
time my daughter in preschool and my son
is eight they're little young children
you are correct Amber these were snacks
to take to the
beach as for the insults about my kids I
was so sick years ago before medical
medium and these kids were raised with
the principles that healed my body none
of them have ever had a cavity they
rarely catch colds and flu and when they
get something they bounce right back I
attribute that to the way that we live
and I would never call that restrictive
illness is restrict restrictive Wellness
is freedom and I know so many of you
would agree with
that yes yes really well said and I also
want to point out how Ashley conflates
medical medium information with raw
veganism yet again I know that your kids
are not raw
vegan yeah Amber my kids are not raw
vegan they never have been I have no
idea why Ashley would put me in that
category there's nothing
wrong with raw vegans but my kids are
not and they never have been my son has
consumed cooked soup that Ashley herself
made while I was staying with
her um that was when we went to visit
her family's home in PPP Beach my son
was also one of the first ones to trial
her cooked bread recipe and some of the
cooked potato recipe in Ashley's ebooks
that I always supported one scroll back
will let all of you see that my kids eat
loads of produce yes they do and they
enjoy it but they also consumed cooked
foods and they eat plenty of Treats
they're kids you
guys once again Ashley got it
wrong yeah once again very wrong it's so
upsetting
and I'm sure I'm sure it's so upsetting
I can't imagine having my kids attacked
like that um it's so Ashley has actually
senen your kids eat cooked food that she
made
herself and she still called them raw
vegan it's it's mind-blowing correct and
correct what's so insane and what also
speaks to how carelessly Ashley just
hurdles out attacks with paying such
little attention to facts and details is
that in the exact screenshot Ashley took
from you and displayed in her post it
clearly shows cooked chips on all of
your kids plates you even tagged the
brand of the cooked chips you gave your
kids as a snack with guacamole anybody
could figure out that they are cooked
chips and obviously if you're feeding
your kids cooked chips they're not raw
vegan and what Ashley's saying doesn't
make any
sense Ashley got all of these things so
wrong anybody who's viewing these
stories can catch the inconsistencies
for themselves but this is how as asy is
sloppy Ashley never has the details
right makes mistakes constantly and
leaves a trail of falsities
everywhere and then in this series of
attacks on your kids Ashley had the
audacity to call your children
small Kim your kids are objectively some
of the healthiest and strongest looking
kids that I've ever seen it's ridiculous
thank you
I'm super blessed in that department and
if you followed along with my journey
you've likely seen the pictures of my
son that I've shared over the past year
I'm pretty proud of him he's ahead
taller than most of the kids in this
grade he's 90th percentile for height
he's a travel and All-Star baseball
player in fact he was on three baseball
teams this year he's strong he's fast
he's unbelievable and I know that sounds
ridiculous because he's my son but I
have every right to be proud after I
went through what I went through with
his birth and postpartum with him and
just being so unwell years ago before
finding Anthony he's not small at all
it's quite the opposite my middle
daughter and there's been a lot of
commenting about her in the community
because I've shared her too she's a
gymnast she's an All-Star cheerleader
who has literally abs of steel um if
you've seen videos of her you've likely
seen a lot of you have commented she's
literally jacked the girl has muscles
that I didn't have when I was training
during some of the most intense training
periods of my life she's muscle and my
baby who is now to is literally a tub
she's got a couple chin rolls um so
while this does make me angry and you
know she did attack my children I really
think that one simple photo tells it all
it's time for me to speak out because
actually Ashley is a bully she bullied
my children who does that really who
does that that these are lies she has no
business commenting on my children she
has no idea how big or small they are
she has no idea what they
eat I'm still laughing at the
accusations from the chips and guacamole
plate that was my husband's
40th birthday it was a party at the
beach this is just one example of how my
life has been disrupted for years now
because of Ashley her social media post
ruined that trip for me and my husband
40th birthday because they changed my
mood completely they were hurtful and
they brought a tremendous amount of
stress by publicly attacking me and my
kids yeah it's terrible and it's
ridiculous Ashley never should have
stooped that low she never should have
done that then after Ashley clearly must
have gotten called out Ashley said she
removed that post because she doesn't
want to tear down mom on here but she
still left another story post up in
which she attacked a different mom and
her kid for their diet it's obvious that
the whole point of these posts was to
put down moms for how Ashley thinks they
feed their kids and the way that their
kids look and like you said Kim who does
that Ashley literally used the word
abuse and applied that you were abusing
your kids by what you're feeding them
when she wasn't even accurate with any
of her claims
there's nothing more egregious Ashley
just didn't get away with it and after
receiving push back that's when she
deleted some of it your kids are not
even raw
vegan some of it yeah she deleted only
some of it and some left other parts up
yeah your kids are not even raw vegan
medical medium information is not the
same thing as raw veganism her posts
don't make logical sense Ashley's raw
vegan attacks are also a especially
baffling to me considering the fact that
many of her own best friends and
co-plot are actually raw vegans yeah I
wonder how Ashley's raw vegan co-
plotters and best friends feel now about
how they have supported Ashley and
getting to where she is now that she
uses her platform to viciously criticize
the diet that they follow and promote in
their businesses going as far as to call
moms who feed their kids raw vegan food
abusive
plus what Ashley said in this Rampage is
wildly contradictive to what Ashley has
said herself in the past in an Instagram
story post that Ashley made at the end
of 2019 to sell her own ebook she said
this you deserve to nourish your body in
whatever way you choose without fear of
condemnation you deserve unquestioned
authority over what your children are
fed unreal
wild
contradiction this is another prime
example of sloppy Ashley it's a prime
example of someone who is always
changing to fit a narrative that suits
her agenda of the
moment Kim this was absolutely
reprehensible of Ashley to do to your to
you and your family and I'm so sorry
that you were the target of this attack
and that your kids were the target of
this attack
it's been a lot it's impacted my husband
in a big way too it's been completely
unnecessary stress and from mother to
mother all I think about every time she
puts these posts out there is that this
is time and energy away from our kids
and away from our families we're not
getting this time
back like I said so many trips so many
family events so many holidays so many
birthdays have been ruined for me
because of unnecessary abuse from
Ashley Kim I can't imagine being a mom
and then being publicly shamed for
feeding your kids healthy
snacks and being shamed in a way that
confuses people into thinking that you
must be some kind of terrible Mom that's
abusively starving your kids it's
uncons sadly Ashley has so many things
wrong another exhibit on how Ashley
makes mistakes it makes sense as to how
Ashley got everything wrong to begin
with with the Stephanie story when you
look at how many things how many details
and how many claims are twisted
discombobulated and just straight out
factually
incorrect exactly exactly and now Kim I
want to just bring us back to 2020 for a
moment
I know that Ashley was attacking you in
a similar way in the comments of her
retaliation post back then and implying
that you hadn't done enough for
Stephanie when she was sick your husband
defended you in a comment in which he
said this to Ashley can't sleep because
your comment of expecting Kimberly to go
in a hospital right after having a child
is ridiculous postpartum mothers are
supposed to be resting she wasn't
resting as she was making food and other
stuff to send to Steph on top of driving
it to her before she was cleared to
actually drive all of this led to the
health issues you mentioned of an
enlarged uterus from not resting and
taking care of herself clearly wasn't
enough for you I guess and for the
record I was the one that held her back
and didn't want her to do even more than
she already did and kept her out of the
hospital which is no place for a new
mother if it can be avoided so I guess
I'm the bad guy here for trying to
protect
Kimberly all of this was was playing out
online at the same time as Ashley was
attacking you in the written and audio
texts we went through
previously and then there was an email
you'd sent to someone who was your
friend at the time the next
morning I have that email in front of me
and it says thank you for the email last
night Ashley started sending me terrible
text messages voice messages and then
that post I'm not sure what prompted all
of it honestly I didn't even read it as
I was at a family event honoring my soon
to be sister-in-law my poor husband was
defending our side of the story as she
put my personal information right in
that post and failed to mention that I
had a baby who was just weeks old as we
were still running around and trying to
do what we could on No Sleep our lives
are very different and I don't think Ash
can understand a family that has to work
for a living and care for their children
without help and servants I'm not being
condescending but realistic the
statements she made about me were
appalling I was driving things to Steph
before I was even cleared to drive a car
after birth these girls put that
pressure on me my husband was so upset
that he took on as much as he could I'm
really really hurt by the twists and
lies it's a different lifestyle and she
can't wrap her head around a mother
working and caring for two children
without a nanny or understand that
husbands leave and go to work all of
this on no sleep with a newborn and a
2-year-old but somehow I didn't do
enough for her I had Gretchen staying at
my home during such a sacred time of
having a newborn not to mention my fear
of her being in and out of the hospital
and around my tiny new baby I don't know
what the answer is here but she is
pointing a lot of fingers and there is
no truth to so much of what she's saying
I feel awful harsh and heavy energy from
her she has an agenda to spread fear and
make herself look like a hero I wish she
would spread life and her love and her
beautiful spirit this is just upsetting
anyway I'm pretty exhausted from all of
this I hope you are resting today as I
can barely move from all the stress last
night
Kimberly can you share more with us Kim
about why why it was that Ashley and
Gretchen were putting so much pressure
on you to help Stephanie more and more
when you just had a baby there was so
much going on and it was up to a 4-Hour
drive one way
for you why did Stephanie need so much
help with food poor Stephanie wouldn't
eat the hospital food she was relying on
friends to bring her food when she
couldn't get enough help from friends or
family she just wouldn't eat looking
back I asked myself why wouldn't an
extremely wealthy friend send food a
chef support something instead I was
pushed to the max I opened up my home
postpartum to Gretchen who came to care
for Steph Gretchen was also met at the
airport with a hot tea and a home-cooked
meal that my husband and I prepared for
her I wanted to support the situation as
best I could at the time but nothing I'm
telling you nothing that I did was good
enough
nothing I don't get that time back with
my newborn I don't get to do it again I
don't get to hold her again as a newborn
I don't get to be there again with my
two-year-old son I I went through all of
this and that time is just it's gone
it's passed and now I live with Ash
trashing me whenever she
chooses and continuing to disrupt your
family time and it just seems really odd
to me that you were the object of blame
here and especially when you and your
husband did as much as you could for
Stephanie after just having a baby and
not living that close to her it seems
like over and over again throughout the
whole Stephanie situation the plotters
Ashley Robbie Taylor Christina Megan
Tony Gretchen have tried to place blame
on people who were actually trying to
help yeah many of Stephanie's friends
were just doing the best they could to
help her when it was possible and that
was all acceptable they were happy if
someone donated some time or some energy
or some food or whatever it was but
somehow I was definitely a Target in the
whole thing I was being pushed to do
more and more and more and whatever I
did it was not good good enough I did
what I could in the situation I was in
with a brand new baby somehow the
2-year-old little boy and the several
week old little girl that I had in my
arms while my husband was away at work
was completely overlooked they just kept
looking at me like I was some kind of
robot that was supposed to go and do and
do more and more it was
horrible wow yeah wow and in reality I
mean you were trying so hard to help
Stephanie in an impossible situation on
no sleep that you actually had gasoline
sprayed all over you to the point that
your hair was drenched and Ashley who
was putting all this pressure on you was
nowhere to be found and an exposure like
that of getting straight gasoline
sprayed all over your head all on your
hair all over your body it's treacherous
that much gasoline all on your body
soaked on you like that gets absorbed
into your breast milk milk you just had
a baby and then your immune system is
already comp compromised because you had
a baby and then you yourself Kim were
sick years ago this is a major exposure
which could trigger your system and then
if you were sitting in your car right
after you just had gasoline dumped all
over you if you had accidentally hit the
car lighter with your elbow or your hand
or your phone just by putting your phone
down you could have gone up in Flames
all it would take is just one spark from
an electrical wire from just the
ignition of the car starting and you
would have burned up and died along with
your baby in the car all because you're
helping out a friend Stephanie while
Ashley was sitting in Malibu in her
multi-million dollar house and then
spreading rumors and false claims about
how you and Stephanie weren't even
friends yeah not
friends it actually haunts me Anthony
the whole situation haunts me it was
traumatic like truly traumatic for me
and to have to live with the constant
social media insults threats and stress
it just brings it all up over and over
and over again every single time I see
her starting posting it's like the antic
start and I just it it all comes up over
and over again for me
I'm so sorry Kim thanks Amber
and yeah you you
also it's awful yeah it's
awful you also ended up unfortunately
with an enlarged uterus because you were
standing up constantly making food
driving long distances before you were
cleared to and bringing food to
Stephanie instead of resting post partum
and at the same time Ashley was nowhere
to be
found while you were going so far out of
your way to help Stephanie that you
risked your own life and your baby's
life and sacrificed your body literally
to help you did all of this because
Stephanie was a close friend of
yours and Ashley was nowhere to be found
yet Ashley has the nerve and entitlement
to imply that you weren't doing enough
for Steph and that you weren't even a
friend of hers at
all Yeah Ashley always communicated as a
very entitled manipulative woman I just
didn't know to what extent back then
that she was
entitled um when we all flew out to
Pebble Beach to stay in her family's
home Stephanie actually didn't have the
money to go and it was a really touchy
subject but meanwhile Ashley the
daughter of a billionaire family didn't
offer support to her then I looked back
at those emails wondering why did Ashley
not just buy her a ticket if they were
such good
friends yeah it's a really great
question and I looked through those
emails there are a few I want to read
off for everyone the first one was from
Stephanie to everyone on the email
thread that Ashley had invited to a
weekend get get away it was sent on
January 11th of 2017 just a few months
before Stephanie discovered her breast
lump and it says hey I'm still in the
unknown territory if I can come or not
financially at the moment not best
however things could turn around and
make it possible very quickly flight
prices are low so that's a plus so I may
have to wait as it gets closer to make a
move is that okay
this question was directed to Ashley and
Stephanie said that flight prices are
low but still too much for her to afford
at the
moment then on January 22nd of 2017
Ashley sends an email to everyone in the
group with a status update and some
background information about each person
for her friends who hadn't met each
other before Ashley's update to everyone
about Stephanie says this Stephanie
possible Steph is trying to make it work
financially I so want her to be there
Steph is a wealth of information and a
bright positive Shining Light in any
group she's part of for dinner she likes
to eat heads of Roma lettuce dipped in
kind pepper and lemon if that's not next
level I don't know what
is I was shocked by this email because
here Ashley is actually praising
Stephanie for for eating only lettuce
with cayenne and lemon for
dinner as we've covered a lot obviously
aead of lettuce as a meal let alone for
dinner is not enough it is not MediCal
medium information this is something
Anthony absolutely advises against it
was Stephanie's pre-existing approach to
food that here we see Ashley praising
and calling next level like restricting
yourself is something that everyone
should aspire to do and Ashley said in
this email that she so wants Stephanie
to be there Stephanie had said herself
that flight prices were low at the time
in 2017 flight prices were quite a bit
cheaper than they are today I'm sure
that she could have gotten a flight from
Philly to La where Ashley suggested
everyone to fly into from a Budget
Airline for 99 to
$150 Ashley is the daughter of a
billionaire and has a trust fund as you
said if Ashley was truly such great
friends with Stephanie and really wanted
Stephanie there why wouldn't Ashley have
just gotten her the plane
ticket yeah looking back I really do not
understand it especially with all the
finger pointing Ashley has done Ashley
let her miss out because Stephanie
couldn't afford it and then Ashley even
asked everyone in the group who was
coming to her family's multi-million
dollar home for a weekend for a cleaning
fee
I saw that in the email
thread unbelievable a cleaning
fee so after the Pebble Beach thing just
a few months later Stephanie discovers
her breast lump in March and then she
injures her back and then she gets sick
during the time that Stephanie was Ill
how would you describe Ashley's
relationship with Stephanie's family do
you know if they interacted were they
close what was that like Ashley actually
talked negatively about Stephanie's
family there was this constant thing
where the family wanted Stephanie to
receive conventional Cancer Care and the
plotters were not in agreement with the
family's wishes Stephanie's personal
wishes were pushed completely to the
side at the time the plotters and the
family were not on the same page at all
so it's so unbelievably strange to me
that now they've come together to blame
and attack Anthony who wasn't even
involved in Stephanie's Cancer Care
because the family cut off communication
with him it was a lot for me birthing a
baby and trying to simultaneously
support a friend who was not well and
listening to Stephanie stress literally
stress about her support people closest
to her not getting along I was dealing
with the text threads with the plotters
that were trashing and fighting with her
family it was horrendous seeing those
same plotters who were disagreeing with
and arguing with Stephanie's family now
representing and advocating for them or
with them is very confusing to me my own
data clearly shows that there was a
major issue between the platters and
Stephanie's family my husband witnessed
this in person when he went into the
hospital to visit Stephanie the plotters
and the family were not on the same
page that's extremely interesting and is
something that's very it's very
confusing to think about that as well
and how things somehow changed and
flipped in that way and then what
happened when your husband went to the
hospital to visit and bring food to
Stephanie what what did he
see so my husband observed an argument
between Taylor Stephanie and Stephanie's
family Stephanie didn't want the
treatment at the hospital that was being
offered at that moment
she was crying it's heartbreaking Taylor
was on her team and she was fighting
with the family Stephany wanted to go to
Mexico for an alternative treatment but
her family didn't agree to this my
husband just wanted to have a genuine
conversation with Stephanie the way that
he had so many times in the past but it
was uncomfortable and impossible because
of this conflict that was going on while
he was there instead he tried to be
helpful and find creative ways to keep
the food cold and be sure the juices
were kept fresh for her but the family
they always hated the way that she ate
dating back years before Stephanie even
knew Anthony the family did not like the
way that she ate the family made my
husband feel like he was a villain for
bringing food to
Stephanie
wow so there was this massive ongoing
battle between the plotters and the
family completely independent of Anthony
and just to bring this all together for
everyone all Anthony ever did in this
whole situation as we've shown was
encourage Stephanie to see a doctor
offer emotional support and try to get
her up off the floor she got stuck on
due to her injury so that she could get
in for proper Medical Care Anthony was
not Stephanie's health practitioner
Anthony is not an oncologist in order to
get diagnosed with cancer you need to
see a board certified
oncologist from the moment Stephanie
discovered her breast lump she was
repeatedly told by Anthony to see a
physician if Stephanie had listened to
Anthony's advice to see a doctor from
the
beginning outcomes probably would have
been entirely different and we probably
wouldn't need to be sitting here today
to talk about this and you Kim you even
talked with Stephanie early on about
doctors she could see in the area that
were near her and you said earlier on
that Stephanie wasn't receptive to that
at the time
and so then Stephanie's battle with
cancer ended up going on for about a
year after Anthony was told aggressively
to stay away during that time again
independent of Anthony the plotters were
fighting for Stephanie to get some kind
of alternative treatment for her cancer
while the family on the other hand
wanted her to do conventional
treatment while Stephanie was sick the
plotters and the family were at odds
Waring with each other and then when did
things change when did you see the
plotter start coming around and and
coming together with the family to try
to blame
Anthony I honestly didn't see things
change until years after Stephanie
passed away months after Stephanie
passed away I was invited to her
celebration of life the plotters were
offering Retreats yeah they were
offering retreats to the medical medium
community and then all of a sudden
the pters changed their tune it was
literally overnight and to me that seems
so clear that an agenda was
born yeah it's pretty crazy and then I
want to bring it back to when Stephanie
was Ill when you went to go bring
Stephanie food at the time that she was
living in her family's home what was
that experience like for you I went to
Stephanie's family's home to pick
Gretchen up who was going to stay in my
home
Gretchen was using my husband's car but
on that day he had to travel for work so
I drove to pick her up I was drenched
and gasolin by the time that I got there
and needed to take a shower and rinse
off as quickly as possible I showered in
one of Stephanie's family's bathrooms it
was really scary time for me I had my
newborn baby and I brought her in her
little car seat because Stephanie wanted
to meet her she actually wasn't able to
hold the baby due to the drugs that she
was on I dropped off some food for her
and was just in shocked from all that
happened with the gasoline and all that
was happening around me in that moment
it was around the same time when I was
told by Gretchen that she had observed
Stephanie with dust bunnies on her head
and face and that Gretchen had to dust
her off when she arrived in her home my
heart was broken and honestly it still
is
Amber that is
horrifying and the fact that it was
Gretchen who is now a plotter who saw
the dust situation is
especially
interesting yeah it was horrible all of
it the the whole situation was horrible
it was so hard to see it was hard to
hear it was hard to experience and all
at the same time with everything that I
had going on I felt so terrible for
Stephanie and I couldn't understand why
and everything that she was going
through that she would be covered in
dust yeah yeah that's something that's
really hard for me to wrap my head
around as well and
so then at some point when Stephanie was
sick Taylor Who's now also a plotter
stepped in could you explain what your
experience was like with her and what
role Taylor
played so Taylor was one of the ones
arguing at the hospital she basically
took over but she also was not fond of
the family and they were not F of her
Taylor was in charge though or at least
she thought she was in charge of the
whole situation she was so manipulative
and so bossy on the text messages and on
the phone I had never even met her in
person like have never met this woman
ever yet she was calling me out and
saying I needed to do more even though I
had a newborn and I remember thinking
that she was really insensitive and mean
and I didn't and and she just didn't
realize I'm like does this woman realize
I have a newborn right now she she just
didn't
understand yeah that that description
especially the bossiness matches a lot
of the experiences that I had with
Taylor several months ago in
person um so so Stephanie was in a
vulnerable position her back injury
prevented her from being able to do much
herself she was having a hard time
getting the food that she needed you
said earlier that she wasn't really
making her own decisions Taylor who was
acting you know as her caretaker and
Stephanie's family were making a lot of
decisions for her you were being
supportive and trying to help out as
best as you could did you and Stephanie
stay in touch throughout the course of
her illness or how did that go so for a
long time we were in Daily communication
personally and also in group chats with
various different plotters that were
discussing Stephanie's situation all of
a sudden out of the blue Stephanie
stopped responding to me I was told by
Gretchen that her brother took her phone
away and I never heard from her
again I was also removed from the group
chats it was very very weird because
Stephanie normally would text a lot and
send a lot of audio messages and all of
that I was again newly postpartum so
swallowing this was all really hard and
I was just trying to survive and feeling
completely heartbroken at the same
time wow yeah so you were told by
Gretchen that Stephanie's brother took
Stephanie's phone away
wow and we actually have text messages
and audio recordings corroborating what
you just said that we'll be sharing in
another episode it's really sad that you
had the same experience as other friends
of Stephanie's who were either cut off
without explanation or were told that
they were not allowed to speak with her
yeah and then I'm also curious about
your experience with Stephanie before
she got sick what were Stephanie's
eating habits like before she got sick
so actually shocking to me as someone
that eats a very clean diet which has
reversed my own symptoms years ago I I
was actually shocked when I met
Stephanie for lunch or at a juice bar
she wouldn't eat it was very rare that
she would eat something she mostly
wouldn't eat at all not even at a
completely organic juice bar one time I
actually had a car full of fresh organic
produce like wholesale produce fresh and
she wouldn't touch any of the fruit and
she would eat only the lettuce and I
just always felt like she was starving
and it just it just broke my
heart yeah so you experienced Stephanie
having some pre-existing problems with
food just eating lettuce is definitely
not MediCal medium information and it's
really sad frankly yeah and
yeah this goes along with so much
evidence that we have of what Stephanie
was eating and not eating which is the
exact opposite of the story Ashley tried
to tell starting in 2020 about Stephanie
following medical medium information to
a
te so Ashley's told many false stories
about Stephanie and many other things
and now you've heard all the different
iterations of the infamous cat story we
shared earlier on in this podcast series
Ashley told me directly in my calls with
her that Anthony had put her on a
fat-free raw diet and completely missed
the cat
allergy however one of the true
versions of that cat story came from a
text conversation Ashley had with you on
September 14th of 2018 which was months
after she had given away their pet cat
because in fact Anthony had said that
the cat was part of the problem in
Ashley's text to you Ashley said that
Anthony told her to cut out nuts and
seeds specifically for her son's eczema
but that fats like olive oil were
okay she also said to you that Anthony
had recommended lots of squash which is
something that would be cooked of course
not raw so Ashley obviously was not put
on a fat-free raw
diet yeah this one is really crazy to
hear so many versions of this story
Ashley and I were actually talking about
this because my daughter had skin issues
temporarily directly following my
exposure to all the gasoline that I was
sprayed with while I was breastfeeding
her I have texts from Ashley saying that
Anthony told her to cut out nuts and
seeds specifically because of the
Arginine and that other fats like olive
oil were okay and cooked squashes were
okay and that he suggested bringing in
cooked squashes again along with
bringing in lots of green
juices yeah okay so
now I'm
wondering it's I mean years ago Ashley
in all all these false stories I'm sure
Ashley years ago told you a lot of the
false stories that we've debunked in
these podcasts like the origin of the
breast lump Discovery and the infamous
cat story and it's got to feel really
weird to look back and realize that you
too were told so many untrue stories
that were Ashley's foundational building
blocks to get Robbie and the others on
board to try to take down the medical
medium Community it has been really
upsetting to see this story evolve after
seeing Ashley tell her healing story at
the medical medium live event I know
some of you remember it or you remember
hearing about it Ashley herself was
suffering and I mean really suffering
and hearing her words firsthand and
seeing her life turn around and now for
her to do this it doesn't make much
sense to me the very information that
saved her life and these are her words
not mine and Sav my life and several of
the other practitioners were
plotters and now to twist it and to
trash it and to manipulate it into an
article and into an agenda is just
upsetting she has been trying so hard to
convince everyone out there of things
that are simply not true about Anthony
and about this situation
she tried to Corner me and make me
believe things that are not true Anthony
saved my life and I've watched thousands
of Miracles over the years thanks to
this information there is such a clear
agenda here and I actually feel really
bad for everyone who has been swallowed
up by this so many of them have been
saved by this same information thanks to
Anthony and I know very personally that
he has helped most of these plotters
some of them in their Darkest Hour even
after Stephanie's death even when they
have walked away from the information
but that just tells you who Anthony
is
yeah
wow I just have to say how sorry I am
again that Ashley targeted you and your
family came the way that she did in so
many different instances she clearly
didn't know the facts about this story
she just felt entitled apparently to say
whatever she
wanted she said herself in her text to
you that she didn't care about any of
the people in the medical medium
Community who she hurt with her 2020
posts if Ashley had genuine questions or
concerns about what had happened with
Stephanie if she had any real interest
in pursuing the truth she could have
asked Anthony about anything she never
did she could have asked you she never
did
she decided to take it public only a few
months after still trying to sell the
medical medium community on herself
self-proclaimed expensive Retreats with
celery juice and a weight loss plan she
tried to act like some kind of hero or
whistleblower when she used a completely
false story Ashley exploited Stephanie
and her private information which is the
saddest part yeah she caused outrage and
Chaos in the medical medium Community
with her false stories she put you and
others in a situation where you'd have
to defend the truth and then she had the
nerve to attack you for
it yeah she attacked my family my
children my profession and I just want
to talk about her weight loss book for a
second twisting the information and
claiming to be an expert Beyond
Anthony's books I don't quite understand
it Amber but I can tell you that it
confused a lot of people Ashley's ebook
was targeting postpartum women and it
was a weight loss plan with portion
sizes in ounce amounts I consulted with
a lot of postpartum women who were
influenced by Ashley's ebook to eat less
food and restrict their calories as a
means of rapid weight loss they were
under the impression that they were
still following medical medium
information when medical medium
information does not restrict calories
they were just following Ashley's
Twisted
information a lot of these women had
their supply of breast milk drop because
they were not eating enough and some of
them even blamed medical medium
information for that when it it wasn't
medical medium information it was
Ashley's portion controlled information
that she was marketing to the community
and it was so
irresponsible Ashley has done a lot of
damage I'm hurt and lost I'm traumatized
by all of it and I just want it to stop
yeah yeah that's crazy that you've had
that you had those direct experiences
and uh with the impact that
Ashley's that her weight loss ebook had
on women particularly postpartum women
in the community that's extremely sad
and Ashley really is the originator of
twisting medical medium information and
um she's had a lot of influence on how
that's happened in more recent times
even you know with other people in other
cases and it's all really sad and Ashley
has indeed done a lot of damage and
that's why it's so important that we're
here you know to set the record straight
to help stop Ashley and the plotters
from misleading deceiving hurting or
taking the chance to heal away from
anyone else so thank you very much Kim
for coming on I know that you're a busy
mom of three little ones and that this
wasn't easy to do I really appreciate
you being here and sharing a lot of
these really difficult experiences and I
appreciate both of you very much it's
unfortunate that we had to get together
for something like this setting the
record straight I'm sure the medical
medium community and anyone even outside
of the medical medium Community truly
appreciates your caring and willingness
to get the truth out there thank you Kim
thank you guys I appreciate you
both thanks thanks
as we are in the process of exposing
Ashley and her organized hateful group
for who and what they really are it's
important to take note of their tactics
and patterns that are likely to follow
the plotters have a documented history
of initiating attacks using lies and
misinformation and then upon getting
called out and corrected trying to flip
it and play victim that is not going to
work here all this group has done is
spread verifiable lies and falsities
they've carelessly attacked and harmed
many innocent people they've used and
exploited deceased individuals and
others in the process of trying to get
what they want they've repeatedly
explicitly expressed the intent to harm
medical medium and they've even
deliberately tried to stop Anthony from
doing a free event to support and raise
money for the community we have every
right to set the record straight and to
defend the truth with facts and evidence
and to defend the chronically ill
against the icious attacks of this group
and we are going to continue to do so we
expect the plotters to evade and ignore
what they have done wrong we expect them
to continue to lie and spread falsities
we expect them to Pivot onto something
new they'll make up and we expect them
to skew and alter data and to hide
critical pieces of evidence that
undermines their entire campaign we also
expect the plotters to fabricate
explanation
as they do everything they can to try to
discredit what we're exposing them for
having done and said in their own words
but we are using their own text messages
voice messages social media posts words
that they spoke on recorded calls and
other published materials there's no use
of any AI in any of these episodes and
never will be all of the information was
fact checked and forensically invested
instigated if you've been harmed
deterred from your healing process
bullied shamed emotionally upset or
physically hurt by flareups of your
conditions from the stress induced by
the plotters attacks like hundreds of
others have reported please go to
medicalmedium.com
safespace to submit your report and
share your story if you've been
contacted by anyone who's tried to deter
you from using medical medium
information please take take screenshots
and Screen recordings and submit them to
the same place medicalmedium.com
slsa space