how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William today we're talking about gut
health exactly the guts your gut
everyone's gut because what people need
to understand is that medical research
and science doesn't understand stand
it's feeble at best because let's face
it how the gut functions it's a mystery
no one knows what really happens when
food enters the stomach the digestive
system is a miracle phenomenon beyond
anything anyone can perceive they don't
have a window into it they don't know
what really happens when food hits the
stomach never mind food hitting the
mouth in this episode we're talking
about the ghost inside your body and I'm
not talking about your soul this time
I'm talking about ammonia get ready for
the ride fasten your seat belts because
this is going to be quite a
trip yeah Auntie I'm in the waiting room
at the doctor's
office what kind of tea do I like uh
black tea black
tea you're in the store now yeah get the
one the brand that I always like
okay yeah know the caffeine high from it
I know Auntie it's got too much caffeine
I know I know you're listening to the
medical medium again I know
um yeah I'm bloed so bad I'm just
bloated um okay oh hold on hold on yep
okay I'm up I'm up I'm called up oh God
I love when that happens when my name is
called cting here okay oh nurse okay sit
down here okay all right is this new
paper on the waiting table is it new
paper or is it old paper I see there's a
crease in there with someone sitting
here okay all right good it's new oh
yeah so Auntie my stomach is bloated so
bad and my breath stinks so bad I know
you know that I know I know I smell up
the whole house just just my breath not
even the dogs and cats they don't even
like my breath you know I know it's so
bad I just need to find out is this
hosis is this something else or I I just
stink all the time I know I know oh
doctor's coming in doctor's coming in
okay I'll I'll talk to you soon bye
you've probably heard of leaky gut
before I remember when leaky gut hit the
town and it just took off and it was
like the answer for everything years ago
a little history lesson right here if
you don't know when you're new in health
and or you just got sick or you're
somebody that just wasn't aware of this
but leaky gut was one of those panaceas
that solved everything but yet solved
nothing cuz nobody got better back then
it was just oh you got leaky gut you got
leaky gut alternative medicine took that
leaky gut they ran with it and ran with
it they would not stop that went along
with candida of course you either got a
Candida diagnosis or a leaky gut
diagnosis and then sometimes you get
both now back then 10 20 30 years ago
alternative medicine wasn't ined with
conventional medicine now it is you guys
they're in bed together and then the
lines are
blurred but back then they weren't so
conventional medicine was like there's
no way someone has leaky gut because
leaky gut to us conventional medicine
would be a puncture inside the
intestinal tract or the colon or in the
stomach or dadum and that puncture would
allow contents from the intestinal tract
to leak into the bloodstream of the body
or leak into a different Avenue of the
body then the person would get an
infection they would be in the hospital
they'd have a fever maybe even a really
high fever or a low grade fever too for
a while and then they would get
sepsis and be really sick and
potentially die that was leaky gut
syndrome to Conventional medicine back
then I'm not talking about 100 years ago
I'm talking about 10 years ago 15 years
ago 20 that was the definition of leaky
gut from conventional medicine's point
of view alternative medicine was just a
term not understood though not
understood but a term leaky gut it was
like the answer for everything at the
time now there was no science for
alternative medicine or conventional
medicine that deemed leaky gut as a
possibility alternative medicine didn't
have an answer they did not have a
microscope inside somebody's intestinal
tract looking at the possibility of
contents leaking from their intestinal
tract into their bloodstream it didn't
happen it just wasn't there science did
not see it nobody saw it it was a theory
it was 100% a theory and nothing but a
theory that somebody had leaky gut and
that's why they were struggling so when
a patient came to an alternative
doctor's office I was like well I'm
fatigued I don't feel good I'm not well
I got aches and pains I got brain fog
I'm bloating what is it and then
alternative medicine would be like well
I think you got leaky guts in
like whoo leaky gut syndrome now I have
an answer I can take that and do
something with it it's not that they saw
the person had a leaky gut nobody knew
there was no test that determin it truly
it was just a guess or a theory and a
guess just compiled onto itself but the
health movement back then was Barren it
was dry it was like a desert and people
were thirsty you're sick for enough
years you hit a new alternative doctor
it's the year
2002 it's the Year
1997 it's the year 2010 and when you hit
that alternative medicine clinic and a
doctor's like you got leaky gut and it's
like The Thirst is quenched in that
moment Hallelujah there's an answer here
I'm not thirsty anymore let me drink
this up you leave on a high it was a
miracle moment in Alternative Health but
really it was just a theory but you know
what when you got stuff in your head
like that and you've been looking for a
long time it makes sense my gut is
leaking darn it that's what it is
because everything I eat matters and
what I'm doing matters my stomach my gut
I don't feel good it has to all stem
from the gut and it was the perfect
opportunity for alternative medicine to
look good especially since conventional
medicine was torturous at the time for
so many people
absolutely torturous all they did was
offer a steroid an antibiotic an
anti-depressant an anti-anxiety Med a
benzo
aspine some type of anti-inflammatory
and you're on your way didn't matter
what was going on where who when unless
you broke your leg or your penic
exploded and you needed emergency
surgery other than that and maybe a few
other things that are life- saving of
course conventional medicine is life
saving but when it comes down to chronic
illness it was just emptier than
alternative medicine truly emptier you
ran through gamma of tests didn't have
any answers and you went home to feed it
everybody went home to feed it and it
even happens now till this day even with
conventional medicine being married now
to alternative medicine like it is it's
still defeating in so many ways but back
then getting an answer was everything
so let's hit leaky gut for a little bit
so when people were getting a leaky gut
diagnosis it wasn't about other things
like ulcers diverticulosis
diverticulitis Pockets that were in the
intestinal tract or colon that were
highly inflamed and very damaged with
scar tissue it wasn't about these things
at all these things weren't even in the
picture this was just people who've
already had
colonies endoscopies they've already had
you know people looking inside the
intestinal tract they had
cameras everywhere inside their
intestinal tract but they still didn't
have
answers it was people that just didn't
feel good for all these other reasons or
having all these other symptoms were
given these leaky gut
diagnosis so it's very different if
somebody has an ulcer that's blowing up
exploding inside their gut an ulcer in
their stomach the water them and that
Ulster is a bleeding hemorrhaging
uler and there could be a possible
Fisher or window into the other side of
that area leaking things into the
bloodstream very different right there
or a puncture which happens when people
get colon oopes the camera goes up they
roll it out and it punctures people's
colons and now they're in the hospital
for 4 months 6 months 2 months because
they have a puncture and they're
fighting for their lives with
sepsis it's different than anything like
that leaky gut that was happening with
people wasn't for any reason besides you
don't feel good you got leaky gut when
it comes to the alternative theory of
leaky gut it's Advanced along the years
now it's all about different things that
are happening medical communities and
alternative medicine describe a
condition in which mold or fungus like
candid
or unproductive bacteria Thrive and
burrow tiny holes in the Linings of the
intestine and cause micro levels of
toxins to leak directly into the
bloodstream resulting in a multitude of
symptoms there are different variations
of this belief and they all mimic each
other though now having an intestinal
tract filled with unproductive bacteria
unproductive mold yeast different fungus
having an intestinal tract fil with all
of that can give you symptoms there can
be problems you can have a strep you can
have an eoli you can have different
bacteria causing different problems in
the intestinal tract for many reasons
and doing different things but that's a
far cry from leaky gut if these
pathogens were truly Crossing
barriers if unproductive fungus candida
mold were crossing into the blood stream
from the intestinal tract lining or
entering into the body through the
intestinal tract in any way the stomach
dadum the colon if that was happening
there would be a war going on and
somebody would be bedridden sick with
fevers and levels of toxins in their
bloodstream creating a sepsis a chronic
sepsis all the time now the hospital
would know that they would have sepsis
it would be a mystery maybe to how it's
happening it would be a mystery to why
they have sepsis
but if there were holes throughout the
intestinal tract or colon and bacteria
was crossing barriers Crossing that
lining and all kinds of other different
fungus and yeast and mold and other
toxins were crossing out of that
intestinal environment into the body in
some way they would know it's sepsis
they would know we have a problem and
maybe a really smart doctor might be
like wo this could be coming from
somewhere maybe it's coming from the gut
somewhere and there's some kind of
fisser there's some kind of opening but
that's a far cry and very different so
different from a whole host of other
symptoms that are created from inflamed
neurological systems and brain
inflammation and viruses and metals and
other toxins and so forth it would be
much different than the sepsis somebody
would have in the hospital where they
would be identifying that really easy
and that would be like okay now that
would be a leaky gut if there was really
a passageway through the intestinal
tract into the body but this is much
different than people being sick or
vetan with neurological conditions
chronic illness aches and pains body
aches and pains all kinds of different
issues far different than that but what
happens with leaky gut enthusiasts
doctors that believe in leaky gut in the
way they do they'll just package it all
up and that's what they did years ago
alternative medicine packaged everything
up in into leaky gut you walk through
the door with all your host of symptoms
everything you're suffering from neck
pain ear pain vertigo dizziness ringing
in the ear tingles and numbness back
pain leg pain feet pain insomnia
whatever it was it would be like okay
this is leaky gut and so let's treat it
and that's what's going on and the sad
part was they were wrong and it wasn't
it wasn't Lecky gut it was other things
viral infection
Epstein bar which originally starts as
mononucleosis hhv6 simplex one Simplex 2
setav virus shingles
hhv7 different forms of bacteria like
strep lots of toxic heavy metal exposure
throughout an entire lifetime and even
before passed down from generations and
generations all kinds of different
toxins and poisons chemicals and so
forth and antagonists neuro antagonists
that everybody gets exposed to to f
Pharmaceuticals people drink in their
water and don't even realize it from all
kinds of different pharmaceutical
exposure all of this plus radiation
pesticides herbicides DDT all of the
above is happening but yet it's all
blamed on leaky gut as if that was what
it was but it wasn't even when people
deal with fatigue and aches and pains
and constipation and digestive
discomfort acid reflux even them those
people are not dealing with leaky gut
they're dealing with other problems like
low hydrochloric acid ammonia problems
which we're going to explore in a minute
liver issues stagnant sluggish toxic
livers and then pathogens all throughout
the body all of that plus weak nervous
systems they're suffering with all of
this but it gets packaged up as if it's
this leaky gut thing when it's not as
the years went by leaky gut syndrome
turned into a new label a new
identification which was intestinal
permeability it was a newer version of
leaky gut the reason why because leaky
gut never made sense to begin with and
they knew it along the way and we're
like wait a minute this isn't leaky gut
so let's call it intestinal permeability
so the name changed it was meant to give
the illusion of progress but it wasn't
progress but what really is happening
inside people's guts is ammonia
permeability ammonia is a gas that's
produced when something's rotting when
something's rotting in someone's gut so
what's happening out there is people
have gut rot instead of leaky gut
syndrome they have gut rot a prime
example of this is when somebody eats
beans and they don't digest properly
because their liver is weakened stagnant
sluggish their hydrochloric acid is very
low to zero their bio reserves inside
their liver is low to zero in many
people so what happens is when someone
eats a whole bowl of beans they don't
digest and break down properly and they
start to rot they rot inside the gut
it's called Bean rot something similar
happens with nuts so many people eat
gobs of nut butter or they eat a lot of
nuts out of hand and what occurs is that
their liver is too weak their bio
reserves are too low their hydrochloric
acid is too low and then the nuts begin
to rot it's called nut rot this can also
happen with eating poultry any kind of
turkey or chicken or any kind of other
Bird that's eaten what happens is the
body doesn't digest it properly through
all those avenues that I talked about
before with nut rot and bean rot and you
get poultry rot this could happen with
fish too Snapper tuna Cod halib bit
Trout the stomach can't break it down
properly because the HCL is low the bio
reserves are low and can't break down
any of the fats and then the liver is
too stagnant and sluggish and what you
have is fish rot same thing happens with
meat beef pork lamb these foods are hard
to digest when someone's digestive
system is weakened and in turn you get
meat rot it doesn't stop there either
when someone's eating chocolate and
maybe somebody you know notice this or
maybe it happened to you later on you
get a really bad breath a real stink
coming out of you right off your breath
someone might say hey that's chocolate
but really someone might also say what's
rotten and what ST thinks it's rotting
chocolate it's chocolate rot the stench
that a lot of people think is hosis just
plain old bad breath or dental problems
is really the stench of ammonia food
that's rotting in the gut doesn't just
stop rotting in one day it could sit
there and rot for
days sometimes people have enough food
in their intestinal tract to rot for
weeks and some people have food sitting
in their guts rotting for months as the
food rots
ammonia gas is produced and that ammonia
gas seeps past the lining of the
intestinal tract and colon and even
stomach lining and dadum and it enters
the bloodstream that ammonia gas travels
through the bloodstream into every
single organ in the body but that's just
one Avenue the ammonia gas travels it
also travels through artery walls the
Linings of veins it travels through
anything
it's like a ghost and it moves through
bones not just in Bones it moves through
them this ammonia gas doesn't just leave
the body through the armpits or through
sweat when someone works out it leaves
every orus every single cell every part
of the skin it leaves your skull at the
top of your head it goes through
everything and it leaves the body in
every way you would think that's a good
thing then it just travels out of the
body and it leaves us but no it also
stays behind it's a ghost that leaves
and stays it's everywhere saturates all
the tissue every cell every organ the
entire bloodstream the lymphatic system
and yet still gases out and leaves us
but there's always more to come more to
be produced it's always there one of the
most annoying parts of ammonia
permeability is when it enters the mouth
especially when somebody's sleeping at
night and they're just laying down the
ammonia gas produced by rotting food in
the gut doesn't just go through the
intestinal lining and into the
bloodstream it goes up the intestinal
tract it floats up it's a ghost that
floats upward so it starts heading up
into the dadum and it heads into the
stomach up the esophagus and into the
mouth and then it sits there while
somebody's sleeping
why should that be a problem one is it
starts to affect oral health it starts
to cause teeth problems over time bad
teeth problems ammonia gas just doesn't
move through bones it just doesn't move
through organs it moves through teeth
and when ammonia gas moves through teeth
it weakens teeth now you might say Well
when it moves through bones it weakens
bones but not exactly it does doesn't
just weaken bones what happens with
bones is there's not a lot of oxygen
inside the body not compared to oxygen
inside your mouth so what happens when
ammonia gas reacts with oxygen from
breathing air in and then the ammonia
gas entering the mouth from down below
the two mix and it becomes more damaging
to teeth causing teeth problems quickly
versus bone problems quickly in the body
the oxygen that enters our mouth helps
to keep oral problems down it's one of
the self-protecting built-in mechanisms
that we have as human beings we breathe
in air through our mouth and the oxygen
levels are high keeping bacteria to a
certain level lower instead of really
high what happens with ammonia
permeability and then ammonia gas when
the ammonia leeches into the mouth it
starts to lower the oxygen levels
meaning bacteria in the mouth grows
faster fter so if somebody has
deficiencies for years mineral
deficiencies their teeth are already at
a weakened state or they're high intoxic
heavy metals or they have pathogens such
as viruses and food deficiencies
nutrient deficiencies antioxidant
deficiencies B12 deficiencies if you
compile ammonia permeability on top of
those deficiencies then you have a real
problem so oxygen diminishes in the
mouth ammonia Rises bacteria Rises and
teeth and gums get worse one thing that
happens though is when someone builds up
their HC they're breaking down proteins
better they build up their liver their
BS breaking down and dispersing fats
better their digestive system is getting
stronger they're healing but they have a
past a past history of decades or years
and years of ammonia permeability and
Amon
damaging teeth so
then Father Time kicks in and that teeth
damage shows later even when they're
healing and getting stronger and
healthier the past shows up and the
teeth start to show what happened
especially if people were eating vinegar
and drinking vinegar all these years
especially if they were doing apple
cider vinegar shots and apple cider
vinegar chews all these years the apple
cider damages teeth all on its own but
it also doesn't help ammonia
permeability it worsens it creating more
ammonia gas people's refrigerators are
filled with condiments and they eat
these condiments and in these condiments
is vinegar or vinegars even apple cider
vinegar a lot of people use it as a
staple in their dressings on their food
in their sauces and vinegar damages the
liver
and it injures the HCL production with
the stomach glands your gastric glands
over the years it contributes to ammonia
permeability and ammonia gas
production another ammonia producer is
salt an overload of salt not just
minimal on the salt or small amounts of
salt let a people over Sal their food or
eat restaurant food that's overs salted
what happens with salt is it injures the
gastric glands it slows down the liver's
function and salt itself when saturated
in the bloodstream it reacts to ammonia
gas Just Like Oxygen reacts to ammonia
Gas Salt reacts creating a much more
potent form of ammonia gas this is
different from natural occurring sodiums
like the sodium cluster salts in celery
juice which neutralize ammonia gas the
sodium in celery juice and the sodium in
leafy greens like spinach and lemon
is a neutralizer it's there to keep a
sodium balance in the bloodstream a
natural occurring sodium
balance another problem with gut rot are
fats that go rancid a lot of people have
high fat diets overt fats are in their
diet morning noon and night or even if
it's once a day overt fats and what
happens is if the blood gets thick and
fat and stagnant and sluggish and the
ammonia gas has a field day it could get
trapped in places you don't want it
trapped in special places like nerves
like the Vegas nerves a hypers sensitive
nervous system one that's already
dealing with pathogen exposure like
neurotoxins produced by Epstein bar
virus can be highly sensitive to ammonia
permeability ammonia gas this affects
nerve response time when somebody has a
thought there's a delay like they think
about lifting their arm and they lift
their arm when somebody has a thought
about running there's a slight delay a
lot of people run into this with loved
ones or they say something and they get
an answer back with a little bit of a
delay the ammonia gas can produce this
type of delay when it affects the
central nervous system so how do we
reverse ammonia permeability how do we
reverse ammonia production inside our
body we have to restore the hydrochloric
acid levels we have to restore our liver
those are the two main things to restore
the hydrochloric acid level you have to
bring back those gastric glands you have
to strengthen them so as we're
revitalizing our gastric glands and
making our hydrochloric acid stronger
we're up against something that
everybody's up against pretty much every
day which is stress everyday stress and
stress puts people in fight ORF flight
when we're in fight or flight our
adrenals are releasing adrenaline that
adrenaline is toxic to the gastric
glands keeping HCL down low so we have
to work harder and longer to restore it
and Revitalize it so what do we do how
do we fix this how do we stop gut rot
how do we stop ammonia permeability
what's the first step celery juice
something that truly works it helps to
restore those gastric glands bringing
that HCL back bringing the HCL blend
back making it strong so that it breaks
down proteins and breaks down food so
the gut rot
minimizes some people are doing 2 oz
some people are doing 8 oz 16 oz 32 oz
some people do 32 ooun twice a day
everybody's different everybody chooses
to drink the amount they choose but one
thing's for certain any amount of
accelery juice somebody's drinking is
helping this problem and in each person
they're different
someone's liver could be really stagnant
sluggish and highly toxic someone's
pancreas could be weakened and highly
toxic somebody's spleen can be weakened
and highly toxic somebody's gastri
glands could have been damaged from
years and years of coffee tea chocolate
vinegar someone could be hind pathogens
lots of different viruses rowing inside
their liver somebody could have a lot of
neurotoxins floating around in their
system and bloodstream and somebody
could just be up against a lot of stress
they're in fight or flight and their
adrenals are pumping out adrenaline
every day and that adrenaline is
weakening their system but we have tools
to battle this it just requires some
patience and some
dedication there are tools that actually
work and have street cred they have a
track record tools like celery juice
tools like the medical medium heavy
metal detox in any form in a smooth form
a smoothie bowl or just the ingredients
on their own throughout the day and then
there's the mono cleanse and the medical
medium morning cleanse and the medical
medium 369 Advanced the medical medium
28-day cleanse and the spinach soup and
the healing broth there are so many
different tools and then protocols
supplement protocols for the gut that
are inside the medical medium book
series hey Dr doctor hey so what's your
uh what's your
diagnosis leafy
gut okay so what do I
do um you have a list of things okay
let's see gut cleanser uh what's this uh
candida killer oh I see you have two
probiotics ooh a Prebiotic too I've
heard of that ooh apple cider vinegar
ches huh oh a bottle of activated
charcoal I'm trying to read this huh
okay I'll just get these um how much do
I owe you my bills at the desk
okay I'm here to to pay for my
bill um
$1,672 okay I'll just give you my credit
card don't be thrown off don't be
derailed
look out it's another
storm gigantic balls of
hail I think I'm getting a flare my
stomach feels like it's getting back to
square
one
two I can't go through another round of
this but I got to just hang in there I
know I can do all that I need to do
don't tell me I can't do this don't
don't tell me I don't have what it
takes I have it all inside of me I may
make a mistake but that's okay don't we
all as we go through this sometimes we
take a
fall we get back up again and we dust
ourselves off no matter what it don't
matter just throw a curve ball and guess
what
who cares if that person is a screw ball
because you do have everything it takes
it's in the hall the halls of our soul
and our body and our free will we know
what the angel saw the intentions inside
of you are of the goodest call you are
on your way to Healing so you can rise
above all all that don't see you for who
you are but instead trip you up in hopes
to take a fall but you are smarter than
the darkness you're a Seer and a
teacher and you don't need to prove
yourself no
more you have the floor it's your time
to heal your time to soar
[Music]
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical SCI and research
instead the opposite only proven right
and then taken from medical medium
published material and used in the
conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion