how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about nature you
know birds bees grass trees rivers
oceans the sky and how it heals our soul
and physical body too
you know nature you've seen it before
but have you seen it do you pay
attention you might be too busy so many
people are do you see a bee land on a
flower and do you give it a minute this
is going to be an incredible episode I
don't want you to miss this hang on for
the ride cuz we're talking about how
nature heals
us nature comes in all shapes and sizes
what that means is maybe someone has
just a little tiny
backyard maybe they have a little tiny
front yard maybe they only have one
window in their house or their apartment
or dwelling somewhere and they can just
see one tree and then once in a while
they see a bird land on that tree or a
squirrel go up the
tree nature can be as small as being on
a rooftop in the city watching a pigeon
on another rooftop and the nature could
be a lot bigger than that it could be
somebody who's always outdoors and
taking hikes taking walks every day out
there by the ocean standing on the
beach camping out by a
lake nature can come in all shapes and
sizes but do we know what nature is
really doing for
us yeah it's winding us down helping us
relax
maybe shifting our train of thought
giving us a break some
relaxation but it could be doing a lot
more for you than you even know and if
you harness it properly or just right
you can get a lot more out of it when it
comes down to Nature anything and
everything
goes it can be simplistic it can be just
listening to a cricket and each individ
ual thing you experience in nature does
something a little different to vastly
different for
you if you're in the wilderness and
you're camped out and a Sasquatch walks
by you're a nature and it's going to do
something for you it's probably going to
scare the hell out of you but
something's going to happen because
there it is a creature in the
woods same thing if you're in the
wilderness and you see a bear walk by
or if you see a squirrel on a branch
they all do different things for us in
different ways they ignite healing they
ignite
emotion they help our soul so let's
start heading into it right
now life can be really toxic down here
on Earth we can get exposed to a lot of
different things not just
toxins not just different things that
are poisonous to us but different things
that are poisonous to us yeah what that
means is other people's emotions psychic
attacks any kind of betrayal or trust
breakage jealousy issues that you run
into people with stress all the
different moving parts to be here on
planet Earth Financial stress everything
stress it's here this place can be
really toxic so there has to be a flip
side there has to be something that's
working in our favor that we can utilize
to balance this madness down here
there's experiences down here in planet
Earth that hurt our
heads it just hurts our heads lots of
annoyances things that shouldn't be
happening but they just are there's a
lot of Darkness on planet Earth you see
it out there all kinds of Wars for what
reason all kinds of different problems
out there for what reason
and then the monetary system and then
everything else including the Illuminati
and what's happening there all of it
puppeteering and controlling everything
offer greed and chaos and sickness and
the system it's set up to make people
sick we know that already so while all
this is happening out there and the
world is spinning and all these
different poisons and toxins are
traveling through the air and their
inner hands on on us we breathe them in
we eat them and then all the different
stress factors involved we have to
utilize everything we
have what constraints and what system is
a toad living with what constraints and
what system is a bee living with a
squirrel a flower growing a river
flowing what are these held back with
what kind of roles are placed on these
animals insects that have any roles are
they worried about a monetary system are
they worried about some kind of stress
factor are they worried about someone
screaming at them Someone putting rules
at them someone telling them to wait in
line for a postage stamp are they
worried about something they're not
worried about really anything they're
just doing what they need to do and they
have an energy and a frequency they're
doing it what's governing
nature the laws of nature that's what's
governing nature they live by the laws
of nature it's not the laws of men it's
the laws of nature huge
difference some say the laws of nature
are
harsher you know you see it on
YouTube you see it in the movies you see
a shark come out of the water
grab onto a
seal pull the poor thing down into the
water and blood flowing
everywhere you see a lion chasing after
an antelope taking it down and ripping
it apart you see a
crocodile taking a swim going after a
whole flock of birds just gobbling them
up feathers everywhere you see nature
portray it like that and yes it's there
it
happens but our world that governs us is
a lot more scarier and more
evil it's actually evil in so many ways
and it's set up like that nature is
nature it's dog eat
dog but life on planet Earth for
humankind is dog Slaughter dog a tiger
chases a rabbit for survival
it's
survival a human does a diabolical thing
to another human or group of humans or
large massive group of humans for sport
and hatred and
jealousy but in animal trying to survive
out there like a wolf or a group of
wolves hunting mice in a cold field
before winter comes there's no jealousy
there's no hatred
it's just get a mouse in the stomach to
survive the
winter get a mouse in your mouth chew it
up swallow it so life can
continue big difference the greed the
hatred the jealousy the Betrayal the
trust breakage on this
planet is getting to its
maximum it's
climbing it's
elevating and that gets into our
Consciousness it can contaminate us it
can poison our brains poison our minds
or Consciousness or subconsciousness
poison our
souls and so we need something to shift
that we need to fill the
garden we need to pull the poisonous
weeds out of the garden and we need to
fill the garden with edible
plants we need something to visualize
something to see something that could be
really
healing like maybe a
worm a worm can be very healing if you
take a little shovel and you're digging
it in the garden or you're just digging
in the leaves somewhere and you see an
earthworm pop out and squiggle
away there's something that happens when
you see that worm squiggling
away your soul
a little portal in your soul just opens
right
up your brain cells and neurons start to
receive the information you're seeing an
imprint is being made
instantly and as you're looking at that
earthworm a miracle is
happening information that's sitting
inside your brain and your neurons
starts to move information that may not
be good that's sitting in the emotional
centers of the brain like experiences
stressful experiences old ones too going
all the way back new ones that were just
the other day or some that have been
PTSD or created PTSD long ago and they
just surface every now and then and
Trigger those start to move along
too and it's not just one
earthworm it can be a potato
bug it can be a any kind of creepy
Crawley that you see move around in the
dirt or under the
leaves and then you hear a flutter a
little flutter and it's a bird it's
moving pretty quick there it is it lands
on a branch you look up at it and take a
good look at it and have respect for it
what happens is that in our busy lives
these things become old hat
old hat we just don't respect it like we
should and we don't really receive what
it really is and what it could do for us
we ignore it sometimes too there's
people out there that maybe with a
family member or a friend they go on a
hike but they're not really seeing
anything they're not really taking it in
digesting it it's helping them it's
helping them heal but they're not taking
taking it all in and receiving it they
got other things on their mind or they
feel it's just underneath them beneath
them it's not important compared to
life but it is important and it is
critical to see and understand when you
lean up against a tree and you touch it
and place your hand on that tree realize
something that there is water living
water filled with minerals coming up
from the
earth and going up traveling up right
behind that bark
layer so when you put your hand on that
tree that's its life force that's its
heartbeat the tree's heartbeat isn't in
the middle of the tree the tree's
heartbeat is actually just under that
thin veil of bark
it's right there you're feeling it's
blood you're feeling it's
fluid you're feeling it's living force
and living
Source something happens to that
tree if that bark is cut all the way
around the tree even if it's just an
inch into the tree all the way around it
can't get that drink anymore it'll still
look green but eventually the tree will
just die and all the leaves will turn
brown and crumble and eventually just
fall off because life force is rushing
up through the underneath layer of the
bark so when people hug trees and they
like to hug trees and it's very healing
and it's good for them what's really
happening is they're wrapping their body
around the trees's life force which is
just underneath the bark
but the key is to really get this to
settle in and work for you when you
touch a tree or be near a tree is to
know that's what's
happening because a rewiring
occurs nature
rewires and that includes every aspect
of
nature if you're standing next to that
tree and you know that that water is
Flowing that that's the veins of the
tree and it's flowing upward and that
tree is drinking that water for its
survival and you become conscious of it
aware of it then you go to the next
level it's not just looking at a tree
it's more than that it's understanding
the tree's existence and life force and
when you understand that the tree will
connect to
you A tree can connect to a human
being why would a tree grow
fruit why would a tree grow avocado
one of the reasons A Tree Grows avocados
it isn't just for the squirrels to eat
them and raccoons to eat them when they
fall to the
ground it's for humans to eat and
survive that fruit is grown for
humankind so think about that for a
minute that tree is doing us more than
just a favor it's supporting our life
force it's giving us a food a
staple when that tree grows a
pomegranate it's giving us that food in
that
staple and so the food is growing for us
the tree is growing it for us it knows
then it's
eaters trees no it's eaters when a
squirrel is on that tree trying to take
down a pomegranate the tree knows that
it's growing a food for that
squirrel and so there's a symbiotic
relationship
developing it's always there so when you
go up to a tree the tree knows that
you're part of
everything and then when you become
aware of this though the rewiring really
kicks in and deep healing occurs because
you're not just thinking about oh what
do I got going on today what am I doing
today oh my God my stress is so bad oh
I'm going to stand next to this tree and
absorb this nature but wow lots going on
the minute you switch out of that and
you're just like wow the water is coming
from the earth it's going up the tree
the bark I can put my hand on the side
of the bark I'm touching its vein path
its artery path and when you do that the
wiring and the rewiring just starts to
go into high gear versus just low gear
now anything in nature helps to rewire
even looking at a painting of nature is
healing there's a lot of different
people out there different kinds of
people some people are
compassionate some people are just blood
suckers some people are just energy
suckers some people it's all about what
I can give you if you give me something
it's all about trading some people it's
just all about
bartering barter and barter and
barter I'm not judging any of these
people or any of the people that live
like a certain way or any way they want
to live that's our freedom it's our free
will but a lot of people out there like
to draw from
people energy
suckers they devour energy off the
person and what happens in nature it
doesn't work like that that grasshopper
is not going to take from you it's not
going to draw anything from you it's
going to do the opposite it's going to
offer
something that Cricket is not going to
draw from you and take from you it's not
a blood sucker it's not a emotional well
Digger it's not anything of the
sort it's there to offer
something a squirrel is not going to
take from you unless you want to give it
a
nut unless you want to hand it a nut out
of your own hand which is really healing
for a lot of people but look out the
squirrel might get spooked and get
squirrly and take a little nibble out of
your hand and take a little bite they
got to be
cautious but a squirrel might want to
get a peanut from you but the squirrel
gives you something back in return for
that peanut squirrel's not going to be
an energy
sucker a squirrel is going to be an
energy Giver in a way that's much
different you might not feel
sparkierdust of
reasons that you're going to be
rewired your brain is going to be
functioning
differently just from that experience
with a squirrel just looking at the
squirrel on a tree watching its pattern
what it does how it rubs its face with
its little Claws and
hands how it looks around real fast and
then takes off chases other squirrels
and plays all around the tree I remember
when I was younger taking a walk through
the woods in an area I've never been I
climbed up a hill and there was some
water running
it was a spring and it was
flowing now the miracle thing was we
were in a
drought there was no water really all
the ponds and lakes were down at their
lowest didn't rain for
months birds were searching for water
everywhere it was not a good time it was
a serious
drought but there was just water flowing
down this little Hill
it was miraculous just to see it and to
listen to it I sat down Sat by it and I
listened to it and I watched it
flow and S so said to me this is healing
your soul I said well it feels like it's
healing my soul there's something
happening here and so so said no
listen every single
Trickle and everything you see is
forming a memory and imprint that will
be there forever and you will never
forget it and it's entering through a
passageway into your soul I'll never
forget that I'll never forget that
moment it's with me in this lifetime
forever and spirit of compassion tells
me I'm taking it far beyond this
lifetime it's going to be in there as a
protect Ive
measure a healing measure to help me
stay
strong and that's how powerful nature
is if you're somebody you're not afraid
of
bees because you're just not afraid
maybe you've never had a
reaction maybe you never even had a bee
sting before and you see a bee on a
flower and you drop down to the ground
and you just look at it maybe it's a
honey maybe and it's on the top of a
dandelion
flower and you're listening to it and
you're watching it is gathering up all
that
pollen and you take a good look and you
listen and it enters into the soul deep
into the soul and you can see Blades of
grass going around the dandelion flower
I can see the bee effortlessly just
floating up and down
and then it decides to take off it's
looking for another flower
somewhere at the same time here comes
another bee lands on the same flower
that one just
left it's these memories these
experiences these references they become
references that hold a lot of power and
our healing and maybe you don't have
access to any of it and you're just
sitting inside the house and you're
looking at a
painting there's power in even a
naturistic painting that you can see
flowers and trees and blue skies and
water very
healing healing on the brain
subconsciousness the Consciousness the
soul mentally emotionally spiritually
and even
physically even if you're somebody that
that's in a city or you're chronically
sick and you can't get outside it's too
hard or you don't have the resources but
you can look out of a window and you can
see a bird passing by you could see it
rain in the raindrops hit the window see
the raindrops landing on the grass or on
the trees or in the parking
lot
anything anything in nature is helpful
and and
healing watching a cloud roll in if
you're somebody that can go outside and
lay on a lawn or in a park on the ground
or a grassy
field and you can look up at the sky and
see the dragon flies and maybe that's
not the type of season or the time of
season that's happening right now for
you but maybe you'll get that chance and
you'll see the dragon flies Roll On
by as they
go dragon flies
highly connected to
humankind and help the brain heal and
the Soul heal in many different
ways and so dragon flies going by and
then birds flying up high in the
sky and trees
rustling and do other things besides C
make sure you listen and hear and then
feel if you have the opportunity to just
sit there on the
ground and just play with little twigs
and pull grass up from the earth and
touch the
grass just that alone is so healing and
so powerful creates references that help
battle chronic
illness and help battle emotional abuse
emotional pain betrayal any kind of
problems that have happened in your life
being let down trust
breakage these very Tools in nature help
to reverse that help to heal it
especially if it's happening on a
continual basis maybe you're in a
relationship and there's a lot of
distrust in the relationship betrayal
and all kinds of
aggravation compromises that are
happening between the relationship for
some
reason and so it's a constant battle or
a constant ARG arent or fight getting
into nature in
between critical to clear the Sate or
help clear the Sate help ease things
especially if you feel like your soul is
taking on water it's like a boat out
there and the waters get rough and
there's a storm coming and the boat's
rocking and water's coming onto the boat
it's taking on water and it's feeling
heavy even when a soul can feel heavy
feeling like it's been beaten or
battered by distress alone or anything
happening in your life nature is a
weapon against
it nature can help get that boat
floating get the Seas to
come get the water out of the boat when
we go through life we feel like we're on
somebody else's playing field
let's face it it's that difficult down
here and we're on someone else's playing
field out there when you get into nature
it's on your playing field now nature is
your playing
field you get to be in nature in
peace you get to see it feel it take it
in for what it is evildoers on the
planet don't want you Tak it in
nature they just want to destroy nature
they do it all the time or they just
want to withhold nature that's why most
of the planet isn't accessible to people
meaning it's restricted land it's off
limits you're allowed to play in Parks
you're allowed to take hikes in Parks
visit national parks and state parks but
there's so much land and so much nature
people are not allowed to enjoy or see
it's it's controlled it's kept from
people but you don't need to do the big
nature thing if it's not something that
you have time for resources or energy
for it can be as simple as your own yard
your own backyard your friend's backyard
anywhere anyhow it could be this small
little tiny Island not an island out in
the sea but an island near your house or
your apartment meaning a little spot
that has a few trees trees and some
grass and if you sat there just for a
few minutes even for 3 minutes you can
take in what nature offers and you might
see something that surprises you you
might see an insect or a bird or a hawk
fly by and that's the power of nature no
matter what we can use it for our own
benefit whenever we need it we can look
in the sky we can take a deep breath we
can breathe in air into our lungs we can
connect to the water sources around us
to the Lakes the rivers the oceans and
maybe only once a year you get to an
ocean and you can walk on that sand and
experience like the medical medium waves
on a beach
meditation and you can experience that
once and then you have that reference
and it stays with you a lifetime and it
stays in your soul and it sits there and
it doesn't leave nobody can take it from
you it can't be
stolen it can't leave you you're not
going to get let down you're not going
to get your trust broken that experience
is going to sit inside your soul and
your neurons and your brain and your
emotional centers of the brain for a
lifetime and Beyond and it's going to
help protect you and help you heal
nature is so powerful for healing that
if you couldn't get out and you can only
watch it on the computer or television
it can still give you benefits to
Healing it can still help your
Consciousness it can still help heal
your soul and also prepare you for when
you can get out someday and experience
nature in your own
hands I see a
bird it's
beautiful just watch it hop around on
that
branch and then look
it's putting its beak in its
wing fluffing its
feathers it's just so
amazing oh there's a hawk up there real
high what kind of Hawk is
that is it a red tail
hawk wow it's just
unbelievable
nature I think that Hawk looking at the
field just watching to see if there's
any mice oh what was that there a
grasshopper just hopped over
me oh I love these
grasshoppers I can't believe people want
to eat
grasshoppers I just can't do it I can't
I can't eat
one oh that's a beautiful bumblebee
Bumblebees are my favorite
look how cute and fuzzy the Bumblebee
is why do they look so
friendly is that a bunny
rabbit on the edge of the
woods look at
that there's a goose over there with
some baby
geese what are those
ducklings I just saw fish jumped in the
pond I wonder what kind of fish that was
was it a
bass I'm just taking it all
in the clouds are
dark the birds are
praying the fish are
flipping the ice is
breaking the wind is hauling
and the water is rushing and
rolling the lakes are
brimming the bottom of the ocean is
crawling I can sense the wood Chucks
gnawing our bodies communicate to the
Earthly mother our souls to the Heavenly
Father Here comes the
rain it far from drives me insane pain
it's
feeling good in some ways and feeding
life and I respect its
persistence all the
same nature fights
arrogance and I know deep down inside it
has the strength to heal the deepest of
wounds the Angels sometimes appear in
nature in the woods in the water to help
with disasters brought on by
disorder can you see the Angels walk
with a light Rod through the woods to
free animals that may have been tricked
by a snare
facade struggling in the bush and only a
compassionate Angelic Force could
acknowledge thank
God look at a
flower it's in its greatest
hour and draw in its energy as it clears
your
frequency and see the bird fly high in
the
sky every sighting keeps you here a
little
longer and longer because a switch flips
behind your eyes that helps you heal and
your
soul will never die
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
boted research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion