how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about
chumming and before you think about it
and you're like what is chumming just
know a lot of people do it they do it
every single day they don't realize
they're doing it but they're doing it so
why should I care about chumming or why
should all of us care about chumming
because it leads to chronic illness it
speeds up chronic illness it brings us
into chronic illness
flares the world is getting sick and
sicker because the world doesn't realize
it but they're chumming get ready for
this ride I say fasten your seat bels
for sure grab yourself a cup of tea if
you need to some herbal tea but I'm
telling you now this is going to be a
wild
ride what a nice day out here in the
water yeah we're almost at a destination
all right the boat slowing down good
good good good all right I say we do an
inventory let's do that inventory now
get the barrels out you got them okay
you got your notepad there okay fish
guts check okay fish guts great p pig
heads you can't find them it's not
Barrel there pig heads oh you got them
great check cow
guts cow guts yeah we got a barrel of
cow guts that's it right there great
fish
guts you don't know which one that is
you think that was the cow guts no
that's that's the fish guts Barrel okay
check pigs
blood that's the barrel filled of pigs
blood
yep okay good
check fish heads all right that's easy
just open up the cap on that Barrel see
all the fish heads right there there all
kinds of fish
heads Perfect all right get the barrel
ready bring it to the back of the boat
you got everything rigged you got your
fishing poles got your
Harpoon all right let's do this dump
that Barrel over okay oh just watch it
you splashed it on me
okay great I just love
chumming this is the best
part so when we're chumming out there in
the water and we're fishing we're trying
to get sharks or any kind of other
creature that actually loves the smell
of blood loves the taste of fish Parts
when we're chumming we're trying to
catch something same thing with trying
to catch crab
people who crab put bait in the
Trap The Crab Trap same thing with
lobsters you put bait in the lobster
trap because you're trying to catch
something and get them what people don't
realize is they're chumming every single
day they're chumming inside their body
but the difference is they're not
chumming so they can capture something
they're not chumming inside their body
so they can catch something and remove
it they're chumming every single day not
realizing it they're chumming to fatten
things up to feed something to feed some
type of creature but it's really not a
creature it's a virus it's a pathogen
it's bacteria they're chumming every day
and they're fattening up the viruses and
the
bacteria public medical research and
science you know what that is that's
stuff you see every day art articles out
there studies out there or so-called
studies cuz a lot of the stuff in the
study really doesn't match the article
and so forth but you see a lot of stuff
out there public medical research and
science it's doctors it's medical
schools that's public medical research
and science well public medical research
and science still to this day does not
know viruses actually eat they're hungry
they love the feed on food they also
don't know that viruses are a cell a
viral cell it's still in debate public
medical research and science thinks it's
like a strand of something maybe RNA or
something else they'll just make up
something too as the years go by to just
kind of go along with The Strand or the
fact that it's not living or the fact
that's not alive or doesn't eat public
medical research and science till this
day doesn't know what classified medical
research and science knows and what is
that bugs eat viruses eat public medical
research and science believes that
viruses are really just genetic
information what that means is they're
not alive they're not really real
they're not a viral cell so to speak
that's living they're just this
mysterious piece of DNA or RNA a strand
of something wrapped up in a tiny ball
in some situations basically just
something that doesn't really exist but
exists how can it do anything how can it
be a problem when it's not even real or
living classified medical research and
science they are wiser they know
something different and they laugh at
their colleagues the ones in public
medical research and science because
they know they're in the dark you see
it's not that public medical research
and science has been in the dark it's
just that they've been in the dark for
over a 100 years well over 100 years now
not just a year or 10 years or in the
dark on one thing they've been in the
dark about pathogens for over a hundred
years classified medical research and
science learned a long time ago that
viruses other pathogens feed they need
feeding to stay alive to keep them alive
in a lab to keep them under the
microscope they can't just exist and not
be fed they can't be supported and still
viewed tested and looked at and
monitored classified medical research
and science learned this a long time ago
when they discovered bugs when they saw
it under the microscope they saw it in
someone's blood they tried to preserve
those those
organisms they try to preserve those
pathogens so they could study them look
at them find out what makes them tick
they subjected the bugs they saw viruses
bacteria to a lot of different things
they noticed what would not keep the bug
around where the bug would just die and
be useless and no longer something they
can view or monitor or watch or grow
they used Mercury and realized Mercury
was a preservative it preserved the bugs
kept them alive kept them around but
they didn't know how or why it happened
they tried a lot of different foods to
keep the bugs going to try to
proliferate them grow them get them to
multiply and there was one food they saw
an unusual outcome real productivity and
it was egg
the egg became the number one food for
pathogens and bugs to keep them alive in
the classified medical research and
science labs and what they discovered
was the viruses would feed would fuel
themselves with that egg they would eat
the egg it kept them alive but more than
keeping them alive it kept them growing
rapidly so classified medical research
and science start at the assembly line
the actual pathogen assembly line you're
sick today because of what they did over
a 100 years ago because of that assembly
line that's why you're sick today
because you have a bug that they created
over a 100 years ago that's why
everybody is sick today that's why they
have all the chronic fatigue syndrome
and the seratic arthritis and the ra and
the Ms and so many other different
conditions and symptoms
it's because of classified medical
research and Science and what they did
over a hundred years ago creating the
bug assembly line classified medical
research and science wanted everybody to
be sick down the road they wanted people
to die and be maimed and be chronically
ill forever that was the plan and they
wanted public medical research and
science to not have a clue and to look
like idiots like they did all these
decades when someone came to the
doctor's office and they didn't know why
they were sick classified medical
research and science grew viruses docile
viruses ones that weren't really a big
problem they grew them they reshaped
them they mutated them they made them
aggressive they fed them they starved
them they made them hungry again and
they created monsters and they took
those pathogenic monsters and they put
it in animals they they watched the
animals live their life they watched for
symptoms and conditions and the animals
that showed symptoms conditions and
disease they then remov those viruses
out of those animals and then stuck them
back into other animals and fed them
again by feeding the animals what they
wanted to feed them they were raising
bugs and eggs and they were raising bugs
in animals and then back in eggs back
into animals back into eggs back into
animals until they found animals that
were getting really sick and really
diseased as the leading animals they
were taking the bugs from again they
wanted aggressive bugs bugs that did
destruction created even long-term
sickness created even death at this time
over 100 years ago public medical
research in science were churning out
doctors the doctors were studying
patients trying to heal them of their
sickness and at the same moment
classified medical research and science
was playing in biological
warfare the past is always forgotten
right now social media is all about the
present moment it's all about what's
happening in the moment not about how we
got here how did we get here in this
position now classified medical research
and science were doing biological
warfare well over a 100 years ago they
were developing monsters that they
planned on getting into humans to make
the chronic illness world what it is
today and a big part of how classified
medical research and science
accomplished this was they used animals
to Chum they were chumming inside
animals once they found out what a
pathogen a virus Lov to eat like eggs
for example they would feed the eggs to
an animal they plac the new virus in
once they were chumming chumming with
the food that the viruses love to eat
and the pathogens love to feed on once
they were chumming they would draw blood
and they would see an increase of
pathogenic material they would see an
increase of viral cells once they
discovered all the foods that viruses
would love to eat and fed on and fuel
themselves with then they knew they had
something here so then when they
released all of these man ufactured
viruses out there in the world they knew
they're going to be fed move us forward
over 100 years and people are feeding
their bugs they're feeding their
pathogens their viruses their bacteria
they're chumming every single day
they're chumming for bugs the difference
they're not chumming to catch the bug
and get it out of the body they're
chumming to feed the bug to get the bug
stronger to move bugs around the body to
get them hungrier for different foods
that they love and to make it so they
grow at a rapid
Pace look at the pig blood what look
what happens when it hits the water
anything
yet who what was that who shark fin here
it comes whoa whoa it just took that pig
head right
down oh my got another one who we got
sharks now lots of sharks whoa okay get
get the get the spear get the spear gun
ready who look look out whoa okay okay
just you got the fishing rods out just
in case something else is hungry too you
never know what you're going to catch
right here all right put the fish guts
out put the cow guts out put it all out
just keep on dumping it in it's like a
Feeding Frenzy oh look at that one whoa
look out all right all right all right
watch out watch out that one almost got
you just coming out of the water there
just be careful dumping
that people have viruses in them they
get them from their families their
parents pass down from generation to
generation that's why the whole genetic
thing with oh well I have a person in my
family that has the disease so I'm going
to have the disease my father had this
illness and symptoms so I have it or
maybe it skips a generation and then
someone else has it in a family line but
it's getting passed down passed down but
what people don't realize it's viruses
and pathogens going back well over a 100
years being passed down generation to
generation and so these viruses live in
our bodies they're there they're sitting
dormant many times inside people's
livers in their spleen in other organs
the liver does hold a lot of different
pathogens they could be sleeping it's
called dorcy they're dormant they're
actually not awakened they're sitting
there cells and they're incubating
they're alive they're staying preserved
but then they can be awakened things can
awaken them like chumming when we're
chumming when we're consuming foods that
awaken these bugs get them out of dorcy
sometimes we can eat foods that can sit
there and Float around them for years
but then one day the bug starts
Awakening and it sniffs the chum and it
goes for it I want it goes forward it
gets an appetite it starts to grow it
produces more viral cells and more viral
cells and more viral cell toxins and
then the chumming takes it to a level
where now we're getting
sick another thing is catching a bug
recently from someone catching a bug
from a shopping Carriage the handles on
it rubbing your eye catching a bug from
a door knob a toilet seat catching a bug
from just bodily fluids from somebody
else getting new bugs new bugs with
appetites new bugs that were feeding in
somebody else's body so somebody else
was chumming they were putting Chum
inside their body all the time feeding
those bugs those bugs are used to their
Chum and as those bugs are sitting
inside of you looking for food they're
looking for food they were raised on
food they like and enjoy so you might be
somebody that contracted or picked up
bugs from somebody else or some other
way and you got these new bugs new
viruses inside of you they're used to
somebody else's Chum when they're
chumming now they're hungry and they
want the food they were used to so they
start giving craving messages to the
person to the new host craving messages
they want the food they were used to
that they ate every day this is when
someone that doesn't eat a lot of eggs
ends up liking a lot of eggs and eating
them more they don't usually eat eggs
they eat them maybe once a month maybe
once every few weeks maybe once every
few months but all of a sudden after
being in a relationship for a while
being with somebody they contracted bugs
from or some other Avenue those bugs are
hungry and they want the food somebody
else used to eat all the time so then
the bug starts sending messages
information leeches out of the bugs they
excrete hungry hormones those hungry
hormones float around get to the brain
and trip up the hunger
senses somebody that didn't eat a lot of
eggs and they might have had their own
bugs in them too but maybe those bugs
weren't really tuned into eggs and that
person really wasn't a big egg eater but
now the new bugs they're getting real
hungry fast so they're sending those
signals and then the person's like I'm
in the mood for eggs now there's a few
different ways to catch pathogens bugs
viruses one is blood
transfusions that's a very popular way
if someone gets a blood transfusion
there's a good chance they going to pick
up a few different new bugs in their
system another one is public bathrooms
being careless in them another one is
shopping handles door knobs that's
another one too but sex is a big one
bodily fluid shared during sex out of
all these ways of getting pathogens sex
is the most popular it's the most
popular way and most common way to get a
pathogen so much so the pathogens rely
on it viruses and bacteria rely on sex
viruses have
information they retain information for
bugs to be living on past that host
viruses want bugs out of the host into
another host host that's one of viruses
and pathogens goals is to send pathogens
viruses bugs to another person and then
to another person that's
Survival that's the way the virus can be
guaranteed it's kind is going to survive
and live beyond that person that host or
that virus it's a pathogen survival
mechanism so when people have sex
intercourse or share bodily fluids it's
one of the great ways to guarantee that
survival so when there's a new host with
new viral cells in them we have to feed
them now the number one food after
having sex of any kind are eggs people
make eggs they do it the next morning or
they do it late that night or early
morning or it's the next meal they eat
but they always have scrambled eggs and
maybe nowadays one person might have
something else else they make themselves
some type of protein smoothie another
person will do something else but mostly
and most of the time there's eggs
involved scrambled eggs top of the list
it's a postex food it is a feeder it's
the ultimate chummer chumming it's to
feed the new viral cells the new viral
eggs the new viruses it's to feed them
to make sure they get a strong start and
they can root and they can have the
strength to
travel one of the reasons why people
fight so hard to defend their eggs is
because their eggs are keeping the bugs
happy they're keeping them solid they're
keeping them strong a lot of people out
there who have been sick with all kinds
of different symptoms all kinds of
different issues fight for their eggs
like nobody's business and then there's
people that aren't really sick yet but
the bugs are dormant and they're there
and they still need that food to feed
them to keep them going cuz dormy
doesn't mean they're totally asleep it
means they're still feeding but they're
staying lowkey waiting for a day to make
their
break people fight for their eggs like
no other they will go to the next level
they will do anything they need to do so
someone lays off of them about their
eggs you could tell them to stay away
from from meat they'll be fine with that
they'll go through their phases you
could tell them to stay away from Beans
they'll go through their phases you can
tell them to stay away from dairy milk
butter they'll go through their phases
and they'll stay away from it they'll
try it you tell them to stay away from
eggs and it's a fight it's
Fierce you can mention hey go off a
gluten that would be a good idea and
they would be like you're right you're
right I should stay away from gluten
it's not good that I'm getting all this
gluten in me but then then you tell them
stay away from eggs and they'll look at
you and they'll get angry they'll hate
you one of the first things they'll say
is what do I eat then what am I going to
eat I have nothing to eat now what am I
going to do to replace my eggs what can
I get what can I eat tell me now I
learned long ago that eggs were a tough
one for people that getting them off of
eggs could be almost impossible no
matter how sick they were they going to
have 100 symptoms and when you bring up
the eggs they freeze up eggs are scary
removing them for so many people and I
knew this I knew that there's
possibilities of keeping the eggs in
there if we need to do other things and
keep on moving forward until their Free
Will got strong enough to realize whoa
I'm feeling better CU of this maybe if I
take out the eggs I could really move
forward almost 25 years ago
my wife and I started an organic store
it was the first organic and wild food
store in the United States and back then
there wasn't such thing there wasn't
just an all organic health food store
with wild Foods included instead it was
mostly
prod departments had very few options
that were organic even in the best
stores around in our prodest department
was the first organic produce department
the first one to have 100% organic
produce in it the store was the first of
its kind the other thing we did was we
never put a markup on the organic
produce the produce department was at
Cost it's whatever we spent and then
that's what we would charge
we wanted people to be able to afford
organic produce now downstairs on the
other side of the building that the
store was in I had my office it was the
medical medium office and people
worldwide came to see me in that office
people traveled from all the different
countries in the world they traveled
from around the United States to see me
in person in that office to find answers
and to have me work and help help their
doctors with discoveries to what was
wrong after somebody's appointment we
would go upstairs to the store and
people would want to get things they
needed to help them heal so we would
walk around we would go into the produce
department and people would learn about
organic produce for the first time in
their life many of them and they would
know what foods were good for them they
would learn for the first time what to
eat to help them heal and what they
would ask all the time was can I eat
eggs can I still have eggs in my diet
and I would say of course you can but CU
you're suffering with all these
different conditions it's best not to
use those eggs to feed all the bugs the
very things behind your symptoms a lot
of people would panic and they would ask
me can you get eggs in the store can you
get organic eggs in the store since the
store's organic and I said yes so we
stocked eggs in the store for people so
we stocked the best eggs you can find at
the time in the store for people so they
had an option and like I've always said
and still till this day if you're going
to eat eggs eat the best ones you can
find if you raise them in your backyard
that's the ones you eat they're the best
ones you can find and there were local
small farms that were raising chickens
they were free range organic they were
feeding these chickens all or organic
food they would come to us and say will
you take our eggs will you stock them in
the store so people can get them and we
said yes of course because these are the
best eggs that are out there that we can
find local fresh free range organic eggs
because as I always said before I'm not
the food police I'm not telling you
don't eat this and don't eat that I'm
telling you if you have a pathogen or a
bug you're unwell and sick you have
these options just just like in the
medical medium anti-bug cleanse you can
pick your level if you need to keep eggs
in for now you keep eggs in for now you
can customize it for yourself you can
take the information and use it in the
way you need to use it and then
eventually you can go to another level
and say okay I'm ready to get rid of
eggs for now every day at the store we
would get requests they would phone in
they would show up at the store people
wanted eggs so we would get the best
eggs for them because they were going to
getg eggs somewhere else anyway and get
a bad egg we wanted to at least offer
them something they were hungry for
something they wanted something they
cared about Good Health they wanted the
best
eggs Spirit of compassion and I always
believe knowledge is power true
knowledge the truth is power it's
empowering so I put a sign next to the
eggs I put a sign right on the
refrigerator and it said eat at your own
risk
eggs feed pathogens they feed viruses
and bacteria inside the body if you're
someone struggling with an illness or a
symptom beware this could actually bring
it about cause a future flare and take
you to a place of poor health some
people were confused by this they did
not know what this meant remember this
is 25 years ago keep in mind now people
don't know what this means today and
there are a lot of people out there that
don't even believe in viruses today at
all even after covid and this was the
Dark Ages this was 25 years ago in the
health movement where were you 25 years
ago there are lots of different doctors
now on social media that are like 30
years old they were 5 years old when
this was going on there are influencers
now and podcast doctors and health
people on social that were in
kindergarten when this was happening or
not even born yet so let's get back to
the sign that was posted on the fridge
in the store where the eggs were a
couple people were really worried they
didn't know what it meant they didn't
understand pathogens or eggs with
pathogens or anything of the sort so
somebody thought maybe the eggs in the
refrigerator actually have salmonella
one day our store manager was over by
the egg Department over there and was
standing there talking to somebody the
person they were talking to was a state
official as a health inspector he was
reading the sign and asking questions
about it our manager explained the whole
thing about what it meant he laughed and
he walked out for decades I've been a
messenger a messenger of information
that's life-changing it's changed Health
itself out there I put up with a lot and
over the years eggs has been a big one
I've taken a lot of because of eggs
and remember I think I said this all the
way back many many years ago publicly
that egg eggs were my favorite when I
was a kid and that my dream was to have
an egg Shack a restaurant a little egg
Shack where I made eggs in all kinds of
different ways for people sunyside up
poached fried scrambled omelets
everything I thought it was the greatest
but messaging the truth about chronic
illness is the most important getting
people better recovering them getting
their lives back getting them out of
wheelchairs getting them back to life
back to work moving them forward healing
them it's the most important thing keep
in mind that 25 years ago that wasn't a
medical medium only store this was a
health food store that was servicing not
only the area but around the whole state
and Beyond it was a grocery store but an
organic health food market grocery store
and that means it was for everybody who
needed something it wasn't a iCal medium
only
store I want you to know I understand
how hard it is it's not easy when you
love a food or have an attachment to a
food especially since it could go back
to when you were a child when your
mother made you eggs your grandfather
made you eggs maybe a time where you
actually had eggs with somebody that you
love and care about eggs get attached to
our soul soul experiences these are
loving experiences more experien es of
comfort and it's a comfort food and I'm
not judging anyone and I've never been
hard on anyone about eggs I've only been
a messenger about the information of
what classified medical research and
science has done to our eggs and how
they manipulated them and how they fed
them to pathogens and got those
pathogens to become little monsters and
then they released those little monsters
onto the public over time so that people
would contract
those very little monsters and those
little pathogens those viruses those
bacteria those monsters they're now
feeding on Chum just like the classified
medical research and science want it to
happen they wanted people to be
oblivious and just eat whatever and feed
the bugs but eggs aren't the only food
classified medical research and science
fed to bugs they fed dairy products to
bugs they fed gluten to bugs they fed
corn to bugs they fed soy to bugs milk
cheese and butter and then there's toxic
heavy metals they fed bugs toxic heavy
metals they mixed the metals in with the
favorite foods the bugs loved they mixed
Metals in with eggs with milk with
cheese with butter with gluten the goal
was for people to Chum their bugs so
anytime somebody ate some of these Foods
these very foods that were fed to these
pathogens long long ago and any time
somebody ate them they were chumming
chumming their bugs that means bugs that
were sitting inside of them were getting
fed so someday they can rise up and
cause a problem the last thing someone
needs is a Feeding Frenzy especially if
they're already sick with chronic
illness they weren't told what to avoid
they weren't taught so they didn't know
and they don't know and classified
medical research and science will never
say a word they want people to not know
they want people to feed their
bugs sharks are splashing around
everywhere oh my god oh look at that big
one look how huge it is wait a minute
watch out watch out oh the shark just B
off our other friend's head oh no what
are we going to do he's gushing blood
everywhere this was a bad idea I guess
he's just used his Chum I don't know
wait a minute don't throw in you're
trying to use him as Chum now too I mean
it's a doggy dog
world it's
evil it's
sick classified medicine games played on
the people who fall for the tricks doing
bad to
humankind instead of good and allowing
the Holy Light to
shine the papete teers at the top so
many of them now control the gov control
apps control the Ops so much doing wrong
will they ever stop it's on purpose to
break down the mind and hurt the future
billions of lives causing them to fold
early in life destroying
Bloodlines listen up there's so much
more to
unwind Sinister bastards they are look
how far they go to let the monsters out
in the park to pray on the masses
setting traps so the innocent beings get
sicker fastest they only want hopeless
Health
disasters and the influencers are
helping the darkness and doing Evil's
bidding to make it go even
faster they don't know it but they're
working for the dark lord beazel buug
the
master over a 100 years ago they grew
pathogens in an egg and they took the
baby chick's
Soul the bugs ate the undeveloped
protein and gained a permanent worldwide
role after enough bugs were cuddled and
collected they placed them in vials and
found different ways to get people
infected
the true battle of chronic illness and
what really happened will stay hidden in
neglected but only for so
long God will someday sing God's song
and write the wrong
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
media podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion