how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about angels
you've heard of angels they're
everywhere but do you believe in angels
do you believe in their power because
they are out there and they are looking
out for people but what about accessing
Angels what about reaching out to them
communicating with angels and do you
know their names and what about angels
that don't have names did you think
about that because in this episode we're
going there we're going to explore and
talk about information from above that's
mindblowing about angels you're not even
aware of now for this one I would strap
yourself in and get ready because this
is information that's
Supernatural everybody is born with the
god-given right to reach out to Angels
whenever you need them now it may not
feel this way you may not feel angels
are out there so many people who have
struggles give up on thinking angels are
even there but they've witnessed your
struggle if you're somebody that went
through a hardship tragedy or just
anything that affected you Angels
witnessed it they're there as your
witness since the beginning of humankind
angels have been in existence they've
been here on Earth to look out for
people they've been here on Earth even
before Earth was here before the planet
itself was here they were getting ready
to service this planet they were getting
ready to serve people getting ready to
serve people here on this Earth but they
were already in existence serving people
civilizations on other planets like
Earth this planet was a new Battleground
for the angels and God's angels were
already helping prepare this planet when
it was forming already there to assist
God in the formation of this planet in
this solar system really early on and
why would Angels God's angels be there
to assist in the formation of this
planet because they had to be here
because of the falling angels the Fallen
ones as soon as the Earth was
inhabitable it was
ready there were the angels all set to
help
humankind now there are different Angels
they're not all the same there's angels
with different names there's different
varieties of angels we're going to be
talking about the group that's called
the unknown
angels in today's time present moment
right now in the Forefront of History
angels are working with us every day
there's a lot of Calamity on planet
Earth there's a lot of adversity there's
a lot of struggle there's a lot of
genocide still
today there's a lot of fights there's a
lot of Wars there's a lot of unjust
poisonous actions being taken out there
there's a lot of different things highly
toxic things on planet Earth that hurt
people in so many different ways and
then there's the everyday grind
accidents happening freak accidents
problems all kinds of different struggle
and Angels they're kept busy every
single day every single hour every
single minute there are m millions of
people on this planet that are praying
to the angels asking for help all the
time but who are they asking who are
they praying to most people pray to the
archangels they're asking for help from
the archangels two of the archangels are
asked upon and called upon all the time
Archangel Gabriel Archangel Michael they
get requests by the second all over the
globe and here's the crazy thing what
about another planet where humans live
who's watching over them who's servicing
those planets or another planet
Archangel Gabriel and Archangel Michael
now because most people pray to
archangels Michael and Gabriel they're
really busy it accounts for why a lot of
people don't get the help they need
they're stretched too thin and the
archangels Michael and Gabriel they got
other problems they have to fight evil
they have to battle Fallen Angels when
God calls upon them they have to go and
battle Fallen Angels at that moment
which takes them away from the job of
helping people individually but there's
a group of Angels the unknown angels and
they're working too really hard they're
working for God but you got a better
chance of getting one of them to help
you at difficult times and struggles
these powerful angels angs the unknown
angels are at a number of
144,000 there are exactly 144,000 of the
unknown Angels working for God this is a
holy number that God reveres because
they're unnamed they have no notoriety
they have no Acclaim their egos are
extremely low the unknown Angels carry
not a sword like Archangel Gabriel and
Archangel Michael and even their swords
are not exactly a sword like the kind of
sword that we see or we think about in
fighting in war but the unknown Angels
carry a light rod and this light Rod
wields a lot of power now the thing
about the light Rod is once you know
about this light Rod you can help access
it in your favor you can ask the unknown
angels to baptize you in a way to anoint
you to touch you with the light rod they
may do it anyway without you even
realizing it but asking them is really
helpful and beneficial because there's a
good chance when you're asking for it
asking for their help and the light Rod
to actually touch you they will do it
unknown Angels travel in numbers unlike
other angels that may travel alone
unknown Angels travel in groups and many
times they travel in threes so when
you're asking for help there's a good
chance three will come now unknown
Angels do travel alone periodically they
often do that now when it comes down to
Angels Angels tend to work with each
other when they're in battle so they'll
get together during a battle sometimes
they'll have to battle alone when it's
Darkness evil when it's against demons
when it's against Fallen Angels but in
this situation when you're asking for
help you're asking for these Holy Angels
the unknown angels
they travel in packs and they're there
to help you now if you hear stories out
there where someone sees an angel or
it's caught on a photograph and they see
the light they see Wings they see an
angel shape maybe they see it floating
above a car in a road maybe they see it
on a bridge but they caught it they
captured it it was miraculously captured
on a video or on film on a picture a
photograph
that light you see when you see the
angel in that photograph that's because
of the light Rod the carry or the sword
that light Rod is actually bringing
light into that photograph it's where
they get most of their light it's the
power coming off of that sword or that
Rod that light Rod is also used to cast
light to shoot light send it in a
Direction so if an angel is trying to
get there as fast as they can can to
stop an overturned bus to save a bunch
of children or to save someone's life if
the Angels not there in time they'll try
to cast a light bolt from that Rod to
get there first to stop the tragedy or
to save at least one person on that bus
or in that car now there's a lot of bad
things happening on planet Earth all the
time and angels are working as hard as
they can now when things are happening
and they're bad Darkness can be involved
and it's that darkness that wants to
take the Angel's time away wants to trip
up the Angels keep the Angels busy so
the Angels can't take care of everybody
and that's why it's important to know
about the unknown Angels the best way to
reach the unknown Angels is saying their
name out loud asking for help out loud
praying for them out loud or directly to
God pray directly to God and ask God for
unknown angels to help ask God to send
unknown Angels or you can just go
straight to the unknown angels and ask
them saying it out of your mouth out
loud is critical because in our head we
just have a bunch of thoughts a lot of
people got a lot of different things
going on all kinds of different stress
different thoughts obsessive thoughts
information flying around and so when
you're asking for help and you're
praying to the unknown Angels it's
important to ask out loud you want them
to hear you there's a couple of things
going on one is the intention the
intention of really needing help it
comes out when you ask for it another
thing we have all these thoughts in our
head and we don't need the angels having
to sift through that it's like walking
down a street seeing a dumpster and then
jumping in it and sifting through it
looking for something in that dumpster
we have a lot of thoughts going on in
our heads a lot of it are junk thoughts
they don't need to be there but they're
there a lot of them are fed to us too
conditioning all from what we see what's
on social media other places so we have
all this jumbled stuff in there Angels
don't want to have to sip through that
they don't want to jump into a dumpster
in our heads and go through all that to
find that one thing you said which is I
need help and that one thing that you
said I need help with or the words I
need help in your mind can be wrapped
around a lot of baggage a lot of people
carry tremendous amounts of baggage and
that baggage contains a lot old
relationship breakups betrayal hurt harm
trust issues trust breakage anything
that happened that day information from
all your appointments information from
when you were growing up when you were
first born lots of baggage all wrapped
up into one it's in there and Angels
they have a hard time going through it
all and Angels they're really busy
they're not just saving human lives
they're saving animal lives so we need
to make it as easy as possible for them
to help us to hear us now if you're
somebody who can't get the words out for
some reason any reason maybe it's just
you're somebody who's very weak and
you're not feeling well your body feels
dry trained you're at a weak point in
your day your neurological system isn't
functioning good you're somebody that's
on mattress Island and you're struggling
or maybe it's the middle of the night
you just don't have the strength the
fortitude the energy to speak in that
moment then that's okay the angels will
know they'll know if you can't get that
out if you can't ask out loud they'll
know this they'll be there anyway
they'll know because a different
intention occurs when you can't get your
words out when you're struggling if
you're in a weakened state with your
condition of any kind and you want to so
bad you want to say something but you
can't and you can't even whisper it
they'll know this because it's a
different intention because thoughts all
kinds of different baggage all kinds of
different SC scrambled different
thoughts they don't take over when the
intention is to get out the world words
when you're in a weakened State and you
can't voice yourself so the angels will
hear your intention and they'll come and
help but if you have a voice and the
strength behind it it's best to ask out
loud almost everything in the world has
a name we like to know its name whatever
it is a plant a piece of fruit a car a
street a state a shoe a handbag
everything needs a name that's how we
work down here every single animal every
insect has to have a name and we're used
to that names mean everything to
everybody if something doesn't have a
name we start losing faith or we lose
Faith instantly because it doesn't have
a name things need to have names for
people to believe in them even a
haunting a ghost people need to know the
name of the ghost a lot of people out
there they don't believe in ghosts so it
makes it harder for them to entrust that
that's a ghost in a house but when
someone puts a name to That Ghost it
becomes believable like that's old Mr
Smith that's who's walking around the
house Mr Smith used to live here Mr
Smith died he died in the bathroom 50
years ago somebody could see a ghost or
tell somebody that they saw a ghost but
when you put a name to That Ghost it's
believable that's the person that lived
here 50 years ago 100 years ago 200
years ago this is the case with angel
sightings a lot of psychics out there or
people that talk about angels they hear
this or maybe it's their own story they
saw an angel and they saw Archangel
Michael or Archangel Gabriel having a
name to that angel makes it more
believable so when someone sees an angel
and they could be seeing a real angel
Archangel Michael it helps because I saw
Archangel Michael and somebody's like
wow that's incredible and it makes it
more powerful the sighting everything
about it especially if someone thinks
that was definitely Archangel Michael
and maybe it was or it was another Angel
but it makes Faith grow even more you
have a name the unknown Angels don't
have a name there's 144,000 of them
which means there would be 144,000 names
so it takes a level of Faith to believe
in them it takes a level of
understanding it takes a level of I
believe in these
angels it takes Faith to believe in God
it takes Faith to believe in angels and
it takes Faith to believe in the unknown
Angels the unknown Angels respect faith
they have a tremendous respect for Faith
and if you don't have faith in them
that's okay they will still have respect
and they will still help even though
Angels work for God they have their own
free will they can make their own
decisions Angels don't take orders from
people Angels don't take direction from
people they choose to do what they want
to do and when you're humble Angels see
this they understand this when you're
somebody and you're asking for help and
you're humble and you've been through a
lot Angels see this and when you're
asking for help from the angels angels
read your heart they read your soul they
read your head they read everything
they're listening they're looking
they're taking a good good look at you
one of the things that Spirit of
compassion has always told me since I
was young when asking help from angels
is to say when asking I know you're busy
I know you're doing a lot out there I
know you're saving others I know you're
protecting people unknown Angel if you
get a chance on your busy day on your
busy time all that you're doing battling
Darkness helping others saving lives if
you get a chance I need some help is it
possible to sit by my bedside and keep
me company Watch Over Me while I'm
healing tonight and when it comes down
to unknown Angels there's a very good
chance more than one will come and it
will be three and they'll stand by your
bedside I saw a big
light it was floating over a
field I was looking out my window it was
early
morning I knew it was real it was shaped
like a
bird shaped like an eagle but everything
I felt in my bones and soul told me it
was an
angel tears dropping from my eyes I was
crying for no reason don't know
why I believe it all took me by
surprise the realization of what I saw
was more than I could ever
surmise I stepped outside the sun was
almost about to rise I walked over to
the spot where the angel was and I
suddenly felt warm and I felt very tall
even though the air had a chill and I
wasn't wearing a sweater or a
Shaw I prayed to God and said thank you
for sending me her
deep down inside I knew she was God's
best God's all I thanked the angel I
could still feel the Angel's light
around me in my farm I remembered what I
just saw the fields started to Glow as
the sun rose and I kneel down on the
ground because the message was clear I
was truly blessed by an angel of God
upon my soul
[Music]
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic ill
illness better if you choose to share or
use the original unique content from the
medical medium podcast books or medical
medium social media please site where
this information comes from so others
who see and learn of this information
have a chance to know where it all
originates to give them an opportunity
to heal so they don't end up losing
years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them
the medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science interest groups medical funding
with strings attached botched research
lobbyists internal kickback s persuaded
belief systems private panels of
influencers health field payoffs trendy
traps or gathered bits and pieces of
gimmicky confusion because chronic
illness is exploding like never before
in our Modern Day history it takes a
greater force than us down here it takes
a helping hand from above medical medium
information has street cred it's an
organic movement of countless people
around the world healing more healing
stories of real people not being paid to
tell their life changing experiences of
rising out of the ashes of sickness and
entering into the light of full recovery
getting their lives back and finally
healing when nothing else in the world
of Health could move the needle and get
them better the information on this
podcast is not man-made it comes from
above from a higher source whatever you
believe in whether God the universe the
light or the Creator or if you believe
in nothing at all that we're just
floating through space together on this
rock know that the information you hear
on this podcast is separate from all the
other noise out there it comes from a
different place a pure untampered with
Advanced Clean uncorrupted original
primary source a higher source Source
Spirit of compassion