how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about sodium salt
do you like salt do you eat salt do you
drink salt are you adding salt to your
water because the trend tells you so and
what about a sodium deficient iy we're
talking about that too it takes some
serious bravery learning salt truth but
it never goes well everyone usually just
freaks out the addiction is stronger
than people believe the salt demon
almost always wins hang on for this ride
and get yourself comfy because we are on
the salt
Express so I've been putting Salt in My
Water yeah you should do it too I saw
this like scientific study online that
says like you need the sodium especially
if you're working out yeah even my
trainer who's like really
hot he said it should be in your water
every time you drink especially since we
work out so much yeah so I thought I
would just try it and I really like it I
feel so much
better the sodium in your water trend
a trend that you would think is so
backed by science and so important for
us but all it's really doing is just
adding salt to already a high salt diet
because that's what our society does
salts everything and we get salted
practically to death so first let's
address the salt in the water trick it's
a dangerous trick no one would believe
it it's almost
unbelievable but here's what happen
happens when you put salt in water and
send it down on an empty stomach and you
may not have had food before or shortly
after then that salt that salt water
goes directly into the liver not to
detoxify it not to help it but to pickle
it to actually pickle it the last thing
our livers want is salt shock salt shock
it's what happens when it mainlines
right to the liver with nothing thing
buffering it you ever see what happens
when a body part is
salted you know like a pig
rump or some type of meat and it's
salted a salt rub and then it sits there
and ferments the salt just sucks the
juice out of it over time if you salt a
human being while they're alive they'll
die if you pack somebody's body with
salt like like pack them with salt where
their whole body's covered in salt and
then wrap them up with foil make sure
they're nice and packed nice and tight
and neat over time their skin would
practically melt off their
juices would leave their body they would
get severely dehydrated their tissue
their muscle meat would get
dehydrated their blood would turn into a
salty soup they would die we're told out
there all the time by people in the
trainer world the exercise world the
Science World that were made of salt the
medical world that were made of salt not
true yes sodium's a critical mineral yes
we have it in our bloodstream and in our
organs yes we need it yes it's the
foundation of a building block an
electrolyte yes we need it for
neurotransmitters
but too much of a good thing goes bad
too much of the wrong good thing goes
worse there's two worlds of thought out
there one is the old standard American
Medical model which is you got to watch
out for sodium too much sodium not good
for your heart not good for your blood
pressure stay away from salt do a no
salt diet that was the old standard
medical model and then the new
Alternative Health SL conventional
medical model SL health model which is
you need sodium you need salt and they
believe the old conventional model of
being salt-free as wrong they think it's
wrong information outdated bad and so
forth but both worlds are wrong we do
need salt our bloodstream needs salt but
the right kind of salt our bloodstream
doesn't need a teaspoon of salt or huge
pinch of salt in a glass of water our
bloodstream our organs don't need a
glass of water every few hours with a
pinch of salt in it either we don't need
direct hits of salt like this if someone
has a liver disease sosis of liver
hepatitis C or a liver that's on the
edge of failing and you do a whole glass
of water and you put a nice hunk of salt
in there or a pinch of salt you're
risking a liver shut down you're risking
a liver failure because your liver is
going to uptake that sodium it's going
to shock it and it doesn't shock it to
cleanse it the shock instead paralyzes
it puts it in a different motion shuts
it down slows it down hard salt is toxic
toxic to the body but yet we're being
told and conditioned every day in the
health movement that salt is healthy for
the body so much so it's actually scary
everybody's pushing sodium pushing salt
of course they're pushing the good salt
and they're standing behind that
rightfully so good salt is good salt if
you're going to use it but salt is still
toxic highly toxic on the body in large
quantities in large quantities and
that's what's happening now it's
different if you have a little bit going
on your food you have a buffer the
liver's buffered it can actually
disperse differently it gets into the
bloodstream differently but when it's in
the glasses of water and thrown in there
like that straight empty stomach most of
the time it shock toxic shock syndrome
to the liver through Salt and when high
quality sodium high quality salt is on
food it has a different delivery system
it can Bond onto something hopefully
Bond onto something temporarily maybe
not longterm but temporarily all these
different nutrients you have have in all
your different foods antioxidants and
phyton nutrients of all kinds sitting
there right in front of you on your
plate the salt gets put on there there's
a chance it's going to bond to something
at least temporarily you have a better
chance when it's like that when it's
with food a better chance you won't get
a shutdown a better chance the salt will
be bonded now remember if you're on a
ship and you're thirsty and you're out
there on the ocean for a long time and
you start drinking that salt water guess
what happens you die you get dehydrated
you get pickled and you die and guess
what it happened over and over again out
there people got desperate they were in
the ocean on the ocean maybe they were
stranded somewhere and they drank and
consumed salt water if it was okay to
stick salt and water every single day
while you're training or exercising or
living your life just doing it every day
if it was okay then it would be okay to
drink it in a glass
right out of the ocean on a ship every
day but what saves somebody to do it now
out of a glass and a pinch is they end
up doing something else a little later
they drink coffee they have a snack they
have a shake they have some food they
have dinner and it keeps them in the
okay enough Zone they're still damaging
themselves they're still damaging their
liver but it keeps them in a safety zone
enough to not notice it now you would
think the brain it runs on electrolyt
neurotransmitters need
electrolytes sodium is something the
brain needs then you would think
drinking seawater every day on a
stranded ship would feed the brain you
would do pretty good but instead it
pickles the brain and that's what
happens it's not just the liver that
goes into shock the brain goes into
shock over time you end up pickling the
brain your brain starts to die you would
think this would be known or common
sense would happen with someone you
can't drink ocean water because of the
salt the sodium you end up with a tragic
fate if you do so why is it good now why
is it good to take a glass of water and
add salt to it and drink it and promote
it like a health thing same as a lot of
things in alternative medicine and
conventional they're just wrong they
don't know it's the wild west mistakes
are made people suffer for it over time
nobody really talks about it it's swept
under the carpet but it becomes one big
great mistake if it was a good idea if
it was smart I would have talked about
it long time ago if it was intelligent
something to do something that was good
for us I would have been promoting it
and talking about it as a healing tool a
long time ago but instead s so told me
lemon water squeeze lemon in water flush
is the liver of all these poisons and
toxins first thing in the morning
flushes the body of toxins it provides
calcium provides vitamin C antioxidants
trace minerals it's a key way to heal
it's a very important aspect of healing
and don't think it's smart now adding
lemon to your salt water don't think
that's a great idea either where you put
a pinch of salt in your water then
squeeze lemon into it you're not
outsmarting the fox the Fox is still
going to break into the property and the
hen house it's still going to kill all
the chickens and then leave a scat and
laugh on its way out you're not going to
fix a problem by altering the problem
but keeping the problem still there
instead by adding the sodium the salt to
your lemon water if you're somebody that
does that you just threw off the balance
of what the lemon can do the lemon water
can't do the flushing action it once did
it can't be that cleanser for the liver
anymore it's been altered the salt
changed the chemistry and when the salt
changes the chemistry someone is not
going to get the results they need or
what they're looking for so when they're
drinking the lemon water because they
hear great things about it but they're
not getting results that they're
supposed to get from the lemon water
they're going to think something's wrong
and yes something is wrong they don't
know it it's the salt they added to the
lemon water if the lemon tree thought it
would be really smart to pull up all the
sodium from the earth and fill the lemon
with it and make it one big salt ball
one big salty lemon than it would have
happened in nature the lemon tree would
have drawn up sodium from the earth just
like celery does or spinach and it would
have been salty lemons would have been
really salty now lemons have a tiny bit
of sodium in it not harsh sodium not har
sodium not sea salt not Himalayan rock
salt but a tiny bit of Trace sodium if
there was supposed to be grams of sodium
in a lemon then there would be there's a
reason why there's not it throws off the
balance of what the lemon is there for
and what it does for us same thing as a
tomato Trace levels of sodium but the
tomato plant isn't producing nor driving
up sodium from the soil into the Tomato
to make it super salty if a farmer or
Gardener Waters their crops with salt
water guess what happens you would think
maybe the salt water would just get
sucked up the sodium would get sucked up
everything maybe be saltier the sodium
would get into all the plants but no
everything dies you can't water a lemon
tree with so sodium based water salt
water you can't even have a portion of
that water to be saturated in sodium the
tree dies you can use a trace Mineral
Solution you can do that and feed your
garden beds feed your plants your
flowers and your fruit trees you can do
it with a trace mineral complex fluid or
liquid that's designed to dilute and
nourish your plants but you can't just
take salt water and feed your plants
with it everything dies because that's
what happens we're like a plant in some
ways you can't just pack us with salt
like a salted fish will die and you
can't just fill us up with salt water
either cuz we will die as well but yet
we need sodium we need that mineral we
need it for our brains we need it for
our bloodstream we need it for our
tissue in organs and muscle in the 1970s
during heat waves science came up with
some information a lot of people were
drinking a lot of water during a heat
wave they were just guzzling gallons of
water throughout the day because it was
about staying hydrated it was really hot
it was sunny maybe they were in an area
without air conditioning a lot of people
back in the 70s did not have air
conditioning and during heat waves
people would eat less l so they wouldn't
eat some big old steak dinner with a
bunch of salt on it they wouldn't eat
some kind of food they wouldn't have
pancakes it wouldn't really have much of
anything the heat waves rolled in nobody
had air conditioning everybody was
trying to put ice on themselves from the
refrigerator and everybody was drinking
lots and lots of water and if somebody
didn't drown themselves where they drank
way too much more water than their
kidney can process more water than their
bloodstream can contain and hold and
they diluted themselves to such a degree
where their lungs filled with water and
they drowned if they didn't have that
happen and they were able to process
that water their kidneys were able to
excrete it and they were able to drink
couple of gallons a day a few gallons a
day during a heat wave then science of
research would say you're not retaining
the water during a heat wave it's
dangerous
there's no sodium people are just peeing
the water out as it's going in and
they're not getting hydrated so science
and conventional medicine had two
schools of thoughts you need to drink a
lot of water when there's a heat wave
and you can't drink a lot of water
during a heat wave cuz there's no sodium
reminds me of sugar we need blood sugar
to survive we have to have a certain
amount of blood sugar or we can't
function or live our brain needs glucose
Co sugar within 10 seconds 5 Seconds
actually before it starts to die if it
doesn't have it sugar is what makes our
bodies go around but yet there's a
massive war against sugar this is why
fruit was under attack for so long
natural sugar and fruit was under attack
Fruit fear I talked about it for many
many years everybody in Alternative
Health was against fruit they just were
they called it all sugar and told people
to stay away from it but if people don't
eat fruit of any kind where are they
going to get their glucose what other
sources lactose from dairy what else
corn different grains where are they
getting their sugar they have to get it
somewhere we have to survive we have to
live on it we have to have it in our
bloodstream but the details and the
nuances are critical in this because
there's healthy sugars that are
naturally derived from an apple and then
there's corn syrup high fructose corn
syrup there's also other sugars too
there's honey which is a very healthy
sugar and then at the same time there's
lactose Dairy which is not a good sugar
all these Details Matter for somebody to
be healthy and to protect your health
and give them what they need same thing
with sodium we need it in our
bloodstream in our organs in our brain
the details matter there's a big
difference from coconut water which has
sodium in it and celery juice which has
sodium in it and spinach which has
sodium in it versus road salt or a
healthier salt like a good Himalayan
rock salt or a good sea salt there's a
big difference plus when you drink
coconut water you can't control the
amount of sodium in there unless you add
it to it it's naturally balanced just
right The Human Condition but when you
farm salt and you hold on to it in your
hand you have your free will and control
you're the one taking it throwing it in
water you see it's not like cooking a
water that's nature doing it somebody's
hand isn't going and throwing salt up on
the tree and it somehow gets inside that
coconut it's not it's sealed but we take
it in our hand our shaker we pinch it
whatever we want and we throw it right
into that water it's different than
adding some sodium to your food the
sodium going into food gets buffered it
may not be the best thing you don't want
a lot of it on there but at the same
time it is getting buffered to a safety
zone unless it's so much salt it makes
things complicated now if you take honey
for example do a tablespoon of honey
because you got your free will you got
the jar of honey you're not just doing a
teaspoon you're digging in and doing a
big old tablespoon in your cup of tea
that's your free will doing it or you're
going to get in trouble not like salt
take a tablespoon of salt dump it in
that glass of water and send it down
there's a huge difference take a
tablespoon of honey put it in your mouth
Chomp on it swallow it eat it it's
different you take a tablespoon of salt
put it in your mouth and sit there and
Chomp on it and Chomp on it and then
swallow it and eat it you'll see two
different beasts but let's talk about
saltwater gargling that's a different
thing all on its own I like it for
certain things somebody has something
like an ulcer in their mouth they can do
some saltwater gargling but understand
this if you make it nice and thick with
salt little glass of warm water you put
a good tablespoon or more salt in there
you mix it up until it disappears and
then you gargle with it you're not going
to want to swallow all of that you're
not going to want to drink that with all
the salt in there because there's a good
chance you're going to vomit it back up
because your body has a mechanism it
knows it's trouble it knows it's
problematic and it doesn't want it going
down and you end up getting a
reflex your brain gets a message sends
it right down to the Vegas nerves your
Vegas nerves say no and that stuff comes
right back up but when you're gargling
you're really not supposed to swallow it
you're not you're supposed to spit it
back out and rinse your mouth out just
like when you're on a ship floating Out
on the Ocean and you ran out of your
water supply you're not supposed to be
sitting there drinking flasks of water
that came out of the ocean salt water
you can garl it but you can't swallow it
but yet once again our bodies need
sodium they do and some people they
fight an addiction because of it because
yeah we do need it but yet we get
addicted to it and our favorite way to
eat salt is with oil especially on chips
salty oily salty greasy salt and fat
it's our favorite combination and what
happens is the fat cuts the
salt that's right the fat cuts the salt
hides it just enough we love that fatty
salty crunchy taste we're the only
creature on the planet that adds salt to
everything all the other creatures on
the planet they're not doing that you
think a family of bunny rabbits are
sitting there saying pass the salt hey
let me have those few Blades of grass
get some salt on this thing it's bland
what about a lion lion wants some animal
meat is that lion saying Oo we need some
salt cracked on top of this meat right
here it's not salty enough I want to
have my meat salt to taste and what
about a monkey that likes to eat wild
figs is that monkey saying this fig
needs salt whoa I'm eating a bunch of
figs I feel like I need some salt here
please pass the salt somebody what about
a bear bears eat some meat too they're
not asking for the salt they're not
craving the salt they're not saying hey
this piece of meat that I just killed
this animal that I just killed needs a
whole bunch of salt it's too land jucky
don't get mistaken when you hear
something about a rock salt deposit
somewhere on a Mountaintop that an
animal went up to and licked and that
was all of a sudden the answer to it all
first of all it's a big planet there's
not a lot of options for that salt just
isn't everywhere laying everywhere
totally exposed ready for every animal
to lick it very few Wild animals on this
planet have access to a salt deposit on
a Mountaintop somewhere on this planet
and when it comes to a when it comes to
raising animals for Slaughter or raising
animals in general for sale and so forth
what happens is they do the salt thing
for salt
addiction they salt up the pigs so pigs
eat more and more the fatter the bigger
the pig can win an award the same thing
thing with anything cows and so forth
fatten up the cows sell more meat
thicken up the steers then you can sell
them price per pound get them addicted
to sodium they sell salt blocks blocks
of salt they want animals to take a lick
if possible because steers can get fussy
with their food if the steer gets too
lean it's not good farmer is mad they
salt the food they want them to lick the
salt blocks it makes them hungry gets
them addicted to more food then they can
feed them more thicken them up and sell
them package food companies for humans
put a lot of salt in there plus MSG
people like it they eat more they get
addicted they fatten up they want to eat
more they buy it again and again and
again same old trick restaurants put the
salt in the food people love it
they come in more and more they eat more
of it they go to a big old open Buffet
they eat all they can eat the salt makes
them nice and hungry everybody's happy
that's how it rolls back centuries ago
when salt was for sale and it was a big
deal it was for preserving because
people didn't have a way to preserve the
either fermented food or salted things
fermented things or salted things or
dried things fermented salted dried it
was a survival tactic doesn't mean it's
great doesn't mean it's good but it was
a survival method and it became a
commodity on sale for sale for centuries
and an addiction people got addicted to
their sodium to their salt and people
still are now every day it's even in
coffee people don't realize it but they
put a little salt in coffee shops now
you don't know it it's in the machine be
in some places it's in the water in some
places it's there to make the cup of
coffee little salty it all makes it
better but it keeps people addicted and
they go back to their coffee shops there
are people out there that try unsalted
butter but let's face it how good is
that have you had unsalted butter at all
did you ever take a piece of toast take
unsalted butter put it on that piece of
toast and eat it what did it taste like
not as good as the salted butter now
there's people out there that are back
to the land they're actually churning
their own butter they're raising animals
they're doing it all but guess what they
also have a bag of salt in the kitchen
and they're adding it to their food for
their children and for their husbands
and for their families they're still
using salt every single day even if
they're not making salted butter the
salt addiction is real but it's okay to
have a little bit of a high quality salt
it's okay to put a little bit on your
food it dilutes it enough it buffers it
enough it's not liver shock like when
you're dumping it in water so people
love their sodium they love their salt
and our bloodstream needs it but what
our bloodstream and our organs really
cry for is sodium that's naturally
derived in something like an herb
there's a little bit of sodium in fresh
herbs cilantro Parsley Sage thyme just a
little bit of sodium in
spirina that's one all on its own
there's a little bit of sodium in barley
grass juice powder there's a little bit
of sodium in tomatoes in lemons and
there's a decent amount of sodium in
celery and coconut water when you use
these forms of sodium they're bonded
bonded trace minerals that hold out they
become hold outs what does that mean
they stay in the blood stream and they
keep a balance a sodium balance so
somebody doesn't go sodium deficient or
sodium overload it keeps the balance for
the neurotransmitters for the building
blocks the electrolytes all of it the
celery that has sodium cluster salts a
subgroup of sodium on top of macro
sodium and then when you make a medical
medium spinach soup it is a powerful
healing tool and it's high and naturally
derived sodium the kind our bodies need
that's in
spinach I love this treadmill yeah it's
like one of the best technology is
amazing see if you use it this way you
could do a quick run on it uhhuh yeah
know I'm a trainer too like how long you
been in this gym like how long you been
coming here
let's see like I've been coming here for
about a year I like this treadmill too
it's like my favorite one I haven't seen
you here though like really you've been
here for like two years I totally have
I've been here for like two years yeah I
just I'm just do you do salt water
because that's something you should do I
see you're sweating a lot you mean like
putting like a pinch of salt in like a
glass of water like every day and every
morning and after my workouts I try like
a while ago you think I should like do
it again you should you should totally
do that I'm I'm a trainer I'm I've been
training for
years and I have a training coaching
practice um I can help you out and we
can figure things out that's one tip I
can give you that's really good okay
like that's really cool I really like
that you know this is like a really
great great
place it's on its way in and soon again
on its way out a new bioh Haack which is
really old hat been tried
before revived and retried sold once
more who can sift through the all and
know which ones can make people live
strong or
fall but Lord Oh Lord can you shine a
light
on the misguided biot tricks that
saturate the health information
Shores Lord oh Lord help the sick avoid
the jagged rocks that are made up of
egotistical Health slum
Lords an ocean trip turns into a tragic
turn of events when the captain says
there is no fresh water left on the ship
and Baton down the hatches it's time to
drink our urine first to quench our
thirst before we have no choice but to
drink the salty ocean water and as the
days go by one by one they sicken and
die for the water with flavor has no
place in a man's stomach before the
bowel labors it's all fun to shout out a
salt trick while science backs it up up
with an animal lick which could be
partially okay if the details and the
nuances were known and taught and
learned in a certain way and not gone
astray so L and behold it finally makes
sense so an unsuspected person doesn't
take another blow and get burned and set
back while trying to move forward never
always is lost your body is healing and
picking back up it tips the scale back
to quicker recovery life restores the
body forgives once more you now hold the
keys to the healing
door original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them them an opportunity to heal
so they don't end up losing years of
their life searching for answers like so
many have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion