how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about fatigue not
just any fatigue the kind that sticks
around and isn't just because you had a
hard day or a long long night it's a
kind of fatigue that Rings The Alarm
Bell that that this isn't normal and
it's not getting in your way it's doing
way more than that it feels
inconceivable arms feel like sandbags
legs feel like lead let's get to it
though lots to cover on this mystery
fatigue train get buckled in it's time
to
heal no I was telling you I already told
you this this is like my 11th Doctor my
11th Doctor yeah oh oh here he comes
he's coming in now so doctor what what's
your
diagnosis I'm tired because I need a
vacation you sure I heard that before
that was the third
doctor that I saw thought I needed a
vacation cuz I work hard but I've
already taken all this time off you sure
that's what it is I lay around all day
on the couch trying to sleep it off and
lately I seem to not even be able to do
that anymore I can't even sleep it off
I'm not even like sleeping good anymore
I already slept way too much and I'm
still tired this isn't normal how are my
blood tests good everything's good there
okay okay and my workup that's all right
too and my stress test that's all right
too all right give it more time I will
I'll be back thanks millions of people
Millions mostly women have heard
something kind of like that since the
late
1940s
Millions mystery fatigue was born around
the late
1940s before that no one was really
tired unless they had a really hard work
day working the factories and still they
weren't tired tired like people are
where they get the fatigue the disease
it wasn't born yet it was just at its
beginning and today mystery for fatigue
is now not a baby it's a toddler
tomorrow mystery fatigue a teenager and
the future not too far from now mystery
fatigue is going to be in its Elder
phase and that's going to be horrible
there used to be a lot of people getting
mystery fatigue lots and lots of people
but now it's a lot of people it is
rampant it's an
epidemic I wish mystery fatigue was just
from processed foods wouldn't that be
amazing you're eating a bunch of junk
and garbage and fried greasy foods and
fast foods and processed foods your
whole diet is based on that and then you
just get rid of it and your fatigue is
fixed that would be incredible but
there's a lot of people out there that
got rid of their processed foods and
they're
bedridden but mystery fatigues not
processed foods I wish it was over
exercising that would be amazing kick
back don't exercise for a little bit and
it all goes away that would be wonderful
but it's not it's not from overe
exercising I wish mystery fatigue was
just from working too hard take a break
take a weekend off you're back to normal
you're not couch bound you're not bed
bound you're just back to normal but
it's not that I I wish mystery fatigue
was partying too much you party hardy
you're a big time partyer you're up at
night late night partying doing drugs
drinking whatever you're doing having
sex just partying way too much and
you're fatigued because of that and then
when you stop all that it's fixed just
fixed you're fine you're great I wish
mystery fatigue was just from stress and
stress alone once the stress backs down
calms down you're back in Action all
gone not bedridden anymore not couch
bound anymore not brain fogged anymore
you're just feeling good you can think
you could feel good you could run you
can do this you could stay up all day
not have to nap that would be amazing if
it was just stress and then when stress
back down you're fixed any of these
things any of them can make somebody
sluggish and tired to a degree it can
beat somebody down I'm not saying that
if you do all those things or any of
those things that you won't be tired
from it but the disease of being tired
you won't be getting you won't have that
permanent ticket on mattress island or
couch Island some rest some recovery
time take it easy relax you start to
recover you start to come back from it
and you get back back to life and that's
what would happen unless there's a
bigger problem and you're somebody
that's just trying to get through the
day you're just trying to do good things
you're trying to work you're trying to
make a living you're trying to be the
best you can be at whatever you're doing
but you can't function or you can barely
function decades gone by medical medium
information is saturated the Health
Arena with information about why people
have chronic fatigue syndrome why people
have mystery fatigue and still till this
day you can go to a doctor's office both
alternative and conventional and it's
very possible you'll get this for an
answer it's all in your head diagnosis
that's right it's all in your head
diagnosis one big mistake in the health
world right now is blaming everything in
anything unprocessed foods that means as
of today right now if someone gets sick
the first part of that sickness is going
to be blamed on processed
foods and then every aspect of that
sickness is going to be blamed
unprocessed Foods it's not that
processed foods are good for us and it
also depends on what kind of processed
foods are we talking about and how
processed are they but either way
processed foods right now are taking the
Highlight the Limelight you're sick
because of those but what about about
junk Runners I don't mean drug dealers
that are running drugs around I'm
talking about junk Runners people in
their 20s and 30s that run
marathons they run for a living they run
professionally they run every single day
many of them run for a living and train
people to run and what do they do they
eat processed foods and junk they don't
even eat good in fact they boast and
brag about it they talk about their
favorite meals after long runs like
bagels and cream cheese macaroni and
cheese donuts cupcakes yes junk Runners
it's not just one person's a junk Runner
out there it's Millions right now
worldwide they do long runs they sweat a
bunch they come back from their run and
they binge they treat them elves they
call it an all Bagel day all donut day
it happens every day right now it's not
a trend or a fad it's reality they're
junk Runners they're not sick in bed
they're not sitting in bed all day all
night they're not on the couch all day
all night they didn't lose their
job they can exercise they can live
their lives they can stay up late if
they want they can play they can work
they can run they can exercise they can
drink alcohol they can eat processed
foods and they're not tired far from it
they're not on this quintessential
perfect keto diet grass-fed beef piece
of pasturised chicken some lettuce maybe
one steamed vegetable a few pieces of
fruit a green apple some blueberries
they're not on that they're on Just Junk
and crap and and they're eating it
candy garbage Donuts cakes cookies and
they're eating that and they're
exercising and they're pro athletes
reminds me of a lot of pro athletes out
there in general a football players the
football players eat perfectly do they
eat a perfect keto diet clean from
anything are they looking at every
single package maybe somebody is maybe a
few people are in the league but is
every everybody doing that no when
they're out on that field are they in
agony with fatigue are they bedridden
are they in a bad situation where they
can't function and their legs feel like
sandbags and they can't walk good and
they're tired no they're not sure a bad
diet filled with all kinds of junk and
crap over time will probably give
somebody a heart attack yes somebody can
live on a junk food diet they can live
on fried greasy Foods processed foods
for many many years and not be tired at
all but yeah they can get a heart attack
they can get a blood clot they can get a
stroke they can get a major heart attack
that kills them definitely over time
things get clogged up their livers get
fatty stagnant sluggish don't function
well it's original medical medium
information if somebody's eating a poor
diet cuz in the past a poor diet was
really just based upon maybe heart
disease diabetes those two but liver
gets clogged up gets sluggish it gets
stagnant becomes problematic puts
pressure on the heart and it's time goes
by a major Art Attack but yet no fatigue
beforehand people can go decade after
decade after decade meanwhile a
19-year-old that's eating healthy
can't get out of bed 21-year-old that's
eating good enough not eating a whole
bunch of junk and garbage can't function
can't get out of bed 25-year-old a
28-year-old 32y old fatigue can be
brutal and depending on the age even
more brutal the younger you are it's
terrifying somebody who sees everybody
else in the world living their life
doing what they want to do seeing their
colleagues their friends their student
friends their family friends all living
their life doing their thing and if
they're stricken with fatigue and
they're watching all of this it is just
terrifying so let's talk about the
reality of it all like what does it feel
like unless somebody's been in their
shoes and experienced it themselves
they'll never know I think one of the
hard Parts about having fatigue of some
kind mystery fatigue is that others
around you don't understand it if
they're not chronically tired there's a
lot of symptoms out there that are
difficult debilitating a lot of symptoms
that are mysterious even if they have a
label or somebody gets diagnosed with a
condition or a disease it's still a
mystery in the end and in all of those
conditions and symptoms so many
debilitating
varieties fatigue is one of the bad ones
because when you're dealing with a shake
it's a symptom where you have a Tremor
you might be able to show somebody the
Tremor if you got a twitch or a tick or
a spasm you might be able to show
somebody the
spasm if you have something where you
have a drop foot or something like that
somebody could see it and they'll be
like whoa something's going on with that
person and if somebody has a really bad
belly ache even though they can't feel
it and they can't feel what the person's
going through who has that belly ache it
still can be like okay and the person's
holding their belly and they're yelling
and they're saying this is terrible I'm
in a lot of pain but when it comes down
to fatigue it's kind of like this
Phantom this ghost kind of thing and
there's only so many times you could say
I'm tired telling family and friends and
workers and co-workers and your boss and
so forth I'm really tired well get some
sleep then did you sleep tonight I do
sleep all the time I'm struggling I got
something going on I can't even keep my
eyes open or I can't even stand anymore
I'm feeling so fatigued well you should
go to a doctor then head to a doctor and
get it fixed I've been to three doctors
already they think I need a vacation but
I can't take a vacation right now okay
well go take a vacation take some time
off come back when you're all better now
they take some time off they come back
to work and they're just as tired then
the boss is like whoa were you having a
lot of fun out there what were you doing
I've been on the couch and in my bed the
entire week it's one of those symptoms
one of those conditions that people
don't have a lot of forgiveness for a
lot of compassion for so if you're
somebody and you're dealing with fatigue
of some kind now there's different
varieties of fatigue different levels of
fatigue and right now I'm just putting
it all in one fatigue Ball but we'll
cover some of the different varieties
but either
way however you look at it it's one of
those things where people don't have a
lot of respect for because they might
say this person's lazy or copping
out but what about other symptoms like
fatigue is bad enough as it is what
about anxiety along with the fatigue
where you're sitting on the couch you're
panicked your anxiety ridden and your
fatigued it's a really salt in the
wounds and a lot of people have more
than just fatigue and anxiety they'll
have aches and pains fatigue Tangles and
numbness ringing in the ears all kinds
of different balance problems and
vertigo issues pain in the jaw pain in
the back pain in the feet pain on top of
their head their scalp trigeminal
neuralgia burning tongue and burning
mouth and fatigue all of it and fatigue
and fatigue is bad enough so let's talk
about different levels of fatigue
there's being tired where you feel it in
your eyes your eyes are tired you rub
them a lot they feel heavy your eyelids
feel like they want to close on
themselves you stretch a lot you yawn a
lot you're yawning more than normal
people are seeing you yawn all the time
people who are demanding your attention
or looking at you and you're yawning
right at them you can't help it you
can't hold the yawn in but wait a minute
that's not just tired it's more than
that you're yawning you're stretching
and then you're kind of nodding off it's
another thing too so many people who
have fatigue nod off as they're talking
to a family member or a friend they
start falling asleep and their family
member or friend is like hey you should
take a nap now now and it could be
intermittent you got a little energy one
hour in the day another hour you're down
for the count another hour you're
feeling better another hour down for the
count and then it could be this thing
where you're half tired during one part
of the day more tired on another part of
the day or feeling pretty darn good one
part of the day and then another part of
the day you're just down it can vary in
so many different ways depending on what
you're doing too
if the fatigue is getting a little worse
and you exercise now you're trashed
trashed for a day some people they'll
exercise with fatigue they're fighting
it they're struggling they're doing
everything they can and now they're down
and out for 3 days after and then
somebody could have a lot of energy in
the morning all through the day they're
doing pretty good and then early evening
they're so exhausted they can only just
lay in bed fatigue can accompany a whole
bunch of brain fog somebody could have
just a foggy mind foggy head foggy brain
they can't get their words out right
they're feeling so low energy they can't
get their thoughts together they're
struggling because they're so tired so
getting words out is difficult all on
its own taking a breath is difficult too
and at the same time their head could be
really brain fogged out and these are a
few of the mild fatigue situations what
about real serious serious fatigue where
you feel like you got lead weights in
your hands you feel like you have cement
shoes on your feet and just walking
takes everything you have and then it
can go even further than that where you
can't take a shower the water hitting
you almost knocks you over it's a big
thing a lot of people deal with it what
happens when people suffer in that way
though they really get alienated and
people don't really want to hear about
it anymore and they end up losing
friends losing touch with people their
daytoday is suffering and they're just
in their house or in their apartment
somewhere and they're really really
struggling where taking a shower is so
difficult they'll get the dizzy spells
they'll feel the water hit them and
it'll kind of light up their nerves
they'll get different Sensations that
are really difficult they'll get a panic
attack their chest will become tight
they feel like they can't breathe the
fatigue will take over and after the
shower they're done they're back on
their bed and they're trying to just
recoup same thing with going to the
bathroom using the toilet just having to
eliminate sometimes it takes everything
a person has even if they don't have the
worst fatigue and they have just fatigue
all on its own going to the bathroom
could mean they need a break afterwards
where after they go after they eliminate
their bowels they have to go lay on the
bed now or lay in the couch or sit down
somewhere and they have to
recuperate one of the problems with
fatigue mystery fatigue is the industry
doesn't like to recognize it you have to
go find somebody to give you a diagnosis
that you have chronic fatigue syndrome
or me chronic fatigue syndrome and
that's difficult because insurance
companies don't care insurance iies
don't want to really know about this
kind of condition or disease so even if
you find coverage it might not last long
or something could go wrong chronic
fatigue syndrome is not respected enough
it wasn't in the past just a little bit
more now than it was in the past but
seriously as far as someone really
struggling with chronic fatigue syndrome
getting a doctor getting some kind of
help is still really difficult
understanding the condition and then
it's like musical chairs it's like
looking for something they're like well
you could have chronic fatigue syndrome
but you might have something else maybe
you have Lyme disease maybe you got
something else maybe it's Ms maybe it's
ra maybe it's just autoimmune maybe it's
all in your head and even till this day
someone will still get it's all in your
head or you're just looking for
attention and along with the fatigue is
guilt and fear and shame those are
things that really accompany it
especially if it's a misdiagnosis and
it's like well you're not really
fatigued you got this going on or you
got leaky gut let's fix it but it
doesn't get fixed you still got the
fatigue so more guilt and fear and shame
occur and then with a lot of people who
deal with chronic fatigue syndrome it's
the ultimate you look fine but you look
fine you can't be sick you look good you
look like everything's okay it's one of
the ultimate versions of that meanwhile
you could barely stand can barely walk
you can't do anything you want to do you
can't go and take a run and be like oo
and jump in a pool or in a beach you
can't just hop into the ocean and live
your life you're in a difficult
situation because you're getting stopped
everywhere you turn and that leads to
the whole you look great so what's
really wrong with you though get to the
doctor but the doctor can't fix you so
more guilt and fear and shame occurs
fatigue is real mystery fatigue is real
chronic fatigue syndrome is real and if
someone doesn't have a big brain tumor
inside their head that's causing fatigue
then it's Epstein bar virus and Epstein
bar virus could even create a brain
tumor in somebody's head so in the end
it originates from a virus
situation now there are some people that
will have some fatigue from the shingles
virus or herpes simplex one two but it's
different it's not necessarily the
fatigue that Epstein bar provides
somebody could have adrenal fatigue they
could have that and it could give them a
tiredness it could make them fatigued
but there's bounceback there's recall
could be at different times different
days but there's bounceback mystery
fatigue that's viral you don't really
get the bounce back in the way you do it
a dream fatigue unless the adrenals are
totally wasted but if they're that
wasted in somebody's fatigue that bad
because they're adrenals are that shot a
doctor should find that a doctor should
be able to diagnose it properly and know
that the adrenals are wasted that the
person really is suffering from adrenal
fatigue doesn't mean someone with
adrenal fatigue can't also have a viral
infection like Epstein bar they're
suffering from both and viral infections
can put stress on the adrenals allowing
adrenals to weaken more when somebody's
dealing with neurological fatigue the
next thing I'm talking about it took
decades for the world of medicine to
realize fatigue was
neurological decades and decades medical
medium information knew it was
neurological because it wasn't just
somebody being tired or exhausted or it
was all in their head or they were being
lazy there were real reasons someone was
suffering with fatigue
neurological fatigue by medical medium
definition is the central nervous system
and other nerves within the body they're
inflamed due to neurotoxins or viral
Invasion when people were diagnosed with
glandular fever or mono and they got
tired doctors knew it was the mono or
glandular fever that was exhausting the
person
but they didn't know how or why and then
if somebody recovered from mono somebody
recovered from glandular fever and they
were still tired it would be a mystery
to the medical system mystery to the
medical doctors they would not know why
the person's tired they're better
they're recovered from mononucleosis
they're recovered from glandular fever
now what's going on here there's a
mystery and what about the person who
had mononucleosis 3 years ago 5 years
ago and has been tired ever since what
about the person who had glandular fever
10 years ago they're still tired a
lifetime of chronic fatigue after
glandular fever after
mononucleosis and they had a lifetime of
being tired no doctor nobody in the
medical world nobody in any medical
University would say they had glandular
fever or o they would say your tiredness
is just something else we don't know
what it is it's a mystery but really
what it is it's neurological fatigue
caused by the same virus that gave the
glandular fever the same virus that gave
the mononucleosis the Epstein bar virus
what Epstein bar does is it releases a
neurotoxin after it's consumed a
favorite food a favorite food to the
Epstein virus could be gluten
it could be dairy products it could be
eggs it could be toxic heavy metals like
Mercury and aluminum and copper but epin
bar virus loves to eat it has to eat to
stay alive it has to eat to survive it
consumes food and then it excretes it
does an elimination process it
eliminates toxins the problem is those
toxins aren't friendly they're highly
problematic to the central nervous
system to all nerves in the body epin
bar releases all these neurotoxins they
float around sometimes they get caught
up in the liver and they sit in there
for a long time but either way they
cause a battery draw an energy draw
those neurotoxins land on nerves inflame
them irritate them and this robs and
steals energy the more Epstein bar virus
the the more viruses the more viral
cells the more feedings that occur the
more neurotoxins that are released the
more symptoms with the chronic fatigue
somebody could have just a little bit of
viral inflammation meaning low-grade
viral infection not a lot of Epstein bar
going on just a little bit tiny bit of
neurotoxins being released
systematically and then they feel tired
all the time they're struggling but then
somebody could have more Epstein bar
virus and more neurotoxins are being
released and maybe they have more
mercury in their system than somebody
else so the Epstein bar virus is feeding
off of more Mercury releasing a more
toxic neurotoxin when this happens and
it's floating around someone ends up
getting more symptoms than just the
chronic fatigue syndrome now now they're
getting tingles and numbness dizziness
ringing in the ears you're getting all
kinds of different blurry eyes without
any kind of real
diagnosis epine bar tends to affect
cranial nerves cranial nerves such as
the vagus nerves when they get inflamed
or irritated by
neurotoxins then a lot of different
strange mysterious weird symptoms can
occur like tightness in the throat
tightness in the chest tingles and
numbness in weird places pains in weird
places as well because the vague V
nerves are inflamed when the vagus
nerves get inflamed that's when people
are running to neurologist after
neurologist after neurologist and
they're getting different answers from
each neurologist and they find
themselves at a lime disease doctor lime
disease specialist then now it's all
lime disease it's all bacteria and we're
off the mark now cuz it's not a
bacterial problem bacteria can't cause
these symptoms virus
cause these symptoms the Epstein bar
virus especially and when it comes down
to Lyme disease doctors now are testing
for Epstein bar interesting cuz I
thought it was all
bacteria that's what they always say and
said medical medium information talks
about it being viral Lyme disease was
actually a virus or viruses epine bar
being one of them but now lime doctors
are actually saying oh back Bia bacteria
bacteria here's some doxic cyclin here's
some different you know antibiotics but
let's go check this epine bar thing ooh
you have Epstein bar too but yet they're
still like oh here's the antibiotic for
the bacteria but yeah you have a virus
as well so medical medium information
turned the tide on that because it's
really a virus causing Lyme disease and
they're off The Mark with the bacteria
so what do we do if we have a viral
infection causing mysterious fatigue we
kill the virus we go after it we destroy
it we starve it we get rid of it we push
it out of our body and we heal and after
we kill that virus or
viruses after we kill the Epstein bar
virus because somebody could have two
varieties of Epstein bar or three
varieties of epsin bar after we kill
them and get rid of them we restore the
central nervous system we heal the
nerves if you're somebody that had a
diagnosis an autoimmune diagnosis a
condition a symptom you're struggling
for a long time you've been through a
lot you can heal yes and you will heal
having the right information is critical
giving your body what it needs like
smart things not just get rid of
processed foods that automatically is a
no-brainer of course but it's not enough
when it comes down to Healing we got to
know what's wrong and when you learn
about these viruses and you learn what
they're capable of how they live in us
what they do you can overcome the
condition and the symptom and not just
manage it overcome it every night your
body does a little bit of healing when
you're giving your body what it needs
every single night you move forward even
if it doesn't feel that way because when
a nervous system has been overburdened
by all those
neurotoxins and heavy metals and other
poisons and so forth when your nervous
system has been overburdened it doesn't
heal in one hour it can't it could do
some healing in 1 hour but it can't
fully completely heal when somebody has
had a long-term low-grade viral
infection that's been wreaking havoc or
viral infections that have been wreaking
havoc or multiple different varieties of
viruses it takes time but as you're
killing off the bugs getting rid of them
breaking them down and restoring a
damaged immune
system Life Starts to
change and you start to heal and you
start moving
forward one of the struggles is being in
the darkness the darkness of not knowing
why you're sick what to do and the
process that's a difficult place to be
but when you know you're restoring your
nervous system and that's the goal
that's a big deal and when you know
you're restoring your immune system and
that's the goal it's a big deal and when
you know you're killing off bugs and
pathogens and viruses it's another big
deal these things bring peace while
you're healing I'm in medical medium
book one Secrets behind chronic and
mystery illness and how to finally heal
I'm in the chronic fatigue syndrome
section the revised and expanded New
Edition and so what I'm going to do is
read some of my favorites here there's a
lot of different things you can do for
chronic fatigue syndrome let's start at
the top fresh celery juice
exactly just fresh celery juice says
here work up to 32 o daily then work up
to 64 Oz if possible a day now you can
just do 4 oz of celery juice every day 2
oz and you're moving the needle you can
just do a little bit but if you get up
to 32 oz every single day you can move
mountains that is someplace that you
could just start just right there and
start moving things forward now keep in
mind you may be somebody that has a
multiple batch of viruses in you
different strains different varieties
you've been sick and down for a while
they all came to roost they're all
causing problems you got 50 different
symptoms mostly
neurological you're going to need
probably more than celery juice so let's
take a look at some of the other things
in here cat's claw one of my favorites
cat's claw two dropper FS twice a day
cats Claw is a powerful
antiviral it is wonderful for chronic
fatigue syndrome or just mystery fatigue
because of the medical medium
information lime disease doctors are now
offering cat's claw pathogens don't like
cat's claw they don't they're allergic
to it but yet our body isn't what
happens when cats claw enters the body
pathogens go oh my God run but it takes
time because pathogens hide out in
different places in the body they hide
out in the liver they hide out around
the nervous system they hide out in the
spleen even around the
pancreas takes a little time to get cats
claw into the body but when you bring it
in you're already moving forward lemon
bomb another one of my favorites it's in
the list what I love about lemon bomb it
helps to soothe the nerves and nerves
get inflamed because of EP bar and other
viruses and that inflammation causes
those nerves to vibrate to
Rattle to have a vibration behind it
where people lay there and they feel it
nerves get so inflamed it even creates
where you hear your heartbeat when
you're laying down you hear a pulse when
you're laying down cuz nerves get
inflamed and because of that there's
pressure building in the body so you
hear your pulse you hear your heartbeat
and that's really hard for people who
can't sleep or they're laying around all
day long and they have to hear that that
inflammation is the nerve swelling
pressing against so many other things
lemon mom calms the nerves eases them
it's really an amazing herb for the
nervous system helps them to heal to
and pathogens do not like lemon bomb
it's antiviral
another one on the list I really like is
licorice root it's antiviral says one
drop or full twice a day viruses hate
licorice root especially viruses that
hibernate inside the liver licorice
fruit is a great great herb for the
liver helps to push out the viruses
helps to gum them up get them trapped
get them doile licorice root is also
good for the immune system helps to
restore the immune system strengthen it
something that you need especially when
you've dealt with fatigue for so many
years and for so long vitamin B12 that's
a big one right there meth cobalamin and
adinos Sil cobalamin the combination is
perfect for the nervous system and what
happens with people their nerves get
fried they get burnt out
central nervous system and nervous
system symptoms are some of the worst
and fatigue is a neurological symptom
it's neurological fatigue that means the
nerves are up against problems and like
we talked about before neurotoxins
inflaming the nerves there needs to be
some help for those nerves and b12 is a
big one right there golden seal is
another one on the list it's one of my
favorites says two dropper FS twice a
day
that's an important one great for the
immune system helps to move the needle
viruses and pathogens do not like golden
seal and one of the most important
that's on the list right here zinc
liquid zinc sulfate it says here two
dropper FS twice a day in the medical
medium book zinc is a big one because it
slows down and stops cyto
storms it gets in the way of path
in every way pathogens viruses
especially do not like zinc and zinc
restores the immune system and the thing
is people who are sick have immune
system problems their immune systems are
weakened they're struggling zinc is
something the immune cells need to
strengthen move forward and attack bugs
that are in your system such as Epstein
bar now the right kind of supplements
always matter there could be alcohol and
supplements all kinds of different
things like MSG or they can just be
really weak this matters when you're
trying to heal go to medicalmedium.com
and check out the best versions of the
supplements that I just talked about and
if you want to customize for your
healing do what's right for you check
out medical medium revised and expanded
medical medium Protocols are
customizable you can also ask your
doctor what's right for
you I'm tired can't seem to beat this
feel like I have the devil on my back
wrestling the Beast trying to get some
peace I have to break
this I remember the days when I wasn't
like what I am now I know in my heart
and soul and in every fiber of my body
I will be back on top like I once
was it doesn't matter if it's a year
from now I will be free from this grip
and I will be looking back behind me I
won the fight I told a demon I rule you
and good night I see that Old Ship
floating in the
distance far away with all the records
of my my pain and suffering I once felt
every day and will be past it all you
will be too believe you me in God we
trust it's true these days of struggle
will be long gone and through I can see
what's coming to me my hard work paid
off and I am sporting so much
confidence I'm showing
off don't cry this this is not your time
to die far from it it's going to take so
much more to knock you out and you're
going to be the last one that says
bye-bye truth be told you're carrying a
motherload it shows your true strength
fatigue isn't going to be your road even
if right now you feel the
overload deep inside of you lies a
strength you were never yet in
introduced to a supreme weapon that will
carry you till you heal down here feel
the divine power that lands on the
number seven it's going to be okay you
are healing now each day you will heal
even more until you are fully healed and
back to the life you once adored
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast cast
doesn't come from broken science
interest groups medical funding with
strings attached botched research
lobbyists internal Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems private panels of
influencers health field payoffs trendy
traps or gathered bits and pieces of
gimmicky confusion because chronic
illness is exploding like never before
in our Modern Day history it takes a
greater force than us down here it takes
a helping hand from above medical medium
information has street cred it's an
organic movement of countless people
around the world healing more healing
stories of real people people not being
paid to tell their life-changing
experiences of rising out of the ashes
of sickness and entering into the light
of full recovery getting their lives
back and finally healing when nothing
else in the world of Health could move
the needle and get them better the
information on this podcast is not
man-made it comes from above from a
higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion