how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about cleansing
who's cleansing out there who's really
cleansing cuz there's a lot of cleanses
that stop you from cleansing that's
right cleanse Stoppers it takes a track
record it takes people really
healing not just little things it takes
people getting out of wheelchairs it
takes people getting their lives back it
takes people and their lives being saved
then you know they're cleansing it takes
the right knoow the information the
right tools all of the
above in the past the health World knew
about toxins but never what kind never
had an name to him DDT radiation wasn't
on the radar as far as a toxin someone
had to worry about that was internally
embedded in their organs no nothing else
either toxic heavy metals Mercury
aluminum lead cadmium arsenic no one
worried about that being behind
illnesses nobody worried about all the
petroleum all the different fragrances
all the different poisons and toxins
from solvents to everything else nobody
talked about that and as far as
pathogens went completely off the radar
not even the early hygienic movement of
Health knew about pathogens in fact they
believed bugs did not exist and you
should never wash your hands the medical
medium information reshaped the health
world it's never been the same so much
of it has changed because it adopted the
medical medium information when the
first book met medcal medium hit the
scene it changed lives people healed and
an organic movement grew and then
life-changing foods and then thyroid
healing Liver Rescue celery juice and
the cleanse the heal book shortly after
that the new addition of medical medium
and the brainsaver books have changed
the world Millions have healed thousands
upon thousands countless amounts of
testimonials of serious chronic illness
serious conditions the books have saved
lives all around the world because they
work and a big part of those books was
the cleansing aspect people were able to
cleanse their bodies properly make a
difference move the needle and save
their lives get ready for some powerful
information it's time to
heal back years ago it would blow my
mind when I would hear somebody in the
health realm say you don't need a
cleanse you don't need to
detox you don't have to worry about
poisons and toxins because your body
cleanses
itself your body does everything it
needs to do all on its own when I heard
that and still hear it today it blows my
mind you don't hear it as much today I
think in part
just the work that Spirit of compassion
medical medium has done along the way
with letting people know that you do
have to cleanse to heal but you still
hear it once in a while your body
naturally cleanses and you don't have to
do anything for it I don't know anything
further from the truth our bodies take
on toxins every single day but it's not
just that we're born into this world
with toxins
even toxic heavy metals Mercury aluminum
cadmium lead arenic just to name a few
and then
copper that's a big one everybody's high
in Copper everybody's copper intoxicated
at this point toxic industrialized
copper so we have a lot of problems just
with toxic heavy metals alone and that's
a big one but then there
solvents solvents the chemical
Industries create that enter our
bodies the thing is that we come into
this world toxic we automatically do and
people still to this day do not realize
that we come into this world with our
parents pasted in us their past whatever
they did drinking any kind of drugs
Pharmaceuticals they may have taken
along the way any kind of exposures
toxic heavy metals Mercury aluminum
copper and petroleum products petroleum
based products gasoline lubricants
different creams and ointments that had
lead in there and different chemicals
perfumes colog
aftershaves things that our parents used
from the past all in us when we come
here and then there's DDT DDT was around
everybody it was everywhere in the past
it was the past and it's the present and
it's the future unfortunately it's in us
all everyone has traces of the dirty
past in them and guess what it stays in
them it does and it gets passed down to
generation to generation and generation
these days we have all that plus
something new the fragrances a whole new
wave of horror a whole new wave of
Terror on the body because our body
doesn't want thousands and thousands of
unknown unidentified chemicals that go
under the GU of fragrance in it our
bodies don't want that newborn babies
today are born with
fragrances hundreds and hundreds and
hundreds of chemicals that are not even
identified no one's taking a blood test
and saying whoa there are a thousand
chemicals in here a thousand ch
chemicals of Unknown Origin the reason
why they're not doing that is because
nobody knows what they are they don't
know what those chemicals are they can
only look for toxins they know and a lab
will test for all those chemicals and
toxins that just reside in us forever
it's not like they go away instead more
and more come every day every hour every
year and our bodies they they have a
natural ability to detox yes they do
they have a natural ability to eliminate
poisons yes they do but what poisons and
what toxins because our bodies are
designed to eliminate
ammonia to eliminate old
adrenaline to eliminate other types of
blood gases and different toxins normal
toxins normal problems that our bodies
are supposed to be up against not
industrialized Industrial Revolution
nightmares as much as we need to
exercise for health our well-being for
our physical body a great mistake was
made in the exercise world the exercise
realm the realm of fitness and that
mistake was you're detoxing you're
sweating everything bad out so what
happens people think when they're doing
healthy exercising cardio they're
running they're jogging they're biking
they're skiing or they're just doing
lots of cardio workouts or lifting and
sweating and sweating and sweating they
think they're getting rid of all their
toxins they think they're detoxing and
then the Shockers come professional
athletes getting cancer or getting sick
you would think they detoxed everything
that could possibly be detoxed out of
their body body they're sweating
profusely they're sweating every single
day they're working out really hard
they're building muscles their abs are
perfect they are healthy healthy
specimens human beings that are in the
greatest shape of their lives but then
they get cancer or they get some kind of
other sickness it doesn't make sense
here they are they're cleansing and
detoxing their lymphatic system has to
be the healthiest lymphatic systems on
this planet because blood and lymph it's
moving every day the amount of exertion
the amount of physical labor in the
exercise realm and the professional
athletic realm muscles that are laboring
every single day and lymphatic systems
that are constantly recycling and
purifying how is it possible cancer
Could Happen how is it possible they
could even get sick it's a shocker it
doesn't make any sense anybody in that
kind of physical shape should be able to
live forever live to be at least
105 but yet it doesn't work like that
people die people get sick people get
diseases literally people fall apart
there's so many different athletes out
there now that were at the top of their
game and could run an unbelievable
distance and now there's sick not well
they're getting surgeries their body's
falling apart and it doesn't make any
sense surely all of that sweating all of
that exercise all of that increased
heart rate all of that lymphatic
drainage naturally occurring should have
clearly detoxed them clearly set them up
for life to be less toxic than anybody
else and to be able to like live a good
long life without a problem but it
didn't no it
doesn't because sweating and exercise is
critical we need it for all kinds of
reasons but it doesn't detox us we can
stay just as toxic and collect more
toxins and they can stay in us and wreak
havoc and cause a lot of problems along
the way physical movement physical labor
exercise is critical for muscles it's
critical for connecting tissue it's
critical for joints it's important to
exercise even on a gentle basis but it's
not the end all be all doesn't work like
that you can still be highly toxic and
die early or just live a miserable life
being chronically sick you can still
have pathogens bugs viruses bacteria
harboring laying dormant or
proliferating in your body while you're
an exercise person while you're working
out and doing your thing out there and
you can still get sick from those bugs
keeping you from eventually exercising
at all that's why there's a lot of
athletes out there that are just stuck
severe chronic fatigue syndrome can't
even get out of bed because you can't
just sweat out those viruses those
pathogens the epscene bars the shingles
the herpes simplex one two the set
megavirus you can't just sweat those out
because they're still in the liver
they're still in the bloodstream they're
still in all the organs they're still in
connective tissue they're still in
muscles bugs and pathogens don't get
sweated out and then they're gone for
good and that brings me to something you
may hear out there it's like sweat it
out when someone has a flu it's like
exercise it out run it off sweat it out
doesn't work like that either in fact
when you're sick with things like
pathogens too much exercise runs down
the immune system doesn't strengthen the
immune system because it takes a strong
immune system to exercise to actually
work out that's why when somebody's
chronically sick they've been
chronically ill for a long time and they
do a workout maybe a first workout in a
long time now they're sick for 3 4 days
more or they get an episode where they
end up breaking out with some herpes or
a rash or some other problem and now
they're down and out or
they just feel wasted more fatigue more
fatigue than they felt in a long time
and they're in an episode it's because
their immune system is already battling
pathogens and probably toxic heavy
metals in that moment and their immune
systems overloaded or it's weakened and
not as strong as it needs to be so then
you're working out and you're exercising
and you end up tanking so many people
with chronic sickness and chronic
illness end up tanking after the
exercise
because their immune system can't do it
all it can't handle the recovery of the
exercise it can't handle the adrenaline
surge of the exercise and it can't
handle all the pathogens pathogenic
Invaders somebody's up against the
reason why they're sick to begin with
because in the end what they really need
is they need to kill those bugs and
cleanse those toxins It's a combination
of both killing the bugs and cleansing
the toxins
whether somebody's an athlete or not the
quality of their life determines how
many toxins they've collected either
entered into this world with or how many
bugs they entered this world with or how
many toxins and bugs they collected
along the way
accumulated that determines how healthy
someone's going to be now there's other
factors around that but those are the
two big core factors right there then
there's also resour sources there's also
upbringing support and love but even if
somebody doesn't have the support they
don't have the resources they don't have
some things they need that other people
get if the pathogens and the toxins are
really high if they're there causing
problems then we're in trouble and then
we're struggling and once we're
struggling with a chronic illness things
get even more difficult because planet
Earth is already hard we carry our past
with us we carry our baggage with us we
all come with baggage it's 10 years 20
years 30 years 50 years of garbage
that's inside our body inside our liver
inside our organs inside our brain it's
our brains being dirty and filled with
all this baggage it's our heart muscle
being filled with this baggage it's our
kidneys it's everything inside our body
including our bones this baggage is a
history
of pesticides herbicides fungicides
perfumes colog scented candles air
fresheners
Pharmaceuticals gasoline petrochemicals
lubricants aftershaves all kinds of
different health and beauty products
hair spray hair color everything that's
toxic out there in the world that past
is with us today and moves to our future
if someone's struggling with a mental
health condition they're struggling
emotionally they're struggling with
severe depression anxiety and it's
because of toxic heavy metals it's
because of mercury and aluminum and
copper inside their brain short
circuiting electrical impulses creating
OCD creating bipolar creating
depersonalization it stays with us it's
moving into the future with us it's the
past which is the toxic heavy metals
still in our brains and if we're not
cleansing these Metals out they stay in
there
the past comes with us to the Future
same thing with anything that's in our
system like pathogens if we're sick with
Epstein bar and that Epstein bar is
giving us thyroid conditions thyroid
issues Hashimoto or it's just giving us
fatigue and aches and pains we have that
bug but unless we get rid of it or knock
it back or clean it up or cleanse it out
unless we do that it comes with us in
the future we take it along with us and
move into the future with it we take all
these toxins all these poisons and these
pathogens and the pathogenic toxins that
the pathogens create and we take them
into the future and we live like that we
have our baggage we have our past we
bring it into the future so many people
out there are trying to get rid of their
past they're burning notes they're
burning journals they're trying to start
out fresh they're trying to meet new
people they're trying to do different
things gain new interests they're doing
healthy things they're trying to move
forward it's all about moving forward
they're doing yoga they're exercising
they're trying to better their lives all
of that is important they are trying to
move forward they are trying to get past
their past they want to start fresh but
unless they're cleaning out the toxins
and unless they're cleaning out the
poisons and the toxic heavy metals and
the pathogens the bugs you're really not
getting that Fresh Start you're not
getting that clean slate and that's why
cleansing is so important the more
toxins you have deep down in your body
the more food you have for bugs because
bugs eat the food they eat the toxins
that's their food okay so why would that
be such a big deal well to begin with
cancer cells those are viral cells those
are viruses that fed on toxic chemicals
and toxic waste which eventually CA C
the viruses to mutate and turn into a
cancer cell at some point so what
happens is when we have all these toxins
in us we have a campground Campground of
viruses feeding off these toxins and
then proliferating more eventually
mutating creating a problem down the
road which could be cancer cells so we
have to get rid of these toxins or we
have to get rid of the viruses we have
to do one or the other or at least a
little bit of both and then when it
comes to auto autoimmune any kind of
autoimmune diagnosis any kind of
condition and neurological symptoms
tightness of the chest tightness of the
throat aches and pains fatigue headaches
all the time tingles and numbness
ringing in the ears vertigo dizziness
any types of ticks and spasms Tremors
shakes restless leg syndrome and so many
more symptoms when it comes down to all
of those symptoms you're dealing with
viral issues viruses that are gobbling
down food toxins that's their food and
then they're releasing all of these
neurotoxins somebody could have more
Mercury than somebody else and then
their viruses are feeding off of that
mercury releasing a Mercury based
neurotoxin and that neurotoxin can make
life difficult for so many different
people could give them multiple
sclerosis symptoms or lime disease
symptoms or some type of symptom so it's
important to clean up those toxins it's
important to clean up those toxic heavy
metals and knock down those viruses kill
off those bugs all the different toxins
and all the different pathogens that
I've talked about so far don't just jump
out of the body and disappear they don't
leave easy they stay with us they live
in our organs they live in our flesh
they live in our bowels and they don't
just go away taking a handful of
charcoal drinking gallons of milk or
doing a long-term water water fast or
juice fast isn't going to get the toxins
out it isn't going to get the
petrochemicals out the solvents toxic
heavy metals or the pathogens they're
not coming out it's not enough you have
to do more than that you have to give
your body what it needs you have to
learn and know how to cleanse those
toxins out you have to know how to get
Metals out you need something that
actually works that matters all on its
own then we need something that works
against the path pens how to kill the
bugs off how to clean up those
neurotoxins that the bugs left behind
and then after that how to restore
organs how to restore nerves the central
nervous system how to restore the brain
after you've gotten rid of all the
toxins and the pathogens all of this
combined means everything one thing
people don't realize in the health
movement experts or gurus they don't
realize the emotional and memory toxins
the cells contain all through adrenaline
what happens when we go through
experiences in our life adrenaline is
involved there's messaging there's
information within that adrenaline
there's connections between our brain
and our adrenals so when we're in fight
or flight and something happened in our
life that memory stays in the cells
stays in the cells through adrenaline
and adrenaline stays in the cells it
could sit there for decades long after
something terrible or something trying
or a struggle or something difficult or
some adversity happened in somebody's
life that adrenaline can sit in cells
for decades sit inside the liver sit
inside all the different organs
including connective tissue and even
bones and when that adrenaline surfaces
because you start cleansing for the
first time in your life you start
releasing toxins and that adrenaline is
toxic that adrenaline has those mem
once it starts to release it starts to
come out you'll
experience certain feelings certain
Sensations even certain memories can
come up with a dream or in a dream and
that adrenaline is circulating now
through the body but it's not going back
into the body when you properly cleanse
it goes out of the body and leaves and
when that toxic adrenaline that old
adrenaline from years before leaves the
body you start feeling lighter you start
feeling more mentally clear because it
was sitting inside of you for decades
wreaking havoc creating chaos inside the
cells of the body and now it's gone if
you're doing the proper cleansing or
you're doing a proper cleanse the
problem with so many cleanses out there
is they're destructive to the adrenals
and destructive to the brain because
they don't offer enough
calories it's critical to be able to
offer calories while you're cleansing
fuel for the brain electrolytes for the
brain sugar glucose for the brain and
for the adrenals and that doesn't exist
in cleanses out there the medical medium
cleanses it does exist it is there it
protects the adrenals it creates a
situation where you can cleanse and heal
while feeding your body what it need
while feeding all of your organs what it
needs and that doesn't happen in
cleanses cleanses often starve somebody
of what they need they often either
starve them or they put a food in that
cleanse that stops the person from
cleansing so what I've noticed out there
all through the years that anytime
there's a cleanse there's either
something in the way of the person
cleansing that's offered in there or
it's starving them so they're getting
damage and truly not cleansing what they
need to cleanse one of the biggest
problems with cleanses is they don't
know what they're trying to cleanse out
up until recently with the medical
medium books educating people on what's
really in them the toxic heavy metals
and all the different poisons and the
Pharmaceuticals and all the pathogens
until that happened till that
information truly got out there no one
knew what they were cleansing it was
just toxins that was it not what were
the toxins not what else is happening
just toxins so the cleanses were
designed for Hit or Miss weak grass
juice lots of water but all guessing
games that's what the cleanses were but
when it comes down to Cleansing you
can't do the guessing game thing there
can't be any games at all it has to be
what works how do you cleanse how do you
heal what kind of toxins are actually in
the body what are they are they metals
how do we get those Metals out they just
don't cleanse out you need a way to
extract them out and what about all the
other toxins and then set that aside
what about the pathogens because in the
health movement nobody knew pathogens
were responsible for all the different
autoimmune the conditions the symptoms
the diseases and so forth nobody knew
that it's medical medium information all
these years that pathogens cause
neurological problems and symptoms so
all the cleanses were already obsolete
or didn't work at all because they
didn't even know that viruses and
bacteria were responsible for so many of
the different ailments so it was all hey
you got candida let's do a candida
cleanse but a candida cleanse would tear
somebody's guts up it would cause a
problem it wouldn't be good for the
person at all and it would starve them
of glucose for the brain and then
there'd be like a sodium bicarbonate
cleanse which would destroy any good
bacteria in their intestinal tract and
wreak havoc on their intestinal lining
and create immune system problems and
then it'd be a milk cleanse but a milk
cleanse just feeds all pathogens it
emboldens a pathogen it proliferates a
virus creating a problem that if
somebody was chronically ill with any
kind of neurological problems because of
pathogens the milk cleanse would make
that so much worse and then the water
fasts water fasting which atrophies the
brain it shrinks somebody's brain any
kind of glycogen storage that somebody
has in their brain when they do a
long-term water fast and they don't have
glycogen going in glucose going in for a
long time what happens is the brain
atrophies and then longterm juice
cleanses without the celery juice
without the sodium the celery juice
longterm juice fasts would shrink
stomachs create an elasticity problem in
the intestinal tracts from no
peristaltic action and then the
dangerous parasite cleanses the ones
that rip the intestinal tracts apart
with Clays using so many different
scratchy scratchy products these gut
health cleanses would irritate the
Linings of the intestinal track and the
colon creating a whole bunch of problems
for people and then there were the fruit
fear cleanses that no fruit allowed on
any level so it would just be like
sprouts and wheat grass juice and
nothing else where the person is being
starved of calories caloric action
starved of glucose for their organs
their muscles and their brains and then
they would atrophy in their muscles from
not getting enough glucose and they
would just be on wheat grass and Sprouts
then there was the long-term dry fasting
cleanses which is disastrous for
multitude of reasons and then there were
the autoimmune cleanses which are still
out there now in some shape or form and
the autoimmune cleanses have so much fat
in them so much over it fat that it's
impossible to cleanse anything therefore
nothing cleanses on an autoimmune
cleanse and what about other cleanses
that are high in fat which means no
cleansing happens with those either
there are dozens and dozens of cleanses
out there that have overt fat in it
which means the liver won't cleanse a
huge mistake in the cleansing world that
nobody knew which is you can't cleanse
any toxins or poisons out meaning deep
seeded ones and deep seeded Metals if
the high fat content in the bloodstream
is too high if the over fats are too
high some fat could be okay depending
but a lot of cleanses have a lot of MCT
oil they have a lot of other oils or
olive oil another cleanse out there
that's popular is drinking straight
olive oil as if that's going to cleanse
a person all that does is throw the
liver into chaotic shock and doesn't
cleanse it shuts down the liver
temporarily not allowing it to release
any toxins or poisons I can do this all
day but there is a right way to cleanse
and it's not just coming from a place
where I just started a cleanse of some
kind I'm excited about it and I want you
to know about it and give it a shot
comes from a place of Decades of
experience using information from above
that's already healed people so think
about that cleans es that already have a
track record that's the cleanses you
want the ones that have a track record
of healing the ones that have turned
people's lives around the ones that
actually worked and got rid of the
toxins and poisons lowered their weight
so they wouldn't have to go on OIC and
other weight loss drugs cleanses that
brought their lives back instead of
doing damage check out medical medium
cleanses celery juice the mono cleanse
the morning cleanse the heavy metal
detox cleanse the 369 cleanses the 28
day cleanse check them all out there's
even more realize that there is
information out there to turn your life
around to help you heal to starve
pathogens and not starve you to feed
your
brain and heal at the same time to give
your body what it needs the electrolytes
the glucose the antioxidants phychem
chemical compounds the nutrients while
you're healing to give you what people
worry about protein while you're healing
all of it is there it's unquestionable
and it works it's not scratchy Clays and
strange crazy ideas it makes sense and
when you do the medical medium cleanses
your life turns around like so many
people their lives have turned around
you can't lose your only win when you're
doing it and you heal and you move
forward keep that in mind if you're
somebody who's been through a lot and
you tried a lot of cleanses of the past
and you know the history of cleanses
know that when you do these you can
customize one to what you need you can
start small you can do the anti-bug
cleanse you can start at level one you
can do the morning cleanse you could
start with just celery juice or heavy
metal detox smoothie but keep in mind
healing is possible and you can move
forward without bringing the baggage and
the old toxic past with
you you can try what they sell you it's
most likely a trick or two their trendy
detoxes shadowed the old ones from
decades ago nothing new if one out of
500 felt better it was a
fluke and that was under strict
supervision so they can watch what
entered their mouths and came out of
their
shoots today one healed shouted from the
roof what a
Roose the other
1,000 under strict watch never
improved no matter how much money was
spent
boohoo milk water parasite
candida mold bicarbonate only juice just
to name a few kept the chronically ill
sick so
uncool there are cleanses that do exist
that have allowed others to get back
into life get back on the
grid mom's getting better able to play
with their kids Dad's getting better
being able to climb up the ladder
families
healing not so worried anymore about
praying because their prayers were
answered they had less time to cry not
worried they were going to die not
living Merry Go Round
lie seeing the
truth about how there is a healing
root inside their
bodies Bottom Feeders in the health
World unable to bleed them
dry time to look back at what was real
and not what's a
fact and now making up for lost time
getting lost time back there is a way to
heal you will get your confidence back
you don't need their false
promises you can rise out of the ashes
you will feel the sunlight in your heart
again
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please cite where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before for them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion