how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
Williams we're talking about parasites
that's right parasites but really we're
talking about the parasitical scam now
if you're somebody that believes in
parasites there's nothing wrong with
that because parasites are real
yes they are
indeed in fact a piece of meat sitting
out in the sun during a picnic will
collect a lot of different microbes a
lot of different food born
illnesses just like egg salad can't
leave egg salad in the sun either
because something will happen the
mayonnaise the Mayo those eggs sitting
out there something bad will happen to
them you can get really sick very sick
sick very ill you can't eat uncooked
chicken uncooked turkey why because you
can die yes you can die and they can't
just eat raw meat because there could be
a parasite on there without a doubt that
parasite can really hurt you there also
could be some bad bacteria there too yes
parasites are real but so is the
parasite scam
if you're someone that's been told you
have parasites or you have a parasite
and now you're going to be dedicating
all your time and energy doing
parasitical cleanses chasing parasites
looking at parasite info out there and
making your whole life about a parasite
you might want to listen to this episode
to start with the parasite biohack
movement has been around it was around
years ago and many of the earlier
chronically old people people with
mysterious chronic illness got into the
parasite movement they were looking for
answers and they tried everything and so
hearing that parasites could be their
problem lured them in it was the next
flashy thing the next shiny object they
went into it thinking whoa I'm going to
be fixed I'm going to be cured but it
didn't work people didn't get cured they
didn't get fixed in fact they got sicker
they were doing all kinds of intestinal
cleansers intestinal cleansers that are
out there now bentonite clay different
Clays thinking they were ridding
parasites they were trying to get
parasites out of their intestinal tract
they were using wormwood shillig fulvic
minerals fulvic acid sodium bicarbonate
and chlorine dioxide simultaneously as
all this was happening during this time
the Lyme disease movement was shifting
no longer was it just bacteria it was
hybrids now hybrids such as babesia
babesia wasn't considered a bacteria it
was considered a parasite although that
is a debate still worth having to begin
with they never found babesia they never
found barnella and they never found
bellia but yet these were the bacteria
and parasitical hybrids that were being
touted at the time so as the Lyme
disease moved M was growing into that
there was the parasitical movement on
the other end of the spectrum they were
working off of each other but still all
in the wrong direction when someone had
a blood test looking for lime bacteria
the lime bacteria was never found
instead it was an inflammatory marker
test but nobody knew that at that time
they still don't know it today medical
medium information exposed it so Lyme
disease took a turn and it went for
co-actors it was was all about co-actors
co-actor parasites like hybrids like
babesia so both the health movement at
the time a small batch of people were
focused on parasites while at the same
time a small batch of doctors were
focused on parasites with Lyme disease
aesia and it never got anybody anywhere
the people with thyroid disease and
chronic illness and vertigo and
dizziness and aches and pains and
Tremors and Shakes and ticks and spasms
and Restless leg syndrome and back pain
foot pain neck pain and severe severe
fatigue weren't being fixed by either
side the protocols for Lyme disease were
intense harsh antibiotics and the
protocols for so-called parasite issues
in the health movement were cleansers
cleansing products Clays intestinal
Clays shiled fulvic minerals fulvic acid
chlorine dioxide sodium bicarbonate quop
pod apple ceter vinegar charcoal
colostrum warmwood and alkaline ionizer
water and nothing worked people stayed
sick they were chronically ill lots of
mysterious symptoms people went through
the machine they went through the meat
grinder they had nowhere to go nothing
was working one reason it wasn't
parasites parasites were not why people
were sick with chronic illness but
parasites made sense to people it made
sense to them this m mysterious weird
creature Critter living inside of a
person it made a lot of sense it was a
fly trap it brought people in left and
right parasitical cleanses were huge
they were huge because people were
thinking that was the answer but they
tried them been there done that and it
didn't fix people hordes of people so
then the parasitical world started to
die that's right in the health movement
it started to die it fell off the map
and was taken over it was taken over
once again by Candida by Fungus it was
taken over once again by Sugar Sugar
being the problem sugar fruit fear took
it over so new thing started fruit fear
sugar sugar was the cause of everybody's
chronic illness everybody believed it
everybody was told it here to high
heaven it was all about sugar parasites
took the back seat died off
sugar was the evildoer it was the evil
one it was Satan to everybody everybody
was afraid of sugar and every shape
fashion or form fruit was evil was very
frightening and along with the fruit
fear came the protein deficiencies
you're not getting enough protein that's
why you're sick that's got to be the
answer you're not getting enough protein
so you're dying so you're fatigued so
you're having chronic illness
you must be protein deficient and at the
same time years ago a new storm was
occurring oxalates oxyc acid everybody
was starting to believe that was the
cause of their illness that's why they
had chronic illness that's why they were
in wheelchairs that's why they were sick
that's why they couldn't function it's
why they had add that's why they had
brain fog it must have been oxyc acid
oxalates that was the big one it covered
up the parasitical craze parasitical
craze died oxyc acid arrived candida
came back and protein was God and then
an upsurge of alkaline water so
everybody who's chronically sick ended
up buying the alkaline ionizer water
machines thinking this would be the fix
all that this would take care of it but
the machines ended up in the closets
everybody's closets people couldn't give
them away fast enough because they were
getting worse drinking the water water
even from the best machines that are out
there today they didn't know that the
metal plates inside the machines were
corroding just like they do today and
will always do the corrosion released
oxidation micro particles of metals
entering into people so that wasn't the
answer either and still isn't the answer
today but back then they had their day
their upsurge and then the alkaline
ionizer and water machine died it
exceeded and fell back just like the
parasite World in fact all of these
things fell back and died and there was
a great big hole in the health world the
health movement people sick and
exhausted tried everything been there
done that nothing worked and they were
all sick chronic illness was on the rise
people didn't have answers to why they
were even sick and biohacks of that era
were on life support Maybe maybe you
were there maybe this has meaning to you
maybe you tried everything done that
been there and maybe this is all just
new to you but it's important to know
imperative to know when it comes down to
being sick and healing it's important to
know that the parasitical scam was here
before and it's here now again and no
disrespect to anyone it doesn't mean
someone's trying to truly scam someone a
lot of people could have their heart in
it they could have invest ments in it
time money energy and truly believe in
what they're doing and some could be
scamming people because that's the
industry now it's a dog eat dog world
now let's talk about parasites and get
deeper into it parasites are real they
exist they're on every single raw piece
of beef raw piece of chicken they're all
over packages in the grocery store
there's parasites all over packages
around meat and pork and chicken and
fish if you go into a grocery store and
you buy some fish that's wrapped in
plastic in a container or some pork or
some beef it'll be on the outside of the
container there'll be parasites all over
the outside and in a display case you
see fish of all kinds seafood or another
display case where you see organ meats
and pork and chicken and grass-fed beef
there's parasites everywhere everywhere
all over it
all kinds of different microbes bad
microbes not good microbes and from a
scale 1 to 10 some of those parasites
could be extremely
dangerous some of them could be very
mild now the mild ones get killed off
easy in your gut all you need is just a
little bit of HCL a little bit of
hydrochloric acid naturally inside your
stomach produced by your stomach glands
and that hydrochloric acid is your
parasitical killer in fact you eat
parasites often and don't know it your
HCL is killing and destroying those
parasites there's parasites on people's
hands there's parasites on door handles
there's parasites in bathrooms and
bathroom sink handles there's parasites
in restaurants on food you ordered and
most all of these parasites don't bother
anybody because they they die off they
get killed off they get killed off fast
sometimes just in our
mouths sometimes in our stomach
sometimes in our dadum and even in our
small intestinal tract but they die off
they get killed these parasites that we
actually eat a lot of and don't even
realize it or get exposed to it a lot
die off they don't stick around they
don't stay anywhere they don't stay in
the liver they don't stay in the
intestinal tract they don't stay in the
stomach they don't stay in the rectum
they don't stay anywhere these parasites
come and they go as fast as they came
they die and our immune system has a big
part involved with killing them our
immune cells love parasites they feed
off of them they destroy them they
gobble them up they break them apart and
they discard them and all of this is
happening when you don't even know it
you're not even aware of it you're
immune system destroys level one level 2
3 4 5 level six level seven parasites
now keep in mind there's hundreds of
varieties of parasites not registered
not documented there are thousands of
varieties of different forms of microbes
and parasites and they all fall under
the parasite umbrella and science
doesn't care there's no money involved
there's no money to be made research in
science doesn't study them they're aware
they exist they're aware there's a lot
of microbes out there many harmless many
not harmless and many dangerous yes
dangerous level 8 n 10 and Beyond very
dangerous can kill someone that's right
can kill someone so let's get into that
a little bit you go down to Mexico and
you drink the water in a basin or a
ravine or a canal or a pond and you
drink that water you're not going
anywhere you'd be lucky if you made it
home because you picked up a parasite
that's right a parasite a real parasite
floating around in dirty water swimming
around in dirty water an amoeba or some
other form of parasite sitting in that
water and if you drink it you'll be
lucky if you can get home and most
likely you'll just end up in the
hospital and you'll be in there fighting
for your life with dis
a broad term for some type of food
poisoning or parasitical infection now
with this parasitical infection you have
to win yes you have to heal you have to
get better what that means is you can't
live with it your body won't allow you
to live with a parasite so it's kill or
be killed it's either the parasite kills
you which happens to a lot of people or
your body kills kills the parasite but
you can't live with it long term you
can't be somebody with chronic illness
going for years and years thinking
you've had a parasitical infection a
chronic parasitical infection all these
years and that's your problem because
it's not you can't live with a parasite
in your system your body has to kill it
and that killing of it is the war and
that war is sickness in the moment death
defying sickness for a lot of people or
difficult sickness for a lot of people
or mild sickness for a lot of people but
it's only temporary it's you win or the
bug wins you win or the parasite wins
it's not I'm sick for 10 years whoa I
just learned that maybe if I do a
parasite cleanse that that'll fix it
because I must have a parasite nope
that's not how it works that you win or
the parasite wins same thing if you end
up with food poisoning you eat in a
restaurant something was in the food
some food born pathogen yes a parasite a
food born pathogen a parasite and you
eat that and now you're sick you're
throwing up you're vomiting you have
diarrhea you have the runs it won't stop
you're in tremendous pain Agony the
worst kind you try to push through a day
goes by you're going through the vomits
again you're going through the runs
again you're going through the diarrhea
is again and you can't get better
something's wrong getting dehydrated now
you're at the hospital you're hooked up
to an IV and they put you on some kind
of pain killer maybe even morphine to
dumb down the pain and you try to rest
while your immune system tries to kill
off whatever that food born pathogen is
whatever that parasite is because the
war is on it's not about living
simultaneously living in harmony living
in some way down the road together
doesn't work like that the bug the food
born pathogen has to be killed same
thing with aggressive forms of eoli that
aren't the normal forms of eoli the
aggressive foodborn varieties they have
to be killed you can't live with them so
you lay in the hospital while your body
fights for its life while your immune
system fights for your life while the
doctors can't do anything about it sides
keep you hydrated keep you plugged into
a salt bag to an IV and then give you
painkillers so you can rest and try to
get some sleep allowing your body to
heal and that is foodborn pathogens
that's food poisoning That's parasites
those are parasites that are aggressive
and they can come in any old shape and
size because there's hundreds of them
and thousands of them and most of them
harmless because we kill them off fast
our HCL kills them the more aggressive
the parasite the less chance our HCL can
kill them especially if our HCL
hydrochloric acid is weakened in a
weakened State our stomach glands aren't
producing good HCL we've been drinking
coffee for years our stomach glands are
wasted we have adrenaline surges from
fight or flight maybe we have vicces
that actually cause adrenaline surges
that burn out our gastric glands and the
CL is not there it's not strong enough
it's not at the quantity or the level it
needs to be so pathogens Escape they
bypass the stomach they enter the dadum
and down into the intestinal tract they
could even find their way into the liver
if they can't be stopped now these are
parasitical pathogens foodborn pathogens
parasites not viruses not stealth
viruses not multi udes of bacteria and
different forms of bacteria like strep
these are food related bugs these are
water related bugs dirty water stagnant
Still Water food poisoning and food
poisoning stories you see and hear out
there all the time and they're even in
the media now where three members of a
family die and they die before they even
get to the hospital or they die in the
hospital one dies at home two die in the
hospital this happens all the time
that's parasites really aggressive ones
and it's you or the parasite you go down
or the parasite goes down there's no
other way it's not something you live
with from here on out where you improve
in the hospital and now you're better
enough to get out of the hospital now
you're home and you're sick because you
still have the parasite or you still
have the parasite for weeks and weeks
and months and months now you might be
injured and triggered by a par partical
infection which leaves you sick for
years after a situation like this but
you don't have the parasite anymore you
know how you know you don't have the
parasite anymore you're still standing
you're still breathing because you would
have died the parasite would have killed
you milder parasites and food born
pathogens food born illness food born
parasites milder less aggressive ones
you kill fast your HCL and your immune
cells kill and destroy quickly and you
move on it could be one bat of diarrhea
it could be one bout of vomiting and
then you're good and maybe just a rough
night you're good the next day you start
picking up your pace and you're back to
normal or you don't even know what
happened your body killed it off real
fast you got strong
HC strong immune system immune cells and
it was annihilated and annihilated with
within the hour or half an hour after
eating or getting exposure or getting
some tainted water or getting something
in your mouth that led to this but
somebody sick for 20 years with chronic
illness with different symptoms and
conditions and neurological problems are
not living with a parasite this is a
misguided Mistake by people in the
health movement that have no idea why
people are sick still even though they
seem qualified or they know a lot about
vaccines or they know a lot about all
kinds of different problems in health or
food chemicals or processed foods and
they're all talking a good game they
still don't know why chronically ill
people are chronically ill but it seems
logical it seems like it makes sense if
I was somebody sick with all kinds of
neurological problems and different
symptoms and I heard maybe it's
parasitical and a parasite and I thought
well my doctors probably don't know I've
been to 50 doctors in the last 8 years
and maybe this is the answer I have a
parasite surely that's what it must be
it sounds like it everybody's talking
about it that must be what I have and
you could be somebody that's like whoa I
got sick last year it's probably a
parasite from all the information I'm
seeing out there now without realizing
what happened 20 years ago 15 years ago
12 years ago
25 years ago not knowing about the
parasitical understanding the trend how
it works and the parasite scam what
people are really living with what
they're really dealing with are
pathogens yes but stealth
viruses that's what they've always been
living and dealing with it's stealth
viruses epscene bar shingles
hhv6
hhv7 different variety of herpes of all
kinds undiscovered varieties plus
simplex one Simplex 2 people are living
with multiple varieties of these at one
time two varieties of epine bar a
variety of shingles and a cold sore
virus herpes simplex 1 all at the same
time along with bacteria strep varieties
some people can pick up over a lifetime
10 15 20 varieties strep some aggressive
causing chronic
sinusitis causing mucus in their chest
in their lungs causing severe acne UTI
kidney infections bladder infections BV
bacterial vaginosis and living with
difficult strep varieties that are
antibiotic resistance not just one
antibiotic resistance strain but
multiple and some people have a little
bit of everything they'll have some
strep other varieties of bacteria too
they'll have sta maybe some SEI maybe
they'll have two Epstein bars and they
can live miserable because there's
different varieties of these bugs some
more aggressive some milder depending on
the person's immune system their
deficiencies are they zinc deficient are
they B12 deficient and so forth people
have chronic illness because of
pathogens they also have chronic illness
because of toxic heavy metals both
metals and pathogens equal chronic
illness chronic mystery long-term
illness and autoimmune where do
parasites fit in with all this
nowhere they don't fit in anywhere
parasites are a problem that when you
get one has to be killed off your body
has to do it that's the fight for your
life if it's a mild parasite very
minimal issues can occur you may not
even know you had a parasite your HCL
killed it and it's gone medical medium
information broke barriers the discovery
of all these different viruses stealth
living in US causing neurological
symptoms it changed everything in health
people found answers and they knew what
kind of protocols to use to heal and
those protocols were entirely different
than the trends of yester year of years
ago the opposite of fulvic minerals
fulvic acid Bentonite Clays and other
different clays chillig apple ceter
vinegar chlorophyll alkaline water
chlorine dioxide sodium bicarbonate
charcoal colostrum just to name a few
these never worked they didn't work for
people years ago they don't work for
people today and part of the reason why
so many people are healing from chronic
illness is the things that do work the
medical medium information that brought
in olive leaf licorice propolis golden
seal Elderberry zinc vitamin C B12 cats
claw and many other tools turned people
around got their lives back with chronic
symptoms neurological symptoms because
it was based on killing off pathogens
medical medium information killing off
stealth viruses like Epstein bar that's
how people got their lives back they got
their lives back back then and they're
getting their lives back now but the
parasitical world is upsurging again and
they're talking the same game
same game as yester year of decades ago
they're talking about parasites when
that's not what people are suffering
with that's not why people can't think
with their brain fog have Alzheimer's
dementia memory problems have ticks and
spasms aches and pains neurological
symptoms Galore restless leg syndrome
balance issues dizziness vertigo tunitis
it's not why people are sick but it's a
good lur they bring them in they get
them to listen because you have people a
whole new batch of people new bees new
sick bees they're there they're sick now
they don't know why they're sick they
already went through the merrygoround a
little bit they've already went from
Doctor to doctor they don't have answers
and parasites seem perfect it only makes
sense so they follow these doctors and
follow these practitioners and these
health coaches and the influencers and
they think they have parasites but some
something's changed about the
parasitical protocols they're a little
different and even a lot different now
they have pieces of medical medium
information they have medical medium
tools they have lemon bomb they got B12
they got zinc interesting they didn't
have that before they didn't have that
before the medical medium books and the
medical medium information they only had
their schillig they only had their
fulvic minerals fulvic acid their sodium
bicarbonate their alkaline water their
chlorophyll they only had those they
didn't have anything else but now you
hear cats claw out there that's
interesting it's a medical medium tool
for chronic illness and neurological
diseases and conditions and symptoms can
that be a good thing they're poaching
medical medium tools but using it for
parasites it could be good in the way
where someone might get a benefit they
might actually get a little window into
healing but it'll be stopped instantly
when they offer something that is toxic
or doesn't work and it goes against it
they use a medical medium tool goes with
the grain then they use something highly
toxic goes against the grain and then
people just don't really truly get
better and they believe they have
parasites when they don't and that's sad
because we're not making the progress we
need to make we need to know why we're
sick we need to know why we have
neurological symptoms we need to
understand that and then we need the
tools to fix it the medical medium
information about what pathogens what
stealth viruses what bacteria what toxic
heavy
metals what other poisons what other
toxins what other exposures and what
about the tools we need the right tools
for the right problems having the
answers matter instead of chasing our
Tails having little tidbits is fun but
we're just playing the game and when it
comes down to health time matters
wasting time matters we have to be able
to heal we need to be doing things that
are working we need to understand why
we're sick to begin with and that's the
sad thing people they don't know they
don't know why they're sick with these
mystery symptoms they're hearing tidbits
that have been poached throughout the
years for medical medium they're hearing
different things it sounds good sounds
like it might work maybe if they're
lucky they'll get a poached tool that
does help but in the end they're still
in the dark and it's really sad
parasites aren't the problem they're not
the reason why people are suffering and
sick out there yes parasites are
dangerous but you now know how and why
check out the medical medium book series
pick up a brainsaver book or a
brainsaver protocols book your mind will
be blown when you read the information
in there get it from the library for
free it doesn't matter go to Medical
medium.com check out more information
free information there's no pay wall and
subscribe to my newsletter too if you
get a chance and check out my telegram
many blessings take care and God bless
you there's a big difference the
parasites that knock you so hard you
take a fall get up from the dinner table
you got some food
poisoning you're barfing in the toilet
all night long huge difference then
worms that creepy crawl
the worms that people get inside of them
that can live in synchronicity with
everyone all day long the tapeworm can
grow and grow and grow and get very
long but is easily spotted and killed so
the person can go back to their normal
lifelong a heartworm in your pet can be
stopped by a good vet there are are lots
of annoying worms but they're different
than chronic illness itself different
than so many people suffering with
different neurological symptoms
struggling so much they can't even move
through their day those are viruses and
pathogens bacteria that keep people in
that way and those stealth pathogens
aren't parasites the ones that knock
people down parasites old parasites that
keep people in their hospital beds
those parasites are so much different
they stay with you until you're dead
unless your body kills that parasite
kills that parasite you're free to live
another night the body's battle against
a parasite is much different than the
battle against stealth viruses and
bacteria different we can live with
stealth viruses in our body for the rest
of our life and worms are different than
parasites and stealth viruses they're
much different we can live with them our
whole life and not even have them cause
a
symptom yes some worms like a tapeworm
can get really big and hurt us but they
can be found really easily and killed
within us don't be fooled these are
three different things these are the
rules parasites worms and pathogens try
not to forget again
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the convention and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place
appear pure untampered with Advanced
Clean uncorrupted original primary
source a higher source Spirit of
compassion