how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William we're talking about the new
medical medium original audio Angels
demons and spiritual tools which you can
find on Amazon audible apple and Spotify
many people are afraid of the word demon
they feel the word itself is something
they should stay away from meanwhile
without realizing it it's possible
demons play a role in their life even
play a role in their
decisions playing a role in their own
free will interfering with their own
choice making empowerment comes with
knowledge understanding not only this
Physical Realm but the spiritual realm
around us and when you have a grasp on
it and know what's going on and you're
not tricked and you're not duped anymore
it's a gamech Cher Everything Changes
Darkness doesn't want you to know about
Darkness negativity negative energy
negative forces demonic forces do not
want you to know they exist even when
terrible things are happening in the
world or something bad happens to a
friend or somebody you know Darkness
still doesn't want you to know that
Darkness has anything to do with it or
anything to do with anything fasten your
seat bels get some lemon bomb tea strap
yourself in for this one make sure
you're sitting down we're talking about
are demons running your
life wow thanks for meeting me out here
I like this coffee shop it's a great
place definitely you can order what you
want here it's like crazy they got
everything here s sit down talk to me
what's happening lately your parents
they're getting a divorce what do you
mean really I thought they were really
happy oh God that's crazy what else is
going on what else has happened you got
hit from behind last week what do you
mean hit from behind a car wow are you
okay the car is mangled somebody was
playing with their phone and then they
just didn't look and they just ran into
you oh they were drunk oh God that's
awful what do you mean your friend
friend what does your friend have to do
oh your friend texted you the other day
what they say something terrible let me
see that thread you are an a there's a
whole bunch of question marks there so
I'm assuming that's what whole and you
didn't bring back the thing that you
borrowed and I can't stand you anymore
and we're not friends anymore
goodbye what is this why is he even
saying this but you did bring back the
leaf blower so you brought it back and
then what he's still saying this he gets
like this all the time okay okay oh his
girlfriend broke up with him okay why
she cheated on him wait he cheated on
her and then she cheated on him and then
he cheated on her wait I'm I'm lost now
who cheated on who first and why can I
ask you something why do you have a
bandage on your face is that from the
car
accident no that's from fall on your
face when you fell on your face you were
just walking along and you just tripped
and fell on your face but it wasn't your
fault you just you were doing fine you
were walking fine and what happened it
just magically happened you just fell on
your face you just lost your footing you
felt like you're a pushed what happened
excuse me can I get a coffee and a
muffin what do you
want people lose Faith because they see
things go wrong they lose faith in God
they lose faith in humanity they lose
faith in anything good in the universe
they lose faith in themselves they lose
faith in others they lose faith in life
itself and a lot of people are suffering
out there and they don't understand why
horrible things are happening in their
lives they don't understand why horrible
things are occurring out there in the
world they see terrible things happen
all the time why people are dying early
why bombs are going off why Wars
continue to start a lot of terrible
things are occurring and people are
distraught it's hurting their heads many
don't believe people are actually evil
instead they think that everybody has
good in them and that people are just
misguided people also believe that
accidents just happen and many times
accidents do just happen but many times
they just don't happen something happens
to make them happen and there are
accidents that are terrifying where
people lose their lives you see it out
there all the time it's not a
rarity it's something you see in the
news something you see out there in the
media where how did these people burn up
alive in a car how come they just
couldn't get out of the car what
happened or how did that person run
themselves over they were getting out of
the car it rolled backwards dragged them
along the way ran over them but how they
weren't looking for that to happen that
day everybody was happy things were
going good how is this possible they
woke up that morning they took a shower
brushed their teeth they had a bagel
they had a drink of orange juice hour
later they were dead they were run over
by their own car a freak accident and
why do we make choices that aren't the
best for us how does that work someone's
young they're in college they're
drinking too much they get alcohol
poisoning they leave the party or they
leave the bar they're walking down the
street talking to themselves they're
walking around aimlessly they walk down
a different street cameras last see them
here cameras last see them there they
disappear nobody could find them 20 days
later they're found in a river nothing
makes sense what soever there was no
reason for it and what about
relationships gone wrong toxic
relationships but why are they toxic to
begin with is it just baggage is it old
hurt Old Wounds and where did that old
hurt and Old Wounds deriv from where did
they come from why are they there was
there any kind of other influence
involved and why do people do dark
things dark things things that aren't
good for them things that aren't good
for others around them things that were
premeditated things that were
spontaneous things that were hurtful but
they didn't really mean it and then
there's people out there that hurt
others that mean it what is this all
about so many people out there live in a
bubble where the thought of Darkness
existing is only meant for the movies
for television they believe when things
happen to people in real life they
brought it upon themselves they caused
it and for those that believe this kind
of thing that when bad things happened
to people they caused it and brought it
upon themselves maybe the worst they've
ever experienced so far in life was a
girlfriend or a boyfriend cheating on
them and that was it or a family member
that they didn't get along good with
well these things can still cause
injuries and not be great people think
that Darkness plays no role in any of it
that it just happened because people are
people and yes people can be people but
there is something to be said that
darkness is involved with so many issues
toxic relationships Darkness can be
involved and it doesn't mean that the
people in the relationship are bad but
they could be influenced yes influenced
by dark Fallen beings demonic beings
inherently involved D in so many of
their issues and to the people that live
in a bubble the thought of demonic and
Fallen beings inherently involved in so
many of the world's problems seems way
way overreaching and totally not any
kind of reality you would think humans
would be elevated at this point at a
place in time and history where we know
that hate and destruction and war is not
productive and you would think at this
point in time in history
people would actually not do terrible
things that institutions wouldn't do
Terrible Things countries wouldn't do
terrible things you would think that
everybody would just get along and
everybody would try to make good things
happen only but how come it doesn't work
that way why are we witnessing so much
constant chaos and destruction and
wrongful death why in our everyday lives
do we experience so many heartaches so
much red tape that thwarts are dreams
and why are there so many unstable
people out there people that create
nothing but static and
confusion some people that like creating
confusion some people that just don't
know they're creating that much
confusion why do people who work so hard
at manifestation still get foiled still
get thrown off their path when you hear
the word demon how do you feel what kind
of reactions do you have have what kind
of reactions do other people have for
some people they just don't like the
sound of the word the word itself scares
them for some people it gives them a
creepy crawly sensation a funny feeling
for some people they're worried they're
superstitious they think it's dangerous
to say the word demon and they think
they're bringing it to them just saying
the word itself that's a problem maybe
they're going to bring a demon to them
to cause problem albums and then there's
folklore demon stories out there demon
stories in films demons in film Seance
boards the idea if you actually talk
about something you bring it to yourself
if you entertain the idea you bring it
upon
yourself now I'm not here to convince
anyone that demons exist you can believe
in demons or you don't have to believe
in demons they would prefer you don't
believe in them Darkness would prefer
you don't believe in Darkness Darkness
would rather have the experiences in
someone's life that are not agreeable to
be blamed on people blamed even on them
or maybe happen stance or freak
accidents instead of anybody thinking
about the possibility that demonic
forces exist if someone avoids thinking
about
demons does that protect them are you
more susceptible to Demons when you
focus on them being real is it unhealthy
to think about the possibility of demons
being real no it's not this isn't like
Beetle Juice or if you say demons three
times you're in trouble Dark Forces out
there are at play no matter what they're
at play out there and you can witness
these dark Forces you could see it out
there every day if not in your own
personal life can witness what's
happening in with planetary politics
Earthly destruction and throughout the
decades lots of innocent people dying
then there are the constant coverups out
there so the darkness can be hidden and
the truth doesn't show many coverups
that the light never shines upon and
some that surface over time demonic
forces play a role in it all they're
always trying to tempt people to mess
with people's heads and many people
carry one or even multiple demons around
them or with them or sometimes in them
people who suffer from addiction issues
can be taunted by demons even long after
an addiction has been healed conquered
or
defeated the person who defeated that
addiction who won over that addiction
and moved forward still can be taunted
every now and then still can be teased
every now and then still feel an UR
merge every now and then on an emotional
level and when they overpowered that
addiction with their free will they
overpowered that demon the Demon's
influence the darkness' influence they
overpowered it doesn't mean that demon
won't come along one day when they're at
a weak moment when they've been chipped
away when they've been beaten down by
something by some other demonic force in
some industry out there some institution
out there there some worldly government
out there or just somebody in the
relationship with them that has demons
in some form shape or in some way and
that demon starts to chip away at them
starts to tempt them when they're in
their darkest hour for the moment or
when they're at a weak point reminding
them hey go back to your addiction I'm
here to tell you once you listen to
Medical medium Angels demons and
spiritual tools you're going to
understand the forces at work in our
lives and other people's lives around
you in the world like never before and
you're going to understand how to regain
your power and draw on something called
spiritual lights of free will the 16
spiritual lights of free will to help
protect yourself and your loved ones and
one of these spiritual lights of Free
Will involves the word Checkmate in
order to regain your power power it's
important to understand the realm that's
very rarely seen by the eyes to have
your eyes open and truly see to
understand demonic forces is to
understand Injustice and wrong and
sabotage and deception and trickery it
is to understand how to start putting
safeguards in place in your life to
protect you to understand demonic forces
is to understand the Soul Your Soul is
to understand the Angelic forces around
you and above you and how to come to
their aid so we can play our part in
stopping demonic forces in their tracks
and what they believe is their playing
field if you're someone who's struggling
spiritually it's time to heal check out
medical medium Angels demons and
spiritual tools it's an original audio
you can find on Amazon you can find on
Spotify and apple many blessings and God
bless
you in all these decades I've been asked
about demons asked about the afterlife
asked about ghosts asked about spirits
asked about angels and the most
inquiries I get are about demons what's
going on with demons what's the whole
demon
thing how does that work or demons even
been real along the way I would shed
some light on fragments of the inner
workings of the spiritual realm and what
seemed to be meaningless
atrocities until now I've been holding
back lots of spiritual information
because the hands of time had not
allowed it now it's finally time for me
to put this information out there for
anyone to access
I want to offer these answers to
everyone I want to offer these answers
to you to be aware of Darkness you don't
have to be obsessed with it you don't
have to think about demons
24/7 or think about their possibility of
existing all the time you don't have to
live like that you can just be aware
that when things are going wrong it's
not because of you it's not your fault
you're not the reason why things are
going wrong there are other things at
hand and that's when we use the light of
God we call upon the angels we learn how
to protect ourselves we finally become
aware and that awareness is powerful
it's
Unstoppable that awareness pushes demons
away helps to conquer demons that
awareness is awareness that God
the angels are aware of as well they
know about the dark Forces they
understand the dark Forces and when you
know too you can finally protect
yourself
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and Alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place a
pure untampered with Advanced Clean
uncorrupted original primary source a
higher source Spirit of compassion