How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William.
We're talking about the spring and how
healing the spring can truly be and even
lifechanging if you know how to utilize
what the spring offers. The sounds of
the peepers peeping in the trees. The
robins as they roll in, land on the
ground, dance around looking for a worm.
The tadpoles, how they swim around the
water and then surface looking for a
gulp of air. And did you know that there
are powers in the spring that help our
bodies heal, especially after a long
winter? And did you know the earthly
mother knows who you are? Because you
were born here on the earthly mother.
Your feet steps on the earthly mother
and she knows everything about you. Get
ready for this one. Fasten those seat
belts because there's a lot to know when
it comes down to your healing. and what
the earth and the spring has to do with
you. It's
springtime. Oh yeah, man. Hey. No. No.
Pull over to here. Yeah. Yeah. The guy's
right
there. Yeah, man. We're here for spring
break. Is there any parking? Oh, yeah.
No, we have our sticker.
Is this beach uh is this the beach
that's next to the other beach that we
want to go to?
Um
okay. Yeah. What's in our
car? Uh
nothing. What's in the cooler? Um
nothing. Uh we we just have soda in the
cooler and some uh
lunch. Okay. Okay. Thank you.
Woo! Phew. Let's park over here,
man. If you're young and you don't have
anything that's really pressing, like a
chronic illness, a mystery disease, a
mystery chronic symptom, something
that's really holding you back,
something that's interfering with your
life. If you're somebody you feel
indestructible and it's time for spring
break and you could just go on the
beach, get a terrible
sunburn, get exposed to all kinds of
different chemicals, drink and consume a
lot of alcohol, get totally shitfaced,
eat hot dogs, hamburgers, cheeseburgers,
fried food. You don't have to worry
about healing. You don't have to try to
heal. You don't have to worry about
getting sick. drinking out of aluminum
cans. They're heating up in the sun.
They're expanding. The liner inside
cracks. All the aluminum's going into
your bloodstream. You're sucking the top
of the can. Aluminum's going in your
mouth. You slather on the worst suntan
lotion on the planet that has anything
from 500 to 700 chemicals. Chemicals
that are terrible for you, toxic, bad
for your organs, your brain, your
bloodstream. You're dowsted in cologne,
dowsed in perfume. You're in your hotel
room. You're using the shower there.
Your feet are on the surface of the
shower. Toenail fungus is everywhere.
Somebody else's fungus from their feet
is everywhere. Gets inside your feet,
inside your toenails. You meet somebody,
you don't care about them. You swap
spit. You're getting their herpes
simplex. You're exposing them to your
herpes simplex. Getting the HPV, you're
exposing them to HPV. Or maybe
somebody's on the edge of monucleiosis.
They got exposure from Epstein bar. You
got Epstein bar and it doesn't matter.
Everybody's having fun. It's spring
break. Nobody needs to heal. Nobody
needs to worry about healing. Maybe down
the road symptoms and conditions develop
and then you're sick and then you're
worried about healing and it's time to
heal and that happens, but for the
moment nobody cares. And that's the
spring for a lot of people. You just
don't care about healing. But if you're
somebody that has a condition, a
symptom, mystery illness, something's
going on in your life, you're working on
your healing process, and maybe you're
somebody that's been sick for 20 years,
10 years, or even a year, you can use
spring to heal. You can use the spring
to move forward and actually catapult
yourself with your healing process.
There are tools in nature and you don't
have to do much. And the earthly mother
provides these tools of nature so we can
utilize them and work on our healing
process. As unforgiving as the earth can
be, as terrible as the earth can be,
nature walking on a path somewhere in
Costa Rica, accidentally stepping on a
fertilance snake, getting bitten, you're
in a shed in South
Carolina, you don't see what's behind
something you're grabbing off the shelf.
There's a black widow spider, a round
body with a red patch underneath its
belly, bites you on the finger. Maybe
you're somebody in Australia. You're
walking down a path near a water basin
or waterway. Crocodile jumps out at you.
Or maybe you're down in Florida and
you're by a pond. An alligator crawls up
really quick, gets you in the foot,
drags you on down into the water. Or you
can be in
Hawaii and there's an area where people
have dared to jump off a cliff into the
ocean. It's a common place people go.
Many people who are really good swimmers
and jumpers and divers take the plunge
and you decide to take that plunge, but
there's an unforgiving wave rolling in
at the wrong time, wrong place, some
kind of upsurge of the ocean and it all
goes wrong. The earthly mother has
endless pitfalls. It has dangerous
areas, dangerous aspects of nature.
Poisonous snakes, poisonous frogs,
poisonous spiders, big grizzly bears,
angry wolves. Also, ice that cracks,
people fall through. Unpredictable forms
of nature everywhere. And then there's
predictable forms of nature, the earthly
mother and her healing powers. So, let's
get down to it. As winter is passing and
spring is coming closer, our bodies know
this. They're aware of this. And so is
the earthly mother. She's aware that
your body is aware of this. So, a
synchronicity occurs. Something inside
of our bodies ignites like a seed.
that's sensing its birth. Like a seed
that's about to sprout. There's energy
involved like the buds that have been
dormant on an apple tree waiting to
swell and burst open and flower. The
buds beginning to burst. All that power
behind it. A healing igniter for the
body is to get that synchronicity to
what's happening in spring. allowing
your body to connect to the earthly
mother and how life just comes to life.
Now, our bodies are alive all year long,
not just during the spring. Our hearts
are beating all year long, every day,
every hour, every minute. But when every
spring comes, we have a little bit of an
extra chance to spark up, to ignite our
healing, to strengthen. Our bodies are
especially in tuned with nature during
the springtime. And it's about making
that connection consciously knowing that
our bodies have this burst of extra
healing at this time of year. Knowing
this alone can make all the difference.
Now, this doesn't mean we don't heal all
different times of the year. The
summertime, the fall, the winter, we do
heal. Our bodies do heal. When we have
chronic illness, every day counts. Every
hour counts, every minute counts. But
the spring offers something a little
different. It offers this ignition that
doesn't happen in other months. Now,
during the winter months, we're not
turtles under the ice and we're not
sleeping bears in their dens. And we're
not bats in their caves. Our bodies are
not truly hibernating. That's not what
it is. And then we're breaking the
hibernation. But at the same time, it
doesn't mean our body systems aren't
tuned in to the sleeping bears and the
sleeping bats and the caves and the
turtles underneath the ice. Our physical
bodies are tuned in. And our physical
bodies are tuned in to the daffodils,
the daisies, the crocuses that are
underneath the snow. And even though our
bodies aren't frozen, they're not frozen
in one place. They're not frozen like
the earth because it was really cold out
through the winter. Our bodies are not
frozen like ice on a lake or a pond or a
river. But yet our bodies are in tune
and know about the frozen. Our bodies
know about the frozen ice, the frozen
earth, the frozen ground we walk on. So
when it all starts changing, all starts
melting, shifting, everything starts to
alter. Our bodies are in tune. But it's
now about getting our consciousness
aligned with our bodies to help it
along, to help that connection along, to
help that synchronicity into spring,
that driving, powerful, energetic,
earthly mother force, and to connect
with that to help your healing process.
Now, it's easy to let spring fly by.
Spring go by really quick, snap of a
finger, in which you don't even see
spring at all. happens to so many
people, more than you think, more than
you know, where they only see spring for
a second or get a whiff of it, a smell
in the air. They're too busy. They got a
lot going on. Springtime can fly by so
fast it happened yesterday. And what
does that mean for our bodies? Does that
mean our bodies had a burst of healing?
A healing ignition occurred? that
magical incredible strength of spring
went through you and you had this
healing. Not necessarily. You might have
had a little bit. There might have been
some there that you weren't aware of.
But it's that connection. It's making
that conscious connection to spring and
really absorbing it and seeing it for
what it is. Making that connection to
the earthly mother that really sparks
that healing, really creates that
ignition. It's not just living your life
and it magically happens. You'll get
some of it. You'll get some of spring's
power. You'll get some of what spring
has to offer if you're not paying
attention at all and you're just going
through life super busy doing your
thing. You'll get a spark, but nothing
like you can get when you're focused,
when you know what's happening, when you
utilize nature in a certain way, when
you really absorb spring. So, how do we
make the best of spring to ignite our
healing process? Let's start with the
first thing. Being aware, being
conscious when the trees wake up. Being
there when the trees wake up. It could
just be one tree somewhere in your yard
or near your apartment or in the park
and you see it. Watching the buds swell
and seeing the leaves come out. Not
just, ooh, I saw a tree. A month later,
oh, the leaves are out, seeing the
process, witnessing it, being aware of
it, connecting to it. And if you have
the ability to touch a branch, to walk
over to a tree with lowhanging branches
that are in this early stage, or a shrub
or a bush of some kind because you can't
reach a branch, go ahead and do that.
Grab onto that branch. Feel those buds.
See those leaves starting to form. And
do it intermittently. Do it once a day.
Do it once every three days. Be a part
of it. Be a part of the trees process.
And if this is all you can do out of all
the different tools, it's powerful and
it's that helpful. Making that
connection alone can ignite healing
because your body wants to heal,
especially in the spring. Now keep in
mind that the earthly mother knows your
every step. So when you walk on the
earth, every single footprint, every
step you make, the earthly mother is
wise to it, understands it, knows you're
on her earth. The earthly mother is
aware of you. And you don't have to be
barefoot for the earthly mother to know
who you are, to know your energy, to
know your life force. These healing
tools work whether you're wearing boots,
sneakers, sandals, flip flops, or
anything else that you wear on your
feet. This isn't about the grounding
theory where you have to be barefoot on
the earth and that heals you or grounds
you. This is far more advanced than
that. This supersedes that. You can have
anything on your feet and it won't
matter. This is about your hands, your
eyes, and your consciousness. And your
physical body, its ignition to spring
and propelling it forward into healing.
And this works if you're on mattress
island. And this works if you're in the
house and looking out the window. This
works if you're in your apartment and
looking out the window or from a
hospital room and looking out the
window. the powerful aspect of spring
and what it does for the healing happens
and you don't even have to be outside on
the earth or walking or walking to a
tree or even touching a tree. You can do
the process and touch the branches and
see it and it's powerful. But the power
in this is also just being aware, having
that conscious connection and having
that knowing that it is the spring and
your body feels it and sees it just like
a bunch of tadpoles that are teeming in
life in a little bit of water. So
connecting to a tree that's waking up
during the springtime is one of the most
powerful tools. And being able to walk
across the yard or the earth or a park
or the ground somewhere up to a shrub or
a tree or a bush and holding on to that
stem, that branch helps to awaken,
creating that
ignition, that springtime healing that
our bodies have been waiting for all
year. Watching the trees leaf out at all
the different stages is profound,
powerful healing tool. all on its own.
Being aware, being in the moment, seeing
it happen, watching the different stages
and the different colors of the leaves,
seeing the colors be red and pink,
eventually light green and then dark
green. All the different stages of
colors that the leaves create have a
truly profound effect not only on the
body, the physical body and the healing
and the ignition, but also on the mind,
the consciousness and for mental health,
strengthening mental health. And as you
watch each stage, each phase of the
leaves forming, changing colors, getting
larger, growing, you're reducing PTSD.
You're reducing old wounds, injuries,
stress, problems that have happened in
your life, betrayal, losses, struggles
start to diminish. At least the injuries
involved from those are starting to
diminish. You're replacing bad thoughts,
bad memories, bad situations,
confrontation. You're replacing it with
things from the earthly mother that help
us heal, change our frequency. alter our
state of being, our state of mind.
People with PTSD and OCD can benefit
greatly from this process alone of what
spring has to offer. When trees awaken
in the spring, they're at their
strongest point. Connect with that and
know that you're at your strongest
point. Even if you're chronically sick
or you've been through so much or your
symptoms feel daunting and pressing and
very hard to live with and you're
struggling, see yourself at your
strongest point. It's spring and you're
at your strongest point just like those
trees are. So now let's talk about the
birds a little bit. Maybe you have
robins come by where you live on the
planet and maybe you don't and you have
another bird
But if there's another bird and it's
springtime and those birds are coming
through, think about them when I talk
about the robins. When the robins come
to town, you know it's
springtime. Sometimes the robins come a
little bit earlier. Sometimes they come
what seems to be a little bit later. And
sometimes they come in packs. They come
really early and then they come a little
later. Seeing a robin can be a spiritual
experience. It is a spiritual
experience. Seeing a robin can be a
religious experience and can be a
powerful rewiring tool. But keep in
mind, you could see something but still
be blind. Your eyes can be open, but you
can be blind to see. And that happens in
the springtime. Not because somebody's a
bad person, not because they don't want
to see something, because life just runs
us down and it runs us ragged and it
keeps us busy and we're battling all
kinds of different battles. We're moving
along. We're trying to work. we're
trying to live and watching a robin and
really seeing that robin and seeing what
it's doing and understanding that robin
and understanding how spring and the
robin connect to you is just something
that may not be possible for so many.
But if you have the opportunity and you
do see a robin for what it is and feel
that spiritual connection, it could be
lifealtering, especially during a
springtime healing process. The robins
roll in and you'll notice they're very
happy. You can see it. There's joy in
that robin. There's joy on the robin's
face if you can just catch a glimpse.
They hop around on the ground. They're
looking for food. Sure, survival, but at
the same time, they're living their
life. They're happy doing it. They have
energy. In fact, they're at their most
powerful in this moment. They know it's
spring. And that means everything to the
robin. A robin exhibits freedom. Try to
get a hold of that. Grab a hold of that.
When you're sitting there and you're
watching that robin dance around, move
around, look for a worm, having that joy
in its heart. Yes, joy in its heart.
Connect to that. Connect to the freedom
the robin has. And when you do, then
your eyes are open and you can see your
body can start increasing its healing
abilities, its healing powers. The
ignition occurs. This is all part of the
springtime healing ignition. Your
ability to increase your healing during
the spring. Since we're talking about
the robins, let's talk about the
earthworms. Have you ever walked through
a park in the morning or through a
grassy yard or a grassy null and saw
these little tiny piles, like little
tiny volcanoes, but they're not
volcanoes. Little tiny piles of dirt.
They're just sitting there and you see a
lot of them. You see one here, one
there, one here, one there. Looks like
fresh dirt that was pushed to the
surface. And you see these in the spring
mostly. Sometimes in the fall, too, but
you see them mostly in the spring. These
are the nightcrawlers, the earthworms.
They were asleep all winter as well,
frozen in a deep state. And then as the
ground defrosted, they came to life and
they started to get active. And this is
during their mating season. If you came
out with a flashlight in the early hours
of the morning on just the right week or
the right morning, just the right time
in spring, and you turn that flashlight
on in a park or a yard or an old
baseball field somewhere or some type of
grassy null, you'll see all the
nightcrawlers out. They're going to be
on top of the ground. And these
nightcrawlers are a delicacy for the
robins. The robins try to get there
early enough before the night crawlers
before the earthworms go back into the
earth. And they're quick when they go
back into the earth. It's hard to catch
them. They're fast. Just like when
you're walking on the earth, the earthly
mother detects you, can feel you, knows
who you are. Just like the earthly
mother knows the nightcrawlers, she can
feel them crawl through the earth. They
are a sign of the spring. And those
earthworms, those nightcrawlers are in
full power. They have the most strength.
They're like an early chute coming out
of the ground, an early sprout coming
up. They're like a plant that's just
starting to bud. They're like a tree
that's just starting to bud. The
strength is in that earthworm at that
moment. the most strength. It's
springtime strength. The earthworm has
been waiting all winter for this moment.
And if you take a walk and you see these
little mounds of dirt, these little
hills of dirt, the size of a quarter,
size of a half dollar, the size of a
dime, and you just look at them, it
helps to ignite healing inside the body.
And if you kneel down to the ground and
you take your hand and your fingers and
you touch the dirt that's on the surface
where those worms came up and then went
back into the earth and you touch that
dirt and you feel it with your fingers.
It's going to be very rich soil,
extremely rich. And you can sense it and
you can feel it with your fingers. And
that connection right there alone does
something in the body. Energy that's in
that dirt is fresh from those powerful
earthworms. And that energy vibrates
through the hand and into the body. Our
bodies sense everything spring. And this
alone, if given the chance to do this,
is a powerful healing ignition. And our
body systems can sense this energy and
take it in, absorb it fast. And
grounding occurs holding that little bit
of soil that came from the worm that
came up from the worm. That very little
bit of soil in between your fingers or
placed into the palm of your hand can
ground you more than walking barefoot in
the grass during the middle of the
summer. If you ever get a chance, you
can try this healing tool. So, let's
talk about the peepers. The spring
peepers. Those sounds you hear during
the springtime. Maybe you're somewhere
on the planet and you're not near a lot
of peepers. Or maybe you hear a peeper,
but you never knew it was a peeper.
Maybe you heard a sound and you didn't
know it was a tiny tiny tree frog or
even a bush frog. But they're out there
and they make their noise, especially
during the spring. Spring peepers tend
to get louder right before it starts to
rain or begins to rain. Sometimes you
hear them at night, sometimes you hear
them at dusk, sometimes you hear them at
dawn. It all depends on where you are.
But peepers tend to squeak the loudest
when it's spring. They're the happiest
when it's spring. They've been waiting
all winter long. When springtime comes
and they spring to life, they have an
energy. They have a sound. And that
sound goes into your ears. It vibrates
throughout your body. That sound is a
spring healing sound. If you choose it
to be, if you partake in the peeper
sounds, those spring peeper sounds are
parts of a spring's fleeting moments.
The frequency to a peeper is similar to
a cricket, though not the same thing,
and they do slightly different things
when it comes down to the healing
process. The peeper is the spring. The
cricket is the fall. It's a very healing
sound the cricket makes. I've talked
about it before. I'm going to talk about
it again. But the peeper is the spring
and that frequency resonates to every
single neuron and brain cell,
neurotransmitter, electrical impulses,
gal cells, cranial nerves, and the brain
stem. And when the spring peepers
release this frequency, when they emit
this sound and this noise, that sound
and noise has spring power behind it and
refreshes the mind, the consciousness
and helps to restore thought. If you're
somebody and you're walking on a trail
or you're walking in your yard or you're
somewhere outside walking down a
sidewalk of a street and it's around
dawn and you hear the spring peepers and
it's springtime, they will keep peeping.
They will. Unless you get so close to
them that they think they're in danger
where you're a foot away and you're
about to hit the branch, they'll stop
peeping. But for the most part, they
will keep on making their spring peeping
noises. But if you were an alien from
another planet, a Sasquatch or a bear or
some other creature that was placed on
this earth by aliens, the peeper will
stop peeping. Instantly stop peeping and
all will be quiet. The frequency that
admits from peepers. The noise, the
sound resonates to the human body. It
resonates to the human consciousness.
And peepers know this. It's been
instilled in the peeper from the
beginning. And the earthly mother knows
this as well. The frequency and the
sound of a peeper during the spring is
extremely healing to the mind and body
of a human being. Let's move on to the
next tool. Spring air. The air, the air
we breathe. When you step outside and
you take a deep breath and you can smell
that spring air. Now, when you think
about it, sure, everybody smells that
air because they breathe that air. It's
the spring. So, that's a tool. That's a
tool where everybody's walking around
and it's springtime and they're
breathing that air so it works. It's not
how it works. There's something
different about that air when you're
breathing it in as a tool, as a therapy.
It's not about breath work. It's about
knowing what you're smelling. It's about
identifying spring in that air with
every breath. When you breathe in
through your nose, you can smell the
air. You can smell the sun hitting the
earth. You can smell the birds making a
nest. Early enough in spring, you can
smell the ice melting on the rivers. You
can smell flowers blossoming. You can
smell the grass sprouting up. You can
smell the decaying leaves from the fall
working its way into the earth. And most
people focus on pollen because they got
allergies. They're pollen sensitive. So,
they're worried about the pollen in the
spring. And the springtime is their
greatest hell for that reason. But as
bad as pollen can irritate a lot of
people, it's also healing. Pollen is a
powerful healing tool on the body. When
we breathe it in, even if we're
sensitive and have allergies to pollen,
it's causing problems. It's also helping
us heal. It's igniting a healing, a deep
healing. At the same time, anytime we
breathe in pollen, we gain strength in
other areas of the body. Our life force
strengthens. Even if our sinuses don't
feel like they are or our ears and
sinuses feel clogged up or our nose is
running or we have headaches from it,
our internal life force, the life force
of our human body, our existence, our
physical existence, strengthens as we're
breathing in the pollen. So, as much as
it feels like the pollen is hurting us,
it's strengthening our life force, our
internal life force. And when we have
pollen problems, it's usually a reminder
that something else is wrong. It's a
pointer because pollen is a natural
earthly occurrence. It's nature. But
it's nature that's not supposed to make
us sick. We're not supposed to be
irritable. We're not supposed to get
inflamed. We're not supposed to have
congestion because of it. We're not
supposed to have an allergic reaction to
pollen. But yet so many do because the
pollen is a healer. It's pointing out
problems. It's a problem finder. So that
means there's other things going on like
allergies to dairy, allergies to eggs,
allergies to other foods that aren't
good for someone that are creating a
mucous barrier. And that mucus barrier
gets triggered by the healing properties
of breathing in pollen. But overall,
when you're aware of it and you know
you're breathing in pollen, you're
smelling pollen from the trees, the
flowers, the springtime, it is a healer.
It is an igniter. When springtime comes
and everything is sprouting out there,
everything is budding, everything is
rebirthing, everything is
awakening, our body starts to do the
same thing. So if we're sick with
chronic illness, disease, if we have
symptoms, aches and pains and tingles
and numbness, dizziness, ringing in the
ears, popping in the ears, vertigo,
tremors, ticks, spasms, bad migraines,
skin conditions, eczema, psoriasis,
dermatitis, vitiligo, back pain, leg
pain, restless leg syndrome, feet pain,
neck pain, constant reoccurring
infection, UTI, kidney infections,
bladder infections, severe chronic
fatigue syndrome, chronic fatigue, brain
fog, and any kind of autoimmune
condition, and hundreds of other
symptoms. The spring is not your enemy.
The spring is your friend. And the
spring offers something very powerful to
help you rebirth, to help you heal. It's
in addition to all the other good things
you're doing. You could be somebody and
you're doing some great things for your
health. You're eating good. You're
taking care of yourself. You want to get
better. You want to improve. And the
springtime gives us that lift. It
increases our chances and possibilities
to heal quicker. And in order to do
that, we got to catch the wave. We got
to catch the spring wave. We have to
feel it. We have to sense it. We have to
see it. We have to partake in it. and we
can't let it slip by because we're too
busy and it's gone. Our blood resonates
to a stream that's melting and becoming
alive again and teeming with life. And
our skin resonates to the rain hitting
rocks and boulders and dripping off of
them. And our organs resonate and
connect to buds bursting on branches and
flowers blooming. a rebirththing for all
the plants coming up from the earth and
the grass. Our organs are rebirthing new
cells. Cells that are dying, cells that
are restoring and rebirththing. And our
endocrine systems resonate to the sun's
shifting, getting higher up in the sky
and that changing light. All of this
says spring is here. All of this says
your body can heal. All of this is
connected to the earthly mother and your
body surviving and thriving and
revitalizing. If you're somebody with a
pollen allergy, check out medical medium
information. Go to medicaldium.com.
Check out the medical medium book
series. Learn how to do the cleanses.
Take the cleanses to your doctor. Ask
your doctor what's right for you. Can do
the 369, the 28day cleanse, and check
out the various tools in the books.
They're really helpful and the
protocols. Check out
medicalmemedium.com. Also, check out
Telegram where I do exclusive messages
there. And remember, medicalmeium
information is free. You can get lots of
that information. Use it, utilize it,
work on your healing process like so
many other people have. And remember,
more people healed with medical medium
information than any other healing arts,
healing modality, or anything else in
the health world. And if you get a
chance, check out Angels, Demons, and
Spiritual Tools. You can find it at
Amazon, Audible, Spotify, or Apple. Many
blessings, and God bless
you, man. Spring break is amazing. I
worked so hard this semester, man. Oh,
man. Hey, can you grab me another beer
out of the cooler? Wow, look at this.
The beach is so nice. Oh, wait. Look
out, sir. What's in the cooler? Open the
cooler, please. Sir, open the cooler. I
don't have nothing in here, man. I'm not
doing anything. I just got a sandwich
and some sodas. I'm not littering or
doing anything. Sir, open up the cooler
now. It's time to heal. Time to move
forward. My body can. The springtime
will push this and move me forward. I
know I can do this. It just takes a
helping
hand. The spring is here. I feel my
healing is
near. I thought I saw a
deer out the window out there. It will
be
okay. I know I'm healing
anyway. I'm not straying. I'm on a wave.
I'm not complaining.
I know in due time I will be
strong. I will be
fine. I can
see the earthly mother is looking out
for me. I can hear all her
sounds. They're out
there. Let me grab a chair, sit
outside, smell the air. I'm aware that
spring be thy
healer. God is my maker. God knows I've
had it hard and have been shaken along
the way, but I'm not weak. God knows
there's nothing that will break me. And
the earthly mothers created spring. And
God won't forsake me. Feel it in your
blood. Don't lose touch.
Spring is in everyone's neighborhood.
And remember this, spring is a tool and
nothing's going to stop you from
healing. It's a tool that's there for
the taking. And there's an ancient
connection you have with the spring.
lifetimes ago, many lifetimes before
this new rain, before this new spring.
Your eyes are open, your heart is
beating, your body is connecting to God
and the earthly mother springing. You
can heal to spring in all springs. Your
body and soul will be singing.
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite. only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back, and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.