How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William.
We're talking about healing and spring
can help with that. Spring has a lot to
offer when you pay attention and you see
it for what it's worth. When you feel it
and you involve yourself in it in any
capacity, spring can help you heal. It
can ignite healing. And spring has
profound rewiring effects. Spring has
the power to inject metaphysical
information into the emotional centers
of the brain. Spring is a mental,
emotional, and spiritual clearing tool.
So, how do we go about using spring to
help us heal? And just like the last two
spring episodes that you might have
heard already, we're on to the third.
It's a medical medium spring series.
Find yourself a comfortable place out
there in a yard, in a park, in a field,
on a porch, and let's do some spring
healing. One of the things I love about
spring is the noises, the
sounds. Life is coming back. As of now,
just sitting here, I hear woodpeckers. I
hear various birds. I hear the wind
blowing. I hear
chirping. I hear dogs barking in the
distance. Everybody's excited about
spring. And what I'm noticing is, I hope
the same thing you're noticing. I'm
starting to feel it, hear it, sense it.
As I'm in it, as I'm sitting in it right
now, I'm sitting on the grass and I'm
looking at everything. I'm looking at
bushes, shrubs.
I'm looking at brand new leaves. I'm
looking at the grass that's coming out
of the ground. It looks vibrant. Looks
alive. It looks fresh. It doesn't look
wasted and dehydrated. It looks plump.
It looks vital. I'm looking at the
breeze, how it's going through the
trees, how it's moving leaves
everywhere, brand new leaves, how it's
moving the grass, the blades of
grass. I just saw a bird that's flying
in the wind. I see the wind carrying
it. It had a stick in its mouth. It
looks like it's going to make a nest.
I'm becoming part of spring. on becoming
one with it. And getting spring to heal
you, to help you emotionally,
spiritually, mentally, and physically.
To help your body heal is to become one
with it. It's to become part of it. It's
to be a part of the spring in it. To use
spring to heal, you have to see it,
partake in it. You have to feel it. You
have to smell it. You have to hear it.
And if you can't get outside, that's
okay because you can still sit inside
the house, crack a window, and hear it
from there. You can still smell the air
as it enters in through a window or a
doorway. You can still see the grass on
the ground from a window. And it's still
spring and you're still part of it. And
that's the point. You just have to be
part of it. Now, there's a lot of things
you can do in the spring. You can set up
a garden, start digging, planting seeds.
Can take a walk on the beach if you're
near one. Can take a walk by a lake if
you're near one. You can take a walk
down a path. You can go ride your
bicycle. You can go on a trail in the
woods. You could go and do a lot of
things in the spring, but that's keeping
busy. All those things have healing
powers. All those things are good for
the soul. And someday we'll go through
each and every one of them. But right
now, it's different. It's about not
doing something. It's about not being
busy. It's about instead seeing the
spring and being a part of it, becoming
it. And not just being busy doing
something spring related, instead
becoming spring for a moment. You can be
busy in your garden. You can be digging
holes and digging dirt, planting seeds.
You can be focused on watering those
seeds. But you're actively being busy.
It's powerful. It's
healing. But we're talking about
becoming one with spring. Shutting
things down for a moment. Sitting there
listening, smelling the air, focused on
the little things about spring that are
really huge and they're actually big
things. By not being actively busy while
you're sitting there and taking in the
spring, you're allowing something to
happen, a release. You're allowing
emotions to surface because you're not
pushing them down. You're not doing
something to push them down. You're not
doing something to keep so busy that you
can't feel those emotions and that
everything stays suppressed, stays
depressed. You're allowing an avenue to
open. You're allowing things to surface
and sit there so they can leave. You're
allowing the toxic emotions, hardships,
experiences, the imprints to surface,
leave, and
dissipate to get grown over and mulched
up. When you're sitting there with the
spring and you're just listening and
smelling the air and sensing everything
and seeing everything, you're not trying
to stuff anything down.
You're not trying to push anything down.
Fear and guilt and shame can surface and
then leave. It can fly away like a
butterfly. A
butterfly can hedge your
way. And as it's
leaving, so can your fear, guilt, and
shame, or anything else that's bothering
you, anything toxic that's inside of
you, any kind of pain and suffering on
an emotional level, any kind of PTSD,
see it lift off of you. See it leave you
as you're sitting there
still. See a
butterfly take it away as it flies by.
Springtime is the great
absorber. It absorbs everything.
Everything you see around you is
thriving. It's hungry. It's thirsty. The
grass is not going dormant. It's not
dying. Instead, it's thriving and it's
thirsty. Hungry and it's growing. See
your body like the grass. It's not
dormant. It's not dying. It's thriving.
It's hungry. It's thirsty.
It wants to live. All the leftovers from
the year, from the winter, from the fall
are being utilized. Nothing is being
wasted. You have to see your body like
that. All toxins, all toxic emotions,
old imprints, old wounds are being
absorbed. Your body's hungry like the
spring. It's hungry like the grass and
the bushes and the shrubs and the birds
and the butterflies. It eats up all the
waste. It utilizes
everything. As you're sitting there with
spring around you, it's bursting. It's
alive. It's growing over everything that
was old. Just like the old grass and the
old leaves and the old sticks and the
old herbs are being grown over.
Everything from last year is one step
closer from being absorbed,
disappearing, dissipating. As you're
sitting there, think about how spring
can do this. And think about how spring
can do this for you. Toxic emotions,
spiritual confusion, losses, hardships,
any kind of letdowns, betrayal, trust
wounds, spring is absorbing them a
little bit at a time, bit by bit. Every
single bird chirp, every part of a
breeze, every squirrel that moves, every
leaf that rustles in the wind, every bee
that wakes up and zips by, every
caterpillar that's walking. There are
sounds everywhere. Some sounds you can
hear and some sounds you can't hear. And
even if you can't hear the sound, it
doesn't mean it's not working for you.
There is life happening underground.
There are moles moving. There are
woodchucks and groundhogs. There are
earthworms crawling underneath the soil.
There are bunny rabbits nestled down in
their nest. There are peepers in the
trees. There's toads and frogs in the
grass. And there's hawks flying high in
the sky and owls in the trees. All of
this is awakening and moving around you
while you're sitting there. And the
spring is attaching to the old emotions
that were stuck all winter inside of
you, to toxic injuries and wounds that
have resided inside of you. The spring
is consuming it all. Now, if you get a
moment, take a deep
breath. Can you smell the air? Do you
smell any wild flowers? In the spring,
there are small wild flowers popping out
everywhere. With your eyes closed, what
do you hear?
Are you honing in on any
birds, any spring
sounds, any leaves rustling.
Every sound that you hear produced by
spring is
healing physically, emotionally,
spiritually,
mentally. Thoughts don't own you. Spring
is in
control. Spring is connected to you.
You're becoming one with
spring. The healing is occurring right
now.
When you devote your time and energy
into spring, spring sees you and hears
you. The earthly mother spring hears
your
heartbeat. Here's the blood coursing
through your veins and arteries. Here's
your stomach gurgle and your digestion
process functioning. your eyelids
blinking and even your sinus cavities
moving. Take a deep
breath. And as you release that breath,
think about you being connected to
spring. Spring being connected to you
and all the healing that's occurring.
Now you can repeat this exercise anytime
out here in spring, out here in your
yard, out here in the park, on a grassy
null, on a hill, on your porch or inside
your house even. Keep in mind there's
different levels of spring, different
phases of spring, different time
periods. There's really early spring,
there's mid-spring, there's later
spring, and many different phases of
spring in between those three phases.
Look out for the wild flowers. Take a
close look at them when you see them.
Look out for the first butterflies of
the season. They happen in the spring,
late spring. And look out for the bees
and the bumblebees, the honeybees. Stare
at them while they're on the flowers.
Keep in mind that spring changes by the
hour. It changes by the day and by the
week. The sounds are going to be
different. The smells are going to be
different. But there's one thing that's
not
different. It's spring always ignites
healing. Always helps us heal
emotionally, spiritually, physically,
and mentally. When you get a chance, you
can listen to all three of these spring
episodes and repeat them
anytime. For more free information, you
can go to
medicalmemedium.com. And please take
care. Many blessings and God bless
you. It's spring. Yes, it is. It's
spring. Did you hear that? There's a
bird about to sing. A bee, a wild
flower. It's changing by the hour. A
butterfly just floated
by. Dear God.
Dear
God, do you think spring's
holy? What would you say to someone who
thought spring was in their way and
thought spring created nothing but bad
days? As I stand here on the lawn, I
feel like something's under my feet. I
think it was a molly. Oh, mole. Oh, mole
down in the earth. It's springtime. Time
to rebirth. The ground seems sound. All
the birds are all around. Oh god. Oh
god. Do the angels treasure spring? Or
is it something that doesn't mean
anything? And where are the
grasshoppers? Oh, that's right. It's
spring, not late summer when the
lightning bugs come out at night and
shine so bright. And the grasshoppers
hop all day, hop around. all happy
because spring was their birthday. When
you involve yourself in spring and take
it all in, a lot of healing can happen
deep within. Angels, angels from above.
Do you soar on the wind? Do you help a
spring animal when you can? Do you help
a possum, a raccoon, a bobcat, a fox, a
turtle, a bunny? When they get in
trouble, do you help them? And when you
do, do they think it's funny? When
spring rain comes our way, the
sunshine comes on another day.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical Medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
medical medium podcast, books, or
medical medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.