How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them.
Whether you're dealing with anxiety,
depression, endometriosis, acne, eczema,
autoimmune, thyroid, lime, brain fog,
fatigue, or any other symptom or
condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William.
We're talking about breaking twigs, a
powerful therapy, something that's
life-changing and even lifealtering in
so many ways. A powerful rewiring tool
that Spirit of Compassion brought to my
attention since I was a child. Now, this
spiritual healing therapy I talked about
a little bit in one of the spring
episodes, but like many of the spiritual
tools from Spirit of Compassion, this
one deserves its own episode. Get ready
and be prepared for this one. Get
yourself outside. It's springtime and
you can do this any time of year. Could
be spring, winter, fall, summer. Gather
up a bunch of tiny twigs. They could be
nice and small, thin, anything you think
you can break between your fingertips.
We're going to talk about how to do
this, what the powerful healing
mechanisms are within it. Get yourself a
spot outside. Relax. This powerful
healing spiritual tool and meditation is
life-changing. I'm so excited. I can't
wait for you to experience it. I'm
getting myself in a nice good spot right
now and let's get
started. So, I'm sitting outside right
now and it's springtime. I just saw a
baby squirrel run across the lawn. I
hear the
birds. Beautiful sounds of spring. So,
now I'm going to get up and take a walk.
And I'm going to look for the right
twigs. You don't want the twigs too
thick. You don't want them where you
can't snap them. You don't want them
where it hurts to snap them. You don't
want twigs and sticks really tough,
really thick, where you're hurting your
hands or your wrists, or you're
struggling or straining to snap the
twigs. It's not about taking big sticks
and breaking them in half on your knee
or breaking them in half with all your
strength and all your might. That's not
what this powerful exercise and healing
spiritual tool is. You want to look for
the smaller twigs, the ones that are
nimble, the ones that can break easy.
Sometimes so easy you can snap them with
just your thumbnail, just your fingers.
because it's not about using strength.
It's not about using all your
might. It's about barely using any of
that at all. So, I see some nice twigs
now on the ground right in the grass.
And I'm going to just bend over here and
pick them up. Now, depending on what
kind of trees you have or what kind of
shrubbery because you can get twigs off
of shrubbery, too. And you're not
looking for new ones. You're looking for
old ones that have fallen. Maybe last
year in the fall they fell. Maybe they
fell the year before. Maybe birds
dropped them along the way. And keep in
mind that you're not trying to snap
living twigs off of shrubs and bushes
and trees. You're looking for twigs of
yester year of last year. Twigs that can
easily break and they're scattered
about. Sometimes a little hard to find
depending on where you are and sometimes
really easy. and many are there and
available. So, I'm walking around and
I'm looking for my twigs and sticks. So,
here I go. Now, some can be really
skinny skinny twigs, like really thin,
like eighth of an inch
diameter. If you go into like quarter of
an inch, half an inch, keep in mind that
you want to make sure you can break
them. You want to break them easily with
your thumbnails, your fingers. So, I'm
grabbing twigs and sticks. If I find
something that's a/ an inch
diameter, I'm making sure that it's
dead, you know, and it's doesn't have
any leftover juice in it from last year
or years before. And you can tell, you
know, it's a twig. You know, it's going
to break pretty easy. Now, you don't
have to count how many twigs. You can
just get a pile. But often I do like
numbers to a certain point only because
spirit of compassion gives me inside
information, wisdom about numbers that's
not out there. Like information about
the number nine that hasn't been ever
talked about by numerologists and so
forth and spiritualists, but I like to
kind of like add up the sticks. So I'm
counting them now. I'm on my fifth
stick, sixth stick, seven, eighth stick,
nine twig, 10 twig, 11 twig. And I'm
going to probably land on 18, which is a
nine, one and eight or a nine. But like
I said before, you can just grab a pile
of sticks and twigs. And you don't have
to have a number associated with any of
it. But as I'm going along, I see other
twigs I like. So I'm going to keep on
adding them to my bunch of twigs right
here. So, you got 19 20 21 22 23
24 25. Here's a nice one right here. 26.
And let me go over here. 27. I'm going
to stop at 27. Once again, I like that
number because two and seven are nine.
So, I'm going to hold that. And I have a
nice pile of
[Music]
twigs. Okay. So, I'm sitting back down.
I got my pile of twigs. I'm getting
ready. I'm getting in the frame of mind.
I'm listening to the birds and the
hawks and the
geese. And now I'm going to get ready
and start this powerful transformational
tool, this spiritual meditation and
therapy. So, I'm sitting down in the
grass right now and you can sit
anywhere. You could sit on a porch. You
could even be inside a house if that's
where you have to be and you have your
pile of twigs. I'm in the grass right
now. I'm outside and I have my first
twig. Do you have yours? Now, what you
don't want to do is just snap the twig
in
half. Instead, you want to snap little
pieces off the twig. You can even keep
them intact after you snap them. The
skin of the twig, the bark, will hold on
to them, but you can also separate them
as well when you snap them. Each snap
can be as close together to the last
snap. They can be as close as a quarter
inch apart or even less depending on the
twig. And you can do it with your
thumbnail. But it's okay if it's not
that close and they're a little further
apart. Half an inch, 3/4 of an inch, or
an inch. That's fine, too. So, let's
start the snapping.
Did you hear the sound of my twig
snapping or your twig
snapping? Did you really listen to the
sound? So, when we do another one, try
to listen to each snap, each click, each
break of the twig. So, I'm grabbing
another twig. And here we go.
Now, you can do any speed you like. You
can do it fast, you can do it slower,
you can have the little twig pieces
dropping all over the place, and you can
go at your own pace. Here's a faster
one.
So let's talk about for the moment of
what it does. Every single break of that
twig, every single snap of that twig
that you hear enters your consciousness
and your subconsciousness. It enters
your mind. It enters the soul.
The snapping and breaking of twigs has
happened thousands and thousands and
hundreds of thousands of times in your
life, long before this lifetime. And if
your soul is really
old, 1,000 years, 2,000 years, 3,000,
4,000 years, or more, then you have
heard the snapping twigs throughout all
those lifetimes for many different
reasons and for many different ways. And
your soul harbors that information deep
within of every single twig that was
snapped. Whether it was for kindling for
firewood or thousands of years ago you
were gathering up sticks to start a fire
to keep warm. Or maybe it was so many
journeys through the woods thousands of
years ago and your soul has the
information of you stepping on twigs
everywhere and they were breaking and
snapping. And maybe it was for
protection reasons. You were in a camp a
long long time ago in a past life or in
a
village and there was a
campfire and there was an animal on the
outside of the camp walking along and it
stepped on twigs and snapped
them. But you've heard that sound before
and maybe in this lifetime you've heard
that sound before.
But what this therapy does, what this
spiritual tool does is it
rewires. It rewires the consciousness,
the subconsciousness, the brain. It
rewires the
soul. It fills the soul. Those sounds of
those twigs snapping is a cleansing
mechanism, a clearing mechanism that
improves mental
wellness, mental
health, mental sharpness. The
combination of feeling the twig in your
hand and interacting with nature on this
level has imprint removing powers.
imprint from negative experience,
imprint from problems that have happened
in the past, imprints from all kinds of
different betrayal, hardships, and
losses. So, the next round of twigs we
snap, we're going to be thinking about
the noises entering into our soul, into
our
consciousness, into our body, into our
physical cells of our body.
So, let's start with the physical
body. Get a twig in your
hand and let's start snapping each
piece.
The noise coming from the broken twig
and the little
snaps are entering into the cells of
your body. There's a frequency to each
snap. That
sound easily enters into our being, our
physical being, our organs.
our
brain, our liver, our pancreas, our
spleen. And each snap of the twig enters
into our neurons. Our electrical
impulses are picking up on it. They're
receiving information. They're sending
that information to each neuron
throughout the
brain. The spiritual therapeutic
technique enters into the physical body
easily. And you can feel the sound of
the twig snapping each time you snap
each piece. You hear the sound, but you
can feel the sound, too. And when your
fingers are holding it and it's snapping
within your fingers, it's also sending a
frequency through your hands, through
your arms, into your body all the way
through. This is a resetter. It resets
whatever's happening in your body
physically. Whatever frequency or energy
you picked up, you're resetting that
energy. You're bringing it back to a
natural state. You're using nature to
set the frequency. And each snap of each
twig sets a new frequency within a cell,
helps to reset it.
Now, twig snapping is so powerful that
even if you're not thinking about
anything, anything at all. You're not
thinking about frequencies. You're not
thinking about the soul. You're not
thinking about your physical body.
You're just sitting there and you're
snapping twigs and doing that alone. It
is life-changing, lifealtering. So, if
you're just sitting there in the grass
or on the porch and you're not thinking
about anything at all, you're just
snapping twigs and focused on the twigs
themselves and what you're hearing and
what you're feeling. If you're somebody
that had a hard night or you had a hard
day or you had a confrontation with
someone or something was just a let down
or you're just emotionally depressed,
sad, maybe feeling a little numb, maybe
you're battling some
depersonalization and you sit down and
you start snapping these twigs, it can
begin to break the triggers. What that
means is that whatever triggered you and
is still stuck triggering you and you're
still feeling it or the after effects of
a trigger, what the twig snapping does
is it breaks that trigger. It's a
trigger buster. It breaks the trigger.
Triggers tend to stick. They don't go
away instantly. You can get triggered by
something and then it stays there like a
stinger from a bee just staying in the
wound. So, with each snap of the twig,
of the stick, you're snapping a trigger.
You're breaking a trigger. Down here in
planet Earth, we often get affected by
toxic things. Not just toxic substances
and exposures that are physical toxins,
but emotional toxins from other people,
from negativity, from stuff they're
exuding, they're projecting, and they're
releasing releasing into the air around
you, releasing to you, directing it to
you. It's a very toxic place for many
reasons cuz people are very toxic out
there. twig snapping and breaking can
shift the triggers that occur from these
toxins, these variety of different toxic
energies. Spirit of compassion always
told me that you could use twig snapping
as a means of
communication. So, if you're sitting
with someone and you're talking to them,
you can snap little twigs while you're
talking to them. Now, keep in mind, it's
not like grabbing big sticks and
breaking them while you're with someone
or you're sitting there trying to break
a big stick on your knee or you got a
big stick and you're trying to use all
your might to break it or snap it.
You're taking these little tiny twigs,
sometimes so small and so thin, they
break with a very light noise. So you
can do it with your thumbnail and go
across it every eighth of an inch to a
quarter of an inch while you're
communicating with someone, while you're
talking to someone. And if you're
somebody that's really sensitive,
emotionally sensitive, you've been
through a lot, this is a way to keep you
strong while you're having a
conversation with someone. This can help
stop a trigger or a trigger reaction
while you're listening to what someone
has to say. If the person that you're
talking to happens to catch on or
they're wondering what you're doing or
they mention it and they see the little
sticks in your hands or the little twigs
and they're even hearing them snap cuz
some could be a little louder. Then hand
them a bunch of twigs. Have them do it
too. Offer this technique to them so
while you're having a conversation with
them, they're doing it as well. And
you'll watch how their demeanor
shifts. Maybe even some angst that they
have or anguish or something that's
happening inside of them they can tell
is coming out. You can watch it shift.
The communication can change between the
both of you. So twig snapping can be
done by yourself but also with others.
You can use the breaking of these twigs,
the snapping of them as a communication
tool, as a communication device.
Even before talking to someone, letting
them know what you're doing, preparing
for a talk, sitting down alone and
snapping twigs before you meet up with
someone and you're getting together with
someone. Or you're with someone and you
start snapping twigs together before you
even start communicating or talking.
Both you and that other person are just
sitting there together breaking twigs
and snapping little twigs. Just hearing
someone else snap a twig with you is
therapeutic on its own because you know
lifealtering things are happening to
them. Frequencies are shifting. They're
healing in different ways. Their soul is
receiving the information. If there's
somebody that's really sensitive,
they've been through a lot and they get
triggered easy. Rightfully so. So many
things happen in our lives. something
might shift in them as they're breaking
the twigs, giving you relief because you
know they may be less
triggerable. Spirit of compassion always
told me this is highly extremely
therapeutic within families when a whole
family gets together and they sit there
and they're all snapping little twigs
together while they're quiet or they're
thinking or talking in between it. And
it's even possible to find other people,
like-minded people that would like to do
a twig snapping get together or
gathering where a larger group of people
get together and they have their piles
of twigs and everybody's sitting there
focused, relaxed, and they're breaking
and snapping little twigs. When your
mind, body, and soul are being purified
from the sounds of the twig snapping,
from these sounds of nature running
through the body and the consciousness
and the subconsciousness, the mind, the
emotional centers of the brain, physical
brain, the soul. Then words change.
Different
phrases, different ways of talking and
speaking, different lines of
communication, different thoughts,
theories can emerge, new
understandings, new approaches to
things, spiritual revelations, epiphies,
and a way to learn about others and talk
to others and find out things about them
and yourself that weren't really
approachable beforehand. Twig snapping
gettogethers are powerful, more powerful
than psychedelics, than micro doing than
iawasa,
psilocybin, fraud poison. Much more
safer, much more real and non-damaging
and non-toxic. And even recording your
twig snapping, actually recording it and
playing it back to yourself is powerful
all on its own. hearing it again, not
just the first time when it was
happening in your hands and it was
vibrating through your body and your
bones, but also hearing it back on
recording. So, I'm going to gather up a
few more twigs right now. I'm picking
them up off the ground. I found some
really good ones. I like the way they
look. I like the way they feel.
So this time I'm going to direct these
snaps, these twigs, and breaking them
and snapping them and directing those
sounds to my soul. Connecting these
sounds to the thousands of times through
my past lives that I've actually heard
twigs snap and break for all different
various reasons and different time
periods. And you can do the same. direct
these little twig
snaps to your soul. So, as you grab your
twig and you're getting ready to break
it, I'm snapping mine right
now. Have it directed to your soul.
Think about how old your soul is. Think
about all the different lifetimes and
situations and time periods where you
were involved with sticks in some way.
Whether gathering them up for a fire,
clearing a pathway in the
woods, throwing a stick to a pet dog
that you had 400 years ago. Making
something decorative and carving sticks
for that
reason. Walking through the woods and
the fields, gathering food. gathering
herbs and berries and foraging and
stepping on twigs along the way and
hearing them break and snap. Directing
the twig snaps to your soul isn't hard
to do. You don't even have to think
about it. It could be as simple as these
are going to my soul and these sounds
are being received by my soul. Now, the
speed in which you snap your twigs is up
to you. It's whatever comes naturally.
It's whatever feels good. Everybody's
different, so they're going to handle
the twigs differently, break the twigs
differently, snap them. Some are going
to be faster, some are going to be
slower. Some days you might change it
up. I'm going to do it a little quicker
right now.
Now, after you're done, you can gather
up all the little pieces and put them in
your hand. Or you can leave them about.
You can scatter them in the yard or the
field or on your porch where you are.
You can put them anywhere you want. You
can save them. can put them in a jar and
bring them inside the house. I'm gonna
walk along right now and gather a bunch
more. When you're doing it alone, it can
be a sacred experience. A powerful true
meditation. Clears the mind, lowers the
stress levels, helps heal the soul. I
just stumbled across some really nice
twigs. Now, if you gather twigs with
someone else, someone you care about, a
loved one, a friend, a partner,
companion, maybe somebody you just met,
it can also be a sacred sacred gathering
of twigs and a healing experience
between whoever you're bringing along,
whoever's with you together. It can be a
powerful emotional healing technique.
Just the gathering of the twigs
themselves. Wow. Just found a whole pile
right here. So many to choose
from. Very excited about this. Hope
you've enjoyed this episode. You can go
to medicaldium.com for more free
information. You can check out the
medical medium book series. Many
blessings and God bless you.
A
sound. A sound that's
healing. A sound that your soul
knows. A sound that your soul
heard long, long time ago. A thousand
years ago, you could have been walking
through the woods, stepping on sticks,
or gathering twigs for a fire. And maybe
you were carving a stick to catch a fish
or making a bow and an arrow. And at
some point you stepped on a stick and
you heard it snap. And maybe at some
point a long time ago you liked the
sound, the sound of a break, the sound
of a snap, the sound of a crack. And how
many times did you walk on a hill using
a stick and even down a path? Breaking
sticks is etched in our soul. Snapping
twigs is etched in our consciousness.
It's part of who we are from a long time
ago. Breaking sticks helps us battle the
hardships. Helps us get through a rough
ride on a ship. Clears our mind. Brings
us back in time. And if you're someone
that feels like you lost yourself a
while ago, you're not sure who you are
because it's been that hard. You feel
like there's a battle on the inside and
life seems difficult on the outside.
There's a powerful force between your
fingertips, a supernatural sound that
redirects and rewires your soul to help
keep it round. sitting in the grass and
holding a twig. You're healing yourself.
Remember this. Don't forget who you are.
You're a healing superstar. You're
strong. You're not subpar. Your soul has
traveled far. You're more than what you
think. Much more than what you thought.
You can heal. It's in your hands. I know
you understand.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical Medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite. Only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science interest groups, medical funding
with strings attached, botched research,
lobbyists, internal kickbacks, persuaded
belief systems, private panels of
influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back, and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.