How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William.
We're talking about geoengineering,
chemtrails, weather modification, or all
of the above. Cuz guess what? They're
all connected. And they work handinand
with each other. And the great powers
that run this world are weaponizing all
of those. The umbrella gets bigger and
bigger. Carbon dioxide removal, solar
radiation modification, reflecting
sunlight to try to cool down the planet.
since we have something called global
warming. Or so they think we have
something called global warming, but now
it's called climate change. Climate
change. Climate change. Meanwhile, these
are just distractions. So, we look over
there when they're doing something
really evil over there. Call it what you
want.
Geoengineering, climate engineering,
weather modification, cloud seeding. But
in the end, there's something dirty
going on and evil and nasty. There are
secret missions. Military jets spraying
metals bury them. All kinds of trails,
chemtrails everywhere, different planes,
different jets spraying chemtrails
everywhere. It's all up in the sky. It's
every day, every hour, every minute, all
around the globe. The truth is, nobody
really knows what's going on. No body of
government, no official seems to
understand what's being sprayed, what
the purpose is. Is it geoengineering? Is
it something else? Is it weather
modification? Are military jets really
spraying things? Are other jets really
spraying things? Is it contrails? Is it
all a conspiracy? Is it all just under
one big huge geoengineering umbrella?
Nobody really knows. In this episode,
we're getting down to the nitty-gritty,
the bottom of it. We're going to make
sense out of what you're seeing in the
sky. And you're going to see the
connection between geoengineering and
military jets dropping barium and other
planes out there spraying all kinds of
trails and helicopters spraying all
kinds of spray. We're going to talk
about it all. Get ready for the ride.
Fasten your seat belts on this one.
We're taking a chemtrail flight.
They keep on spraying every day. They
never stop. And who's they? Nobody
really knows. Is it the military? Nobody
really knows. Is it private military
contractors? Nobody really knows. Is it
Is it private
organizations? Nobody really knows. But
what's really obvious at this point in
time is there are airplanes, jets in the
sky way up there spraying something,
releasing something. So there's a lot of
guessing out there to what they're
releasing to what they're spraying. Some
say it's weather
modification. A lot of people think it's
part of a program geoengineering where
different metals are being released in
the sky, for example, barerium. So, it
reflects the sunlight, alters the
weather, alters the atmosphere. It's set
up to begin with where no one is
supposed to notice it. No one is
supposed to know what's happening.
Everybody is supposed to believe that
it's just contrails. Yeah, contrails.
Moisture in the engine, the plane or the
jet is going up. It's going up and up
and up. It's colder up there in the sky.
The moisture in the engine and the heat
leaves a trail, condensation, and
nobody's supposed to know about it. No
one is supposed to believe it's
anything. It's just supposed to happen
day in and day out. Not just every day,
not just every month, not just every
year, but how about since the 60s?
Everybody's supposed to be going about
their business and not seeing it, not
knowing what's going on, but it's
happening above them. That's the goal
anyway. But over the years, people have
noticed. And now with the internet,
social media, and then the fact that
everybody has cameras in their hands,
and there are more trails in the sky,
more spray trails, more chemtrails than
ever before since the ' 60s, '7s, 80s,
and '90s. More than ever now. It's
become quite obvious something's wrong.
I've been talking about it for decades.
I did a podcast about it years ago. I
dedicated a chapter into one of my books
and I've been one of the voices that's
made a contribution in getting the
information out there of what's going
on. Even if it meant more censorship
because of it. So the talk of the town
isn't chemtrails, it's geoengineering.
Chemtrails is supposed to be all
conspiracy, a theory, all fake. And even
geoengineering is supposed to be a
conspiracy, a theory, and all fake. But
yet it's more acceptable to believe that
they're doing geoengineering because
there is such a thing as geoengineering
and climate engineering and weather
modification. And even though it's a
real thing, it's supposed to be
offlimits private classified. So much
so, no one really knows where the
funding to create it goes. Nobody knows
who's being funded. In reality, nobody
knows who's really doing it, who's
responsible, who's behind it. It's all
kind of up in the air. But what public
authorities are learning is that
something's being sprayed out of jets up
in the sky above the states, above towns
and cities. And it's under the guise of
weather modification. It's under the
guise of geoengineering. In America,
some states are trying to pass laws.
They're passing laws so that weather
modification can't occur above their
sky, above their state. Public
authorities are trying to stop the
spraying. They're sick of seeing it
happen day in and day out up there.
They're sick of having a cookout or a
birthday party for their child and
looking up in the sky and seeing 30, 40,
to even 100 strips across the sky that
are unnatural. They're not clouds.
They're coming from jets and public
officials don't want this stuff dumped
on their children and on their families
anymore. They don't want these unknown
chemicals falling out of the sky on
their families. So, some public
officials in the United States are
trying to alter the law in the states,
saying it can't be done in their
airspace. Passing new laws to stop
geoengineering. Passing new laws to stop
weather modification, trying to change
the course of history, trying to stop
chemicals from pouring out of planes
purposely to alter the weather or for
any other reason. But it's not going to
be an easy task even though it's a noble
one because there's a lot of problems
involved with chemtrails. That's right,
chemtrails. It's not just weather
modification. And who's doing it? Is it
the military? That's who's doing it? Is
it private contractors? Is it a private
organization? And where are the planes
landing? Where are they landing? It
takes us to another talk all about how
many planes there are. And are
geoengineering planes different than
chemtrail planes? The truth is there's
more planes up there doing different
things. There's more organizations
behind it. Geoengineering could be one.
Regular chemtrails could be another.
Massive insecticide campaigns going on
with helicopters flying at night,
dumping it all over villages, towns,
cities, states, and of course,
mysterious drones that are up in the sky
releasing something out of little tanks
attached to the drones. Let's just put
it this way. There are a lot of things
flying in the air that are spraying
stuff on everybody. really simplifying
it. is falling out of the sky and
evil people are doing it. So, let's talk
about the planes, the jets. There are
thousands, not just 10 or 20 of them or
hundreds of them, but thousands and not
just thousands, tens of thousands of
jets and planes in the sky that have no
passengers on there. Meaning, they got
pilots but no passengers. They're not
commercial flights. They're not filled
with 100 people, 50 people, or two, 300
people. They are empty. They're empty,
but yet filled. They're filled with
tanks. The tanks are in place of the
seats of people. Sometimes it's just two
or three extremely large tanks on a jet.
And sometimes it's a lot of small tanks.
And the seats have all been ripped out.
They've all been ripped out. And in
place of the seats are the tanks. And
the tanks are bolted into the jet. And
then the tanks are filled up. They're
filled up every day. They're filled up
every hour, every minute, because there
are tens of thousands and hundreds of
thousands and millions of these planes
all around the world, these jets all
around the world. And the tanks inside
of these planes and jets are tanks full
of chemicals. And get ready for this
unknown chemicals. It's not that
anybody's getting informed about what's
being dumped on them. It's not that you
go to school or you go to university,
you go to college and you learn, okay,
here's the chemtrail program. Here's
what they're putting into the tanks.
Here's what they're dumping on you.
Check it out. Here's the patented
chemicals. This is the ones we're using.
None of that. We're not supposed to know
anything. And if anybody questions it,
it's a conspiracy theory. You got a
tinfoil hat. You're a nut. Something's
wrong with you. You're just making up
stories. What you're talking about
doesn't really exist. Or you're just a
paranoid crazy prepper. Meanwhile, what
they're doing and what they're doing up
in the sky and the chemicals that
they're dropping on everybody is a
crime. It's a crime on humanity. It's a
crime to humanity. And it's a crime
against humanity, an evil, evil one. And
it happens like clockwork every single
hour, every single day. What's
interesting is you have all these tens
of thousands of planes doing it all day
long up in the sky, every minute and
every hour. But yet, not one of those
jets, not one of those planes lands in a
commercial airport. Yet, they have to
land somewhere. Where are they landing?
They're not landing in any commercial
airport anywhere in the United States.
There's tens of thousands of them, even
hundreds of thousands of them up in the
sky. Where are they going? Where are
they landing? They have to be landing
somewhere. And they are. They're landing
on private land or governmentowned land,
federal land. And we're not just talking
about one airport or two airports or
three airports. We're talking about
hundreds of them all around the United
States. and thousands of them all around
the globe. All top secret, all
classified. So, let's talk about the
money it must cost to actually pilot
those planes. The money it must cost to
fuel those planes and to keep the upkeep
going, to maintain those planes, house
them, store them. And think about the
money involved in the chemicals to
loading them up, trucking them to the
airports, filling the planes. How many
people are employed? We're not talking
about millions of dollars. And we're not
talking about billions of dollars
either. We're talking about in the
trillions and how many years, how many
decades, all the way going to the 1960s
when it started. And where were these
jets and planes manufactured? Who made
them? Who manufactured them? What kind
are they? What do they all cost? Because
it's not 10 planes. It's not 10 jets.
It's not a 100 jets. It's not a thousand
jets. It's tens of thousands. It's
hundreds of thousands. It's millions
worldwide. What did that cost? And what
about the airports, the air control
towers? What about each one having its
own air control tower? What did that
cost? because it's not the same thing
with commercial airports and commercial
planes. The other thing that's really
interesting is chemtrail planes. Yes,
chemtrail planes, you can call them
geoengineering as well. And we'll kind
of talk about the difference between
them, but chemtrail planes and
geoengineering planes that are spraying
every day out there, they're at a lower
altitude. They fly at about 20,000 ft.
It's interesting. Commercial airliners
fly roughly around 30,000 and private
jets, small private jets fly roughly
around 40 to 45,000 ft. Chemtrol planes
are the lowest ones. They're the ones
flying low and they're dumping the
chemicals. So, the chemicals fall on
everybody. I've been on commercial
airline planes and I've watched through
the window as the plane is
descending going right into a chemtrail
that was somewhere around 20,000 ft. No
matter how you slice the pie, they're
all chemtrails.
Geoengineering is supposed to be
barerium, reflective metal. When dropped
out of the sky, it's supposed to reflect
sunlight, cool down the planet, stop
global warming. That's the goal anyway.
Climate engineering,
geoengineering. But really, it's more
than that. And nobody knows because no
one's ever got their hands on a batch of
this stuff that's being dropped out of
the sky, being shot out of the planes.
It's not like anyone has access to any
of it. It's not like there's a container
you can buy and study it or some kind of
public authority can look at it and see
what it is. It's all mystery. It's all
top secret. It's all classified. You
can't just walk into a store, a hardware
store, or go into some other type of
construction store and say, "Can you
direct me to the aisle where you can get
a container of what they're dropping out
of the planes on us every single day?" I
think it's maybe barerium. I really
don't know what it is. Is there any
containers? Oh, here they are right
here. Let's see. for chemtrails for
classified use. Let me turn this bottle
around and look at the ingredient list.
H bar berium, mercury, lead, arsenic,
aluminum. It's just not going to happen.
It doesn't exist. Nobody knows what it
is that they're dropping on people or
really what it is. Let's talk about
geoengineering versus chemtrails. Well,
for one, it's all chemtrail because it's
all being dropped out of planes, shot
out of planes, injected out of planes,
out of jets on everybody. But there is a
slight difference. Geoengineering is
supposed to be militarybased. And maybe
it's not because guess what? People
still don't know the definitive answers
to that either. Not even public
authorities really have direct answers
on that. But it's supposed to be
military military jets releasing some
kind of mystery chemicals that are
somewhat saving the planet somehow
involved with weather modification,
changing the weather, altering it so
crops can get better so rain can be
dispersed in other areas so it helps
protect the planet. But that's not
truth. That's not what's really
happening. It's way more sinister.
geoengineering, the release of dangerous
chemicals out of planes every single day
are for other reasons, for destructive
reasons, for despicable evil reasons.
Has nothing to do with saving the
planet. And it's its own
organization. And with geoengineering,
the planes are usually different. The
jets are usually different. They're more
cargo style, military style, cargo jets,
cargo planes. Different than rogue
chemtrail planes. What are rogue
chemtrail planes? TWWA planes. Panam
planes. Old retired beat up old
commercial
airliners that aren't supposed to even
be flying anymore. even as old as the '
50s, the 1960s, the 1970s,
80s,9s. Many of them refurbished. Many
of them just were purchased in auction
or privately purchased. And also new
planes, too, brand new ones being
manufactured for purposes of chemtrails.
And who's manufacturing them at that
level? How many? How's it possible? And
how much money are we talking about? And
how huge, how big are these
organizations? They're massive. Now,
this geoengineering chemtrail episode is
going to be one of many in a series
because there's lots of ground to cover,
lots of information, a lot of details,
including information on how to protect
yourself and your families, and how to
cleanse and eliminate the metals and
toxins that they're dumping out of the
planes onto everyone. along with how to
keep the immune system strong and how to
keep emotionally strong while
understanding and being aware of what
they're doing and what's happening up in
the sky. So stay tuned for the next
geoengineering chemtrail podcast. Also,
you can go to medicaldium.com for more
free information. You can find me on
Telegram and you can find me on YouTube
and you can check out the medical medium
book series. And have you gotten a
chance to listen to Angels, Demons, and
Spiritual Tools? You can find it on
Amazon, Audible, Apple, and
Spotify. Many blessings and God bless
you. Happy New Year. Yeah. Can you
believe it? 204. What a year. 204. How
old are you? 25. Yeah, I'm 24. We
partied last night like it was 1999.
Yeah, that was crazy. Let's sit out on
the porch, get some air. Ah, chemtrails.
Oh, look at that one. Oh, those are
beautiful, aren't they? Oh, look.
Rainbow colored chemtrails. Ooh, purple
chemtrails. Oh, they're so great. You
know what I love about these chemtrails?
The world governments are really looking
out for us. No, I know. Because those
chemtrails, they're saving the planet.
Yeah. Isn't that amazing? They're saving
climate change. Yeah, they're fixing our
climate problems. I know. Oh, that's a
pretty one there. Oh, don't you love
when they're X's? X. Look, another X.
Ooh, another X. X X X in the sky. Kind
of like 666, right? Oh, I don't know.
Hey, remember the old ban many, many
years ago when states try to stop it? Oh
my god, we're taught in schools. Did you
hear that your university? That that was
terrible that time when they're trying
to ban him over all those years ago. I
know. I know. Now we know better. Thank
God. We know. We know that this is
saving us. Hey, I'm going to make a
Bloody Mary. All right, you watch those
chemtrails. I'll be right
back. Fill it up. Get it on the runway.
Tanks are filled with skull and
crossbones. Stamp of approval. The boss
will be thrilled. There it goes. Up in
the sky, a private radio guy making sure
the path is clear. Get that plane safely
in the atmosphere in the sky. The pilot
was trained, told when to flick the
switch or die. Pull it off without a
glitch. This is flight 666 reporting
back to the base that sits out there in
the sticks. This is the base. Did you
empty the tanks? Did you unload the
poison all over the place? Flight 666,
you know the drill. What's your ETA
after you dumped the spell? This is
flight 666 to the base. I flicked the
switch, left a trail a mile long, all
over the place. Base, can I ask a
personal question? What do you think all
this poison's going to do to our own
families down there? This is the base
fight 666. Don't be thinking about that.
Pull yourself together. You got a
mission to finish. What you're doing is
to help humanity. Get back to the base.
Do everything you can. Keep your sanity.
[Music]
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite. only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.