How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William. This is episode two of
the geoengineering chemtrail series. In
this episode, we're going deeper into
the sabotage, and we're going to start
with the weaponized decoy called the
contrail. The contrail, the ultimate
psychout. It's not a chemtrail you're
seeing up there, sir. It's a contrail.
Reminds me of the old bait and switch.
Remember the old days? That's not a UFO
that landed in your yard, Mr. Hansen.
That was a weather balloon. And now
these days, we're in a time everybody
knows aliens exist. Everybody, or almost
everybody believes they exist. They
believe there's spacecrafts, spaceships,
UFOs, unidentified objects flying in the
sky, in the atmosphere, life on other
planets. nowadays. Too much proof, too
many videos, too many people with too
many sightings, even the government
talking about it as being actually real.
And worldwide, there's an understanding
that alien life exists beyond our solar
system. But in the ' 50s, '60s, '7s,
80s, '90s, no way. It didn't exist. It
was weather balloons. It was the fog.
That's what it was. or something else.
But now we know better. We have so much
proof. It's obvious. But what about the
chemtrails? What about geoengineering
and weather
modification? Why is that such a
mystery? Why are chemtrails such a
mystery? Why does it seem like such a
conspiracy theory? And why is there so
much censorship around chemtrails? And
how come no one comes clean? They're
dumping this stuff on everybody every
single day. Planes are releasing toxic
chemicals on people every day, every
hour, every minute. And if someone says
something, it's make believe. Just like
the old weather balloon, they're told
it's not true. They're told they're
seeing things. There's no toxic
chemicals being dropped on everybody
from planes. That's absurd. In this
episode, we're going to explore the
contrail. The con. The ultimate con.
Fasten your seat belts and get ready for
this one. We're taking another plane
flight. Mister, what's your name? Um,
yeah. Um, John Applebee. Okay, Mr.
Applebee, explain what you saw. Um, I
saw a spaceship flying over our farm.
And then my son saw a little gray man
that ran across the yard and into the
cornfield. And then the spacecraft, the
spaceship did weaved a whole bunch of
stuff in the corn field and all the corn
is all wrapped together like in a knot
and then the spacecraft just flew off
into the sky and disappeared. U Mr.
Applebee, there are lots of reports of
weather balloons in this area and some
thick fog. We're putting on record that
this was a weather balloon and uh I just
need you to sign the statement. Uh, but
wait a minute. My son saw Mr. Applebee,
no disrespect to your son, but he's 9
years old and children have
imaginations. But I saw the spaceship
and it was over the house and it made a
lot of noise. Mr. Applebee, John, you
saw a weather balloon. You understand
this now, do you? You have your hand on
my shoulder. Can you just take your hand
off my shoulder? If you don't understand
this and what you saw a weather balloon,
we're going to have to question you and
your family further. Do you understand
this? Uh, I suppose you're right. I
think I did see a weather balloon. Um,
and uh, it was a big weather balloon and
uh, the fog is kind of thick tonight.
And I I appreciate um, you guys coming
out here and uh, uh, let me just sign
that document right here. I see. Uh,
John um Applebee, have a good night, Mr.
Applebee.
[Music]
Many times over the years, over the
decades, the 40s, the '50s, the ' 60s,
'7s, '8s, '9s, it was just like that.
Alien abductions, UFO sightings, alien
sightings, all swept under the carpet.
All tucked away, hidden away. classified
reports, redacted documents, hidden
documents, missing footage of sightings,
a 100red years of aliens aren't real,
UFO sightings aren't real. There must
have been some sand in your eyes. You
must be tired. Are you on drugs?
Meanwhile, we've come a long way and
it's obvious now. And so much
information is released and so much
footage is taken because everybody's got
a camera in their hands. The world is
different. It's accepted. aliens, UFOs,
life from other planets, flying saucers
is accepted. Are there some people that
still believe there's no such thing? Of
course there is, and there may always be
that. But the world, for the most part,
has accepted life from other planets,
sightings, UFOs. There recently are even
police officers coming to people's
residences that saw a UFO land, aliens
running through their backyards, and the
police were actually afraid to go and
seek out those aliens because they knew
it was real and it was frightening. But
we're not there yet with the
chemtrails. We're not there yet even
with geoengineering. That's a whole
mystery. People don't even know what
geoengineering is or have a clue about
weather modification and what that
means. And the powers that be that run
this planet, that actually really run
this planet, the evildoers that have
caused so much harm throughout the
decades and the centuries, don't want
anyone to know about the chemtrails.
They want people to believe in contrails
that chemtrails don't exist at all. They
want people to believe that it is an
actual conspiracy theory, a ridiculous
thing. Dangerous toxic chemicals have
been being dumped on everybody since the
1960s. Planes filled up with tanks
inside of them. No passengers on there,
just a couple of pilots. and dangerous
and deadly toxic chemicals, toxic waste
being released out of these jet planes
into the atmosphere, dumped on us day in
and day out since the 1960s all the way
till now every day and you can see it up
in the sky. All you have to do is look
and you see the white streaks going
across the sky. But even though we see
it every day all around the globe, we're
told it's not real and what we're seeing
is not real and it's not actual reality.
It's not the truth. That these are
chemtrails. We're told these are
contrails. Contrails. The ultimate con.
World governments, world authorities
don't want to fess up. They don't want
to truly admit what it really is. And
there's still a lot of push back over
the chemtrail thing. There's a lot of
censorship over it. Even weaponized
fakeipedia, Wikipedia, the ultimate
fakeipedia, puts out statements about
contrails anytime anything's mentioned
about chemtrails out there. Then why is
everybody trying to hide it? Why is
Fikipedia, Wikipedia trying to hide it?
Why is authorities around the planet
trying to hide it as if it's not there
when planes are flying every day over
everyone dumping highly toxic chemicals
on everybody? And here we are
2025 and there's no transparency with
this. 2025, people are out there having
a picnic. They're grilling on their
grills. They're outside taking walks
during Easter. They're taking jo.
They're running on the streets. They're
exercising. They're in the parks. All
the kids are in school and on the
playgrounds. And in the sky above
everybody are these streaks, these white
streaks floating everywhere. Dangerous
chemicals released out of planes.
Meanwhile, it's all a dirty secret. And
these chemicals being released every
single day are cocktails. Highly toxic
cocktails. And the contents of these
cocktails we're going to talk about in
detail in upcoming episodes. But if you
like spoilers, mercury, lead, aluminum,
copper, petroleum byproducts, acids,
barerium, solvents, herbicides, mosquito
killers, thousands of different kinds of
byproducts from worldwide industrial
chemical industries, chemicals from old
storage bins from World War I, chemicals
from storage bins from World War II,
Agent Orange, DDT, and these are just
the chemtrails. We're not talking about
geoengineering chemtrails. It's a little
bit different. Lots and lots of metal
and custom factory-made combinations to
block the sun to manipulate the rain to
create floods and different unique
weather
combinations, deflectors and reflectors
to actually start up tornadoes and
hurricanes. Geoengineering is a fancy
word which really means we're going to
steal your sunlight. We're going to try
to create a tornado or hurricane. We're
going to try to create a flash flood.
We're going to dump a bunch of metal
particles in the sky. We're going to try
to change the electrical currents of
mother nature and storms and rain and
clouds. All while guaranteeing somebody
with asthma is going to have a rough
day. Because these evildoers behind
geoengineering and weather modification
and these evildoers behind chemtrails
and the chemtrail programs don't care
who gets sick. They don't care who
breathes in what. They don't care what's
dumped on everybody's heads. They don't
care what's dumped on everybody's food,
the gardens, the farm fields, the
produce that grows. And they don't care
about little children with asthmatic
conditions and all kinds of different
lung problems. And they don't care about
the chronically ill. They don't care
about people with different kinds of
symptoms and conditions that are hyper
sensitive. And they don't care about the
stuff that they release in the sky
creating Alzheimer's and dementia
contributing to it. What they care about
they the evildoers, the people that run
this planet way above public
authorities. What they do care about is
if you know it's a
chemtrail is that you know the truth
that they're dumping stuff on you. They
don't want the chemtrails to stop. They
don't want the classified programs to
stop. They don't want the millions of
planes worldwide to stop flying. They
want to keep on dumping what they want
onto people. and they want everybody to
believe the ultimate con that it is a
contrail that they're seeing, not a
chemtrail. So, let's get into contrails.
What is a contrail anyway? A contrail is
moisture. Moisture in the engines. And
as the plane rises, starts to head up,
goes up to higher altitudes, the weather
changes. the cold air against the
engines, the hot engines and the
moisture involved. Just like on a really
cold day, you start your truck or you
start your car and you see the exhaust
and you see all that white fume and
smoke come out the back of the exhaust
pipes until it disappears and there's
nothing there. An exhaust trail, a
conra. And when the jet's going up, it's
really cold up there in the atmosphere.
And the hot engines and the moisture
involved in the engines and the cool
air, the icy cool air. As the plane
climbs to a higher altitude, you get a
contrail. But here's the key. The
contrail can only last so long, and it
can only be so long. It can't be miles
and miles long. A contrail can only be
100 feet or a couple hundred feet long
or 100 yards at best. And in the sky, a
contrail is really short, very short. So
you see the jet plane and you see the
contrail. But keep in mind, it's when
the jet plane is climbing high,
ascending, not descending. A jet plane
when descending cannot create a
contrail. A plane when it's ascending
can create a contrail, but only when
it's ascending, going up, not when it's
been up already and it's flying. So when
a plane is 20,000 ft in the sky and
flying, it cannot create a contrail
anymore. It can't. It can only create a
contrail when it's heading up to that
20,000 ft and then it stops. And that
contrail is short. Once again, extremely
short. So, a contrail can only last so
long because there's only so much
condensation. Condensation burns away
really quick. It can't just leave a
streak in the sky 5 m long or 10 m long
or 20 m long. But the geoengineering
industry and the chemtrail industry
wants you to believe that it's
contrails, not chemtrails, not deadly
chemicals, not metals. instead just
condensation water that becomes ice
particles. And they want you to believe
that these ice particles can last for
miles, can span miles, can be a white
streak in the sky that can go 20, 40
miles long, but contrails can't. And
that condensation that turns into ice
crystals doesn't really turn into ice
crystals. It vaporizes just like out of
your exhaust pipe in your car on a
really cold day. Ice isn't shooting out
of your exhaust pipe. And that steam,
that condensation that's coming out of
your exhaust pipe isn't turning into ice
particles and floating in the street. As
a car goes by and it's 10 below zero,
you're not walking across the street and
hitting ice particles. And as the
exhaust steam passes by or floats out of
the exhaust pipes and floats into the
air or the wind takes it, that's not a
stream of straight ice particles. Just
as you breathe out of your mouth and you
see your breath, you see it float in the
air on a really freezing cold day, 20
below zero, you're breathing. You're
seeing your breath leave your mouth and
you're seeing moisture come out of your
lungs. moisture. As this water vapor
leaves your lungs, it's like a liquid
gas. Gas formed out of water. And on a
really cold day, you won't see
snowflakes come out of your lungs. You
won't see snowflakes form and come out
of your mouth. You won't see large ice
crystals come out of your mouth and
float in the air. And up in the sky in
those planes, the exhaust, it's
different than our lungs and it's
different than our physical bodies and
our breath. But there are similarities
when it comes down to moisture, hot
moisture, and when it's hitting cold.
When moisture in a hot engine that runs
through hot exhaust leaves and gets into
the air and becomes airborne does not
turn into snow crystals, does not turn
into snow, does not turn into ice.
Instead, that liquid gas is a vapor. And
that vapor
vaporizes because that water wasn't a
mist. That condensation wasn't a mist.
And even at some point where there was
enough condensation or an extreme amount
of condensation coming out of those
exhaust pipes, it would be short-lived.
Coming out of those jet engines, it
would be short-lived. As short as
seconds, as short as 10 to 15 to 20
seconds, not enough to make a chemtrail.
Instead, just a small contrail. Now,
there is a difference between chemtrails
and geoengineering.
weather modification trails and they are
two different organizations that share
the skies. One is using dangerous
chemicals and dangerous metals to
manipulate weather and weather patterns.
Another is just dumping dangerous
chemicals cocktails including fungus,
different forms of fungi onto the public
purposely. When it comes down to
contrails, in the end they have nothing
to do with any of this. nothing to do
with the programs of releasing dangerous
chemicals and toxins from planes into
our skies and on top of us. But it's a
decoy. It's a trick just like the old
weather balloons. The contrail
explanation out there is there to soothe
the beast. It's there to make scientists
happy. It's there to make people feel
good. It's there to convince people
there isn't anything sinister happening
in the sky above them. The sinister
evildoers learn to weaponize contrails,
the term contrail. And in the end, it's
just an ultimate con. There's a lot of
darkness out there. There's a lot of
evildoers out there doing despicable
things to people on this planet. And
this one belongs in the top 10 list of
assaults on humanity. So, next time you
think about a chemtrail or you see
something out there or someone talks
about a chemtrail being a contrail or
something on the internet that's saying
that contrails are actually chemtrails
and that there isn't any
chemtrails and that geoengineering isn't
the spraying of all kinds of dangerous
toxic metals. If a media outlet or news
authority believes it's just contrails
or is trying to tell people that's what
it is as if science is backing it up and
definitively it is a contrail not a
chemtrail and sources like Wikipedia
which is really fakeedia says it's
contrails and that chemtrails just don't
exist then you know it's just weaponized
or they're working for darkness or
working for peace. people who have
immense power on the planet. So when you
see a streak in the sky, when you see a
chemtrail, don't be fooled. It's not a
contrail. And when you do see these
chemtrails up in the sky, sometimes
hundreds of them as they fan out as the
jets go by, when you do see them, keep
in mind what you're seeing isn't being
dropped on you. What you're seeing isn't
coming down on you. You're not breathing
in those
chemtrails. You're breathing in
chemtrails that you can't see, that have
already fallen, that were dropped many,
many miles away and floated your
direction, but they're not in the sky
anymore. And the ones you see in the sky
are going to fall somewhere else, very
far away from you. So when you look in
the sky, don't fear those chemtrails.
Those aren't coming your way. Don't
worry about those chemtrails. They're
not affecting you. There's already
chemtrails in the air for everybody all
the time. Not only in the United States,
but all over the entire planet. We
breathe them in every single day we step
outside. We even breathe them in a
little bit in our own homes. They seep
in during the night and during the
daytime. They're nothing to fear.
They've been up there since the 1960s
when the program started. And we're
going to go into detail all about it,
who's behind it, what's occurring, when
it's occurring, how to protect yourself,
and how to cleanse out and clean out the
many toxins. In the upcoming episodes in
our chemtrail and geoengineering series.
For more free information, you can go to
medicalium.com. You can find me on
Telegram and YouTube and Rumble and
check out the Medical Medium book
series. Many blessings and God bless
you. Look up in the
sky. The blue has faded. I wonder why.
Did the weatherman lie? Or have we been
jaded? I see some jet planes up there.
They're not that high. No, they're
flying pretty low. What do you know? The
plane is leaving a trail. How is that?
So, look, so many more to go. I'm losing
count. How insane. They're just laying
it out. I feel we're getting blasted.
It's as thick as
molasses. This is flight 222 calling the
base. How does it look down there? A
painted sky. No questions asked. Kept a
straight face. This is the base. Flight
222. Landed airirstrip New Mexico if
you're through. Refill the tanks and
back up you go. Roger that base. This is
flight 666 to the base. I made an X over
the interstate. Flight 666. This is the
base. I see you're keeping your chin up
while releasing the white lace. Roger
that. This is flight 666 base. Can I ask
you another personal question? Do you
believe in God? This is the base. Fight
666. In this work, God has no place.
This is fight 222. I'm back on route. I
overheard that I'm a god-fearing man.
Base. Are you saying God's not part of
the plan? This is the base. Flight 222
and flight 666. Just be men and keep on
spraying the chem. Roger that. Roger
[Music]
that.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from, so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.