How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William. We're talking about
extraterrestrials watching chemtrails.
That's right. You heard me. Aliens
watching what's happening out there. And
whether you believe in aliens or not,
whether you believe in flying saucers,
UFOs or not, they're out there and
they're being filmed every single day by
people and their cameras. Because it's
not like the old days when people didn't
have a phone, a camera on them. It's not
like 911 in 2001 when the Twin Towers
went down. Very few people, very few
people caught that on tape. Meanwhile,
tens of thousands of people watched it
happen. And so much of the corruption
was missed. So many details because
people just couldn't pull out their
camera and take a snap. They couldn't
pull out their camera and take a video.
It was far and few and rare. But not
now. But not these days.
Extraterrestrials, spaceships,
spacecrafts, UFOs, unidentified flying
objects are caught every hour, every
minute all around the globe. And you
know what else is caught on those
videos? All the chemtrails. All the
white streaks and the foggy haze and the
white haze in the sky. It's in so many
people's videos and so many people's
photographs. Now, in this episode,
episode four of the geoengineering
chemtrail series, we're talking about
all those UFOs up there and all those
chemtrails. And do they have any
connection with each other? Are they
related in some way or are they
connected in some other way? We're going
to talk all about it. Get ready. Fasten
your seat belt. Strap yourself in. We're
going on the Alien and Chemtrail
Express.
[Music]
Aliens. They're out there. Look up at
the sky enough, you'll spot one. In due
time, you'll spot one. You've never seen
one before. You never seen a UFO,
unidentified flying object. You will
eventually look up at the sky at night
enough and you'll see one. You'll spot
one. They're there. And people are
filming them every single day. All they
got to do is pull their camera out of
their pocket. They're driving down the
highway. They pull over, pull the camera
out. They're on an old farm road. They
pull over, pull their camera out.
They're on the street in a busy city.
They look up in the sky, they pull their
camera out. Everybody out there will
eventually see one at some point in
their life because there's that many
flying around. And there's good aliens
and there's bad aliens. And there's good
aliens and there's bad aliens. And
there's in between, too. There's in
between, not so good, not so bad. The
thing is, a lot of people probably don't
want to hear this, but thank God for the
good aliens. Thank God for the good
extraterrestrials. Because when you
think about it, there's bad aliens out
there. And those bad aliens have some
pretty darn big ships. And those big
ships have weapons on them. Weapons we
cannot even
imagine. The power we cannot even
imagine. And why? Why aren't they just
sending down a beam, a laser, an
explosive of some kind, blowing up
cities, blowing up towns, annihilating
the Earth. There's a reason. Because the
bad aliens are worried. They don't want
to go into war. They don't want to go
into war with the good aliens. Because
the good aliens have weapons, too.
Powerful weapons, large ships. And the
peace treaty goes on. The alien peace
treaty up there in the sky lives on
every single day. If it didn't, there
would be a big problem. There would be
alien wars up in the sky and on our
land. And the bad aliens, the bad
extraterrestrials, the bad spaceships
would be doing some serious damage,
annihilating cities. So, make no
mistake, there's a peace treaty up
there. Bad aliens and good aliens living
with each other, living in each other's
space, flying around around the planet,
in our atmosphere, in our skies. Now,
what does that have to do with
chemtrails?
Geoengineering planes releasing
dangerous and deadly toxic chemicals day
in and day out a lot because they're
sharing the skies. They're sharing the
skies with chemtrail planes. Now, keep
in mind, there's more chemtrail planes
in that sky above you than there is
military planes, commercial planes,
private planes, helicopters. There's
more chemtrail planes, geoengineering
planes flying around you up there than
any other common flight or common plane.
They dominate the skies. Geoengineering
planes, chemtrail planes dominate our
sky, dominate the air. And aliens,
extraterrestrials know this. They're
aware of this because they're seeing it.
They're witnessing it. And spaceships
that enter our atmosphere are aware of
what's in our air, what's in the
atmosphere around the planet. They're
aware of what toxins are floating around
in our sky because they get an instant
understanding with their technology.
It's an easy one. It's a no-brainer.
They have to know what they're flying
into and what they're flying through.
And they also need to know if there's a
threat, a threat against them. Is there
something that's flying around even
though it's primitive and it's fossil
fuels and all of our planes up in the
sky are driven by
petrochemicals. And aliens know this and
they understand that we have engines
that are burning fuel and are extremely
primitive, low technology, not elevated
high technology. So when an alien ship
is flying up there, it knows what it's
flying through. It's getting readouts.
It's understanding the terrain. It's
understanding that there are toxic
chemicals, toxic waste, dangerous
metals, dangerous poisons being
propelled, shot out of these planes. And
they know that it's dangerous to our
health. Aliens,
extraterrestrials know our health. They
understand our physical bodies. They
know it well. And they know that what's
being released out of those planes is
highly toxic to human life and to nature
on planet Earth. So, good aliens know
there's corruption. Good aliens know
there are evil beings, human beings on
the planet that want others sick, that
want the planet damaged and want people
to suffer, suffer greatly. It causes a
questioning. Good aliens flying around,
good aliens concerned about this planet
are wondering why other humans want to
destroy it, want to pollute it, and want
to hurt people and want to poison the
people here on this planet. So good
aliens see this. The truth is they not
only see it, they see everything. They
see it spew out of the planes. They see
it spew out of the tanks inside the
planes. They can do an
analysis. They can look inside the plane
as they're flying alongside the planes.
They can see everything. They can see
the contents in the plastic tanks that
are sitting inside those planes. They
can see how the technology works. They
can do analysis on what the chemical is
that's spewing out of the plane. They
see it all and they understand it all.
Just like they know about the nuclear
weapons on this planet. Just like they
know about the warheads, the nuclear
warheads that are in the silos just
waiting to blast off. They see it all.
They understand it all. They know what's
there. And so do the bad
aliens. So do the evil aliens, the evil
extraterrestrials. They see the silos.
They see the nuclear warheads. They see
the chemtrails. They see it all. And
they have the power to send a weapon
down to the silos, to blow up the
warheads, and to create a war, untold
damage. They have the power to destroy
the planet. But they're not going to do
that because they're in a peace treaty
and they don't want a problem because
the good aliens don't want that to
happen. And so there strikes a balance,
a balance up there. But when it comes
down to chemtrails, something else
happens. Somebody else is looking at the
chemtrails. It's not the good aliens,
and it's not the bad aliens. It's
somebody else. It's the aliens that sit
a little bit in between. They're not
totally bad. They're not all good. And
they're doing analysis of the
atmosphere.
They're testing the quality of the air.
They're flying through it. They're
looking at it. They're seeing the
chemtrail planes everywhere. They're
watching them. They're watching the
poisons come out of the planes. And
they're wondering why it's happening.
And they're wondering why people are
trying to hurt people. They're wondering
why people on the planet, human beings,
are trying to hurt the planet itself and
hurt nature at the same time. And
they're wondering something that the
good aliens are wondering too and the
bad aliens. They're wondering why the
evildoers on the planet are doing it
when it's obviously going to affect
them. They're going to be breathing in
all those toxic chemicals. But one of
the problems with these aliens, the ones
that aren't the good ones and they're
not really the bad ones, they're in
between, is they have no peace treaty.
They're not worried about anything.
They're not worried that if they do
something terrible or something wrong
that they're going to be really
punished, although they are concerned to
some degree, but they realize they're
not in the same battle or war between
good and bad aliens. if a peace treaty
fell through. And that's when one of
these alien ships could go rogue. And
that's when some of these aliens could
go rogue and alter history or create
history that's not good. Now, because
people are not being punished for the
crime of dumping these toxic chemicals
onto children, onto people, onto
families, onto the planet. And they're
not being called out. and they're not
being found out. And the evildoers are
free free to actually just keep on doing
what they've been doing since the
1960s, dumping trillions of tons of
toxic chemicals out of planes, out of
the sky onto
humankind. No repercussions, no
ramifications, no punishment. No one's
knocking on their door telling them to
stop because there is no door. There is
no door to knock on. There's no way to
find them. It's classified. It's top
secret. Nobody knows who's even doing
it. No one's even sure it's
geoengineering or is it a chemtrail?
What is it at all? There is nobody to
hold accountable. Accountability is
impossible. Who is it? Who's doing it?
What are the evildoers? Who are the
evildoers? Where are they? Where are
they located? Where are their airports?
Who are their
pilots and how can they be stopped? One
of the problems with this is they're
seen as a free radical. They're seen by
spacecrafts, spaceships, UFOs,
extraterrestrials. They're seen as free
radicals, dangerous, toxic free
radicals. And so it's really a matter of
time before one of these
spaceships, one of these alien crafts,
one of these
extraterrestrials says enough is enough
and starts to eradicate the chemtrail
planes and starts to eradicate the
geoengineering planes because they share
the same space because aliens are using
the same airspace. they're flying
through it and they don't want to see
that. There's going to come a time where
there's going to be a rogue alien, a
rogue
extraterrestrial that's going to say,
"Time to put the foot down. Time to stop
whatever this is. This isn't helping
human beings down there. It's not
helping us as we're flying through it.
It's dangerous. It's traffic that's in
our way. It's traffic that's not
productive." an alien craft that's
traveling at an extremely high warp
speed can accidentally run into one of
these chemtrail planes and one of these
chemtrail planes is really just causing
damage causing destruction. So, I
wouldn't doubt at all that some of these
chemtrail planes or a lot of them start
either disappearing or going down
because of
extraterrestrials acting as vigilantes
thinking it's very possible they can get
away with doing it because the good
aliens are probably not going to say
anything cuz they know that the
chemtrail planes and the geoengineering
planes are highly dangerous, highly
toxic and destructive. So they may not
do anything to these other aliens. And
the bad aliens the same way. The aliens
in between are not worried about them
possibly too. They're not worried about
the bad aliens punishing them. the good,
the bad, the in between aliens can all
come to an actual understanding where
these chemtrail planes and
geoengineering planes shouldn't be
sharing the sky, shouldn't be in their
way, and should be poisoning the people.
Even the bad aliens may not want people
poisoned. Sure, they want to mine the
land. They want to make deals with
higher governments, secret governments.
They want precious metals and minerals
out of the earth. They want to make
deals with evildoers. And with all that
said, it doesn't mean they think it's
right that chemtrail planes are
poisoning the planet and poisoning the
people. And they are. They are poisoning
people. They are affecting people's
health. They are dumping trillions of
gallons of byproduct, trillions of
gallons of chemicals from the chemical
industry straight onto everyone without
a care in the world. So why do people
evildoers that are responsible for this
deal for the geoengineering and
chemtrail deals and other things that
are sprayed in the sky which we're going
to talk about in further episodes? Why
are these evildoers allowing it to
happen to them? Allowing these toxic
chemicals to be dumped on their
families, their children, themselves.
For one, it's greed because they're
being paid to allow it to happen. paid
to do it. They're getting trillions of
dollars. They're not billionaires.
They're bigger than billionaires.
They're trillionaires. The illumination,
the people who are responsible for this
want more money. They have money. They
always want more money. One of the
reasons why so they can keep on
exploring
technology that allows them or them to
believe that they will live forever or
their offspring will live forever to
either be frozen then defrosted into the
future or some other form of technology
that allows them to be revived later on
in the future, put to sleep and then
revived. or their spiritual belief
system where they think they're going to
come back. Not just come back, but come
back into the same family. Come back
into the same exact family. Or they
believe they're going to be rewarded.
Rewarded by darkness, given things that
no one else has, given things that
nobody else will ever get, things that
they can obtain from darkness because
they're doing dark deeds. But these evil
doers, the illumination, are building
castles. They're building castles with
air quality that isn't the air quality
we breathe from the outside of their
castles. They're building castles that
don't get affected by radiation that
don't get affected by nuclear waste.
They're building underground bunkers,
underground castles, underground
mansions, and they're using the money
they're making from the deals of the
chemicals being loaded into the chemtrol
planes. They're using that money from
those deals, which equals trillions of
dollars over time to build all of that
to protect themselves for the future and
their families. It's a long-term gravy
train that's been happening since the
60s. And aliens, they're aware of it.
Now, aliens know the difference between
jet fuel, fossil fuel, petroleum,
petroleum products. They know the
difference between the exhaust that's
coming out of the jet engines compared
to the chemicals that are being released
out of the plastic tanks inside of the
airplanes. And they know the difference
from a commercial plane that has a
couple of hundred people on it that's
transporting passengers, human beings.
Aliens know this. They know the
difference of every single thing that's
flying through the sky, that's flying in
the air, every machine, everything that
has wings, everything that has
propellers and jets. And they know the
toxicity level of the planet, planet
Earth. They know the toxicity level of
planet Mars, but they know the toxicity
level in the way that they're monitoring
it. They know here in planet Earth, it's
becoming more toxic. They know the
chemtrails are part of that, a big part
of that. Just like they know about the
wars, they know about the missiles
taking off and blowing up. They know
about the smog coming out of the
factories and so many other facets of
how this planet is slowly dying. But
chemtrails, it's a whole another level
of
toxicity, whole another level of
poisoning.
It's not killing people direct like in
wars or evil madmen plot evil killings,
mass destruction, killing masses of
people, thousands and thousands and
hundreds of thousands of people. It's
different. It's a slow kill. It's a
slow, longated kill that takes decades
upon decades. It's for the long run. And
the extraterrestrials, the aliens, they
know when they started it. The first
chemtrail plane that ever entered the
sky,
extraterrestrials know what plane that
was. They know what aircraft that was.
And aliens, extraterrestrials know where
every single classified private airport
is. They know where it's located. Every
single one of them around the globe.
Now, before you get worried and you
think about how toxic this must be, how
toxic chemicals are, you got to think
about one thing. Your body has an
ability to cleanse and to heal. And when
you're using the right tools, you can
protect yourself. And we're going to
talk more about that in coming episodes.
Check out
medicaldium.com. Lots of free recipes.
Check out the medical medium book
series. You can find me on Telegram. You
can find me on YouTube and of course
here at the Medical Medium podcast. And
if you have some time, give a listen to
Medical Medium, Angels, Demons, and
Spiritual Tools. Information that's
empowering, powerful information,
profound information that can even be
life-changing. Information that can
protect you. Many blessings and God
bless
you. This is flight 312 to the
base. 312. This is the base. Got an
unidentified object flying with us. It's
on the south side of the plane. It's
flying at our speed. Over flight 312.
This is the base. We have six other
pilots in the area. You sure it's not
one of us? This is flight 312. Back to
the base. No, it's not one of us, sir.
The shape of the object is round and
it's got no wings. Over. This is the
base. Flight 312. Keep it steady. Just
flight 312. Uh, we're getting kind of
nervous. Uh, 100 yards now to the left
of us. Uh, staying steady at our speed.
Over. Flight 312. This is the base. Keep
on standby. Roger that. Flight 312, this
is the base. Are you currently releasing
a chemical load? Flight 312 to the base.
I currently am releasing 5,000 gallons.
Over. Flight 312. This is the base.
Abort mission. Kill all switches. Stop
contents from leaving the plane. Roger
that. All contents not leaving the
plane. Everything's locked down. Flying
steady. Over. Flight 312. This is the
base. How's the unidentified object? Is
it still there? It's flight 312 to the
base. Object is gone. No longer in
sight. Over. Flight 312. This is the
base in 55 miles. Drop the next load.
Turn the switches on. Release the
contents. 5,000 g. Fight 312 to the
base. Roger that. Over.
[Music]
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite. only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from, so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.