How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William.
We're talking about chemtrails, the
geoengineering decoy, aliens, and the
numbers in the sky. Numerology that's up
in front of everybody, floating above
them everywhere. That's right, numbers
in the sky that evildoers hierarchy on
the planet are creating. And as the
chemtrail planes are spraying and the
geoengineering planes are spraying their
trails, the trails add up and they have
numbers and they're purposely being put
out there. So the numbers add up in the
way they want them to add up, gaining
them power or they're believing gaining
them power on a spiritual level that's
protecting their mission. dropping those
chemtrails. As you look up in the skies,
you'll see X's. Maybe you'll see them
one day and maybe another letter another
day. They not only put X's up there,
which are sixes, but they put L's and
M's and E's and Fs in the sky for a
reason. So, not only are they dropping
toxic, dangerous chemicals on everybody
every single day, they're also trying to
curse everybody in their own way at the
same time. They're trying to gain their
power that they need and hamper down any
kind of power or empowerment that we
need down here through their chemtrail
programs. This is episode 5 of the
geoengineering chemtrail series. In this
episode, we also explore the
geoengineering decoy and how it works
and what their plan is. And if you think
you've heard enough about geoengineering
and
chemtrails, get ready. We haven't
scratched the surface. There's so much
more to go. Strap yourself in. Fasten
your seat belts. We're taking another
plane flight.
[Music]
Nothing is what it seems. You've heard
that before, right? That old saying,
nothing is what it seems or nothing is
as it seems. Well, if there was ever a
time to use that old phrase, that old
saying, this is the time for
geoengineering, for
chemtrailing chemtrails, and for alien
involvement with chemtrails. If you want
a chemtrail stopped because you're sick
of seeing those chemtrails up in the
sky, and you don't want chemicals dumped
on you, and you want it to end, you
can't just call out into the sky and
say, "Stop." You can't just pick up the
phone and dial a number and reach
somebody and say, "Look, I want those
chem stopped. Stop poisoning the air I
breathe." And the thing is, not only can
you or me or somebody else not reach
whoever it is up in that plane or not
reach a service to tell them to stop,
not only can we not do that, a public
authority that has awareness to it can't
even do that. Even though states are
actually concerned here in the US and
states are passing laws or one state has
and others are hoping to follow that
same pattern, they don't know who to
call. They don't know who to find. They
don't know who to stop. It's not like
they have access either. No one has
access. It's that top secret. It's that
classified. If someone sees a UFO in the
sky, an unidentified object, an alien
ship, an alien craft, there's a
similarity there. You can't call them
and say, "Hey, aliens. Hey,
extraterrestrials, will you stop? Will
you get out of my airspace? Will you
stop flying around up there cuz I don't
know really what you're doing. Will you
stop messing around? Will you stop
studying us? What are you looking at?
What are you doing? And what are you
looking for? And who are you looking
for?" And what's strange is that's a
similarity. Same thing with
chemtrailing. Same thing with
geoengineering planes. You can't ask
anybody anything and you can't find out
anything. So even if you pass a law,
there's a lot more work to be done.
There's a lot of different phases to it.
Don't get me wrong, it's progress. If a
state passes a law to clear the airspace
and stop weather manipulation, weather
modification, and geoengineering, it's a
miracle. But it's kind of the same
thing. You can pass a law for aliens not
to fly in your space. You can pass a law
for UFOs not to fly by or be up there in
the sky. You can pass that law, too. But
who are you going to call and what door
are you going to knock on? Some alien
ship is not going to actually stop in
mid-flight and say, "Oh, sorry. I'm in
the wrong area right now. I'll go and
move over the next state or I'll move
over to the next continent." And this
needs to be talked about. the whole
classified operation of it all. The fact
that we don't have access to any of it,
the fact that it's rogue, it's
mysterious. And even if you see an
influencer now talking about
geoengineering cuz they want to keep up
with the times and they put out a post
about geoengineering, how much awareness
are they really going to bring or should
I say confusion? Because it's a setup.
It makes it look like it's something we
know all about. It's something that's
happening like there's some organization
that we can just reach. Hey, stop
dumping that trash over here. Go pick it
up and dump it over there. Oh, hey, stop
doing geoengineering. Stop doing weather
modification. If that's what they're
even truly doing or what plane you see
in the sky that's spraying something is
even accomplishing. Nobody knows. Nobody
knows if that's a geoengineering plane
or if that's a chemtrail plane. But
that's the problem. People talking about
it now are talking about just
geoengineering as if that is it. But
see, that's a problem because that is an
ultimate decoy. Geoengineering is a
setup. It's a setup so we focus on it.
It's similar to trash on a beach and
then everybody's passing around flyers
to clean up the beach or there's a
couple of people that want to start a
nonprofit, get some donations and work
on trying to clean up beaches. And
that's what today's talk about
geoengineering is. It's similar and it's
dangerous. Not cleaning up beaches, but
making it seem like that we know what
geoengineering really is. when
influencers have no idea and when local
governments and public authorities have
no idea. By doing this, we're creating a
situation where it is what it seems.
Hey, that must be geoengineering planes.
Wo, they must just be doing weather
modification. Wo, states are going to
try to stop it. Great. Now, let's move
on because it must be all set and all
figured out. But things aren't what they
seem. And if you're somebody just
learning about geoengineering and you
didn't know they were spraying anything
up there, it's a big deal. And you're
like, "Wow, it's geoengineering, weather
modification. Wo, they're manipulating
the weather. That's serious stuff. I'm
so glad people are aware of this." But
it's like fool's gold. You think you
know the gold. You think you learned the
gold, but you didn't. You didn't learn
the gold at all because things aren't
what they seem. You may be aware that
something's happening up in the sky now,
but it's just a grain of rice compared
to a silo of rice. That's all it is. And
as I said before, awareness is actually
amazing. It's a positive step forward.
And passing laws to clear the skies is
epic. It's legendary. It's profound. A
state in the US taking it upon itself to
say, "Hey, I want our skies clear. Stop
playing with our weather." this movement
forward, but we're a long way from home
and we're playing with fool's gold. So,
we got to be careful because just like
the Contrail game, there's a
geoengineering game. Just like the
Contrail decoy, there's a geoengineering
decoy. So, when you look up in the sky
and you're told it's a contrail, but yet
it's a chemtrail, as more awareness
grows and you look up in the sky and
there's a contrail, but yet it's a
chemtrail, but yet you're going to be
told it's a geoengineering trail. You
see where it goes? Because as it stands,
no one's allowed to believe or think
that there is actually a chemtrail up
there, that somebody is dumping garbage
on them, toxins in the air, dangerous
chemicals in the air. Instead, they're
supposed to believe it's a contrail,
just moisture, vapor coming out of the
engines, and it's a natural process up
there in the sky. When a plane is flying
in the atmosphere, when a plane is at a
high altitude, they're told it's a
contrail. And eventually as awareness
grows about geoengineering and laws pass
to stop geoengineering and that
geoengineering is weather
modification and that it's an injection
of metals or an injection of something
to try to deflect the sun, cool the
planet down from global warming or
climate change to try to make things
better to try to help the planet a
positive change. And once more awareness
and more people view it like this, they
become numb. And then there could be
campaigns saying it's a good thing for
our planet. It's trying to help us and
we shouldn't be trying to stop it. It's
just like a contrail. It's harmless.
Good people are up there in the sky
trying to protect us from the future.
Trying to stop the water from rising,
the oceans from rising, trying to stop
all the other problems like the thinning
of the ozone layer and the ice melting.
So, we think geoengineering is good.
It's a good thing. We were wrong. Surely
scientists have our backs. Surely
scientists are looking out for us. And
maybe we're just being stupid. And maybe
trying to stop geoengineering is just a
dumb thing. And that's part of how the
geoengineering decoy really works. It
ends up being a decoy. The system is
built to keep us out of touch about
geoengineering, to keep us out of touch
about chemtrails, to keep us out of
touch about what's going on in the sky.
And right now, we are in the early
stages of awareness for geoengineering.
And it's mysterious all on its own
because nobody knows really what
geoengineering is. Meaning nobody on the
planet understands it. Now that sounds
kind of crazy, but it's true because no
one has access to anything classified.
They don't have access to the pollutants
that they're dropping on us. They don't
have access to the chemicals or the
metals. They don't have access to seeing
a plane leave a tarmac somewhere. They
don't have access in knowing what plane
it is. Is the government involved? Is
the military involved? Whose military is
involved? Are scientists involved? Are
they really working on something? None
of it is known at all and not allowed to
be known. All geoengineering is as far
as we're supposed to know or is known is
that it's a vague operation somewhere
where they're trying to protect the
planet. They're trying to help with
climate change. So they list it as
climate engineering and it's all off
limits. The truth is there is a fraction
of the trails that are up in the sky.
There is a fraction of them that have
something to do with the
geoengineering with weather
modification, weather manipulation, but
it's just a fraction. And it's not
helpful to this planet. It's evil.
Downright evil. And it's just one of the
programs up there in the sky. Are you
somebody that remembers when CO first
hit when everything was being closed
down and barely any flights were leaving
air strips, commercial flights in many
cities, there weren't anybody really
walking. Beaches were all closed
everywhere. Towns and city streets
looked like ghost towns. Barely any cars
driving. There was this one moment where
it was like everything was just stopped
in time. And while this shutdown was
happening up in the sky, there were
thousands and thousands of chemtrail
planes, geoengineering planes, chemtrail
planes, mosquito helicopters, mosquito
planes. Nothing stopped up there.
Instead, only everything increased.
That's the power of the chemtrail
organizations. That's the power of the
evildoers. During CO when everything was
on lockdown, there were thousands and
thousands of planes, millions of planes
worldwide up in the sky. And all you saw
were white strips everywhere. White
strip X's, white strips, hundreds of
lines in the sky, thousands and tens of
thousands of pilots up there. They
weren't worried about CO. They were told
to fly and dump those chemtrails. They
were told to fly and ordered to fly and
dump those geoengineering trails. They
were ordered to fly their helicopters
and dump their mosquito spray by the
droves. Think about what kind of power
we're talking about if the whole world
was shutting down because of CO and the
whole world was on lockdown, especially
at this one certain point in time. But
yet the power up in the sky, the amount
of trails that were going miles long,
the amount of chemicals that were dumped
on people, the amount of planes
releasing all of the chemtrails to the
degree that they were doing, to the
degree that it was happening. Chemtrails
never stopped. Geoengineering trails
never stopped. Nothing stopped up there.
And that's what we're talking about. The
whole world was in lockdown. But yet the
power behind those chemtrails, the
illumination, the hierarchy, way above
all laws, way above every law on the
planet. Can you imagine those air
traffic controllers at the time watching
all of those thousands of planes flying
back and forth releasing trails while
all the other planes were practically
grounded because of CO? Can you imagine
what was going through their heads?
Those commercial air traffic
controllers, they must have been
mystified. Truly mystified and beyond
confused. And this is the kind of power
we're talking about behind the
chemtrails, behind geoengineering. As
awareness about geoengineering grows,
the truth about chemtrails themselves
will grow weaker because geoengineering
in itself will be the great new decoy
that keeps people from realizing there's
more happening up in the sky and there's
more evil going on up there in regards
to chemtrails. Geoengineering is going
to be that lame decoy duck that just
gets people numb over time regardless of
nobody really knowing who's behind it
and exactly what they're doing. But yet
laws passed to stop it to stop
geoengineering, weather modification,
weather manipulation above a state has a
potential of being miraculous.
Geoengineering is one dangerous program
up in the sky. Another dangerous program
in the sky are chemtrails.
Chemtrailing. Geoengineering leaves a
chemtrail, but it's a little bit
different than the chemtrails that are
involved in the chemtrail program. A
separate program classified of course.
And this program is the involvement of
dumping old used up chemicals, excess
chemicals, excess chemical storage,
chemical industry byproduct, old
chemical storage and backlog that can't
be dumped anywhere else. So they have to
dump it in the sky. Now, this is a
different organization, but yet run by
the same bosses, run by the same evil,
controlled by the same hierarchy, a
criminal endeavor with no one ever being
held accountable, truly above the law of
all laws. So, now it's time to talk
about numerology a little bit and how it
plays a role in chemtrails and
geoengineering trails. What people don't
realize is there's numbers in the sky
and that the hierarchy, the illumination
behind chemtrails and geoengineering
believes in numerology and they have
their own experts, their own classified
experts that deal in numerology and some
of their information, some of their
numerology has been taken from aliens
that they've encountered along the way
in the last 150 years through alien and
hierarchy communication.
Although there are many aliens that want
nothing to do with chemtrails and are
tired of sharing the airspace with
chemtrail planes and chemicals coming
out into the air that they actually
travel through too. They still
understand numbers and they read the
numbers, the numbers that the chemtrail
planes are leaving. The chemtrail
organization creates their flight plans
based on how many trails they're going
to leave, the number of trails
And they often send out groups of
planes. Groups of planes with an
allotted amount of trails are going to
leave. The chemtrail programmers, the
bosses, want a certain amount of trails
in the sky. They want numbers to add up.
They don't treat the sky as one. They
don't treat the sky as a whole. They see
the sky as sections, sections of the
sky. So if you look up and you count 10
trails, they want you to see 10 trails.
You look up and you count 20 trails,
they want you to see 20 trails. Now
counting trails is not easy. You can't
always see the sky. You can't always see
the sky line. So you won't be able to
count the amount of trails that they
want left out there up in the sky. So if
they want 22 trails, it doesn't mean
you're going to be able to count 22
trails. You might only see 18 of the 22
or 14 of the 22, but they lay out the
trails in numbers. Numbers that they
know and are keeping track of. They
believe if they lay out trails in
certain numbers, they change the course
of history and time. They change the
atmosphere. They change the Earth. They
change the way we live down here. And
they control how they poison us. They
control how they manipulate our health
through these chemtrails. Now, I'm
outside now and I see four trails up in
the sky. But it doesn't mean that they
just put out four trails in this sector
of sky. To them, they may have put out
40 trails or 20 trails and I only see
four and that's it. But one number that
you can identify with ease is the number
six. They tend to use that number a lot.
They tend to X the sky and sometimes
they'll X the sky multiple times so
they'll give you a 666 and another 66
and six. Sometimes they'll just do
straight sixes. They'll purposely lay
enough lines one way and then
coordinates change and they send their
pilots another way and they try to
cross. They try to make multiple sixes
and many of them. There's a reason for
this. They know how many sixes they're
putting out there. If they want 20 sixes
in a sector, then they will put 26s out
there. And their pilots have to obey. It
can't be super sloppy. There can't be a
lot of mistakes. They have to do it
correctly. So, they create letters up
there. They create X's. But that's not
the only letters they create up in the
sky. Chemtrails can create a variety of
letters, a number of letters. So, not
just the letter X, which equals a six,
but they'll create the letter Y. They'll
even create a letter Z. Now, these
letters don't have to be perfectly
formed up there in the sky. That part
can be sloppy, but they have to be close
and intentional. They have to make up
what a letter just about looks like.
Often the letter E, the letter F, the
letter Y, even the letter Z, and of
course the letter X are seen up in the
sky. Even the letter M and letter L. Now
there are numbers associated with these
letters and they know these numbers.
These are numbers they believe are those
letters and they use them up there. They
also love ones. So they purposely leave
a lot of lines, a lot of trails, and
they add up. A whole bunch of ones, a
whole bunch of trails add up to a whole
bunch of other numbers. And they know
these numbers, and they believe this
holds power and that it creates power.
They believe it makes them more
untouchable and it protects them and
hurts us at the same time.
Extraterrestrials, UFOs, unidentified
spacecrafts, spaceships, aliens know
about these numbers. They're watching.
They're watching carefully. They see it
all. They know what's happening. And
they know that certain humans are being
evil by dropping these trails, by
creating a sequence, by creating codes
and using numbers to gain power while
poisoning the people here on the planet.
The number games that the evildoers are
playing up in the sky are going to end
up being one of the triggers that sets
off a rogue alien race to say enough is
enough and to start eradicating
chemtrail planes. Not everything is what
it seems or nothing is what it seems,
especially when it comes down to
chemtrails. Especially when it comes
down to
geoengineering. Another decoy. a real
problem and a serious problem, but yet
still a decoy. If you get a chance,
check out
medicaldium.com. Free recipes, free
information, a tremendous amount of
health and wellness information about
chronic illness. Check out the medical
medium book series, a lifesaving book
series that has helped millions of
people around the planet. It's gotten
people out of wheelchairs. It's got
people who have been there and done that
and tried everything. It has helped
people recover from some of the worst
diseases and conditions who were
seasoned and looked around for answers
for years till they stumbled across the
medical medium book series, the medical
medium information and got their lives
back. Make sure you sign up to my
newsletter and have you checked out
Angels, Demons, and Spiritual Tools.
Powerful life-changing spiritual
information. I wish you well. Have
compassion for yourself. Pat yourself on
the back. Know that you're a good
person. Know that you can
heal. Many blessings and God bless you.
Don't make too much noise. Okay. When
you're duck hunting, you got to stay
calm and quiet. You see all those ducks
out there in the pond? Yeah, I know. But
they're not moving, right? Yeah, because
they're happy. They're calm. They're
just What? They're not moving. Why
aren't they moving? I don't know. You're
right. We've been here for a while. How
long we been here? Half an hour. They're
just floating around out there and
they're not really doing anything. But
wait, there there's a duck right there.
It's that one just flew across. You hear
it? Yeah. But why aren't those over
there moving or doing anything? Let's
fill them with some buckshot. Let's just
do it. No. All just you walking up.
Okay. You're walking to the duck. Okay.
All right. I'm walking to I'm with you.
Let's Let's just head to those little
ducks. They're not moving. Good. Just go
ahead. What? It's just sitting there
floating. It's not dead, right? It's
sitting up. Do you want to try to grab
it? Go ahead. Wow. You got it. Wait a
minute. What is that? That's a decoy.
Bring that over to me. Let me see it.
What does it say here? Geoengineering.
This is flight 312 to the base.
Over. This is the base. Flight 312. Sir
was finishing out the aerial injections
full schedule and then had equipment
failure. Over. Flight 312. This is the
base. What kind of equipment failure did
you have? Over. Flight 312. Sir, we're
doing the diagnostics. There was a ball
of light unidentified object flying
around our plane. And then equipment
failed. All switches went down. Over.
Flight 312. This is the base. Head to
Falcon Crest Airport, Pennsylvania.
Flight 312, sir. On our way. Over. This
is Flight 666 to the base. This is the
base. Flight 666. Already put 22 sixs in
the sky. Made 22 X's, but I'm running
out of fuel, sir. Running out of fuel.
Running low. Over. Flight 666. This is
the base. You have two more X's to go.
Supposed to do 24 X's. Over. Slight 666
to the base. Don't think I'll make it.
Someone else is going to have to do it
for you. Think of running too low on
fuel, sir. Over. Flight 666. This is the
base. Land at New Mexico airport. This
flight 666. Roger that. Over. Flight
222. This is the base. Do you read
me? This is flight 222 to the base. What
can I do for you? Over. Flight 222. This
is the base. Can you do two more X's on
your route before you're done today?
Over. Yes, sir. I could do that for you,
sir. Two more X's coming right up. I got
a little more fuel and we should be
fine. Over. Let's fight 666 to the base.
Anyway, tomorrow I could do some M's and
some L's. Maybe some E's and Fs. Try to
break it up, sir. Tired of doing the
X's. Over. Flight 666. This is the base.
We'll give you what we tell you to do.
Remember that. Over. Fight 666. Roger
that. Flight 222. Roger
that. Flight 312. Roger that.
Over.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite, only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science interest groups, medical funding
with strings attached, botched research,
lobbyists, internal kickbacks, persuaded
belief systems, private panels of
influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back, and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.