How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William.
We're talking about the black box, the
flight recorder on chemtrail planes and
geoengineering planes. How if a
chemtrail plane ever goes down somewhere
and public authorities get a hold of
that crash, they'll be looking for that
black box. They'll be looking for that
flight recorder. And that's the last
thing chemtrail programs, the sinister
geoengineering programs want the public
authorities to have access to. They
don't want the truth going out there.
They don't want a device that has all
the records and the
communications between the chemtrail
pilots and other pilots and the
chemtrail pilots to the base to air
traffic control. Air traffic control
they have no access to or understand on
any level because it's classified. We're
also talking a little bit in this
episode about the conditions of the
chemtrail planes and the condition of
commercial airplanes and the difference
between the both of them and what that
all means and how that plays a role to
what's happening up there in the sky.
And just when you think that's it for
this episode, hang on to your bridges
because we're going to be talking about
how chemtrails travel, but not just
travel around this planet, but travel
instead through the paranormal triangles
and how that's not a good thing. We're
going a little deeper in episode 6 in
extraterrestrials and how there's a good
percentage the chemtrol planes and the
geoplanes have to worry in the coming
years ahead. When it comes down to
aliens and
extraterrestrials, friend or a foe,
friend or a foe, it all depends. When
somebody's planet is getting littered
with toxic chemicals and unknown toxic
waste that's entering their atmosphere
through a gateway, a channel, a channel
of paranormal means. So hang on for this
ride. Strap yourself in. Fasten your
seat belts because your mind is about to
be blown. We're going on another plane
ride.
[Music]
Sometimes it's every other day you hear
about a plane problem, some kind of
problem,
malfunction, a bad landing, a fire in an
engine. You hear about two seaters going
down. You hear about three people dying
in a small plane crash. You hear about a
plane almost hitting another plane, a
plane landing almost hitting another
plane, a plane taking off almost hitting
another plane. The media reports about
it all the time. And then you hear about
fights on planes, arguments on planes,
problems on planes, all kinds of
different issues. You hear about
somebody going to bathroom on a plane in
the walkway where their feces are
scattered about all over the floor. And
then you hear about people vomiting,
projectile vomiting on a bunch of other
people and the plane has to head to land
to a different airport out of nowhere.
And what about people getting arrested
on planes? That's something you hear in
the news as well. The media covers that.
It's endless. We can go on all day about
it. But what's interesting is commercial
planes and small private planes only
make up a tiny fraction of the airspace
up there. a tiny fraction of what's
flying around in the airspace up there.
A tiny
fraction compared to chemtrail planes
and geoengineering planes. So, you have
to do the math. You have to take a look
at it. If that tiny fraction of planes,
commercial planes, and small private
planes, fill up the media with
incidents, accidents, and problems and
tragedies and disasters. And it's
reported on almost every other day or
every day out there globally. And once
again, it only makes up a fraction of
what's flying around in the airspace. It
only makes up a fraction of what's up
there in the sky. So what does that mean
for the majority of the planes that are
flying up there? Does that mean the
millions and millions of chemtrail
planes, the millions of geoengineering
planes all around the globe leaving
trails day in day out, night day, every
minute, everywhere? Does that mean not
one of them has an incident? Not one of
them has a tragedy or a crash or a
disaster? Not one of them has an engine
that blows up? Not one of them has a
fire inside the plane. Not one of them
has to land on an emergency basis.
Hundreds and hundreds of thousands of
chemtrail planes, thousands of
geoengineering planes in the US alone
flying around. And not one problem. Of
course, the chemtrail planes are having
problems. And of course the
geoengineering planes are having
problems. Of course they're having
malfunctions, emergency landings, fires,
engine blowups, pilot
complications. But you'll never know and
the media won't care and the media
doesn't want to know. And the media will
never know anyway. And they'll never
have the interest to look and try to
see. And corrupt media outlets all
around the globe, they don't want to
report on it. They don't want to just
snap out of it and realize there's
chemtrails everywhere. They don't want
to look into it, understand it, find out
how to fix it. And maybe you're somebody
that has a trusted media source. And
maybe that trusted media source that you
get your information from is mainstream.
Or maybe it's not mainstream and it's
more on the fringe. And you trust the
political information you're getting
from it. You trust all the wellness
information you're getting from it. You
trust everything you're getting from it
or almost
everything. But yet, you're not going to
hear about these chemtrails. You're not
going to hear about the information
we're talking about here. You're not
going to hear about the geoengineering
or truly what it's about. You might
start hearing a vague geoengineering
term out there. And you might start
hearing about injecting possible weather
manipulation, weather modification
agents in the sky. But that's about it.
It's going to stop there. Shops going to
be closed. And when the media does start
talking a little bit about that, a
little bit about
geoengineering, they're either going to
side up with it, or of course, not give
any full explanation or true
understanding or depth about it out
there. They're not going to go there, at
least not now. Maybe in the future
someday, but for nefarious reasons, but
at least not now. They'll report on
alien sightings. They'll actually report
on those. They'll even report on an
alien sighting in someone's backyard.
They won't talk about the chemtrails.
Let's hope they do. But even in this
moment, if you listen to any one of
these chemtrail episodes, you'll get a
banner. The banner will say,
"Contrails, courteous of Wikipedia,
fakeipedia, of course. Global powers
don't want chemtrails to stop. It's how
they bank trillions of dollars. Global
powers are okay with political change
because they think it's temporary. They
think over time the tide will shift. But
chemtrails have to keep on pumping. They
have to keep on going. Chemtrail planes
have to keep on flying. That can't stop.
They do not want that to stop ever. Now,
when it comes down to the condition that
chemtrail planes are in, it's a better
condition than regular commercial planes
that everybody flies because commercial
airline companies are known to penny
pinch. Torn seat covers and worn out
bathrooms are common. Broken levers and
scratched food trays also occur. All
signs that if the inside of the planes
are starting to get worn and torn and
older, then that can equal to landing
gear, tires, engines, and computers. So,
chemtrail planes are taken care of
better. There's a few reasons for that.
One of those reasons is they don't want
the planes going down. Now, the planes
still go down. There's still
malfunctions. There's still emergency
landings. There's still crashes. There's
still tragedies, but nobody knows about
those. But yet, they want less of those
because there's more chemtrail planes in
the sky and more geoengineering planes
in the sky than there are commercial
planes. And yes, no airliner, no company
wants any plane to go down. In fact,
they just don't. But there's still a
difference because if chemtrail planes
go down, geoengineering planes go down,
epic toxic disasters occur and it could
gain attention. The chemtrail plane goes
down in a village somewhere in the world
or a town or a city in the middle of a
city and blows up and 50,000 gallons,
20,000 gallons or 5,000 gallons of chem
dump out and go all over the streets all
the way down or blow up and burn
everywhere, then there's a big problem.
There's going to be a major
investigation and authorities, public
authorities may start peeking into what
kind of plane was this? Especially if
there's no passengers on the plane, just
a pilot or two, the plane becomes
mysterious, mysterious to public
authorities. They can't have these
planes go down because of this reason.
So when parts manufacturing goes scarce,
like when CO occurred, a feeding frenzy
happens. The classified geoengineering
industry and chemtrail industry will pay
the highest prices and stop up all the
parts, all the new parts in the
industry. Now, keep in mind
geoengineering industry and the
chemtrail industry. They're also
rebuilding their own planes,
refurbishing their own planes, and
building and manufacturing their own
parts, too. But they're also putting
more planes every day in the sky than
any commercial airliner can ever. So,
they're always going to need more parts.
And when COVID hit and manufacturing was
scarce, commercial airline companies
won't pay the price or can't pay the
price. They couldn't afford it. They
could not match the chemtrail industry
or the geoengineering industry. So what
happens is the commercial airliners tend
to use refurbished parts when times are
tricky. Not all the time, but just like
when COVID happened and parts were
scarce, it was a tricky time. It was a
pandemic, for example. Chemtrail planes
and geoengineering planes cannot afford
to go down. Too much can be discovered.
Let's talk about the black box. All
commercial airliners have a black box, a
flight recorder. So the mystery can be
solved if something happened to the
plane. pilots being recorded,
information being collected, all feeds
into the black box, including all sounds
and movement and positions of flight
controls. And most importantly, radio
communications. Now, make note of that
one. Radio communications. That is a
critical one for what we're about to
talk about next. Chemtrail planes and
geoengineering planes do not have black
boxes. They don't keep flight recorders.
There's a critical reason for this. When
a chemtrail plane goes down and public
authorities are looking after the plane
crash and they take control over the
incident, the accident or the tragedy,
it's imperative that the public
authorities do not take control of that
black box. It's important that they do
not obtain that flight recorder because
if they do and that's a chemtrail plane
or a geoengineering plane and public
authorities have control over their
black box, their flight recorders, then
there's a huge problem. It means they're
going to hear the pilots talking to an
air traffic control that is an unknown
classified air traffic control. Nothing
that they know of. a private entity they
know nothing about and then there's
potential of the chemtrail industry or
geoengineering industry being discovered
or evidence of what they're doing. So
there can't be black boxes which are
really orange mostly but there can't be
black boxes on chemtrail planes on
geoengineering planes. Now, it's bad
enough that if a chemtrail plane goes
down and it's empty, doesn't have seats
or passengers, instead chemical tanks
built in it, and it's spewed all over a
highway or in a town or a city, that's
bad enough as it is. Never mind
obtaining a black box with
communications on it. Communications of
pilots talking to air traffic
controllers, private classified air
traffic controllers, and about what?
about the chemicals they're releasing in
the sky, what they're dumping, what
they're doing. The information on those
communications is much different than a
commercial airliner and a pilot talking
to air traffic control. And this is why
there are no black boxes on those
chemtrail planes and those
geoengineering planes.
[Music]
So, let's talk about identifying a
chemtrail plane. It's actually pretty
easy because chemtrail planes fly lower
than commercial planes. Geoengineering
planes and chemtrail planes fly around
20,000 ft instead of 30,000 ft like
commercial airliners and many times
15,000 ft which is not that high. Now of
course a commercial airliner can fly
15,000 ft. A commercial airliner can fly
20,000 ft when they're coming close to
the airport when they're a few miles
away. when they're actually coming in
for the last 15 minutes of the journey,
the trip, they start to descend. But
you'll never see a chemtrail behind a
commercial plane. You'll never see a
white streak behind a commercial plane
ever in your day, in your
lifetime. Never a white streak that's
miles long. It's not going to happen.
Unless it's an old used up retired
commercial airplane that was adopted by
the chemtrol program or the
geoengineering program or an old
commercial plane that's now forgotten
about because the airliner company went
bankrupt many many years ago. So the
entire fleet was taken over by the
chemtrail program, the geoengineering
program. Mostly the chemtrail programs
take the old planes, the old commercial
planes. But you'll never see a chemtrail
or a geoengineering trail, the white
streaks behind a commercial airplane
where there's passengers on it or behind
a commercial airplane that dropped off
passengers and now it's flying empty.
Now, the reason why we're talking about
this identifying chemtrail planes and
geoengineering planes and the white
streaks behind them versus commercial
flights with passengers on them is
because of the paranormal triangles, the
Bermuda Triangle, Alaskan Triangle, and
many other triangles because commercial
flights don't pose a greater risk in
these triangles as chemtrail planes do
and geoengineering planes do. So, let's
talk about what that greater risk is.
I'm sure you've heard about the
paranormal triangles, the Alaska
triangle and the Bermuda Triangle and
many more. Now, not all the triangles
that people are talking about out there
are legit. People are looking for
triangles. They're interested. They want
many triangles out there, and there are
many, but not every triangle people say
is a triangle is a mysterious paranormal
triangle. And one of the things is
paranormal triangles aren't just
triangle. They're circles. They've been
identified and estimated as
triangles. They've been noted as
triangles, documented as triangles, but
in reality, not all of them are
triangles. They're actually circles.
They're areas that are actually
circular. And in these paranormal
triangles, which are actually circular,
at least most of them are, there's a lot
of UFO sightings. There's a lot of
sightings of light beams, of light
circles, of crafts, of
spaceships, also
disappearances, missing ships, missing
planes over the last 100 years. So,
where do chemtrails and geoengineering
trails fall into this? Where do these
play a role? They play a role by acting
as a magnet for alien races, as a magnet
for
extraterrestrials, for unidentified
objects, spacecrafts, spaceships,
chemtrail planes, the chemtrail
programs, and the geoengineering planes
and programs act as bait. They act like
a worm on a hook. The chemtrails can
draw unwanted guests. Aliens we don't
want flying here. Aliens we don't want
in our airspace. We don't want flying
around Earth. Possible rogue aliens, not
good ones. None of the aliens that are
in the peace treaty. Rogue aliens that
are baited to come. They're attracted.
They're lured in. And what are they
lured in by? The pollution, the
dangerous chemicals, the toxic waste
being dumped in the sky. the chemtrails,
the geoengineering trails because what
happens is that gets sucked into the
triangles that gets sucked into the
circles. It gets sucked into the Bermuda
Triangle, to the Alaska Triangle. And
where do those trails go? Those trails
go into a portal, a wormhole, right
through the triangle, right through the
paranormal triangles and circles and
into the atmosphere of another planet in
another solar system, either in another
galaxy or in this galaxy. So even though
chemtrail planes and geoengineering
planes don't normally go over the
Bermuda Triangle, don't normally go over
the Alaska Triangle, they go near them
and all the chemicals being dumped out
of them, the trails go into the
triangle, into the circles. And then all
of a sudden, if a portal opens in that
circle in that paranormal triangle,
whatever's in there in that airspace
gets sucked through it. So if there was
a ship or a plane, it could go missing.
But here's how it works. There's so much
toxic waste in the sky in the atmosphere
floating over those triangles that it
increases greatly the chances of that
chemical, those trails entering a portal
at any given time and entering another
airspace on another planet with highly
advanced life forms. And most of that
toxic waste is coming from the
geoengineering planes and the chemtrail
planes. And as that toxic waste sucks
through that vortex, sucks through that
portal and gets to another planet, we're
littering another planet's atmosphere.
And if that planet is highly advanced,
they're not going to put up with it.
Especially if that planet is highly
advanced and aggressive and understands
the channels in which to travel from
from point A to point B, like where the
chemicals are coming from. if they can
lock it down and travel from point A to
point B, their planet through that
channel to our planet to find out why
that littering is happening. Then there
could be trouble, lots of trouble. It
could happen tomorrow. It could happen
10 years from now. It can happen 30
years from now. But it can happen. The
paranormal triangles just don't go to
one planet out there. It just doesn't
connect to just one planet out there.
It's a constant revolving group of
doors. And many of the planets that the
paranormal circles, paranormal triangles
connect to may be involved in the peace
treaty. Whether they're good or bad
aliens, they can still be involved in
the peace treaty. The peace treaty here
on Earth, making sure there isn't any
wars or battles up there, battles up
there in the sky. But keep in mind, as
more and more chemtrails get sucked
through the triangles and the circles
and end up on other planets because it's
a constant revolving door, there could
eventually be an aggressive race, an
aggressive extraterrestrial race that
doesn't want to put up with it and
doesn't care about any peace treaties
here. And then they send an army through
that wormhole, an army through that
vortex, through that opening, through
that gateway in search of the ones
responsible for littering their planet.
Because the last thing they want is
large swaths of toxins, toxic chemicals,
aerosols, metals, industrial metals of
unknown origin. And seeking the ones
responsible for littering all of that
and it getting to their planets may mean
anything. It could mean removing the
chemtrail planes and removing the
geoengineering planes, evaporating them,
getting rid of them. But it could also
lead to what people talk about out
there, an alien war against humans.
Alien races coming in and battling us
humans. A war on the Earth. Something
that everybody's talked about for years
and years. And if there's ever a way
this could happen, it would be a rogue
extraterrestrial race, an alien race
that's tired of getting polluted by the
chemtrails, the onslaught of deadly,
dangerous, toxic chemicals constantly
getting into their airspace through the
triangles, through the circles, the
paranormal triangles and circles.
Because in the end, what do they have to
lose if it's detrimental to their
planet? And that alien race, that rogue
alien race, is not going to care about
the peace treaty of good aliens and
other bad aliens here that are already
flying around our atmosphere, already in
our airspace here on Earth. They may not
care about peace treaties or deals or
contracts. They may not care about who's
mining what, what aliens are doing, what
kind of deals with the humans they have.
So, it could be those very chemtrails
and those very geoengineering trails
that triggers off the true problems that
people talk about that they're awaiting
for down the road when it comes down to
aliens and humans battling. Or there's a
good percentage and a good chance it's
just going to be about the chemtrails,
the chemtrail planes and the
geoengineering planes and that aliens
from another planet. Just focus on those
and only those because that's the
pollution that's traveling through that
gateway, through that avenue to their
planet, to their airspace, and they'll
want it stopped. If you get a chance,
check out medicaldium.com.
Get on the Medical Medium newsletter.
Check out the Medical Medium book
series. A life-saving book series that
has saved countless lives around the
world. Millions of people with their
lives changed, healed from all kinds of
different symptoms and conditions.
Subscribe to my Telegram. You can find
me on YouTube and even find me on
Rumble. And remember that you can heal.
Your body wants to heal and your body
loves you unconditionally. Many
blessings and God bless you. Well, I
mean, just don't be antsy. You don't
have to be antsy. We're only about I
don't know, like 7 miles from the
Bermuda Triangle. Well, at our speed.
Yeah. Well, what are we doing? 400 miles
an
hour.
Yeah. Then we're 6 miles now from the
Bermuda
Triangle. Okay. We're 5 miles now. Why
are you nervous? It's not like anything
happens in the Bermuda Triangle. He
can't be just like fallen for every
single thing. What? You know a story?
What? What is it? What? A a friend's
plane that was on the edge of the
Bermuda Triangle? What
happened? All of a suddenly the controls
the controls on dashboard went. We're
We're one mile away from the Bermuda
Triangle. Okay, hang on. For some reason
this it's getting bumpy. Maybe the
ride's getting bumpy. Whoa. Whoa. Yep.
Oh, that has a little
turbulence. You think that has anything
to do with crossing the triangle?
Crossing into the triangle? You
do? Should we turn turn around and try
to skirt the ED where we're not going to
make good timing, though? We're on a
deadline. We got to get somewhere. Yeah.
I I guess. Do we have enough fuel? Why
don't we just cut through the triangle?
I told you that that was the plan. We We
have enough fuel to do it that way. If
we turn around, we're going to have to
Yeah. The dial is twisting. You see
that? What altitude are we at? You're
not sure? Okay. Okay. Let me Let me turn
Let me just turn this thing around.
Forget about the fuel. Let's just start
moving out of here. Yep. All right. All
right. Just hold on. Hold on. We're Yep.
Let's Okay. Let's try to ascend, not
descend. Let's try to ascend. Hold
on. Whoa.
Okay. This is flight 222 to the base.
Can you read me? Over. This is the base.
Flight 222. What's your position? We
can't find you on the radar. Over. This
is flight 222, sir. I think we're over
the Alaska Triangle. And it wasn't on
purpose, sir. It kind of drew us in.
Over. Flight 222. This is the base. Turn
left. Go north. Head to Anchorage. Over.
This is flight 222 to the base. Wish it
was that easy,
sir. Tried that, sir. Running out of
fuel. Actually running on fumes. Every
time we try to get out of this triangle,
we keep on getting sucked in. It's like
a constant circle. Over. This is the
base flight 222.
Drop altitude 10,000 ft. Start
descending over flight 222 to the base.
Got something on our tail. Something's
following us. It looks like a round
ball. And now it's circling all around
the plane. And now our gauges are
getting wacky. Lights are blinking on
and off. Landing gear went down. Now it
went back up. Sir, over flight 222. This
is the base. Keep on standby. Base. This
is flight
222. Running out of fuel. Getting the
parachutes ready. Looking for emergency
door. Getting ready for emergency
protocol. Sir, we're going to jump.
Flight 222. This is the base. Can you
see the ground? Can you see the ground
out there? Any visibility. Over this
flight 222. No visibility, sir. No
visibility at all. Nothing but fog and
cloud. No visibility and no control over
the aircraft anymore. Running out of
fuel as we speak, sir. We're getting
ready to jump. Flight 222, this is the
base. We see you on radar now. You're
over water. I repeat, you're
overwater. Do not jump. Flight 222, do
not jump. I repeat, you're overwater.
Come back.
Over. Flight 222, do you read me? Do you
read me?
Over.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. instead the opposite. Only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.