[Music]
all right I'm making hummus these are
garbanzo beans I am gonna put sesame
seeds and the other decision is am I
gonna put herbs in here yes I am is that
insane it's insane a pinch of salt down
in there too I'm even gonna drop some
lemon juice down in there look at that
gorgeous little display making nut milk
too I soak these almonds so what I love
about this machine is because it has an
ability to pulverize to such a degree
it's going to extract nutrients out of
those almonds that you wouldn't get from
the traditional store-bought almond milk
this is the biggest sale on this machine
ever so far it's a hundred dollars off
you guys know I work with the mega and
everything the price is unbelievable for
what it can do for you and what it has
to offer
okay your mind is going to be blown you
taste pureness you taste cleanness next
on the list we're making the guacamole
a little bit of lime down in there and
I'm gonna put a little bit of salt down
there too and there we are right there
probably one of my favorite things to do
is make the parsley shot which is the
nerve gut acid stabilizer I'm running
parsley through here parsley is not easy
to juice and this is totally crushing it
you need a powerful juicer that doesn't
destroy the nutrients but still juices
The Parsley when you're sick you need a
main line of direct nutrients and when
you're using something like the mm-1500
you're getting that many nutrients out
of it you're getting a main line
directly into your system this is
practically dust good luck with any
other juicer ever seeing that we're
making a lot of things but this is an
important one right here right there
boom check it out
wait a minute here you know what I
forgot
ah
I forgot the natural flavors and the MSG
and the carrageenan I forgot to put that
in here oh bummer
I forgot to put all the poison into the
almond milk what was I thinking