How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them. Whether you're dealing with
anxiety, depression, endometriosis,
acne, eczema, autoimmune, thyroid, lime,
brain fog, fatigue, or any other symptom
or condition, you're far from
alone. Living with symptoms has become
the new normal. So, no more guessing
games. It's time to get answers. Welcome
to the Medical Medium Podcast. I'm
Anthony William. We're talking about
birds. Birds falling from the sky
because of chemtrails and geoengineering
trails. And we're not just talking about
a few birds. We're talking about
millions of birds, hundreds of millions
over the course of the last 50, 60, 70
years. Especially now, there's more
chemtrail planes and geoengineering
planes in the sky than ever before in
history. and they're spewing out and
dropping out and injecting so many
chemicals and toxic waste into the
atmosphere into our skies that birds are
losing ground. It's truly a war, a war
on our birds. And maybe you're somebody
that has seen this or witnessed this.
Maybe you're somebody somewhere on this
planet that walked down a street or a
trail in the woods and saw hundreds of
birds laying around or flopping around
as they were dying. This has been seen
by many people around the world. We're
covering how it all happens, how it all
goes down, how the chemtrails and the
geoengineering trails are destructive on
our birds. Get ready for this one.
Fasten your seat belt. Strap yourself in
because this episode is not for the
faint-hearted. We're taking another
plane flight.
[Music]
Chemtrails are the number one bird
killer long term. Now, of course, a
contender is the bird flu, and that is
killing a lot of birds right now. But
over the last 50, 60 years, chemtrails
have taken the cake when it comes down
to killing birds. Chemtrails have taken
out entire large flocks during migration
or thousands upon thousands of birds
just hit the ground, flop around and
die. People have seen this before.
They've watched it. Now, keep in mind,
there's a lot of land. There is a lot of
land people do not see or walk on. There
are a lot of woods, forests, mountains,
hills, valleys that people are not
allowed on. Government land, classified
land, land for testing, land for mining,
or just endless swaths of land, vast
amount of acres that nobody has access
to. And even private land nobody has
access to. But the birds do. They have
access to this land. And the majority of
the birds fly and die over this land.
Die from chemtrails and land on the land
dead or dying. And no one sees it.
Millions and millions of birds over the
years have fallen into these federal
lands, into these private lands, into
these forests, these hills, these
valleys, on these mountains, and the
death is not seen. These birds are not
seen. The majority of them die this way
in these places because there's that
much land out there. There's that many
acres out there that are not being used.
And when birds die in the streets by the
thousands, tens of thousands, even
hundreds of thousands, and they die in a
town or a city on a city highway, it's a
shock. And people have seen it. They
have they videotaped it. It's out there.
People have seen it throughout the
decades and talked about it, too. And
it's a shocker. Birds falling out of the
sky. But an hour later, it's just a
bunch of dead birds. People drive over
them. Vultures go and pick their bones.
Maggots take over and they just
disappear. No one's saying, "Hey,
everything should stop right now. Let's
examine this. Let's tape this area off.
Let's call the authorities. Let's look
at these birds. Let's do autopsies on
these birds. Let's see what chemicals
are in them. Let's see what's wrong. How
did they die? What happened? Was it
something in the sky? Did they get
affected by something? Did something
hurt them? What caused this? And right
now, today, there's only two things that
knock flocks of birds out of the sky.
It's the bird flu, which is happening
right now out there. The bird flu is
rampid and flocks of birds are falling
from the sky because they're infected by
the bird flu. And chemtrails,
geoengineering trails, both of them.
That's the other thing that kills
thousands and hundreds of thousands and
millions of birds. But here's the thing,
the bird flu is recent and just starting
to take out birds. And that may grow
worse over time. But right now,
chemtrails and geoengineering trails
dominate in bird killing. And the blood
is on the hands of the chemtrail
programs, the hierarchy, the elite
that's secretly behind the chemtrails
and geoengineering trails. The blood is
on their hands, on their souls. And
maybe some people don't really care
about birds or think birds are
important. They really are. And for too
many reasons to count and this crime
needs to be talked about and it needs to
be seen. So, how have millions of birds
died from chemtrails and geoengineering
trails? To begin with, we need to talk
about how high birds fly. The altitude
that migration occurs, the altitude that
birds fly at. When birds travel, they
travel at a height anywhere between 300
and 1,000 ft, depending on the species,
because many birds fly even higher than
that. There are many factors that
determine this. Weather is one of the
big ones. During migration, storms can
force birds to fly much higher. And if a
weather front is pushing low pressure,
it forces the birds to fly higher. If a
weather front is pushing high pressure,
forces the birds to fly a little lower.
So why does any of this even matter? It
matters because we're talking about how
the chemtrails kill the birds and how
the geoengineering trails kill the
birds. Now remember in the previous
episodes I talked about how commercial
airliners fly at an altitude around
30,000 ft and chemtrail planes fly
around 20,000 ft, 15,000 ft and even
10,000 ft. And many chemtrail planes and
geoengineering planes fly at 3,000 ft.
Yes, 3,000 ft. Now how is it that
chemtrail planes are flying this low
3,000 ft? They do this in mountainous
regions. Now, if a chemtrail plane or
geoengineering plane starts heading to a
mountainous region and that chemtrail
plane is flying at 10,000 ft and the
small mountains ahead are anywhere from
3 to 4,000 ft above sea level, the
chemtrail plane doesn't raise altitude,
doesn't ascend or climb higher, stays at
that altitude of 10,000 ft, and then
closes in on the small mountain range,
which is 3 to 4,000 ft. ft above sea
level. So now that chemtrail plane is
released 6,000 ft above sea level, 6,000
ft the altitude. Now, this is important
because a flock of birds migrating could
be flying at an altitude from 2,000 to
5,000 ft above the mountainous range,
leaving only a short distance of 1 to
2,000 ft from the chemtrail plane from
the actual chemtrail being released out
of the chemtrail plane. So, what's the
chances of this happening? The chances
are great, cuz it happens all the time.
People see birds at the park or they see
birds in their backyard, but the
majority of the birds are migrating and
passing over mountainous regions. And
the distance between that chemtrail,
between that geoengineering trail is
close, very close to the birds. Now, for
example, ducks can fly and migrate up to
10,000 ft. And regardless of mountainous
regions, and we're just talking about
land close to sea level, ducks flying at
10,000 ft will match a chemtrail plane
flying at 10,000 ft. So simplifying it a
little bit, birds fly high, chemtrail
planes fly low, birds get caught into
the chemtrails themselves and get
snuffed out and then die. And we're not
just talking about a few birds. We're
talking about thousands of birds, tens
of thousands in just a flock migrating.
We're talking about a massive amount of
birds dying close to death almost at
exactly the same time. And keep in mind,
every batch lot in the plane, every
group of chemicals that they have that
they're dumping, whether it's
geoengineering planes or a chemtrail
plane, can be different at any given
time. So, some concoctions could be
instantly deadly, while some are
intoxicating and dangerous enough to
weaken the birds, causing their flight
pattern to be disturbed, causing them to
weaken and have to drop out of the sky,
causing them to have to land early for
the day, which could ruin everything for
them on the day after, depending about
the weather, disturbing the process of
nature, destroying the very birds we
love. So, how do 10,000 birds die at a
clip? How does it really happen? To
begin with, as the chemtrails are
released into the sky, or geoengineering
trails are being released in the sky, as
the deadly metals and deadly chemicals
are being pumped out of tanks that sit
inside of the jet planes, they begin to
enter the airspace, creating a trail.
And that trail begins at around 100 ft
wide. And as the plane keeps on flying,
that trail becomes not just a mile long,
but it can go about 20 m long. Now, some
chemtrails can go 10 m long, some 20,
and some even 50 m long depending on the
speed of the plane. Now, as the
chemtrail or geoengineering trail sits
in the sky, it starts to drop slowly,
but not just drops slowly. It starts to
spread out. It starts to expand. Now,
exhaust fumes aren't chemtrails. So,
when a engine is burning fuel and that
fuel is turning into exhaust fumes, that
is not a chemtrail. Now, a lot of people
that believe in chemtrails and talk
about chemtrails out there believe it's
chemicals in the fuel tank. So, it's
chemicals in the fuel itself and it's
what the planes are actually burning.
And the trail is that trail coming from
the engines. But that's not true. That's
not how it works. You can't put all of
those toxic chemicals in fuel and expect
a plane to fly. It's not going to
happen. And with geoengineering, you
can't put weather modification chemicals
like barerium, like metals and solvents
inside a fuel tank and expect that to be
released and alter the weather. That's
not going to happen either. All of these
chemicals and metals and pollutants and
toxins are released from tanks that are
inside the planes. The planes are
hollowed out. The tanks are installed.
All the chemicals are filled into those
tanks and then the pilot clicks a switch
and then the contents of those tanks are
released out of the side of the jet.
Now, normally the injection valves and
injectors, these little pipes where the
contents are released, squirted out into
the air, are located near the engines.
They locate these near the engines on
purpose for a reason. So that if someone
sees this with a telescope or binoculars
or they happen to be living in an area
where they see it in a better way,
clear, like on a perfectly clear day, or
if one of the chemtrail planes is flying
lower than normal, and someone happens
to see that the contents are being
released nowhere near the engines, and
then it gets suspicious where it looks
like the trails are being injected out
of little pipes at different areas of
the plane. Now, the chemtrail programs
and the geoengineering programs and the
hierarchy behind it all do not want
people to see that. So, the pipes, the
injectors, the injector valves are
actually positioned near the engines.
Now, now in the old days, it wasn't like
that. Nowadays, because of the amount of
people having the technology to really
hone in on these planes, they have to do
it differently. Back in the 1990s and
the early 2000s, you can clearly see the
injector sights on the planes. They were
different. They weren't in the position
of the engines. They were away from the
engines. And it was more than obvious
that it was actually being done. Now
even now in 2025 not every plane is set
up like that they are away from the
engines. Many of them you can tell and
you can see that. But a lot more planes
the injector pipes are stationed near
the engines now. So they're upgrading.
They're changing it up so it looks like
a contrail instead of a chemtrail. So,
as these chemtrails and geoengineering
trails leave the plane, they're not
leaving as
exhaust. The reason why I'm talking
about this is because when exhaust fumes
enter the air and they leave the jet
engine or even the car engine or truck
engine or bus engine, oxygen from the
air will interdisperse between it after
it's been released. oxygen will enter it
and help it disperse. So that when
you're walking across a street and a car
just went by and you're smelling exhaust
fumes, there's still oxygen there with
it. You're still breathing in both.
There's still a mix of air, oxygen, with
those fumes, with that smog because
you're 20 ft away, 30 ft away, 10 ft
away, or much more. The air you're
breathing has a mix in it. It has a mix
of the exhaust fumes that came out of
the pipe and a mix of the air that's
surrounding it. So, you're getting
oxygen at the same time you're smelling
the exhaust fumes. Now, the jet engines
do the same thing. They're releasing
exhaust. Fuel is burning up there. And
when the planes are on the runway and
the guys that work on the tarmac
directing those planes, they breathe in
the exhaust fumes from the jet engines,
but they're also breathing in oxygen
from the air that's surrounding them as
well that's mixing in with the fumes
from the jet engines. They're breathing
in some oxygen staying alive while
walking around the tarmac, walking on
the runway, and walking around the jet
engines. So, why are we talking about
this? And why does any of this matter?
Because when 10,000 to 20,000 or 50,000
birds die in a clip, there's a reason
for it. And the reason isn't exhaust
fumes coming out of a jet plane in the
sky.
50,000 birds
migrating, flying, don't die from
breathing in some exhaust fumes mixed
with air mixed with oxygen in the sky.
They don't breathe in exhaust fumes from
a jet engine and all fall to the ground
and die. It doesn't work like that.
Something else is killing them. And as
the planes are flying and the fuel is
burning and the exhaust is venting, that
exhaust interdisperses with the air and
there's oxygen in that air and oxygen
stays in that air. And yes, that exhaust
fume is toxic. And yes, if you were too
close to the engine, it would not be
good. But birds are not dying because of
it. Now, when it comes down to a
chemtrail being released, something
different happens. The contents in a
chemtrail are so toxic that when they're
released, oxygen cannot sustain itself
within it. And there's a reason for
that. Because the contents in that
chemtrail eat up oxygen. They destroy
it. This means that when air intermixes
with the chemtrail, it's different than
air intermixing with exhaust. The free
radicals are so deadly in a chemtrail
that it destroys oxygen instantly,
providing no hope at all for a flock of
birds to survive when entering a
chemtrail or when a chemtrail is
descending upon a flock of birds that
are migrating. So when a chemtrail is 50
ft wide, 100 ft wide and then expands
more and more and becomes 500 ft wide
and becomes 1,000 ft wide and then
becomes 2,000 ft wide and eventually
becoming more than 5,000 ft wide. There
is nowhere to go, nowhere to breathe.
Birds can't survive in that. They can't
sustain themselves in that. Now, if
birds are far enough underneath a
chemtrail, it's safer. It's different.
They can survive their flight pattern
eventually going in a different
direction of that chemtrail. It's all
about Russian roulette. It's all about
hit or miss. It's all about being in the
right place at the right time, wrong
place at the wrong time for birds
because deadly free radicals use up
oxygen. They destroy and eat up oxygen.
So oxygen cannot exist within it. It
cannot interdisperse or mix in on any
level. It gets used up, burned out
immediately. What this means for birds
at the wrong time, wrong place is
immediate death. Now that's why millions
of birds have been falling out of the
sky for years. That's why 10,000 at a
time, 20,000 as a clip, land on roads
and villages or forests where no one
ever sees it or sees them. Now, the lung
of a bird is able to take in air at a
speed and velocity that the bird flies.
And the lung of a bird takes
approximately one breath per flap when
flying at an elevated altitude. Now, the
lung of a bird is able to process oxygen
differently than humans because when
migrating, a bird flies high, where
there's less oxygen, where the air is
thinner. Now, even though birds are
designed for this, it's still a
struggle. It's still difficult. It's
difficult for them to get oxygen when
flying that high. But it's the only way
to keep up with migration, to make the
distance for survival. Now, there's a
rule of thumb for birds. Fly or die. fly
or starve because food runs out. Not all
birds, but most birds have to fly away
to another area to collect food. Which
brings us to the reality, the grim
reality that over time, it's all the
birds that migrate that fly in large
flocks that will eventually get affected
by the chemtrails and most likely die
because of them. If it's not the bird
flu that gets them, it's going to be the
chemtrails that gets them in the end.
Birds that stick around all year and
don't migrate won't be affected so
severely by chemtrails, just partially
because it's in the air, just like
humans get affected partially because
it's in the air. So, as a chemtrail is
released from a plane and starts to
descend upon a flock of birds migrating,
oxygen literally gets dissolved out of
the sky through a chemical interaction
of highly toxic chemicals intermingling
with oxygen itself. A chemical
combustion where the oxygen gets
vaporized instantly. Now, as birds
either fly into this chemtrail or a
chemtrail descends upon a flock of birds
flying and the birds begin to inhale
that chemtrail and those chemtrails,
those toxins enter the lungs of the
bird, any oxygen within the bird's lungs
gets vaporized immediately. The same
chemical interaction occurs. This then
leads to the bloodstream. As the toxins
enter the bloodstream through the bird's
lungs, it begins to vaporize all oxygen
that's in the bloodstream itself and
organs of the bird. Oxygen gets sucked
right out of the bird. And this is why
not just three birds out of 50 birds die
or 100 birds out of 5,000 birds die.
Instead, all 5,000 birds die. or even
50,000 birds in a massive flock die all
at once. This is the sinister assault on
birds that occurs. Now, if there are
birds on the edge of the flock that are
on the edge of the trail or birds that
are on the edge of the trail, the far
edge or the trail as it's descending
upon the flock is missing hitting some
of the birds and they only get partially
sickened. They may go down as well, land
on the ground, flap around before they
die versus all the other birds landing
on the ground already dead. They died up
in the sky. Now, birds flapping around
on the ground sickened by the chemtrails
die with a delayed effect. They can't
survive it even if they were given help.
The reason why is because the poison is
still in their system and dissolving the
oxygen, taking it out of their organs
and out of their blood. They're just
having a slower death from having less
of the poison. But still, in the end,
they die from it. Now, birds are
profound spiritual creatures. So, it's
not a surprise that the chemtrol
programs and the geoengineering programs
are killing the birds at the pace that
they're doing so. The hierarchy or the
shadow government and others that are
responsible for the chemtrail programs
and for the classified geoengineering
programs bask in the practice of killing
such profound spiritual creatures like
birds, which now takes us to a different
topic, but yet it's a topic that's
related. How did the birds get here? Not
all birds were naturally created here on
this planet, planet Earth. Many birds
were brought here from afar, from
distant planets by
extraterrestrials. So man on this planet
that are using these chemtrails and
destroying these birds are in violation
of extraterrestrial laws that brought
the birds here to begin with, which is
another reason that over time aliens,
extraterrestrials will not put up with
the chemtrails and the geoengineering
trails. I hope you enjoyed this episode.
You can go to medicaldium.com for more
free information and find me on Telegram
where I leave exclusive messages. You
can also find me on Rumble, YouTube,
check me out on IG. Sign up to my
newsletter and check out the Medical
Medium book series, the book Cleanse to
Heal, the Brainsaver books, Medical
Medium New Edition, Liver Rescue. Those
are just some of the incredible books
that have saved so many lives around the
world with advanced medical information
that nobody knew. Answers to chronic
illness that opens the door to finally
healing. And if you're someone who's
interested in powerful life-changing
spiritual information, check out medical
medium angels, demons, and spiritual
tools, which you can find on Apple,
Spotify, and Amazon. Always remember,
have compassion for yourself. You're a
good person. Your body loves you
unconditionally and always remember you
can heal. Many blessings and God bless
you. Flight 666, this is the base. Do
you read me?
Over. This is flight 666 to the base.
What can I do for you?
Over. Flight 666. There's reports you
haven't released any chemicals today.
Over. This is flight 666 to the base.
The day is still early. I still have one
more hour to go, sir. Over. Flight 666.
This is the base. Give us a report. Give
us the reason. Is there a malfunction?
Why haven't you released the chemicals?
Over. This is flight 666 to the base,
sir. Well, quite frankly, it's
migration, sir. Lots of birds flying.
Just waiting for an opportunity to
release the chemicals, sir. No harm
done. Over. Flight 666. This is the
base. Release the chemicals. Open up
injectors. Over, sir. This is flight
666. Can't quite read you. Uh, breaking
up, sir. Breaking up. Transmission not
coherent. Over. Flight 666. This is the
base. Stop fooling around. Release the
chemicals. This is going to be a strike
on your record. Over. This is flight 666
to the base. May I ask a question, sir?
Do you like birds, sir? You see, at
home, we have some bird feeders up, and
we watch the birds every day through the
kitchen window, sir. And right now, I'm
kind of giving the birds a little chance
just to get out of my way, sir. Nothing
more than that.
Over. Flight 666. This is the base. It
would be in your best interest if you
release all chemicals now. There's more
problems that come along with defying
orders beyond insubordination. Flight
666, open up all injectors now. This is
flight 666 to the base. Opening up all
injectors, turning all switches on.
Releasing full 50,000 gallons of content
as we speak, sir. Over. Very good.
Flight 666. This is flight 666. Roger
that, base.
Over.
Original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite, only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back, and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.