How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them.
Whether you're dealing with anxiety,
depression, endometriosis, acne, eczema,
autoimmune, thyroid, lime, brain fog,
fatigue, or any other symptom or
condition, you're far from alone.
Living with symptoms has become the new
normal. So, no more guessing games. It's
time to get answers. Welcome to the
Medical Medium Podcast. I'm Anthony
William.
We're talking about your body's ability
to heal. And you have an audience. God
and the angels are watching. That's
right. When we go through chronic
illness, we're not really alone. When
people get sick, they feel that way.
Even when they have people around them,
it's easy to feel lonely when you're
struggling with a sickness, with a
chronic illness, cuz in the end, you
just focus on the symptoms. And how come
everybody else out there looks like
they're living their lives? They feel
like they're fine. They look like
they're normal. But are they? Pretty
much everybody's getting sick out there
and they're getting their turn. But if
you're already struggling, if you
already have chronic illness, keep in
mind that you're spiritually strong.
You're emotionally strong more than you
even know. You're just being rebuilt
from the bottom to the top. You're just
being restored, renewed. Your body wants
to heal and you're in that process of
healing. In this episode, just relax,
get a good comfortable spot. We got some
ground to cover. Are you ready? Let's
get started.
A lot of people are going through it.
They're going through a challenge, a
health challenge. They go to a doctor.
They're trying to get answers. They
think they get answers and maybe they
do, but yet they're still stuck with the
symptom. Doesn't really go away or it
comes and goes or they're better for a
little while naturally just heals and
then it's back but back worse than it
was before. Then it's back to another
doctor and another doctor. Some people
see dozens of doctors throughout the
course of years. There are people out
there that see up to a 100 doctors,
practitioners, health professionals
looking for answers. Their hope is
strong at first, but then it can dwindle
over time. And it gets harder and harder
to get out of the house, to get to
appointments. No one understands unless
they've been there, unless they've felt
it themselves, experienced it
themselves. It's not easy. There's
nothing easy about getting sick. There's
nothing easy about having a mystery
chronic illness. There's nothing easy
about pain. There's nothing easy about
suffering and struggles. And then
another hard part is relaying the
message, relaying what you're going
through. People who are sick, they don't
have it easy for so many reasons and so
many ways. One is expressing themselves,
being able to communicate their pain,
being able to talk about it, being able
to tell somebody else, being able to
have the confidence behind them as
they're telling someone because PTSD
comes along for the ride, and even OCD
can come along for the ride. And then
something people just don't talk about
in the health field enough or at all
even is that most all illnesses chronic
mystery illness is neurological. There's
neurological symptoms involved and
neurological symptoms being involved
means expressing themselves talking
about the problem. Communicating is
difficult because neurological symptoms
lead to the inability to express the
suffering someone's going through. And
when somebody heals from a chronic
mystery illness, a neurological
condition, or any health condition, they
become a treasure trove of experience, a
treasure trove of knowledge. Knowledge
that's much different than everyday
knowledge, than everyday wisdom.
wisdom that's above other wisdom.
Because when you come from ground zero
in your health and you rise out of the
ashes, the pain and suffering is left
behind. But not the experience of the
pain and suffering that stays within
you. It's instilled within you. It
becomes a force, a holy force. And one
of the reasons it becomes a holy force
is because God was there all along. God
was watching with every single struggle.
With all your pain, all your sorrow, God
was there all through it. Whether you
knew or you did not know, God was by
your side. God was watching over you.
God was seeing you sleep at night while
dreaming. God was seeing you sleep at
night knowing you were struggling. God
saw you wake up in the morning knowing
you were sad because your symptoms were
still there because your condition was
still the same. God knew. And if you're
somebody going through any symptoms or
chronic illness or struggles now, God
knows. That's why your recovery and what
you're going through is holy. That's one
of the reasons why it's spiritual and
should never be looked down upon. Should
never be disrespected. What you've gone
through, your healing, your sickness,
your chronic illness, your experiences,
your struggles should never be frowned
upon. They should never be demeaned.
They should never be judged by anyone.
You deserve to heal, but maybe you don't
think you do. When you're sick too long,
you start believing you don't deserve
it. That there's a reason why you're not
getting better. And that reason is
you're a bad person or you did something
wrong or you put yourself into this. You
got yourself sick. You did all the wrong
things. But that's not how it works.
That's not the truth. It's easy to get
conditioned here on earth believing that
you don't deserve to heal, that you're
supposed to be stuck that you don't
deserve to get better. And the minute we
get sick, the minute we get a symptom
and it doesn't resolve fast, the minute
we're not well, we start doubting
everything. And everything means our
body. We doubt our body's ability to
heal. We doubt we did the right thing to
heal. We doubt our own confidence. We
doubt our own hope. We doubt our own
faith. It's easy to believe when you
have chronic illness long enough that
you don't deserve to heal. And it's easy
to start questioning what kind of person
you are, especially that people around
you are wondering why you're still sick.
It happens all the time. The lack of
understanding can occur around you.
People don't understand what it's like
to be sick unless they've been really
sick themselves. Unless they've been in
your shoes or in the same position of
somebody who's been chronically ill for
a long enough time. The truth is is that
everybody at some point in their life is
going to experience some form of
sickness. whether it's acute, whether
it's severe, whether it's mild, but
long-term, but they're going to
experience it. Now, if you're
experiencing it now and you look outside
and you see people living their lives
and everybody looks like they're fine,
they're driving around, they're doing
things, young people look
indestructible, older people are walking
around, nothing's wrong. Keep in mind
that they may get their turn or they may
not be as healthy as they look from a
distance or they seem. Some of them may
be struggling like you. If you're sick
now, if you're struggling with symptoms,
if you got chronic illness and you're
younger, you're a young person, then you
got sick earlier. You earned your
stripes. You're obtaining knowledge.
You're growing spiritually. You're
becoming a stronger soul. You're
becoming a seer.
You can see things other people cannot
see. You got life experiences other
people do not have yet. You may feel
weaker physically, but you're stronger
spiritually. And when the day comes that
you heal, when you recover, you're going
to take all of that with you. And as
you're living your life, people are
going to walk up to you and they're
going to see it and feel it. They're not
going to know what it is, but they're
going to sense it that there's something
different about you. And as you're
standing there, God is going to be
watching. An angel is going to be
seeing. And they were there the whole
time when you were sick. They were there
throughout your entire struggle, whether
you were aware of it or not, because you
weren't alone when you struggled. You
weren't alone when you were sick. It may
have felt that way, but God and the
angels knew what you were going through.
They were watching, seeing your courage,
admiring your strength, understanding
your battle. And if you're in that
battle of chronic illness now and you're
not healed yet, they're watching. You
have an audience and you're not alone.
People think when they get sick and
they're struggling and they're not
getting better that they are weak. But
that's not true. It's the opposite. They
are strong. Really strong. The
strongest.
Just because they can't run 10 miles, do
a backflip, lift heavy weights for 2
hours, athletically compete in a sport,
doesn't mean they're weak on any level.
Sure, physically they're struggling,
physically they're not there, but
mentally they're stronger than anyone.
Spiritually stronger than anyone.
Because what it takes to sustain
yourself when you're chronically sick is
like no other. What it takes to talk to
your mind, to talk to yourself, to walk
yourself through it every single day is
like no other. Everything gets
challenged. Your confidence, your
consciousness, your subconsciousness,
who you are as a person, it gets
deconstructed. It gets purified. And
then it gets reconstructed. Before you
heal or as you're healing, you rebuild
your soul, your consciousness, your
subconsciousness.
Being in the woods for a long time can
do that to a person. Reshape them in a
way that's unmatched. And that person
out there who's athletic or they're
strong or they can exercise every single
day or they're in a sport, they won't
know what that is. They just won't. Just
because they're free will and they're
using their willpower to exercise or
perform doesn't mean they're stronger in
every single way than someone who's
chronically sick. They're used to
battling gravity, battling tiredness
because of overexertion.
People who are chronically sick are
battling mercury, metals, pathogens,
toxins. They're battling a lot of
things. They're battling an inner
struggle that can't be seen. Weakened
nervous systems, mystery, inflammation,
PTSD, OCD, things that come with
illnesses. They come for the ride
because it's so difficult. And the
battle is every single day. And the
strength they have when they're sick,
the strength you have when you're
chronically ill and sick, is unmatched.
It's unlike any other. Over the years,
I've seen athletes become ill, get
chronic inflammation, brain
inflammation,
or some kind of other chronic illness,
and it hits them hard. And they're like,
"Wow, I didn't know that this kind of
challenge is different than the other
kind of challenge I do every day
athletically. I didn't know that it
takes everything I got. Everything
mental, emotional, spiritual, physical,
and how difficult it really is. And
that's what they say. And the same goes
for somebody who isn't an athlete. Maybe
they're just somebody that never got
sick yet. They're not there yet. Maybe
they're in their 20s, their 30s, maybe
early 40s. Nothing really happened. It's
really small stuff. They're living their
life. They're doing what they want and
suddenly it all stops. They get sick and
now they're chronically ill. They're
going doctor to doctor to doctor and
they're realizing it's a different
world. It's a different part of them.
They have to dig deeper than they've
ever dug before. They have to get to
know themselves because that's what
happens. You have to get to know
yourself. You learn things about
yourself you would have never learned if
it wasn't for getting sick. And do they
have what it takes? Do they have what
you have? Can they sustain themselves
emotionally, mentally, spiritually, and
physically before they find the
information, before they find the
knowledge, the keys to how to heal, to
how to move forward? And they will they
will sustain themselves. They will
discover that inner strength. Whatever
guilt you hold, whatever guilt you have,
whatever guilt that sits deep down
inside of you during the process of your
healing,
it's time for it to shed away. It's time
to leave it behind. You didn't create
your chronic illness. You didn't bring
yourself to this place of chronic
illness. You didn't bring yourself
purposely to a place of sickness. It's
not something you wanted. It's not
something you did on purpose. You didn't
do it at all. You didn't purposely do
this to become unwell. It's not a
contract you signed before you were
born. You became unwell, sick. You
became chronically ill for reasons that
were not in your control. But what is in
your control is your healing. No matter
what, you can heal. It is in your
control. And you are going to heal. As
each day goes by, you're getting closer
to healing. Your body's repairing
itself. Your body's recovering. Your
body wants to heal. It's working hard
for you every single day. So each
moment, each hour, each day, you're in
the healing process. And you have to
remember that you have to know that you
are healing and you didn't cause your
sickness and it's not mistakes that you
made. Never believe in any way that it's
because of you and because of any
mistakes you made along the way because
that's not true. That's not how chronic
illness works. We cannot judge ourselves
for why we're sick. We cannot beat
ourselves up for why we're sick. We have
to be gentle about it. We have to be
easy on ourselves. We have to have
compassion for ourselves. And you have
to know that every day your body is
getting closer to healing. If you get a
chance, check out the medical medium
book series. Millions of people from all
around the world have healed using
information from the Medical Medium book
series. Check out medicalium.com to get
a chance. Subscribe to the Medical
Medium newsletter. You can find me on
Telegram, on Rumble, on YouTube, on IG.
Many blessings and God bless you.
Your body is fighting for you every day
and loves you unconditionally. Your body
wants to heal and it will heal. And it
is healing. And it's healing every
single hour of every single day. This is
a truth you can hold on to and never let
it go. Let it be a healing seed, a seed
that's planted, a seed that grows with
every little thing you do for your
health. Always remember you're a good
person. And this is your time to heal.
Never be hard on yourself. Never judge
yourself. Every single morning you wake
up, gently pat yourself on the shoulder.
Tell yourself you're working hard. Tell
yourself you're working for God. Tell
yourself God sees you and understands
your struggles. And tell yourself your
body just did more healing. And when you
lay down to go to bed at night, keep in
mind you have an audience. Keep in mind
the angels are there. Call upon them.
Ask them to sit by your bedside. You
deserve it. You're worthy. You're worth
it to the angels. They see your
struggles. They know what a good person
you are. They know the good works you're
going to do when you're healed. They
know the good works you're doing now.
And the angels know what kind of soul
you have, what kind of soul you are. And
never doubt who you are. You're a good
soul. It's not your fault you got sick.
You didn't create it. You didn't cause
it. It wasn't a form of punishment God
was placing upon you. And you can heal
and you will heal. This is your time.
And always keep in the back of your mind
that good days are coming. And you're
going to look back in the past and
you're going to see how far you have
come, how far along you have gone with
your healing.
Original
published medical medium information
gets stolen and poached by podcast
doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite, only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.