How many people do you know who struggle
with their health? Chances are, whether
they show it or not, most of the people
in your life do. And chances are, you're
one of them.
Whether you're dealing with anxiety,
depression, endometriosis, acne, eczema,
autoimmune, thyroid, lime, brain fog,
fatigue, or any other symptom or
condition, you're far from alone.
Living with symptoms has become the new
normal. So, no more guessing games. It's
time to get answers. Welcome to the
Medical Medium Podcast. I'm Anthony
William.
We're talking about angels. That's
right, angels.
Do you believe in angels? There are a
lot of people that do and then there's
some that don't. And did you know you're
not alone? Now, it's easy to think
you're alone when you don't feel good.
You're on mattress island or you got
some aches and pains and you're sick
going through a lot of different
struggles. Or maybe you went through
some betrayal, some hardships, some
letdowns. It could make somebody think
like, "What's the point?" But the thing
is, there's angels, angelic forces, and
they're around. They're looking out. And
there's a lot of crazy stuff happening
in the world right now. Seems to be
getting worse and worse and worse with
the quickening, but it just puts the
angels on guard. The angels become hyper
aware. This means hyper aare for you.
This means looking out for you. We just
have to learn how to call them. We just
have to keep our eyes open. We just got
to think about them because they're
there and they care. Now remember, we
have an audience. God and the angels are
looking out. Now, in this episode, we're
going to cover some different angels.
Angels you can call upon. Angels that
are hoping you call upon them. Now get
ready. Fasten your seat belts. It's time
to connect to some angels. It's time to
be connected, tuned in. And with angels,
you're in the right place at the right
time.
I've seen signs in my lifetime. I've
seen angels. I know they're real. And
not just real, real. I've seen one when
I was almost drowning underwater saving
my dog many, many years ago. And that
angel saved my life. And throughout the
decades, I've seen others. And I've also
seen the signs. And you have, too.
You've seen the signs. I know you have.
Think about it a little bit. What about
that time you could not explain and it
just didn't make sense how it all
happened? That day, that moment. You
knew something was up. And maybe you're
somebody where you didn't know. You just
don't remember. But it happened.
Something happened. There was a sign.
There was an angel. Something occurred.
Because what happens with human beings
is we block things out. Yes, we block
things out. We don't see it in the
moment. It's not crystal clear.
Something supernatural happens and we
don't really see it. We experience it.
It gets locked up in our
subconsciousness.
Our subconscious holds on to it. Our
soul holds on to it. But we kind of pack
it up, lock it up, and move on as if
nothing ever happened. But it did
happen. It did. And a lot of people out
there, they think back and they're like,
"Wait a minute. That would have never
happened unless this happened. That
would have never occurred unless this
occurred. I would have never got through
that if something supernatural didn't
occur. I would have never made it if God
wasn't involved. If God didn't
intervene, I would have never survived
that. If it wasn't for some kind of
angelic force. And I remember I remember
seeing something. It was there. There
was something holy present. There was
some kind of angelic force present.
There was some kind of godly force there
and present. And what about the people
that had a difficult experience in life,
a struggle, something happened and they
just barely made it out alive and they
know deep down in their heart it could
have been so much worse that something
intervened. Yeah, they got hit hard.
Yeah, they got scarred with something.
But in the end, they know something
interveneed. They made it. They survived
it. As bad as it was, they still
survived it. Every little thing we do
here has an impact. There's an impact
spiritually. I recently heard a story
about a guy that loved to save animals
of all kinds. That's my kind of guy
because I like to do that too. He used
to save bunny rabbits, cats, dogs,
foxes, turtles, coyotes, whatever came
his way. And one day he saw something in
the road as he was driving his car and
it was a snake. He parked his car. He
jumped right out. And he grabbed the
snake without thinking about anything.
And then the snake bit him. Bit him
good. And the snake wasn't a friendly
snake. It was a timber rattlesnake. And
the venom started traveling. Traveling
to kill this man. He went numb. Couldn't
talk. Couldn't walk. First responders
got to him. They got him to the
hospital. He got treatment. He got the
antivenenom and he nearly died. He was
on death's door. When he finally started
coming around and they pulled him out of
the medicine induced coma, he knew he
knew supernatural means, supernatural
powers were there that day. supernatural
powers that either came with the first
responders or were there in his car or
were there above looking down at him as
he got bitten by that snake. And he was
all heart wanted to rescue little
creatures. Little creatures that other
people wouldn't care about. Little
creatures that other people would just
run right over in the streets. Who
cares? But the angels above knew he had
a big heart and had their eyes on him.
And he knew he was saved. And they knew
he cared. He cared about life. He cared
about little animals and their lives.
And is he ever going to jump out and
grab a snake without thinking for a
moment? No. He's never going to do that
again. But still, he was seen from above
and he was spared. He still had
important work to do on planet Earth.
He still had important purpose. He still
had a lot of work to do for God. And
what if he wasn't spared? What if he
died that day right on that road after
being bitten by a snake? Then God had
bigger plans. God and the angels had
another plan for them. And that's what
happens to a lot of people that leave
early. They were watched. They were
seen.
But they needed to go somewhere. They
needed to cross over. They needed to get
to the other side because they needed to
come back because there was a bigger
plan and God needed them to start all
over again. You see, we're never truly
alone down here. Now, when it comes down
to angels, angels tend to walk through
woods. They tend to stand on highways.
They like to stand on bridges. They like
to stand on top of buildings. And
they're experts at chaos. Not chaos
because they create chaos. They do the
opposite. They're experts at knowing
about chaos, seeing it, understanding
it, knowing how it's caused. All the way
from wars to little things that happen
in people's lives that don't feel so
little. Angels are no stranger to chaos.
And angels know people like to do stupid
things. They like to drive drunk, drive
under the influence. They like to peer
pressure people, pushing them over the
edge. They like to bully people till the
people give up and lose hope. And
angels, they watch it all. They see it
all. And angels are looking for people
to tune into them. They're looking for
people who think about them. Angels want
people to be connected. They want people
to care about angels. And there's a
reason for that. Angels want people to
have faith because angels, holy angels,
love God. And angels know people
struggle with God. And that's okay.
Angels protect God and care about God.
And if somebody doesn't care about God,
that's okay. Angels like to turn people
around. Angels like to show signs. Signs
that make people doubt everything they
thought before. Signs that are
miraculous. Signs of things that people
can't explain. Angels want to turn
doubting Thomases around. They want them
to get that aha moment. They want that
wait a minute here. Something is going
on that's beyond anybody's imagination.
Because then a spark of light, a spark
of faith begins. So why are we talking
about all this? Because it's about
getting a deeper connection to the
angels. It's about learning to call upon
the angels. It's about knowing you're
not alone and you are seen from above
and that you can call upon the angels
and you can talk to the angels. You can
ask for help from the angels. And the
one way to do this is to know that
you're worthy. Yes, you're worthy. And
it doesn't have to be a big ego thing.
It's a humble thing. It's a humble
understanding that you are worth it and
that you are worthy. And when you're
sick or been sick, the angels know you
got something they love. They don't want
you sick. They don't want you to have
chronic illness. That's not what they
love. But you got something else they
love. It's that unbelievable powerful
spiritual growth that you have inside
that you have within. And that life
experience of being sick, stricken with
an illness, having a symptom or a
condition is worth everything to angels
is worth everything to the angelic realm
because all that spiritual growth is
collected inside your soul. Your soul is
on another level and it means you have
spiritual power. That spiritual growth
equals spiritual power and it can't be
taken from you ever. Mental hardships,
emotional hardships and physical
hardships are worth their weight in
spiritual light, spiritual wisdom,
spiritual power, spiritual light from
above, God's light, the angel's light.
But you have to see it. You have to know
this. You have to be able to get in
touch with this. And you have to look
out for the signs. They're there. You
just have to see them. You have to be
open-minded. You have to be open to it.
You have to look for them. And it's okay
if you're not. The signs will still be
there. You might see one. You might
catch one. They're still there. But what
if we make that connection stronger?
What if we learn to call upon the
angels? You see, you have every
God-given right to reach out to the
angels. You were born with this right to
reach out to angels. So, let's talk
about the 27 essential angels. To begin
with, these aren't the only angels.
These are just some of the angels that
are around us, that are above us that
work for God. Let's start with the angel
of faith. And although the angel of
faith is there to help you build faith,
to help instill faith in you, you can
call upon the angel of faith for other
things, too. She's there to help you
build conviction. She wants you to have
faith. If you're lacking faith, she
wants you to have strong faith. She's
one of the easiest angels to call upon,
especially if you're sick, especially if
you have a symptom, especially if you're
ailing, if you're hurting, if you're in
pain. The angel of faith wants you to
hold that faith strong while you're
healing. And then she wants you to have
a faith that you're going to heal, a
faith in healing. And you can say,
"Angel of faith, I need your help. I
need to build my faith. I need it
stronger. Can you please come and help?"
Another angel that's really powerful and
easy to call upon is the angel of trust.
And if you're somebody and you're
hurting and you don't feel good and
you've been sick a long time and you
lost trust in your body, trust in the
system, trust in the medical system,
trust in people, trust in anything, then
it's time to call the angel of trust to
help you when you're struggling, when
you're trying to recover. And one of the
hard parts about losing trust, one of
the hard parts about being sick is you
lose trust in your own decisions. And if
you're losing trust in your own
decisions, then it's time to call the
angel of trust. Angel of trust, I need
help. Can you please come down? Are you
there? I need your guidance. I need my
trust to get stronger. I'm trying to
heal and I need my trust stronger to do
so. Another angel that's really powerful
is the angel of mercy. One of the most
powerful angels out there. An angel that
can match the archangels and strength.
An angel with a lot of compassion. An
angel that works for God, the angelic
realm with all its glory. And the angel
of mercy is called upon, is summoned by
God many times to battle darkness, to
fights for humankind. The fight fights
for God. Do you think she's too out of
reach? No. The Angel of Mercy is not.
She's there for you. You just have to
ask. You just have to ask for the Angel
of Mercy's help. Angel of mercy, I need
your help. Will you please come down?
I'm having a fight, a battle in life. I
need help. I feel like my soul's being
challenged. I feel like my body is
losing steam. Can you help me? One angel
I truly love is the angel of healing.
The angel of healing helps with the
soul, helps with anxiety, helps with any
kind of struggle, helps with a sickness
and illness, especially for long term.
The angel of healing is a wonderful
angel to call upon when there's a sick
loved one, someone you're sitting by
their bedside, they're struggling,
they're going through a lot. You call
upon the angel of healing and things
start to calm down. You'll notice
something change as she enters the room.
And then there's the angel of
restitution. This angel understands the
soul, understands the spirit and how it
can be beaten down. This is an angel
that understands emotional trauma,
emotional abuse, emotional hardship. She
understands if somebody has done you
wrong. She understands if some worldly
power, some institution, or some
individual has harmed you. The angel of
restitution has your back. Just got to
call upon her. And then there's the
angel of purity. There are so many
people out there with addictions. It's
how this world works. You can get
addicted to anything. Darkness in this
world wants us to have temptation. Wants
us to have addictions. Wants us to be
slaves to addictions. And if you're
struggling, struggling with anything,
any kind of addiction, you call upon the
angel of purity. Angel of purity, I feel
stuck. I feel trapped. I can't break
this addiction. I can't stop my coffee
drinking. I can't stop my cigarette
smoking. I can't stop my arguing. I
can't stop the recreational drugs. I
can't stop from running away. And I
can't stop my worrying. I need your
help. You have to come. You have to help
me, please. And then there's the angel
of peace. I love the angel of peace and
I've used the angel of peace many times
in my life. I've asked for help along
the way. You can ask for the angel of
peace to quiet your mind to help you
think about positive things, to calm
your brain, calm your mind, calm your
neurotransmitters,
calm down your electrical impulses,
relax your neurons, soothe your soul, or
just ask the angel of peace to sit by
your bedside, to sit there at night. Ask
the angel of peace to sit there all
night long. Especially if you're sick,
if you're unwell, you don't feel good,
and you have a lot of worry, ask the
angel of peace to come by. Tell the
angel of peace that you're unwell, and
you would love her support. And then
there's the angel of dreams. You can ask
the angel of dreams to enter your dream.
Enter your dream state, to be in your
dream, looking out for you. guarding
you, protecting you while you're
dreaming. Ask the angel of dreams to
help you decode your dreams, give you a
better understanding. And if you ask the
angel of dreams to come to your dreams
every single night to enter them,
something profound happens. Your dreams
become more clear, more vivid. They
become more understandable and you make
connections with your dreams and you see
signs in your dreams. And then there's
the angel of time to help you remember
things that you forgot. They're in
there. They're in your soul. They're in
the memory banks. They're in your
neurons, but they're not accessible.
You're asking the angel of time to time
travel for you. You're asking the angel
of time to look for those memories to
bring you back there, to actually bring
you to that place. So all of a sudden,
these memories start to arrive. Good
memories, beautiful memories. Memories
that have been lost. They're gone.
They've been forgotten. Ask the angel of
time to help you find resolve.
experiences that were forgotten that can
solve puzzles in your life that can
solve problems. Say to the angel of
time, "Angel of time, can you help me?
Can you come here? Can you sort things
out? Can you take me back in time? Can
you help me remember things,
experiences,
moments that were precious in my life? I
want to feel that feeling that I had. I
want to experience
what occurred back then. I want to use
it now in my difficult times. I want to
remember moments in my life that needed
resolve so I can resolve them now. Can
you help me? Never be afraid to call
upon the angels.
Never be scared to ask for help. Never
feel that you don't have the worth, that
you are not a good person, that you
don't deserve help from the angels.
Never feel you don't deserve help from
God. Never feel that you don't deserve
anything. You're a good person.
You should call the angels. You should
ask for help. You deserve good things.
And you're a spiritual person.
And you have a spiritual connection, a
connection up above, a connection to the
angels, a connection to God. Never
forget it. If you get a chance, check
out the Medical Medium book series.
Life-saving information. Check out
medicaldium.com for free recipes, free
healing information. You can find me on
Telegram, YouTube, Rumble, IG. And
always remember, you can heal. Many
blessings and God bless you.
Comes to a point in everyone's life
where they think no one understands and
they feel they're alone in what they're
struggling with. They're alone in what
they're facing. Even when there's people
around them, even when loved ones are
around them, they can feel lost. They
can feel sad. They can feel lonely. And
they can feel like no one's really
listening. And when it comes to chronic
illness, it becomes a personal battle.
Every day could feel like a struggle.
Even every hour can feel like a
struggle. And with so many aspects of
chronic illness, it is a struggle. A
struggle that others can't understand
unless they've been there before. And if
you're in that struggle and you feel
like you're alone, I got words for you.
You're not alone. The angels are
watching. the angels you can call upon.
There are people out there that feel a
loved one is watching them. They feel a
loved one is around them, that has
crossed over, that has left. And that's
true. Maybe there is a loved one that's
keeping an eye out. And that does
happen. But also what happens is that
angels are around. They are nearby. They
give out an energy. They give out a
warmth. You have to look for the signs.
And you might have seen the signs
before, but just don't realize it that
they were there. You might have walked
by the signs. You might have heard
something. You might have felt
something. Angels want you to believe in
them. Angels want to help, but they need
you to be involved as well. Angels want
your faith strong. And if it isn't,
that's okay. The angels love you anyway.
There comes a time when you look back
behind you and your struggles are far
away. Your pain, your suffering, your
illness, your sickness have been long
gone and you're standing strong. And
you'll remember that you weren't alone.
You'll see it clear. You'll remember a
time when you now know an angel was
near.
Original
published medical medium information
gets stolen and poached by podcast
doctors, social media doctors,
influencers, and medical clinics.
Medical medium information has never yet
been proven wrong by medical science and
research. Instead, the opposite. only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative health
communities. Medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better. If you choose to share or use
the original unique content from the
Medical Medium podcast, books, or
Medical Medium social media, please site
where this information comes from so
others who see and learn of this
information have a chance to know where
it all originates to give them an
opportunity to heal so they don't end up
losing years of their life searching for
answers like so many have before them.
The medical medium information here on
this podcast doesn't come from broken
science, interest groups, medical
funding with strings attached, botched
research, lobbyists, internal kickbacks,
persuaded belief systems, private panels
of influencers, health field payoffs,
trendy traps, or gathered bits and
pieces of gimmicky confusion. Because
chronic illness is exploding like never
before in our modern-day history, it
takes a greater force than us down here.
It takes a helping hand from above.
Medical medium information has street
cred. It's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing. More healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their
life-changing experiences, of rising out
of the ashes of sickness and entering
into the light of full recovery, getting
their lives back, and finally healing
when nothing else in the world of health
could move the needle and get them
better. The information on this podcast
is not man-made. It comes from above,
from a higher source. Whatever you
believe in, whether God, the universe,
the light, or the creator, or if you
believe in nothing at all, that we're
just floating through space together on
this rock, know that the information you
hear on this podcast is separate from
all the other noise out there. It comes
from a different place. A pure
untampered with advanced clean
uncorrupted original primary source. A
higher source, spirit of compassion.