369 cleanse 369
cleanse by the way you can download this
right here link is in the bio link is in
the description you can go to Medical
mem.com you can download it that's it
right there you'll see it
backwards see backwards on IG but 369
cleanse okay free download it's not
$3,000 it's not $5,000 program it's not
$1,000 program but yet it's healed more
people than any of the $5,000 $3,000
$1,000 programs out there it's gotten
that many people's lives back around the
world I mean just read the
testimonials read the reviews 369
cleanse and cleanse the heal book so if
you don't have it you should and if
you're somebody struggling if you're
suffering you should have this cleanse
you should have the book and I'm not
doing this thing where I'm trying to
sell you a big old cleanse for like
$33,000 or do like subscription fees on
my website pay walls all that stuff you
know that do you guys remember me saying
that like four years five years
ago remember like five years ago where I
would talk about that I would be like no
subscription fees no this no that it's
free go to the library get the book for
free still I'm the only one saying that
out there now as far as like what's
going on I mean seriously so get the
download for free the 369 cleanse a
lifesaving cleanse I'm not trying to
sell you anything it's a life saving
cleanse right there in my hands you can
this is the print out of it but you can
get the download link is in the
description link is in the bio if you
don't have cleanse to heal I don't know
what to say at this point if you don't
have it you should have it go to the
library yes take it out for free borrow
it for free why not hey you guys good to
see you just get it out for free what do
you have to lose if you're somebody
that's struggling you got a sickness you
got an illness you got a symptom conquer
it conquer it yeah definitely break that
symptom down break that illness down
kick its ass conquer it you can you can
you can do it you can recover you can
break through your illness you can
recover you can heal yes you can heal
I'm just trying to get the message
through if someone's out there some
somebody that sees this that is dealing
with a
symptom you can move forward you can
move the needle it's possible it really
is because it's already happened for
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of people you guys it has and you guys
know the
369 cleanse we're talking about the 369
cleanse truly an incredible cleanse
really is just want to say one one last
time for now download it for free all
right download it for free right here
and this isn't the full 369 okay but you
can get this download it has so many of
the parts and pieces and the points in
it and it even has five recipes in the
simplified that aren't in the book five
recipes that are in the simplified that
aren in the book it's really a great
download by the way mm school I just saw
that yeah so we got cleans the heal rate
here so if you're somebody that doesn't
think they don't need to
cleanse just look at the mock one
illnesses mock
one illnesses the mock one sicknesses
The Mach One symptoms out there The Mach
One cancers out there just look at
what's happening it is
insane Stephie Synergy 144 over there on
YouTube this 369 cleanse gave me my life
back that means everything to me it does
it means everything to me that's why I'm
doing this that's why I'm messaging
Spirit of compassion it's information
this isn't just a made of CLE cleanse
like la la put this here put this here
it's from Spirit of compassion and
that's that's the whole reason I want
you to heal I want to be that messenger
so you heal Michelle over there over on
YouTube I healed completely from all
symptoms and conditions with the medical
medium information I did the cleanse I
did heal wow lupus whoa oh my God all
that W waving like all that amazing
amazing um shine bright hello this
cleanse is amazing with
healing whoa condenses so much in
healing into a smaller amount of time
for me I get to jump forward on my
healing Journey whoa so you actually you
you downloaded this then you should or
or you got the book cleanse to heal
right amazing look I just want to say to
you guys okay seeing you heal seeing you
get your life back it's everything to me
it's what matters it's what matters the
most that's what it's all about I don't
know if you have cleanse to healed here
it is right here you guys I just want to
show you do you have cleans a heel over
there on Tik Tok cleanse a heel over
there on YouTube do you have the book
you won't be disappointed
okay go go into the library get it for
free I don't care I don't care I mean
it's on Amazon it's 48% off right now
something like that you can get it on
Amazon Anna I recommended cleanse to
heal to a personal trainer this week he
knew of you but wasn't sure if your
information was for real I told him that
I healed my migraines and varicosa veins
you know the varicose veins thing is a
big deal I hear that a lot with the
cleansing the heel book and the
different cleanses in there I hear that
a lot with the 369 where varicose veins
back down they heal they start going
away spider veins back down and start
going away that's a big deal for a lot
of people like spider veins that that
that really bothers a lot of people
spider veins get like they get out of
control and they're all over the ankles
and they're all over the calf and
they're all over the shin and they're
all over the knee and the spider veins
or everything everywhere they show up
like spiders you know on somebody's
body to get rid of that without surgery
to get rid of varicose veins without
surgery I mean there's people that go
and they're just getting their their
legs cut open and they're doing you know
and then or they're doing electronic
surgeries where all this where that
whole thing is brutal and then all of a
sudden they all come back it's important
that we get toxins out of us it's
important that we cleanse the poison out
so that we can do some healing this
matters it really does getting your life
back getting back on track moving
forward come on it's the new year we can
do this we can heal we have the tools we
have what it takes sense over there 369
took away a lot of the patterns which
were so so
toxic duly noted duly noted that's a big
deal that's a really big deal deal this
matters to me okay this is why I do what
I do wake up in the morning I do it over
again I don't care I'll push through
I'll fight for it I don't care about the
hassles and the hate or the jealousy
that's out there the sabotage or
whatever because nobody no the world
doesn't want that many people healed
don't get fooled don't get fooled it
doesn't it doesn't want a large swath of
people on the planet here
it doesn't it doesn't mind a few people
healed here a few people he healed here
the world doesn't mind that the powers
at
be the darkness the evildoers on the
planet they don't mind a few people
healing here a few people healing there
but they don't want a large large large
crew of people healing like in the
medical medium communities where massive
amounts of people have healed and turned
their lives around and in the jealousy
and in the health field that's a whole
another level you know what happened
with medical me this book right here
okay this book right here was brought
into every doctor's office around the
globe millions and millions of copies of
this book right here went into people's
hands all around the world and they
walked into their doctor's offices and
they're like look at this because nobody
knew anything about pathogens and
viruses and what in the upen bar how it
actually caused neurological problems
nobody knew that I'm sorry but nobody
knew Epstein bar caused neurological
problems that's medical medium that's
Spirit of compassion right I can't take
the full credit for that at all I'm I'm
the messenger but the point is is that's
medical medium information and then
everybody heard it everybody out there
they're hearing medical medium medical
medium medical medium more people
getting the books medical medium and
they're healing and healing it was this
Grassroots movement where people were
healing and using the information right
it's really that that amazing but I wake
up in the morning and I just do it all
over again I put the kick me sign on my
on my back and I say let's do this um
yeah because you healing and getting
your life back is all that matters and I
say this and I said it before you don't
have to like me you don't have to like
my glasses you don't have to like the
way I look you don't have to like the
way I
dress like
when does that really matter if you're
sick you got chronic fatigue syndrome
you got trembles Tinkles numbness
dizziness vertigo you're gonitis
screaming in your ears you don't feel
good you're totally unwell who cares
what I dress like or what I look like or
something like that who cares or you
don't like my voice or something people
like I don't really like that guy I like
this other guy here okay well then go
heal go heal with that other guy fine
that other guy can heal you that's
amazing can't come back here get into
the
information get what you need and heal
definitely move forward because that's
what it's about it's about that right
there
um yeah so anyway you know I say this
because
sometimes we need just we need just a
little tug you know we get sick we stay
sick and we stay in that sickness and we
get worn down and beat up and beaten
down and we just can't seem to pull out
of it so a lot of people they get so
beaten down by the process of being sick
doctor to doctor to doctor to doctor and
by the way take this to your doctor and
ask your doctor what's right for you
take the cleanse the 369 right out of
cleanse to heel take it to your doctor
ask your doctor can I do this please can
I do this take a look at this doctor can
you look at this and see defin itely you
should do that you should do that ask
your doctor if it fits into what he's
doing or she's doing in the whole
bit sickness can beat us down it can
people can get really really run down
and tired from it it's not just the
doctor's appointments it's nobody
understanding it's people misjudging you
people misunderstanding
you people trying to shame you people
trying to blame you all of that
becomes a problem when you're sick and
it it's tough It's really tough because
not only do you have to deal with all
the BS and not only do you have to deal
with all the hardship and the struggle
but you got to deal with your sickness
too how about that you know other people
out there be like yeah well you know I
got it pretty hard I got this problem I
got this issue I got it hard you it's
not about their health it's about
something else yeah you know I got this
car insurance problem and I was on the
phone for two straight days well you
have a car insurance problem once in a
while you're on the phone for for two
straight days you have a phone problem
once in a while you're on the phone for
two straight days but you're sick you're
sick they're not you know a lot of
people that don't realize it and they're
not chronically sick they have to do the
same crap they have to go to the store
they got to deal with things they got to
take things back if something was like
you know if if something wasn't right or
they got to do this they got to do that
whatever it is they got family stuff
they got emotional stuff they're dealing
with
right they get all the struggles you
still got all those too but you're sick
and you're struggling if someone's sick
with chronic illness they have all that
plus
that you know I got a friend and my
friend was complaining and complaining
complaining about a bunch of things and
I'm like dude whatever you're
complaining about can you imagine if you
were sick with chronic illness and all
that because that's that's that's the
hard part right there is living with a
symptom or a condition and dealing with
all the stuff that everybody has to deal
with in life it's the combination of
both think about that that's really hard
for a lot of people a lot of people so
what's so special about the
369 number one the only cleanse out
there along with the other medical
medium cleanses that protects your
adrenals saves your adrenals so you can
cleanse yeah saves your adrenals you
want to do a long long water fast just
destroy your adrenals do you want to do
do you want to do a big old milk cleanse
you destroy your adrenals do you want to
do intermittent fasting you destroy your
adrenals nobody gives a [ __ ] out there
they just don't they don't meaning all
the makers and pushers of this stuff
they have no idea probably anyway but
even if they did have an idea I don't
think most of them would care just do my
cleanse just do my
cleanse and what happens is that these
cleanses here from above were designed
so your adrenals are saved but nobody
would know how to save an adal Ral gland
out there because in the world of Health
I don't know if you guys knew this going
back 10 20 30 40 years ago there were no
understandings of like how you can
cleanse or do something for yourself and
protect your adrenal did did you guys
know that it's not like there's this
thing going all the way back that
existed where protect your adrenals
while you're
cleansing the whole adrenals and
protecting adrenals while you're
cleansing is medical medium information
is the only cleanses that protect your
adrenals while you're
cleansing there's so much adrenal
information in the books I almost think
the books are just all adrenal
information
sometimes like
seriously like that's how much adrenal
information is in the books it's
insane so yeah what people don't realize
out there is with cleanses you drink a
whole B here's this is ridiculous if you
hear this if you hear about a cleanse
where you drink a whole bunch of olive
oil in the morning or something like
that run run
screaming run
screaming
seriously what a way to get yourself
sick wake up in the morning be like ah
I'm going to try to do this biohack
right here and maybe try to cleanse or
something I'm going to drink a glass of
olive oil and send it on down Run Run
for the hills man run for the from the
hills okay great way to mess up your
adrenals great way to screw up your
liver just great
way yeah yeah May they're
new yeah
so the whole point here is what I'm
trying to get at is these cleanses
actually protect and help even heal your
adrenals protect and even help heal your
adrenals so much
so when you actually restore your
adrenals after you're getting rid of all
the toxins and you're cleansing and
you're cleaning everything up and you
restore your
adrenals look
out because then if you go and you
change your
diet and you actually start bringing in
stuff you haven't eaten a long time
you're going to feel like a burst and
what that burst is your adrenals then
going explode explode
explode yeah well I've been doing
medical medium I got my symptoms down
I've been healing I've been doing mm and
what does that mean anyway we got to
talk about that a little bit too like
what do you mean you're doing mm like
seriously have you been just doing hmds
that would be amazing if you you're just
doing the celery juice are you doing a
monoc cleanse for a long time are you
doing all the supplement Protocols are
you picking and customizing your own
supplement protocol like what is it
you're doing there people every day out
there I hear it there I do medical
medium and then you all of a sudden see
they're posting something later on or
something and they're posting all this
other stuff it's terrible it's not even
mmm or anything it's like okay thanks
for saying you do M but you're doing a
bunch of other stuff and it's not
working for you
but what happens is when people really
do medical medium they do right really
do it they're they they understand stay
away from the natural flavor stay away
from the canola oil okay keep the fats
low right do the cleanses periodically
if you want do a straight 369 you could
do it for life but do do it right and
they doing it what happens is is you
start cleaning up you start healing your
symptoms you start recovering you start
rebuilding yeah you start rebuilding and
recovering but then you're kind of like
on an even
Keel and then you get off and you eat
big old greasy pizza with pepperoni on
it and cheese or you eat a whatever
something else and all of a sudden
you're like boom wait a minute I can do
this well yeah you did so much healing
you did so much recovering you how many
people have done that so much recovering
they're just back to eating whatever
macaroni and cheese this this this this
I'm not talking about medical medium
macaroni and cheese and they're and then
boom or say they've been doing the
cleanses and they've been not they
haven't been eating
beef they haven't been eating red meat
for a while his medical mum information
is not about being anti-red meat you can
do the information do the protocols do
some healing do the hmds and still do
meat it's about making sure you do all
the right things and you're doing all
you know looking out but if you're doing
the cleanse and you're doing one of
these powerful cleanses like the 369 and
then you come off that cleanse and you
start eating red meat you're going to
get a burst you're going to be like oh
my God because what happened was during
the 369 you're restoring your adrenals
and they're getting stronger and
stronger and stronger and they're
healing you're bringing your adrenals
back and they're getting stronger
stronger and they're healing that's
what's happening and as your adrenals
are healing all you got to do is shove
down some red
beef red beef shove down some
chicken and then your adrenals are going
to go meaning they're going to release a
lot of
adrenaline because there's all of a
sudden all this heavy overt fat in your
system so okay okay forget that you're
going to shove down a whole bunch of
tablespoons of almond butter you're
going to shove down a whole bunch of a
whole bunch of nut butter
and your adrenal glands are going to or
you're going to have a pizza with a
whole bunch of oil on it and cheese and
your adrenal glands are going to go and
you're going to be high you're going to
be euphoric you're going to be like oh
my God this is what I needed I needed
this all my all this time I needed this
hard good high quality cheese I needed
this raw milk I needed this red beef
I I needed this this
whatever and then you're just your
adrenals are just going to go boom and
they're going to be pumping you're going
to feel it coursing through your veins
and you're also going to be kind of like
on a high because you're going to be
like well the first time in a while even
though I healed my symptoms even though
I'm like 80% better which I could never
do anywhere else but I'm doing it on the
369 and I'm like 80% better I'm going to
go and eat this chocolate bar and this
chocolate cake I'm gonna go and eat this
one thing for I haven't had in a long
time with some friends and what's G to
happen is your adrenaline you're GNA be
like your adrenal your adrenals are
going to be getting ready for it and
then you're G to eat it and they're just
going to go
like is what they're going to do and
they're going to release all that
adrenaline it's going to go coursing
through your veins you're going to be
like yeah yeah this is what I
needed this is what I
needed that's what it's going to be like
you know I haven't had migraines aw
since I met you at Cafe Gratitude
enjoy let's see enjoy your
pets enjoy your
Parks
um well you know we did the light
blast we did the light blast I say that
because
woo I needed a nap after that K I needed
a nap
sorry Maggie the cleanse is what really
help help me heal it's
amazing you guys and I'm going to do
listen I'm working on some stuff with
how I can serve how I can serve you guys
it's all I ever think about is how I can
serve you guys what way can I serve you
guys free information that's life saving
sure free information that's life saving
constantly right whatever I can do free
free free free right I've said that
before over the years okay you know not
like somebody who was just like talking
crap about me the other day today in the
health field and they were like don't do
medical medium stuff but make sure you
uh pay my subscription fee for
information once a month okay yeah I'll
give you $50 once a month to read your
regurgitated crap that's not even like
legit Black Island girl over there I've
been following your protocol for six
months now and I've never felt
better whoa whoa whoa that's that's
incredible that's
incredible it really is okay absolute
okay Angels abound says absolutely
life-changing cleanse thank you for
changing my life 369
cleanse it's just it's miraculous it
really is you can do the
simplified you can do the
advanced I mean you can
do any one of the three and you can you
can say hey can do the original you can
do any one of the
three and you can just crack at it
little bit at a time do one day do two
days you push through three days four
days you push through five six seven
eight
nine you can get yourself to the
advanced
369 the advanced 369 you can get
yourself to hear the advanc
369 okay over there
all right so
yes I'm moving the needle and I feel so
damn good thank you Anthony and S
so 369 cleanse right
here why do we have to be so much
more strict with cleanses than 10 plus
years ago what's going on so we're going
to talk about that intoxification
intoxication
toxified free radicals poisons toxins
we're going to talk about that in a
little bit Advance 369 right here okay
now I get it I get it I get it everybody
wants like Quick videos under 30 seconds
of shocking awe with a biohack involved
I get it a lot of people want that they
do they do but when you're sick and
you've been through everything you've
done everything man it's time to do some
healing it's time to
heal it's time to get into the
information from above the
369 right
there it isn't just more toxins than
ever before and I'm going to tell you
right now we used to worry about the
oceans the oceans are toxic the oceans
are toxic the oceans are toxic look out
look out they're toxic they're getting
more toxic there's mercury in the oceans
there's all kinds of you know dioxins
dioxins they all you know in the ocean
right glysophates in the ocean
everything's in the ocean it's all in
there pesticides in the ocean all these
things in the ocean
right human bodies are dirtier than the
oceans
now human bodies surface Sur surfing on
the big waves are dirtier than the big
waves yeah that's right that's right I
don't know about you guys but for me
when I think about that I'm like when I
think about that
seriously okay people swimming in the
ocean are more toxic than the
ocean yeah that's right they
are people swimming in the ocean and
their armpits sweating while they're
swimming they're out gassing with
flatulence in the
ocean their feet all kinds of fungus all
kinds of yeast around their toes there's
swimming in the
ocean like feet collect all kinds of
crap I
mean like the the whole thing with feet
right and the feet fetishes out there
and stuff you know people biting other
people's toes and stuff like that
whatever the yeast the fungus the mold
the like the bacteria in between toes
and on feet I don't mean after the
person soaked their feet and their nice
nice and squeaky clean because it it's
still there it's still there it's still
there you know anyway them swimming in
the ocean people are more toxic than the
ocean now it used to be the other way
around where the oceans were just more
toxic they were more toxic they just
were Metals dioxins Mercury algae algae
blooms but people believe it or not are
even more toxic their livers are filled
with more garbage more junk more crap
their livers are really really toxic
that's the world we live in now people
are highly toxic and the irony is so
many of the biohacks are making them
more toxic which is
crazy crazy Pearl powder great way great
way to tear up the intestinal track also
add toxins it's like you know people
don't even realize that's just one thing
and everything else and what about the
protein craze here's what happens the
protein the protein
demon the protein
demon is literally going
to
destroy destroy the brains of so many
people so they never heal so they never
heal yeah there's a new upcoming wave of
sick young people and they're being
conditioned on the protein scam
conditioned on the protein scam all you
see on social is protein protein protein
proteins everything that's all it's all
you see on social is people screaming
about protein it is by far one of the
stupidest things I've ever seen hands
down one of those and I would actually
be one of those people too if I didn't
know if I didn't have Spirit of
compassion I would easily be if I was
into health I wasn't into Health when I
was when I was a kid Spirit of
compassion made me and made me be into
health I wouldn't be into it I
wouldn't no way no way no way even
though these are the most unbelievable
medical Bibles out there in the world
that have turned people's lives around
it wouldn't have been what I wanted to
do I was you know pushed into it forced
into it by Spirit of compassion but the
protein thing I would be a sucker for
that one too easily easily I'd be like
yeah you got to count your protein okay
don't count your protein but you need
enough protein did you get enough
protein are you protein deficient yeah
what about the protein oh you're on some
kind of diet what are you getting enough
protein oh good it's high enough in
protein amazing wait are you sick are
you dying you didn't get enough protein
something's wrong with you I would be an
insane nut job like you see out there
totally consumed in the protein fear the
protein demon it is insane to the degree
the protein fear and the protein demon
actually do their thing out there the
conditioning the conditioning of prote
protein utterly insane that's all it is
out there now and even the people
that're like I don't count protein I
just live my life you see some
influencers CU they want to stand out
and be different than the other people
you'll see some influencer be like I
don't worry about protein and I don't
really worry about what I eat I just do
the right things I eat a couple healthy
things they're worried about protein you
look at their feed three months later go
in their feed back a year ago they were
crazed about protein the whole point is
everybody is it is literally literally
literally
unbelievable unbelievable
ridiculous stupidity the protein
problem everybody gets enough protein
everybody's been getting enough protein
unless unless you live somewhere and
you're like poor and you're eating
dirt and you're you're just like digging
and looking for a worm which is high in
prote
unless you're
like like all you have is white rice
that's not brown rice it's just white
rice it's been processed just totally
processed unless you're living somewhere
and you're in a hut somewhere and you're
only you've only been given just white
rice meaning the center of the the
center of the grain stripped stripped of
anything right bleached and stripped and
that's the only thing you've been given
I I mean you might get you might get
protein deficient over time you
might nobody's protein deficient nobody
has protein
deficiencies nobody
does you don't unless you're being starv
to death and what you're being starved
on doesn't
have even one amino
acid nobody nobody's deficient of
protein but you'll see people are sick
sick and dying people are dying and
they're on tons of
protein I know there's a there's a guy
on social that's been screaming about
things like protein and everything else
and protein and all this stuff and the
guy's blood letting himself because he
has he has a condition and he's blood
letting himself because he has a
condition so he's bloodletting himself
the protein didn't fix him the protein
didn't fix the guy
the is literally blood letting himself
and his protein protein and everything
else about protein wasn't the answer for
the guy the guy's in the health scene
and he's bloodletting himself he's
teaching people how to bloodlet real
smart real smart the point I'm trying to
say is how come the protein didn't fix
you
man Josh I gained over 50 pounds of
muscle on lowfat low protein plant-based
medical medium um thank you for saying
medical medium because there's
plant-based but it's
different there's plant-based and it's
different okay you can be like doing
like what you call keto or something and
but you could be doing medical medium
style so you can heal and say you know
it's good to have the medical medium
there when it applies when it applies
Fazio over there on YouTube I survive
because of your information especially
also the spiritual information thank you
for acknowledging that my
build it up because of what you do thank
you for acknowledging the spiritual
information I mean I remember was it 4
years ago or something like that people
screaming that I wasn't spiritual or
something like that oh no I I only hear
a voice The Voice put talks about the
soul in the books um the voice talks
about the golden rope I mean I don't
know what to say as a messenger I'm just
doing the best I can but remember there
was like there was like a moment in time
where people like he's not spiritual
he's not
spiritual and and I was scratching my
head saying the spirit of compassion
like did we do something wrong because I
don't know I I thought I put spiritual
information in the books that you told
me
about Erica you're laughing out loud
laugh out loud out loud
so the protein thing is insane watch it
grow it's going to grow into a massive
monster conditioning people and and it's
going to be the Takeover it's the next
takeover it's protein you're going to
see 10 more stupid drinks you know out
there on ad running ads about proteins
in it you're going to see more protein
talk than ever before you're just going
to see and hear about protein left and
right you know CLA says you're the most
spiritual I'm honored and you know and
in spirit of
compassion the the amount of protein
talk that you guys are going to be up
against pretty soon it's going to be
unbelievable but everybody gets protein
you eat one bean you eat you eat hummus
you eat an ounce sure an ounce of
steak whatever it's everywhere you eat a
nut you eat a leaf of spinach you want
protein protein that's actually
assimilable you want protein that
actually absorbs do the medical medium
spinach soup because it's it's the
protein that actually goes into into to
the body and gets utilized and broken
down what about spirulina what about
spirulina spirulina is is is one of the
most
bioavailable protein
sources most bioavailable protein Source
barleygrass juice powder is one of the
most bioavailable protein sources you
know why I don't scream about protein
medical medium information you get
plenty of protein you get the best
proteins you get the best best proteins
I'm sorry but you do medical medium
information you get the best
proteins I mean I if I'm annoying
anybody just you know you could say so I
don't know what to say but it's true you
get the most bioavailable protein from
the sparina the barley grass cheese but
are you kidding that's just two things
the spinach soup all the leafy greens
nobody talked about leafy greens medical
medium
information I mean I'm just saying
medical medium information didn't create
and grow a leafy green leafy greens
aren't here because of me no because of
the spirit of compassion no they're
[Music]
not God's seeds you know God seed seeded
the planet the leafy greens
okay but people were eating like the
hygienic movement was eating just
iceberg lettuce it was eating iceberg
lettuce right iceberg lettuce
and now they're attacking leafy greens
this is the hilarious part right here we
need leafy greens we need leafy herb
greens like parsley and
cilantro and now they're attacking
it it's like that one idiot that keeps
on running ads 24/7 to the medical
medium Community him and his
daughter-in-law or something like that
they got that sham of a business right
they're they keep on talking bad about
cilantro they keep on talking bad about
spir Lina they didn't even know what
spirina was years
ago they were probably like balloon
sales people or something like that
nothing wrong with people you know
selling
balloons I don't know don't quote me on
that part but I can tell you
this I can tell you this they're talking
bad about spirina and cilantro cilantro
is one of the most life-saving
herbs
God God God up there how dare you make
and create
cilantro you must have been wrong God
you must have had something wrong with
you when you created cilantro
because that like doctor that lost his
license and his daughter-in-law thinks
cilantro is really bad so you know what
God you must be wrong all this time and
they must be right the doctor that lost
his license the chiropractor that lost
his license and his
daughter-in-law they must be the right
ones but not you God you're the wrong
one cilantro is terrible no one should
eat
it like sick
sick but oh but by their supplements and
by their program and their expensive
programs instead why they talk about
toxins and
cells sure they didn't know what caused
vertigo or anything else they didn't
know any of that they didn't know you
know if you look into their crap years
ago they had no idea what was wrong with
anybody with anything but
oh steal and Rob medical medium
information left and right read the
books and take the info and then try to
throw the guy under the bus by saying
spene is not good in cilantro sure I'll
listen to you you lost your license yeah
you got your daughter-in-law working for
you yeah okay but then they can
say
whatever then you know it's some but
then they could say whatever they
want but then they can say God created
coffee God God you created coffee
everybody should be drinking it right
you could you created coffee everybody
should be drinking
it exactly so here's the here's how it
works
okay right God creates good things that
heal people God creates other things
right that may not heal
people that's how it works God creates
people right that create chemical
factories to kill people
right God creates the ability for us
to manufacture machines and make
machines and poison the oceans but God
also puts things out there to recover
people to get their lives back like
parsley and
cilantro and leafy
greens yeah things that get our lives
back things that can recover us like
sparina things that actually can bring
us back and that's the miracle that's
the miracle we got to pick and choose
the things that actually work you know
got to pick and choose the things that
actually
work there's a lot of things that grow
down here that aren't God created there
a lot of things that grow down here that
God did not
create something very important to know
that were seeded Long Ago by guess what
aliens there's a lot of things growing
on this
planet that God didn't put down here and
they were
seated and grown by aliens because we
got hundreds of thousands of years of
civilization
we got a lot of different
civilizations and we have a lot of alien
interaction and
seeding I mean that just happened
spirina is the
Mana that's the Mana it was brought here
to save people's lives and then you got
people [ __ ] on it
unbelievable spirina is the Mana that
was actually brought down here that's
the the Mana that God gave us so that we
can save our lives and then you got
somebody doesn't know
anything talking bad about it so people
get thrown off their game and can't heal
anymore it's
unbelievable it's
unbelievable anyway let's get back to it
just reading comments you
guys yeah no you you called that shot
your spot
on all
right about the Mana you actually you
actually
understand pretty
amazing yeah yeah just reading comments
you
guys all
right wait you're loving this come on
you don't like my other lives but you
like this live you don't like the other
lives this live you
like I'm just drinking too much that's
it too much licorice tea that's all I
think that's it all right let's
go so 369 the 369 cleanse okay protects
the
adrenals there aren't cleanses out there
that do that intermittent fasting
trashes the
adrenals you try to do the fast track
can you try to water fast along water
fast especially if you're chronically
sick yeah the adrenals aren't going to
like
that you want to do an olive oil cleanse
your adrenals are not going to like that
they're not going to like that they're
going to get worn out from that you want
to do a green tea cleanse your adrenals
will hate you they will they will hate
you you want to do want to do milk
cleanse your adrenals will hate you you
want to you want to sit in an ice bath
freezing cold ice bath your adrenals
will hate you sure I mean if you got
strong adrenals and you're not
struggling with any kind of you know
condition or Pro you know sickness or
anything like that chronic illness and
you want to sit in ice bath for a little
while you know your adrenals are going
to go into shock and they're just going
to go because they're going to be like
wait a minute you just fell into the
Arctic you just fell into a lake that
was frozen you must have fallen through
the ice your body's in crisis you must
be dying about to drown under the ice
and no one's there to save you and your
adrenals are going to be doing this no
one's there to save you even though
you're just in an ice tub your adrenals
are just going to be flooding because
your brain and adrenals are going to be
like emergency emergency person fell
through the ice in some frozen lake they
were ice fishing they fell down in there
that's what's going to happen you keep
on doing that overall you're just going
to be
wasted adrenals are going to be
wasted yeah exactly that's how it works
protecting the adrenals is number one
it's what the 369 does it's what the 28
day cleanse does that's what the mono
eating cleanse does the mono cleanse
it's what the morning cleanse does it's
all about protecting the adrenals you
know why Trace mineral salts trace
minerals glucose trace minerals glucose
trace minerals
glucose what trace minerals glucose
that's right glucose to the brain so you
don't have to run on adrenaline trace
minerals and mineral salts to the brain
so you don't have to run on
adrenaline you do a cleanse and you
don't have enough of that there enough
glucose because when you do a milk
cleanse you you got fat in there the
glucose doesn't get to the
brain it just doesn't the fat blocks it
just doesn't get to the brain so when
you try to do a milk cleanse the fat
blocks it see how it works that's how it
works you can't let the glucose be
blocked so the medical medium cleanses a
369 cleanse doesn't stop the glucose
from getting to the brain if you're
going to cleanse you need sugar you need
glucose to do the cleanse critical you
don't need table sugar you don't need
gobs and gobs of table sugar that that's
nothing to do with
it I love that love the whole carnivore
thing now it's just like I
predicted I mean you want to know
prophecy you see this every now every
now like prophecy this prophecy that out
there prophecy
is years ago me me saying that the
carnivore guys the ones that were all
just meat only meat only meat only and
then raw meat raw meat and then meat
cooked meat and cooked meat remember the
pro what I said I said a bunch of times
they're going to hit the wall and
they're going to start adding lemon then
they're going to start adding honey then
they're going to start adding berries
now they're just on a keto diet and
they're calling it carnivore prophecy
came true came
true the reason why I'm talking about it
kills the adrenals you want to do just
all meat only and only meat you're going
to kill your adrenals because your
adrenals have to push adrenaline to your
system to try to keep your body floating
through all that fat all that overt
fat think about it if you're going to be
on meat only you're going to be on a
high overt fat diet 247 so your adrenals
are just going to suffer they're going
to suffer Marie you remember Marie you
remember YouTube you can't believe you
remember this is years ago what the heck
Allison I remember you said I remember
you said fat was evil what are we
saying you know the thing went
listen
so the prophecy was they'd all be kind
of hit in the wall five years later four
years later they all are and then you'll
get a new person starting up right a
brand new person some trainer or
something like that I'm on Carnivore I'm
going to try it I'm on all meat great
you take your crowd down there you take
your crowd down to hell with
you you take them down and whoever
survives six months later and a year
later because you know what's going to
happen you might break your carnivore
diet for in a month later but you're not
going to tell your crowd you're going to
keep that a secret but you're going to
have people in your crowd that won't
they won't lie and they won't break it
and there's going to be people in your
crowd that are going to do it and
they're going to be hitting the walls
and those are the people that turn
around and say I did carnivore and
almost killed me because they did
carnivore the way the other person was
saying they were doing it but they
weren't that happens all the time you
know lra says 144 do you have more
prophecies yes lots of them I also know
why they're doing you know the whole I'm
actually the only one unfortunately that
knows why they're doing the uh the Drone
thing but I don't want to say it because
when you're the only one that knows what
they're really doing but no one else is
talking about it expect people with
black suits coming to your door and I
don't think it's going to help any of
us anyway Ross Adams says how are they
losing weight on
Carnivore they lose weight on Carnivore
okay all right because they they mono
they're mono eating and they left
whatever they were doing like they were
doing carbs mixed with protein you know
like bulker and Cutters you know bulking
and cutting you know that whole thing
bulking and cutting right they get into
the gym and they're bulking and they're
cutting
what happens is the bulking and cutting
process they can't keep up with it they
end up bulking bulking bulking and it
doesn't work anymore so now they're
stuck and they don't know where to go so
they end up getting rid of every single
bad carbohydrate they get rid of the
bread they get rid of the the grinder
you know the bread they get rid of the
the the cheese steak the bread around it
right
okay and yeah they get rid of their
peanut butter they get rid of their
almond butter they get rid of all that
coconut oil they get rid of the peanut
butter they get rid of the almond butter
do you know what I'm saying you guys
they get rid of all that and they get
rid of all the bagels all the bagels and
cream cheese they get rid of all that
they get rid of all the cookies cakes
and ice cream they all eat ice Everybody
Eats ice cream almost everybody out
there eats ice cream just go in their
freezer psychically go into their
freezer do that you're watching them
online you're watching all their crap
you're do watching whatever they're
doing t psychically go into their
freezer I guarantee you there there is
ice cream in their freezer and then the
chips they love chips they get away from
chips everybody has a crunch attack they
get rid they get they get they throw
away the chips they throw away all that
and now they're just eating a they're
eating meat only yeah they're going to
lose weight but don't let that fool you
cuz the weight comes back don't let that
fool you cuz the weight comes back it
does it actually comes
back yeah you didn't know that that the
way it comes back uh-huh it just does
I'm telling you right
now and then they have to work out more
and work out more and then all of a
sudden they start getting tired in the
brain because they got no glucose
anymore Trace mineral salts are gone
glucose is gone and now they got to
change their carnivore diet and they got
to they got a break and they break on
the honey that's why the carnivore diet
isn't the carnivore diet anymore
everybody just keeps the name carnivore
it that should be outlawed if it's not
the carnivore diet anymore why is it
still called carnivore somebody should
say
something it's not carnivore diet
anymore when you add honey and now
Honey's in it the carnivore diet was
meat only but okay let's keep the name
carnivore and then add honey now they're
adding honey because it's the only way
they can keep their brain working so
they don't bump into the wall it's the
only way they can keep their their head
space working function after a year a
year after 6 months only meat eating
meat only they're hitting the wall and
when you hit the wall because you got no
sugar to your brain you start sucking it
out you start sucking eggs
fast and that's what they do it's
exactly what they do what's my opinion
on fulvic asset it's
useless 100%
useless can give you 20 million reasons
why but it's not a fulvic acid show it's
a 369 did you guys you guys got cleanse
to heel get the book from your library
take it out I don't care if it's do it
do something get it for free don't let
me get the $127 or the 39 cents I get or
what whatever it is from the
book I don't care just get it for free
then I mean it's on Amazon it's 48% off
have this book it's a life-saving book
it's a life-saving tool if anything get
one she can give it to someone a lot of
people got sicker from Medical
Treatments by the way in the last four
years hint hint hint hint
hint it's okay for somebody else to
scream about that stuff out there but I
don't know if you guys know I got enough
crap for for because remember medical
medium information heals the most people
on the planet so I'm Target number one
okay other people can scream you know
what I mean that other stuff they can
scream it you know medical treatment
they can scream it you know they can
scream at all all they want no one's
going to bother them no one's going to
bother them but when you heal as many
people as Spirit of compassion is healed
yeah they'll bother
me so people will be like why am I
getting sicker why am I getting sicker
uh you had the medical treatment it's
going to be a little tough and you're
going to have to work
harder why am I getting sicker you get
those few people why am I getting sicker
well what are you doing to begin with
first of all what are you doing I'd like
to see your credit card
statements what restaurants are you
eating at that you're not telling
anybody what did you buy at the grocery
store because if I was with you while
you you know pulled your shopping cart
in there and loaded up with stuff I
might be like dear Lord that's what
you've been eating and you're not
telling
anybody I'd like to go through your
freezer how much coconut ice cream's in
there natural flavors and all your [ __ ]
I'd love to take a look what about like
how many benzos have you been on five
years ago eight years
ago they're saying benzo damage is like
terrifying it's like lethal they're
saying
now all these things but no was the
celery juice and what were you doing
that's another thing when someone says I
did medical scker really what were you
doing I'd really love to know cuz the
fly on the wall should come back the fly
on the wall should come back I have to
bring the fly on the wall back it's just
that I put the fly on the wall in
storage and I have to dig the fly on the
wall out and then got to
get that's the only
thing
yeah what causes men's testosterone to
drop liver is getting dirty Mucky
disgusting
livers plus men do the whatever too much
you want to know why testosterone drops
for men they're throwing their seed
everywhere that's
why cuz men you know most men out there
they're they're seed throwing
attics they throw seed in the shower
they throw seed everywhere they're just
every morning and they wonder why their
testosterone's going down
yeah
so
people PB says sounding so angry today
really I was thought I was in a good
mood Dr fwn plenty of people want I'm
passionate today don't confuse passion
with
anger
huh Dr Fawn plenty of people want to
heal but taking benzo and other
Pharmaceuticals and then blame medical
medium it's not working and then would
they doing that medical medium he said
I'm the fun guy to blame on you know put
the blame on I'm the fun guy to do it
it's like you know well he's a medium so
I I think that maybe will do it because
you know we'll pick on him but we won't
pick on who's who's he Watts or that
person or that person who did this and
that you can have millions of people
heal hundreds of thousands of
testimonials of medical medium
information one person gets a medical
treatment doesn't do anything right or
anything at all they die for some reason
oh it's medical medium stuff but you go
look if there even is communities out
there nothing like how big and tight
this community is if there is
communities out there you look through
it people are dying left and right left
and right someone told me that recently
a doctor friend told me he's in some
kind of thyroid Community he said the
people dying in there is it's just
unbelievable but no one's saying a word
but they're just dying they're fall in
like like literally dropping like flies
he said and he's a medical doctor and he
said they're just dropping like
flies they're doing all the wrong things
they're just dropping like
flies Jenny Max says your information
saved my life
Wow
listen you know I don't know what I can
do I hate doing this I hate doing this
okay I used to do this years ago was it
5 years ago six years ago years ago 8
years ago I used to do this okay I did
right I used to say I can give you the
golden ticket just smack it out of my
hand that's
all you know I don't know what else I
can get on my hands and knees and I can
go save yourself please please save
yourself and you can kick me in the
face I don't know what to do I just know
what works I know what heals people I've
seen it I understand understand it I
know it the information comes from
above I certainly certainly am not smart
enough to put this information
out and never have it
contradict it's
unbelievable unbelievable and then you
know and then the spiritual book that
you guys are going to
get I'm just preparing you now I'm still
questioning myself because
there's a reason why I don't release the
spiritual information that I'm releasing
in this book there's a reason
why it's it changes all it breaks all
paradigms and so what happens is when
Spirit of compassion answers questions
for me privately or I or you know for
somebody else that I that I whatever
that I know if Spirit of compassion
answers a question for
me like what happens when someone dies
and this and this or what happens with
this and this
what is this what is that when I when I
ask those questions and you get the
answers and if you're not ready for that
I don't know what to say I just know
that I'm doing it
anyway I'm going to I'm going to do it
and so the spiritual book is coming
um you're getting my pre- apologies
because your brain is just going to
probably go like this and when you're
reading what you read Denny Jen says and
now so many people are taking the weight
loss injections who knows what that will
eventually do to their health yeah but
they'll blame it on medical medium
they'll do weight loss injections for 2
years 3 years then they'll they'll get
sick they'll try something medical
medium and they'll get sicker because
their weight loss you know injections
have like hurt their cells and giving
them chronic inflammation cu the
toxicity of it but yeah it'll be the
celery juice or something you know or a
medical medium something protocol which
they're not even
on smoke cigarettes for 10 years micro
do blame it on medical medium right
micro do iasa micro do some psilocybin
some frog poison but blame medical
medium smoke for years smoke weed blame
medical medium recreational drug use for
years blame medical medium taking all
kinds of
medications taking your Aderall and your
amphetamines I mean I get it I'm not I'm
not shaming anybody if they got to take
medications that's not it go go to your
doctor and do what's right by your
doctor and you and I tell people that
that's not the problem but just don't
blame medical medium that's
all that's it I mean you know I'm for
what you need to do in your life but you
know don't blame medical medium just cuz
what you're doing eating disorders not
eating for years then eating not eating
for years then eating getting severe
deficiencies and then saying you started
medical medium and it gave you a
deficiency
dude you know what happens to your soul
when you start pulling that kind of
crap it's not good it's not good be on
an eating have an eating disorder that's
not the problem having eating disorder
you have an eating disorder and you're
on and off food and you're water fasting
and you're doing this and you're doing
that right and you're doing all this and
then you try medical medium you blame it
on medical medium when your deficiency
is literally from 10 years of eating
disorders and ups and downs and caffeine
for years and all kinds of stuff and
you're blaming medical medium for a
deficiency when you just had blood work
over and over again and caffeine and and
and all this stuff and I mean really I
mean come
on you are literally the only one who
confirmed my fear of iasa cold white
spring
said
iasa oh man just don't don't do it do
what you want it's your own free will
don't listen to me then don't listen to
me how about this I would if your doctor
tells you to do it then do do what your
doctor right whatever you and your
doctor are doing right by you don't
listen to me but I wouldn't do iasa you
couldn't pay me a million dollars to do
iasa you ready for this you ready for
this you couldn't pay me $50 million you
couldn't pay me ready for this $100
million to do iwasa you
couldn't and get ready for this one get
ready for this
one you couldn't pay me and I mean this
you couldn't pay me 1 billion mother
dollars to do
iasa you couldn't birth control for 5 to
10 years messing up your hormones
messing everything up birth control for
5 to 10 years messing everything up with
blame it on medical medium when you try
to do something because you heard
somebody else you know lie about
something you know like I I'm telling
you the stuff that's going
on meanwhile what am I doing offering
free information how many how many
Retreats have you guys had to pay like a
retreat where you have to pay $1,000 to
sit with me at a retreat and you know
and I control your life and everything
how many of you guys are having to pay
my subscription fees all my you know
like over and over and over again all my
pay walls to get any information I
dangle it like a carrot how many of you
guys are doing you're not how many of
you guys are like right programs are you
buying my $5,000 programs oh by the way
I don't have one you know I see somebody
out there talking [ __ ] about medical
medium some some trainer guy the guy
sells $11,000 programs $2,000 programs
$5,000 programs $10,000 programs all
[ __ ] sells them all but he's he's
talking crap about medical medium this
is for free free free it's not like I
get off and done with this right here
this live right now and I can be like pH
I probably sold $100,000 in programs I
probably sold a million dollars in
programs that was worth my time and
energy because I'm you know I'm God and
my ego is massive
I get off this live right here and I
hope to God that you just found a way to
heal so you can get your life back you
want to go to the library get the book
from there if you don't want to give me
the 39 cents or whatever it is just fine
if you my publisher whatever fine my
publisher gets these books out there in
the world for me and and and I am in
deep deep deep
gratitude because I don't have PR firms
working for me I don't have PR firms I
don't ask my my publisher for PR firms I
don't do anything of the sort and I
don't have PR firms that are built into
you know get the books out there and
stuff my publisher you know has
distribution and thank God for that so
somebody can wake up in the morning and
realize they're they're really sick and
then go where do I go and walk into a
bookstore somewhere in some other
country and find the medical medium book
and it speaks to them and because you
know what an
angel was nearby
sent a message into their
Consciousness you
know and they found the book and they're
getting their life back now and that's
what matters right there it's all that
matters anyway this is free 369 cleanse
download with five extra recipes that
are not in the book right there link is
in the description link is in the
profile check out go to medical.com or
you guys on my telegram I'm going to
start leaving telegrams pretty soon not
tonight but I'm going to start leaving
them pretty soon so Gear Up Get on my
telegram make sure you subscribe to my
telegram for a price of just
nothing the 369 Advanced cleans one of
my
favorites right here okay oh by the way
you guys Cafe
Gratitude Cafe Gratitude Venice location
right Larchmont location okay the
wellness reset they have a medical
medium
cleanse there on the
20th medical medium cleanse on the
20th it's the wellness reset it's Dirt
Cheap in my opinion for what it is it's
jammed jammed packed this thing is
amazing I don't make a penny off of
this so I I'm going to have to say it I
don't care I'm going to have to say it
you guys see this Wellness recet
okay that's right this is in Cafe
Gratitude on the 20th this can change
your life this well in this
reset it's a medical medium cleanse in
Cafe Gratitude can change your life and
it's dir cheap I really believe that and
it can change your life for what it is
it is and guess what I don't make a
penny I don't make one red scent not one
red scent Cafe Gratitude is not giving
me any money for this Wellness reset
cleanse I don't have a deal with them
where they're going to give me a penny
for this Wellness reset
cleans think about
that when somebody's talking crap about
me maybe you can say you know
what I mean what the
heck the thing is with me is like you
know I got a thick skin but I'm worried
about other people losing their way so
they can't heal it's my always my always
always concern it's always my concern
it's people not being able to make their
way to their healing process cuz they
get thed you know by whatever a li or
misinformation and then they lost their
chance to heal how crazy is that that
right there that one's a tough one for
me other than that I don't
care Erica says we got you so check this
out cleanse the heel is a
book 48% off amazon.com if you don't
want to get it free at the library or
this isn't the whole cleanse but this is
the download powerful information with
five extra recipes right here link is in
the bio link is in the description and
like I said Wellness reset at Cafe
Gratitude I am grateful for them the
fact that they're putting medical Med
they got medical medium items on the
menu right now you can go in there they
got incredible items on the menu that
are medical
medium incredible items on on the menu
that are medical
medium have you tried it have you tasted
it sushi rolls
they got a potato bowl that's just to
die for and to live for they got fajitas
with the Millet
wraps wait till you taste that so good
so good so
good it just
is just is have you tried them you're
doing a 36 369 cleanse now really
amazing amazing proud of you really
proud of you right rise with melum how
you doing after 6 years on medical
medium 6 years it's amazing I finally
healed
fibromyalgia never thought I would see
this day after suffering from it for
over 14 years nerves that get fried from
the pathogens and the toxins and the
metals six years you're into it amazing
getting a little dry dry spell in my
throat so let me just get a little Licor
Shake
Susan Gabriel I completed 369 and I'm on
my second 369 repeat and want to keep
going I feel
great keep going keep
going Lara 144 I did the potato monoc
cleanse for months now healed my
digestion and now I'm ready again for
another 369 L 144 totally proud of you
Rowan France hi Anthony was inspired to
start the 28 day cleanse
again that's this one right here after
you sent that email about it last week
and I started two days ago putting a
smile on my face and already feeling so
much lighter emotionally and dry skin
easing up that's what it's about that's
it right there that's it Alexandra
Sophia good to see
you 369 a 36 69 is what allowed me to
get to the Culver City book signing with
you my energy was gone from profound
grieving 369 gave me back energy and I'm
about to start it again you're going to
get me to look I'm about to cry on
that Debbie mlan I heal debilitating
vertigo working on ADD
vertigo debilitating vertigo
unless you experienced
it if you ever talk to somebody who
experienced it like did you ever have
her to go I had it really bad and then
you you can
relate you're barfing in a bucket you're
barfing on the the bedroom floor you're
barfing on the living room floor and if
you're lucky and you're not barfing
you're just like trying to walk along
your head spinning you lay at night and
your head spinning like
this brutal
brutal
Allison the comment went down Benjamin I
told my doctor I wanted to try the
cleanse to heal 369 and his response was
quote then that is what you need to do
quote
wow I mean praying hands over
here with
gratitude Jess elain how you doing my
brother I did 6 months mono eating
potatoes and it was unbelievable
especially for my
gut love it love it love it Kate
Courtney potato mono cleanse 7 months
and 14 time
369 are saving my life aw and I'm not
stopping they truly work I was couch
bound and unable to work now I'm living
life
again wow
just got to do one of those The Details
Matter like I always say you said a w
like you always say the details matter
they do this is what I keep on telling
people to heal with from
men then amazing thank
you yeah 10 years medical medium
vertigo three years all gone plus so
much more
vertigo you know like
whoa day 30 day wait a minute wait a
minute what am I
say day 335 of no fat see I had to I had
to I had to try to like in my mind how
to process that in almost N9 years on
medical medium such a game changer for
me
terat bless your heart terat Tom you are
a warrior you are a warrior
Tara Tara thank you for that comment
seriously thank
you grassfed mom how do I heal if I
can't get out of toxic chemical
situations from a
neighbor okay been
there I've been
there you know been there you
know I you know my house burned down
years ago not in this La thing now no
I'm not talking about now in LA with the
fires burning right now house burned
down years ago
right and I got such severe because I
was trying to save pets you'll do you'll
do anything for pets you'll run into a
burning house to try to save a pet I
mean I I know people that would I
did anyway so I got such severe lung
damage from it
right without Spirit of compassion and
this information you see in front of you
like cleanse to heal and everything else
I I I don't know what would happened I
got a good idea a really good idea what
would
happened but it
healed I healed it using my free will
listening to Spirit of
compassion and using Spirit of
compassion's information
yeah and I remember I me I uttered it a
little bit it slipped out a little bit
the other day where I said something
about it I read a comment I don't know
if it was on YouTube or Instagram
something like someone said he's the big
medical medium he's never supposed to
have a problem that's very suspicious
that he had to heal a lung problem and
it took a year to do it he must have
been he I don't know if I trust his
stuff now are you
kidding it's a good chance I should have
been dead after that years later with
lung damage like that I healed it you
using Spirit of compassion's information
it was
severe totally 100% healed but the point
is and it healed within a
year and yeah I had a doctor friend who
was like are you on this thing I'm like
yeah I'm doing it he was like people
don't heal from that I'm like yeah I
know I know all about it and you know
what so it healed using Spirit of
compassion's
information you know so yeah it works
my brother healed with medical
medium when the injection stopped
working when the injection stopped
working
yeah there are stories upon stories upon
stories people miraculously healing
using medical medium information but
cleanses that's a big one not just the
protocols supplementation Protocols are
otherworldly man otherworldly the
information and the supplement protocols
you can just pick three supplements four
supplements you can customize it I put
it in the I put the information in there
from s so about like how to do that how
to use the supplementation
protocols
seriously you like look into it look
into the supplementation protocols you
might need the cleanse and some
supplementation protocols you might be
really sick with a lot of neurotoxins
you might have a lot of damage to the
nervous system you might have a lot of
pathogens there's a way to heal you can
do it but you got you got to get into it
happiness from
within I was just I was just checking
out your
channel I was just checking out your
channel and I was looking at stuff
you're doing having this from within the
food at Cafe Gratitude is incredible on
medical medium menu thank you medical
medium for all you do you can heal with
my mm info anyone reading this
amazing proud of you proud of you I
think it's shanet right I mean I think
proud of you yeah it's shanet
um I
think I love repeating
days
789 so my
369 tends to go for 12 days the the
things are so quick going by so quick I
can't keep up to with any of it
wondering Wishin amazing okay that's who
that is wondering Wishin thank you for
leaving that
comment when you're seeing a whole bunch
of comments and a whole bunch of people
come through you're trying to grab on to
it Rena I healed a ton of
symptoms including trigeminal neuralgia
over 50 369 cleanse 14 monop potato
cleanses I'm so grateful
girl the results from the cleanses are
always mindblowing spiritual healing
alone is out of this world amazing 369
gives me a tremendous amount of energy
says
Barbara
Carbone camiller I had vertigo insanely
bad in 2016 and no more you know what's
crazy no one understood is that what
you're saying Kim no one understood yeah
yeah when you have vertigo and it's
really bad it's hard to get anybody to
understand unless they had it themselves
unless they suffered with it unless they
dealt with it totally
agree art for the soul Advance 369
seriously saved my life actually healed
me physically emotionally and
spiritually
incredible Christy Paul five years on
medical medium saved my
life my
God it's amazing Len Len Sony is banana
monoc cleanse okay for
adrenals it's definitely okay for
adrenals you know ask your doctor we
your doctor thinks of course but yes I
tell my friends it's okay for their
adrenals I have them do it for their
adrenals
yes Fabrizio everybody Andre you guys
are amazing this has been a really
really fun talk
um getting to read your comments and
everything is so fun Andrea thank you
Anthony for helping me get my life back
a decade of bed bound that see that that
breaks my heart to know you were even
like for a decade bed bound I lost my
20s that breaks my heart and so much
excruciating pain daily I just finished
nine backto backs Ben raw fat-free and
salt-free since June oh my God so June
July August September October November
December we're in January Andrea that's
mind-blowing mind-blowing okay I'm so
sorry you were bedbound through your all
through your 20s and you you know and
you lost your 20s with sickness like
that and so happy you're doing the
backbacks that is amazing I'm proud of
you just incredible incredible for
real I'm choked
up I think the hardest part the hardest
part is knowing that you guys have
suffered and many of you are still
suffering and you're suffering now and
it's hard and you're just starting your
you know Journey or your journey needs
to take more time because the problem is
even when you kill off a pathogen you
you know annihilate an epscene bar virus
right the problem is you can pick up
another one somehow and then have to go
back and do it again and clean it up
right another problem just say you
annihilate your viral issue your
shingles your epscene bar you annihilate
something and you clean it up right okay
but the neurotoxins are still left over
in the liver and take a year or two to
clean out because neurotoxins from the
virus are toxic just as toxic as the
virus itself so you're trying to clean
up the neurotoxins and so your nerves
are still short circuiting right and it
takes time and now you're two years into
it three years into it and now you're
finally healing but you don't know you
might not know to keep on the journey
because you don't know it's hard it's
hard when you know you have the viral
stuff you have the Mercury you have the
neurotoxins you have the metals you have
other things that might have happened in
your life like benzo or medical
treatment right you might have like you
know all these different things you're
working on healing and it takes time and
then the nervous system here's another
thing too you can rid most of your
toxins you can rid the
pathogens you're you're on your way to
healing but your nerves are damaged and
they need time to
heal and now you need to like ask your
doctor about medical medium B12 you know
B12 protocol where you're doing the you
know the B12 protocol
the whole
bit you're doing the shock therapy a lot
of people have a lot of emotional stuff
come up and they're used to eating and
numbing those emotions down and that's a
tough one all on its own so man I get it
life is hard are you kidding life is
hard why do you think why do you think
I'm not tough like I'm not tough on
people you don't think I I I don't
understand that eating a bag of chips is
like helpful like feels helpful for
emotional thing that you're going
through you don't think I don't know
that you don't think I don't know the
big old you know bag of chips that like
say say like an avocado oil chip or
something or something an olive oil chip
or something that's you know better for
you whatever still right a big bag of
chips you don't think I don't think that
life isn't hard enough where we fall for
that we do that of course I completely
understand are you
kidding someone goes for a cheeseburger
I get it someone goes for some kind of
like you know cream cheese on a bagel
some goes a bag of chips cooking at ice
cream in their you know fridge in their
freezer you don't think like I know
emotions they come up and they're coming
up of course talk about it in the books
too the and I've talked about it in in
in an emotional live emotions come up
and they surface they come out of cells
emotions that are trapped with
adrenaline I've written books from
Spirit of compassion's information about
this
where the adrenaline in the moment of a
hardship gets
trapped trapped in the fat
cells in organ tissue and then sits in
there and then when you're trying to
cleanse or you're trying to get it out
it just releases and man sadness all
kinds of emotional you know feelings
hardship start to you ring up you
trigger it easy boom boom you're
triggered all this stuff can happen and
then you're eating something mac and
cheese bagels and cream cheese I don't
know spam you know you're eating spam
I mean yeah medical medium brain shot
therapy can be very helpful when those
emotional emotional things come up when
you're trying to you're trying to battle
that there's the Cravings shifter
there's a lot of things the brain shot
therapies are so amazing I haven't even
scratched the brain you know the brains
saver books you guys the brainsaver
books when they were released I think I
did one thing I did one brain saver kind
of like
talk like it was like a 10day thing
whatever it was it was the brain saver
don't quote me on that I don't know how
many days but it there was 20 days my
God it was 20 and I did I did the 20
days so I'm trying to remember I thought
I did two of I did one of them the 20day
and I haven't even talked about those
books and they're lifes saving just the
supplement section of what to avoid for
Dangerous problematic
supplements right that alone is life
saving you if you have those brainsaver
books they're right there in the corner
you might not be able to see them on IG
they're in the corner but man Tik Tok
you probably don't see
him betrayal broken trust stabilizer
huge for emotions burnout stabilizer
these are in the brainsaver books
finding your purpose stabilizer brain
saver books nerve gut asset stabilizer
The Parsley shot parsley shot I mean
come on relationship breakup stabilizer
sleep and recharging stabilizer speaking
your truth stabilizer I mean all of them
trauma shock and loss stabilizer wisdom
and intuition
stabilizer
yeah yeah yeah yeah I mean come on come
on craving shifter boom dream
shifter ego shifter do I need the ego
shifter today do I need one I'm going to
grab the ego shifter today energy
shifter right food fear shifter whoa
guilt and shame shifter mood shifter
nerve shifter my God obsessive thought
shifter that's a good one that's a
really good
one yeah it
is have you heard my free will podcast
episode that that is information that is
information you guys are keeping up with
the medical medium um
podcast on
Spotify Apple podcast
Spotify keeping up with the uh podcast
some really really good episodes in
there you go into telegram make sure you
subscribe to telegram subscribe to my
YouTube and you guys on YouTube can you
give me a thumbs up or give me I never I
never like to ask for anything you give
me a like I don't know what is it called
is it a like is it a thumbs up up on
YouTube can you give me one of those I
don't know does it even matter I
mean it's cool though if you do if you
don't that's all
right
anyway unbelievable Advance 369 we're
going to do a series of 369 talks and
we're going to get into the cleanse at
some point okay we are comment what your
favorite part of this live was and
hopefully it's not the embarrassing
parts are if you're going to comment on
the embarrassing parts of this
live you can all right I'm not perfect
man I'm only human I'm only
human I'm not perfect I could take a
lick in and keep on ticking though and I
got a skin I do I do it's it's why
Spirit of compassion came to me when I
was four years
old because I wasn't going to jump
ship jump ship cuz hearing a voice from
the outside not the inside I wish it was
just scrambled up inside my own thoughts
I wish it was that but hearing it on the
outside and having no control over it
and is actually on the
outside yeah I hung in there so if you
guys hang in there with me it makes it
worth it it makes it worth it okay when
the demons come knocking on doors on
social and they're just like he's a bad
guy whatever it is you know if you're in
it for the ride I'm in it for the ride
with
you your recent podcast have been
incredible thank you whoa garlic
gal garlic gal thank you for that thank
you I'm trying to serve I want every
line
impactful you do have a thick skin Tera
said God bless
you bless your heart
you
guys just one last thing um we're
getting closer to information and
spiritual
book so when's and where's and what's
but look a lot of people ask me a lot of
questions I've seen you guys ask me a
lot of questions over the years I
answered
them I don't know if it's to my
detriment or not but I answered them so
so when you do get your hands on this
and you read
it or listen to it or whatever it is
um just take one page at a time
process all right you
guys oh Jasmine do you wear earplugs to
not hear
Spirit I've played a lot of loud music
I've tried the earplug
you know but it got me into some
situations by wearing
earplugs
so the problem is if I try to wear ear
plugs to block out Spirit of compassion
then I might not hear something I need
to hear Spirit of compassion tell me and
I've gotten into that jam a couple of
times one that was
grave
and freaking
grave yeah yeah and that was from
plugging my ears and not wanting to hear
Spirit of
compassion
yeah anyway are you
guys signing off
104 can't wait for the spiritual book
pixie
pixie okay but when you read it be easy
on me okay Jackie isn't that why you
were drumming it was why I was drumming
Jackie it was why I was
drumming it was I'm a
drummer
um pth says I loved your show it's clean
it's truthful and I wouldn't take anyone
else's advice other than you been
following you for 7 years years nothing
has shifted my illness more than Spirit
of compassion has thank you from
Melbourne Australia bless your heart
from Melbourne careful of the
crocodiles I don't know how many
crocodiles are in Melbourne though it
might be rusty and my
Australia Australian it might be might
be rusty how many Crocs are in Melbourne
careful of the snakes there's more
poisonous snakes in
Australia than there is in California
and Florida and
there's more poisonous spiders I think
in Australia than in California and
Florida and I think there's more you
know poisonous
toads
grego I [ __ ] love you I love you
aw I take that
swear deep into my heart I do I do and I
love you for it I [ __ ] love that pump
says amazing live ad du good
energy you don't think Spirit of
compassion doesn't tell me not to
swear don't worry s so tells me not to
swear but s so forgives me for
swearing ssc1 said to me if swearing is
is all we have to worry about with you
with this gift and you not jumping ship
we'll take it
truck
driver truck driver
mouth best all right you guys we're
doing more of these 369 talks though for
warning you keep your notifications on
even though they don't let you get
notified even though nobody lets you
gets notified keep your notifications on
okay keep them on all right I'm getting
loud all of a sudden keep your
notifications on check out my telegram
I'm check out the last telegram messages
I've done though seriously listen to
those go back to those Pride and
Prejudice ones going to talk about Pride
and Prejudice again I can't help it
there's just good information in there
there's lessons in there all kinds of
stuff Pride and Prejudice I want to talk
about that a little bit more on telegram
if that's okay if you guys are okay with
that I want to talk about other stuff
and keep your lights turned on man notif
notifications on okay and um because 369
cleanse talks we're going to have I
didn't even get into the cleanse we got
like work to do there's work to
do ah just a motor mouth today there's
work to be done all right you
guys all right love you love
you boy those Instagram people they're
really oh I'm still on Instagram crap oh
man them Tik Tock people man always
giving me a heart oh crap Tik tok's
still on what am I doing I'm getting
busted left and right I'm still working
on the book finishing up but I'm almost
done and once it done goes off and boom
then to the Press boom Publishers happy
because they want people healed boom