you doesn't mean you're not exposed to
Pharmaceuticals
exactly
exactly I don't take any Pharmaceuticals
I'm all natural
I'm a vegan I take no Pharmaceuticals
crazy thing is vegan steak
Pharmaceuticals all the time they take
antibiotics they take
all kinds of different stuff drugs for
their acne there's so many vegans out
there that take they take
Pharmaceuticals for their acne that's
what they do every single day duh right
there's all kinds of stuff like that and
then there's
uh animal protein people still they're
on Pharmaceuticals as well all the time
and they're doing animal protein people
that are actually really into all
natural living
still take Pharmaceuticals everybody
does it doesn't matter what side of the
aisle you're on you can be on the beacon
Isle you could be on the animal protein
aisle they just do anyway but you might
be somebody that's like no I'm not I
don't take I just had to peel this lime
you guys sorry about this I I don't take
any Pharmaceuticals at all does it mean
you're not exposed to Pharmaceuticals do
you have a partner do you have a loved
one do you have a boyfriend do you have
a girlfriend who is on a pharmaceutical
and you share bodily fluids with that
girlfriend that boyfriend that partner
or that husband that wife that fiance
that whoever and
you know are you are you sharing bodily
fluids are they on an Acme medicine are
they on a Statin huh how did you think
about that one that one's interesting
isn't it okay you're sharing bodily
fluids with a loved one that's on a
Statin how about a loved one that's on
high blood pressure medication you don't
take any Pharmaceuticals but you share
bodily fluids with the with a loved one
that's on high blood pressure medication
think about that for a moment
uh-huh and so it's just it's we
pharmaceutical pharmaceutical exposure
it's really easy to occur for anybody
so that's important too anyway we're
doing the pharmaceutical exposure shot
would you believe it day 14 of the
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge
I have brain saver right here brain
saver is critical it did you read the
blood draw chapter in this book
you guys you have to read the blood draw
chapter in this book
you you just have to seriously if you're
ever considering getting any blood drawn
on any level for anything routine
anything
critical to own this book I am telling
you for sure and someday if you own this
book five years from now you're gonna
wish you owned it five years before
because that's how powerful and how
important this information is in this
book to protect you from when you get
your blood test so when you get your
blood drawn right
so when you're doing this you get your
blood drawn right you got the thing on
here and they're taking Blood Out
it's critical to know I'm just just
telling you
so important all right so we're doing uh
what let's just let's just talk about
the shot for a second too
um
let's just do that so there's a chapter
first of all the pharmaceutical exposure
shot I just want to show it to you
before we get started so that's it right
there do you have what you need let's go
over that in a moment really quick I got
some apples right there I got some
lemons are you prepared I got some
cilantro some green onion right there
right some some scallions I got
asparagus I got lime and I got lemons
off to the side you probably can't see
it on IG
but you guys can see it right so do you
have what you need
all right and let's talk about this next
part here I want to read a little bit
about pharmaceuticals chapter 19 in
brain saver foreign
common Pharmaceuticals any of these ring
a bell
antibiotics
Bing
antidepressants
being
anti-inflammatories uh-huh
sleeping pills
yeah
biologics
uh-huh
immunosuppressants yeah somebody might
not know they're on any of these you
might not know you're on biologic you
know look
you should take your medic medications
if your doctor wants you to do what's
right by your doctor and you choose you
know
your doctor out there get your health
care you know situated if you're taking
medications uh listen to your doctor all
that stuff right
I'm just talking about pharmaceutical
exposure shot and I'm on page 19.
common Pharmaceuticals I'm talking about
Okay so
antibiotics
antidepressants
anti-inflammatories
sleeping pills
biologics immunosuppressants
prescription amphetamines
Adderall whatever okay prescription
amphetamines
opioids
and the list goes on statins
blood pressure medications
hormone medications
thyroid medications I know a lot of
people are on thyroid medications I know
that
steroids
a lot of people are on steroids
the pill
a lot of people are on the pill right
pharmaceutical alcohol
interesting
people don't realize how much
pharmaceutical alcohol they're on they
have no idea
recreational drugs
is anybody on recreational drugs these
days
man I think that business is booming out
there
so I'm on page 199 of brain saver if you
want to know okay
here we are
if you're on medication
or you received a medical treatment
you're aware of it
you may not be completely aware of what
was in the medication
you at least know it was administered
what you might not know is what you were
given in your Early Childhood or even
babyhood
that could still be in your system
so that's a good point right there all
on its own
what have people
been on in childhood
what was administered to them in
babyhood
right we forget as we go along
or don't know
what you might not know is what you were
given in your Early Childhood or even
babyhood that could still be in your
system
it's very common to receive antibiotics
early in life
pre-memory is interesting right
pre-memory
even if you've never taken medicine
Pharmaceuticals
it still can be in your brain and body
now and you don't know pre-memory you
took it when you were a baby or a child
so this is an incredible little chapter
right here in the medical medium brain
saver I'm reading out of okay you guys
just wanted to
start with us today and we're making the
pharmaceutical exposure shot
so it's a brain shot therapy I'm excited
we're day 14 today
water supply
interesting
more and more Pharmaceuticals are
entering the water supply
because people who are taking them then
eliminate them when they go to the
bathroom
so think about that
where does it all go
it has to go somewhere no matter what
billions of people going to bathroom
well over a billion people easy on this
planet or are on Pharmaceuticals
more than that
where's it going
when they go to the bathroom
this also means that medication laced
water can become a part of our food
through reservoirs
irrigation
Public Water Supplies
well water near septic tanks
and fish swimming in lakes rivers and
oceans
there are other ways to get this
pharmaceutical laced water
such as brushing our teeth
cooking with tap water
swimming in lakes and rivers pools pools
swimming in poles
and that's a whole thing there too if
you're on vacation and you're swimming
in a pool
public pool
you don't take Pharmaceuticals
but maybe a whole bunch of people in
that same pool take Pharmaceuticals and
it's leaching out of their skin their
pores their armpits
and everywhere else
that water is not being replaced
that's sitting in a pool
that water can be the same water in that
pool for 10 years
they don't drain pools and replace water
it's too expensive
it's not it's not a common practice
so in hotels or anywhere else in public
pools that water can be 10 years old
thousands of people could have swam in
it and pharmaceuticals could have
leached off their bodies into that pool
water and now pool water is never being
tested for pharmaceuticals
water parks
restaurant water normally contains
pharmaceutical runoff
did you hear that one
restaurant water
the really good one there
so
you're eating in a restaurant that water
most likely contains Pharmaceuticals
all right let's go let's hit pools and
water parks
I'm on page 200 brain saver I mean this
is an interesting topic right I mean I
think this is really interesting when
Spirit of compassion was giving me this
information I was just like okay no I'm
I'm hooked I'm hooked
foreign
water parks swimming in a pole or water
park doesn't only lead to pharmaceutical
exposure via the water supply
there's also the runoff coming from
people's bodies
when you're swimming in a hotel pool
here we go for example
there's pharmaceutical runoff coming
from people's skin and out of their
armpits their genitals
yeah
Pharmaceuticals coming out of their
genitals in the pool
Pharmaceuticals are coming out of their
mouth if they get water in their mouth
how many people are swimming and they're
spitting out water they're getting water
in their mouth
it's not like someone swimming in a pool
and they close their mouth perfectly and
they don't talk to their friend that's
also swimming and they're swimming
around with their mouth sealed shut and
after they get out of the pool they dry
off their face
no people get water in and out of their
mouth when they're swimming in the pool
I've seen people just
spitting water out of their mouth in the
pool of course
when you're swimming in a hotel pool for
example there's pharmaceutical runoff
coming from people's skin and out of
their armpits their genitals their mouth
if they get water in their mouth and
even their urine and feces
if they urinate defecate or pass gas in
the poll
the pool water becomes a filter for
what's in the gas
it's a pharmaceutical bath
so which is interesting right here
anybody who farts in a pool
the pool becomes a filter for that gas
that's coming out of the person
the gas that's coming out of the person
has Pharmaceuticals in the gas
so if there's a whole bunch of people
swimming around in a pool and they're
farting in a pool and they're letting
out gas
that gas is loaded with particles of
pharmaceuticals it's like a
pharmaceutical aerosol coming out of
their body if they're on anything
thyroid medication statins blood
pressure pills antibiotics
the pill anything doesn't matter what it
is
um amphetamines prescription
amphetamines all of it right so opioids
whatever it is that they're on
it's coming out if they were at the
dentist and they had lidocaine they had
novocaine lidocaine septicane whatever
it is that they had it's in their body
so they went to the dentist they just
had lidocaine
they had some dental work done they're
swimming in the pool they fart in the
pool lidocaine is now in the pool water
syriana says chlorine doesn't eliminate
this no
chlorine is just for microbes you know
like
microbes microorganisms amoebas stuff
like that
stuff that's naturally happening because
it's it's it's Standalone water
the water is
standing still
so because it's not like it's just water
sitting in a pool
it has to stay fresh so they kill off
microbes with chlorine chlorine doesn't
eliminate any of this that's not an
Eliminator of all the Pharmaceuticals
Elena says oh my God I remember when I
was swimming this summer in a pool it
got so much worse and there was a time
when someone
threw up in a pool
they just fished it out laugh out loud
never drained the pole and we all went
back they never drained the pole it's
too costly for the hotels
so and and water parks and stuff like
that gotta remember if you're gonna
drain 200 000 gallons of water
you have to pay for that 200 000 gallons
of water to get put back in hotels don't
do that your water will stay there for
10 years 15 years unless the pool has to
be fixed if the pool cracks or breaks
then they have to drain the pool they
have to eat the money and the cost they
have to seal to crack and then they have
to fill the pool back in right
so what I'm trying to say is your pool
water can Harbor Pharmaceuticals for 10
years building up in the water it never
goes away
sure oh here's something interesting
here so since the person that I read the
comments said does Chlor chlorine get
rid of it right
chlorinating it sure they chlorinate the
water to shock it for parasites bacteria
and algae
that chlorine doesn't remove any of the
pharmaceutical residue in the water
supply or the runoff from people's skin
do you have the book I know the person
said what about chlorinating does that
help that means you might not have the
book because it says it in here
you should get this book and read the
blood draw agenda chapter
it's just incredible
inner truth healing says oh my God makes
so much sense
but not common sense
because it's not common about this
information it's from Spirit of
compassion yes it makes sense though
Red Raven says oh people put babies with
diapers on in the pool indeed they do
and babies get Medical Treatments
everybody's well aware of that ends up
in the pool
and adults get Medical Treatments
everybody's aware of that ends up in the
pool
somebody says on IG free as a bird says
144 good number I think this is the most
shocking info I heard so far even if we
are on no meds we can get them from
others
never like fools
every time Spirit of compassion gives me
a piece of information from above it's
the most shocking ever
over and over again
how many years
how many times have I had to deliver the
message of shocking information
and then I get branded the worst crap
hit pieces on me saying I'm
fear-mongering hit pieces on me saying
whatever
and I'm just trying to deliver the
information from above and yes it's
shocking
just like the blood draw agenda that's
shocking too that blows people's minds
when they hear about that it's just it's
all the medical meme information is
mind-blowing people deserve to know the
truth so they can make their own
decisions but I get to discriminated
against and punished for it
punished for I mean people they use a
new tactic now oh oh reliable source I
got a reliable source that says don't
trust medical mediums information that's
the new thing now on social
oh yeah it's from reliable source that
says you know don't trust medical
mediums info oh really and what's a
reliable source some other influencer
that hates me
anyway
check this out sure they chlorinate the
water to shock it from for parasites
bacteria and algae that chlorine doesn't
remove any of the pharmaceutical residue
in the water supply or the runoff from
people's skin those Pharmaceuticals stay
in the pool water unless the pool is
fully drained which guess what the poles
are never fully drained they're never
drained
unless 10 years later there's a crack in
the pool
pool water can stay in the pool for a
very long time without ever getting a
repair that calls for it to be drained
at a hotel for example you could have
pharmaceutical filled water for five
straight years or more
where it concentrates year after year
and doesn't dissipate
and pools never get tested for
pharmaceutical levels ever
there are so many Pharmaceuticals in
pool water
no one could even imagine it is a
pharmaceutical bath of hundreds of
different kinds of pharmaceuticals
all right
I'm glad that's the most shocking thing
you've ever heard because there's a lot
of shocking stuff in the medical medium
books way more shocking than that all
right let's go into food supply
antibiotics
I can't help but I'm just laughing today
I don't know why I'm laughing today but
I am Danielle says why is 144 a good
number I'm always seeing it and I was
born at 144. listen to my telegram audio
message on numbers I talk about 144
talked about it for years
since I was a kid
okay food supply
antibiotic fed animals
translate to our ingesting antibiotics
when we eat their eggs meat fish and
Dairy
even if you take care to find the
highest quality best treated animal
products for when you prepare food at
home
yeah
but you don't eat antibiotic fed animal
products do you
so you think
which is a great perspective measure if
you eat animal products because you
don't want to take any you don't want to
eat animal
products that are
subjected to antibiotics
and other Pharmaceuticals you've likely
been unable to avoid eating conventional
animal products when dining out or
eating at a friend's house
and that means antibiotic exposure so
you mean to tell me
there's not one meal you had
over a friend's house or a family
member's house or in a restaurant
that you can guarantee
was
not an anti-antibiotic fed animal
like you can guarantee it
like there's not one meal you had
eating out somewhere friends house
family's house wherever
now you can guarantee
that there were no antibiotics fed to
those animals
you've likely been unable to avoid
eating conventional animal products when
dining out or eating at a friend's house
and that means antibiotic exposure
should I go on you guys
also animals are treated with
antibiotics when sick even if it's not
an antibiotic fed animal or meat I'm
going to go into details about that
even if you take great care to avoid
eating animals fed antibiotics now
what about the first 10 years of your
life
was that 100 antibiotic
free animal products
were the first 20 years of your life or
even the first 30 years of your life
those antibiotics
that you were exposed to during a
previous chapter in your life's store up
over time your entire lifetime basically
what it said is
you had antibiotic fed
Pro animal products long ago and stored
up in your body and never left
never left
Mina Levy says I am living proof of my
experience
I am livering proof my experience was
terrifying until this man described what
was going on
not one doctor could
you saved my life
and my sanity
he's the real deal and his source is
knowledge to the haters of the solution
not the problem
thank you Anthony
thank you Tamara says oh my God this is
shocking what a barf face you know the
emoji with the green barf coming out
appreciate all your info I so cherish
your books my books even more now thank
you on YouTube thank you Tamara
Andre here
all right should I keep on reading a
little bit more we'll talk about it
because I'm a brain saver get a whole
bunch of ingredients here for the
pharmaceutical exposure shot I'm excited
about
keep in mind
grass-fed animals
grass-fed beef
free range
pastured chicken
organic fed pigs
still occasionally get infections and
get sick and get treated with steroids
and antibiotics
here's how it works
grass-fed cows
don't get antibiotics and steroids mixed
in with their grass
they're a grass-fed cow
but when the grass-fed cow gets sick
which
most of them do at one point
they get treated for that sickness with
antibiotics
and steroids
but they don't have to legally
put that on the package that that cow
that you're eating that steak from
was sick for a week or two and was on an
actual treatment you don't get told that
it won't say it on the package instead
it'll say grass fed beef
because they didn't do a daily drug
treatment mixed in their food like they
do the industrial cows and animals
keep in mind grass-fed animals grass-fed
beef free range pasture chicken organic
fed pigs still occasionally get
infections and get sick and get treated
with steroids and antibiotics
if you're eating chopped meat grass-fed
chopped meat
remember that chopped meat isn't one cow
that chopped meat can be a hundred cows
a chopped meat
is chop me
that's mixed
with a hundred other animals
all ground up together
maybe 20 of those hundred animals never
experience a pharmaceutical in their
diet obviously not in their diet they're
grass-fed right never experience a
pharmaceutical treatment for being sick
but the other 80 cows that are ground up
into that chopped meat to make that
grass-fed Burger
could have had
treatments for being sick
foreign
against animal protein or animal protein
eating
I support everybody regardless of what
diet they choose I just teach people how
to do it better
that's it I message information from
above
so they can learn how to take care of
themselves better
so if you're a vegan
you can be a vegan I'm pro-vegan Pro
plant-based but there's a way to do it
that you can customize to heal because
there's a lot of sick vegans out there
they never heal and they're getting bits
and pieces of medical meme information
that's shrinkling out of the communities
and they poach it and stuff so it's
helping vegans out there
and they don't say to back them in but
the point is is as a vegan as a
plant-based person someone might be
this information is here for them to
take it to the next level and still stay
vegan or plant-based now if you're an
animal protein person it's the same
thing
I don't shun shame or judge anybody for
being an animal protein person
in the medical medium community
quite the opposite instead if that's
what you want to do I want to help you
do it right so you can customize
and do what you need to do to heal if
that's what you want to do
so I don't want anybody thinking this is
some weird you know animal protein
campaign slash vegan thing that's not
what this is this is just information
from above that I have to message to
everybody it's just the truth
foreign
Spirit lover says what about natural
salt water pools like not public pools
but for home it's not about if it's
natural salt water
Spirit lover
or chlorine based
which snaps or salt water kind of is is
a type of fluorine based it's just
different it's the natural salt right
the point is Spirit lover
it's not about that it's about who's in
your pool
it's a spirit lover you said
but for home instead of a public pool
right well yeah a public pool means you
got a whole bunch of people going in
there and all their gunks coming out of
their body at home in your own pool I
don't know who's swimming in your own
pool I don't know who's in there
is Auntie Jane in there is Uncle Bob in
there are they on 10 Pharmaceuticals are
they swimming around in your pool and
then that pharmaceutical is in your pool
for a lifetime unless you drain the
water but the point is Spirit lover it's
about who's in your pool doesn't matter
what kind of
system you have whether it's all salt or
chlorine
problem is with medical medium
information over and over again there's
one huge problem
because it comes from above it does this
all the time
just close your mind and then people are
just like what the f and then the word
gets out they're always like fear Monger
fear Monger instead it's more like
Empower and Power
because the information empowers people
hit the thumbs up if you like this video
if you don't like the video hit the
thumbs up please
keep in mind grass-fed animals grass-fed
beef free-range bastard chickens we're
getting that big still occasionally get
infections get skin problems get sick
and get treatments with steroids and
antibiotics they're just not as
saturated for the most part with
antibiotics for chronic contagious
infections or conventionally raised
foods with the drugs in them that
animals are on in the industrial places
when chronic infections do occur with
grass-fed animals raised free range and
pastured some animals are out of
commission for a while due to an ongoing
infection that takes a month to treat
once recovered the animal is back in the
running again
you're set free cow you're better now
you were sick for a month and went into
a different station on the farm and Now
cal you're free you're free to roam and
everything right oh let me see here and
that's what happens it's like
like cow is now free
the cow's free to roam and everything
right
now once a cow's free
yeah
the cow goes back into
playing reindeer games on the farm
the cow might have been sick for a month
and then put out a commission
but the cow gets better and then goes
back in
for the slaughter later
to be on somebody's table
once recovered the animal is back in the
running again
it's still listed as grass-fed beef
doesn't matter if your grass-fed cow was
sick for a month it's still listed as
grass-fed beef
doesn't matter if your grass-fed cow had
antibiotics and steroids and
anti-fungals like they do
you don't hear this stuff getting talked
about in all the animal hate stuff like
all the vegan stuff and all the
propaganda out there everybody says
they're an expert you don't hear any of
this stuff talked about because
you know you'll hear it talked about now
now that the books are out right well it
didn't come from medical medium though
they'll say
Liars it's still listed as grass-fed
beef and ready for the market when the
time comes we're shielded from this
information it's kept from the inside
goings on when you're in the market
you're shielded from the fact that the
grass-fed animals were still treated
they still have drugs inside of them and
they were put back on the market and
they have the label of grass-fed beef
you can't always avoid all these things
the pharmaceutical exposure shot so you
can get them out of your system you
can't always avoid all of these things
it's not about shutting your life down
it's not about you can't live your life
anymore it's not about being afraid it's
just about being empowered so you can
make choices I would like to know what's
going on personally I would like to know
what's going on myself
laughs
and having tools like these brain shot
therapies is incredible because not only
can we deep like know about it we can do
something about it we think it's
inconceivable that the animals have ever
had something wrong with them
there's no way in hell
this package of grass-fed beef
had an animal
have something wrong with it there's no
way in hell this package of grass-fed
beef I'm holding my hand somehow this
animal that once was an animal and now
it's in this package wrapped with
whatever
and sealed in this package there's no
way that this was a sick animal it says
grass-fed beef you know
we think it's inconceivable that the
animals have ever had something wrong
with them any kind of infection or
illness it's inconceivable there's no
way one animal had something wrong with
it it's grass-fed it's pre-range
pasteurized there's no way it had
anything wrong with it
I don't want you under the illusion that
you're not going to get antibiotics from
grass-fed meat because it's not true I
don't want anybody under the illusion
the scam illusion
that you're not going to get any
Pharmaceuticals from your grass-fed
products and so forth and free range
products and everything
Marion
McGinty
McIntyre says blowing my mind today
okay more pharmaceutical exposure
sources are you guys ready you guys
ready for this
all right
thank you
sorry guys
a lot of people get medication exposure
from the flea or tick powder or cream
they apply to their dogs and cats
if you can tell me
that you never had a tick collar or flea
collar on your dog or cat
if you can tell me you never put a flea
powder or tick powder on your cat or dog
if you can tell me they never received a
medication before
that would be amazing
at least you don't have to get exposed
right and it's okay I I love
doggies and cats I love animals
and um I would never ever shame a dog or
judge a dog or cat or animal because
they had to have a medication from the
vet or anything
I'm just saying that if there is
exposure we got the brain shot therapy
a lot of people get medication exposure
from flea tick powders creams they apply
to their dogs and cats or from flea and
tick repelling pet collars
intimacy
is another form of pharmaceutical
exposure for example kissing someone
who's on medication
I talked about that earlier
then there are medicated creams that
have a powerful out gas
now
I'm not trying to be like take this so
far
that it's like so mind-blowing
but I'm just gonna tell you what happens
at the stores at the grocery store
a lot of people
have medications that are creams and
they rub them on all parts of their
bodies
it's one of the biggest pharmaceutical
industry part there is
creams
creams that are pharmaceutical based
drugs and creams
everybody puts their creams on in the
morning
wherever they're going to rub it
like wherever
their butt wherever creams are big
creams for their butt
the rectums
for hemorrhoids
creams for everything
creams for their skin rashes creams for
their skin tags
people are on creams
and then they go to the grocery store
after they creamed up
steroid creams everything
and now they're going through all the
produce and they're rubbing their creams
on all the produce and packaged food and
everything
but it's not just one person thousands
of people going through the grocery
stores and farmers markets
and they're getting their creams on
everything
chemotherapy cream
I can't tell you how many times Spirit
of compassion has told me when I was at
a farmer's market that someone's
chemotherapy cream
was rubbed on produce
or something else
so many people are on chemotherapy
creams
that's why they're at a farmer's market
they're trying to eat healthier they've
been diagnosed with cancer
and they're using the creams
foreign
there's
a lot of pharmaceutical creams
so that are that it's it's incredible
right how it works so so many people
have creams on them and it's getting on
everything
so I'm not saying
I mean we just got to live on planet
Earth can't hide from it
but that's why I like having tools
so that if I'm getting some of that
stuff in me here and there somehow
grabbing this package grabbing that and
I'm getting it in me
I want to have a tool to help
Danielle says I've worked at a ranch
all grass fed every year they brand them
and cut the balls off the steers and
they give them a shot of antibiotics
every single baby cow
it's pharmaceutical exposure
oh God that's awful
um
then there are medicated creams that
have a powerful out gas
a large variety of medicated creams from
steroid creams to chemotherapy creams
out gas a very potent pungent smell that
the person using the cream is unaware of
because they live in it breathing in
this gassing is exposure
but I talked about about the exposure in
the stores right basic contact with
shopping carts handles
um
Ardent Advent says all the things we
don't even think about thank you for
bringing awareness you're welcome
basic contact with shopping cart handles
shopping cart handles are a big one
that's a big one
if I have to grab a sharping a shopping
cart handle sorry
Linda kluskey says
so the point of this is to let everyone
know that no matter how healthy pure
they think they are we all have
Pharmaceuticals in our bodies yes so I
would love to do something for people I
would love to know they have tools
so they can help themselves protect
themselves defend themselves and so
forth
basic contact with shopping cart handles
is another surprising source of exposure
because those handles are
where a lot of pharmaceutical residue
resides not just bacteria and viruses
and herpes and everything else that's on
those shopping cart handles I take an
alcohol wipe and I wipe the handle with
an alcoholic
often from pharmaceutical creams
and sweat from individuals Palms so what
I don't like about the shopping cart
handles is because
Pharmaceuticals come out of people's
Palms
their sweat from their palms they start
holding the handles and pushing the
handle through
which contain pharmaceutical residue if
they're on medication
all right you guys want me to read a
little bit more we okay
foreign
Pharmaceuticals and our brain
Pharmaceuticals are manufactured to
affect the brain or body in specific
ways generally stimulating or
suppressing certain neurological or body
processes
so when you take a medication it could
very well be for the purpose of trying
to enhance or subdue particular
functions of the brain
at the same time you know like
antidepressants any
uh any anti-anxiety meds
benzodiazepines right at the same time
Pharmaceuticals can affect the functions
of the brain in ways that aren't always
ideal
metal says I'm not an animal eater but
does this apply to the Kosher meat
industrial industry too yes it does
see
there are side effects sometimes
debilitating and life-altering and even
creating a dependency that outweighs the
original problem for which the person
took the medication for so we all know
that a lot of medications prescribed for
people for their brains
because their brains aren't working
right
but then a dependency happens and then
the problem can worsen and so forth
and that dependency outweighs the
original problem the person even took
the medication for right
medications can be in general toxic to
all areas of the brain here's how it
works
some on page 201 a brain saver just want
to give you a little run down here
before I go any further
new people that popped on here okay two
best books right now hands down
in health history I can say that because
I can judge these books I'm allowed to
judge it myself and have an opinion on
these books best books
hands down greatest books of all time
in history
letting you know
Miramar says I was going I was going to
make this today now let's see wait
I wasn't gonna make this today I thought
I didn't need it now I'm making both for
me and my daughter
pharmaceutical exposure shot
that's what marama is talking about
hands down the best books
truly and you'll know it when you read
them I can judge him because the
information came from above it wasn't
I'm not being biased it came from above
if I don't like it I can say I don't
like it but they're incredible
okay
um
Char dream says what if you have to take
medications to live it's fine of course
this isn't this isn't about stopping
your medications if you're on your
medications
no this is about pharmaceutical exposure
shots
which means yeah you can take the book
to your doctor or doctor can I take the
pharmaceutical exposure shot
it's apples
it's lemons it's cilantro it's onion
it's limes it's asparagus it's lemons I
said that right can I take the shot
foreign
pharmaceutical shot is for recent
exposure
which is incredible
and other medical medium information and
stuff is from for past exposure but I
like the pharmaceutical shot also for
some past exposure too because past
exposure can Leach out of our liver and
become recent exposure so I like the
Pharmaceuticals shop for that
okay
um
I'd like to read a little bit more if we
can
let's see Polly Wren says Anthony I love
your life so so much
especially this brain shot challenge
Hearts I prayed to catch this today
because the timing usually clashes with
my kids
with my kids bedtime and here I am yes
and yes you are and this is an amazing
Live two-day talk about pharmaceutical
stuff which is always fun to talk about
I mean come on it is right
okay medications can be in general toxic
to all areas of the brain here's how it
works
he's got a brain over here
excuse me guys I might have to take my
Pharmaceuticals right now
um
and nothing to drink them with
you guys don't mind right
could I can I take it with my celery
juice or is that is that not good I'm
gonna take away
let me just take it with some water here
oh
I'm joking that is an L-lysine capsule
from vimergy my favorite company
vemergy.com he's in Victor i m e r g
y.com I endorse these guys their stuff
is incredible and that is a lysine
capsule licing capsule from beverages
all right enough fooling around let's
get down to it you guys
here's how it works when a medication
enters a person's body system the liver
absorbs some of it every time we take a
medication the liver absorbs some of it
right here the liver I haven't seen this
guy in a long time I think it's been
like a couple of years before he's
before I've had him out here on the
stage
okay your liver absorbs part of that
medication every time you have a
medication
much of that medication enters the
bloodstream directly
bypassing the liver at first
[Music]
sound effects
because some medications have an uncanny
ability to absorb into your bloodstream
through your mouth medications can
absorb through the mouth in through the
throat
esophagus
stomach
duodenum
when medications find their way as far
as the small intestinal tract that's
when they find their way into the lining
of the track and eventually into the
hepatic portal vein and where does that
go up to your liver
even medications that bypass the liver
at first eventually find their way there
through the bloodstream so even a
medication that absorbs here boom
absorbs through here here esophagus
stomach duodenum still find their way to
the liver
when the liver absorbs the medications
as part of its bloodstream cleanup the
kidneys aren't the only part of the
blood cleanup equation
the liver is doing blood clean up
Lynn aubers I feel like I have a
fighting chance now yes best books ever
I mean best books ever thank you Lynn
thanks for agreeing
thank you
um
no one you know what they try to throw
at Medical medium I noticed that the
influencers try to pull this stuff
it's kidneys it's kidneys and kids it's
kidneys he knows nothing about the
kidneys it's like
it's like dude
your kidneys don't stand a chance if
your liver's not being taken care of
am I going to be that fool that's just
like kidneys kidneys kidneys all these
years and and not even knowing anything
about the liver and how what the liver
does and how to clean it up kidneys
kidney kidneys am I going to be that
fool that does that or am I going to
listen to Spirit of fashion it's like
liver liver or liver that's how you can
save your kidneys if you don't take care
of your liver you can't save your
kidneys
same thing with lymphatic system medical
medium doesn't talk enough about
lymphatic system lymphatic system that's
what the influencers do it's like dude
your lymphatic system is a Dumping
Ground when your liver is sick
you want me to talk about a lymphatic
system all day long and not and not like
in in in message the truth about the
liver and what the liver does because if
you don't take care of your liver
your lymphatic system is just going to
be filled with all the time your
lymphatic system is going to be drowning
in garbage if you don't take care of
your liver your lymphatic system is
going to be drowning the medical medium
cleanses and Protocols are pro-lymphatic
system because it's taking care of the
liver it automatically takes care of the
lymphatic system but you'll find
influencers goes he doesn't do anything
about the lymphatics are you kidding me
he used to know anything about the
kidneys like what if you don't take care
of your liver
then forget your kidneys
they don't know what does what they just
say lymphatic system or or kidney so
they can sell you a product
that's an affiliate product
coming from another place in another
place that convinces all these young
influencers oh you've got to get your
lymphatic systems what if you don't take
care of your liver or understand your
liver you're never going to take care of
your lymphatic system I don't care how
many lymphatic drainage massages you get
you can't take care of your lymphatic
system if you don't take care of your
liver that's just the bottom line
it is for your lymphatic system that's
what all this is for they just don't
know it
anyway
okay I had to get one rant in today
so let's let's move on to the
medications
when the medication is out of your
bloodstream it's living somewhere else
such a stored deep inside the liver
where the medication is then Time
released back into the bloodstream for
future years to come inevitably a
stagnant sluggish liver with a storage
bin of old Pharmaceuticals has to pop a
cork every so often
so if we don't take care of our liver it
pops a cork and then our lymphatic
system takes a hit
releasing residues they find their way
to the brain eventually if someone's not
cleansing
then all that Gunk is just going to the
brain
you can squeeze your lymphatic system
all you want if you don't
clean up the liver
then you don't stand a chance of keeping
your lymphatic system clean
oops
they still say this is for your
lymphatic system so do do this product
do this program you know it this is what
it does in your body which they don't
even know it's all a scam anyone can
sense like scam scam scam everywhere
it's for your lymphatic system this is
for your kidneys here's a product for
your kidneys here's your product for
your lymphatic system
but they don't even actually know what
does what or what
the liver is up against a lot when we
don't know how to care for it so it
can't hold on to every brain betrayer
forever which is Pharmaceuticals example
as the liver gets over saturated with
various cocktails of medications you
might have taken along the way or taken
long term including over-the-counter
medications it starts letting go of some
of those medications liver starts to let
go of some of those meds
they circulate throughout the
bloodstream again and again and they
find their way back to the brain no
longer just affecting The receptors the
medications were originally intended for
the longer the meditation the meditation
is Fun the longer the meditation stay in
the body the more
efficacy the medications lose
for their intended purpose so what
happens is all the med just stay in our
body and they don't even work anymore
for their intended purpose now the
pharmaceutical Brew can act as a toxic
substance
to the brain overall
on IG Hillary thank you aw for helping
me save money and not by trendy fad
items that don't help the root problem
and boy
boy oh boy oh boy
that's why I'm not like so much by so
many people creating hit pieces is
because if you tell the truth about an
ionizer water machine or you tell the
truth about
whatever Pearl powder Shiloh G charcoal
whatever you want us to call I mean
people get angry as
angry Infinite Wellness says my
lymphatic system was drowning until I
found you and healed
foreign
plus Pharmaceuticals contain toxic heavy
metals Pharmaceuticals also contain
caffeine these additives are part of how
medications affect the brain so potently
because there's Metals in
Pharmaceuticals and caffeine in
Pharmaceuticals and they get to your
brain
medications of any kind whether intended
for the brain or elsewhere have the
ability to get past the blood-brain
barrier and enter every part of the
brain because Pharmaceuticals are tissue
soluble how's that word how do you
pronounce that word soluble
cellulable
soluble
I'm not a scholar I'm not an academic
I'm a messenger that writes word for
word from Spirit of compassion doesn't
mean I'm the best reader
there's no part of the brain that's
immune or unexposed medication also gets
stuck in the brain
in which case it doesn't get time
released
it stays there indefinitely okay so what
this is saying right here is what Spirit
fashion was saying that these meds get
stuck on our brain and they're not Time
released in the brain out of the brain
they're Time released out of the liver
so liver will pop a cork and let some of
that out all the time but the brain
won't pop a cork and let the meds out
they saturate the brain unless we work
on getting them out with tools
these toxins stay definitely raising
toxicity levels within the brain tissue
slowly denaturing brain cells and then
never leaving the brain until someone
learns how to actively and proactively
work to clean it out of the brain tissue
and that's why people can go mad
just all that stuff just building up in
their brain
it's terrible
for more information
on how recreational drugs can affect our
brain see chapter 11 micro dosing I had
to read that little part
some medications can be useful in crisis
situations such as injuries or severe
infections I love how they're trying to
make micro dosing so hip and trendy it's
unbelievable and it's I notice
that
it's like ridiculous too it's like
it's like preying on kids now for real
the micro dosing thing is preying on
kids now because you got all these
young people that have brain problems
they got brain fatigue they got brain
fog they got folks in concentration
issues and then you tell these young
people
about microdosing psychedelics and
everything else
and you know it hits that science-minded
thing like micro dosing it must be
science proven there must be people who
have done you know just right they know
what's going on it's a micro dosing
culture that's starting up is actually
insane
Colleen bloomhuff I'm soaking in water
that's connected to the ionizer machine
I thought it cleanses the lymph system
and heavy metals out of the body Colleen
you can do what you want and do what
your doctor tells you but I'm going to
tell you my
my
thoughts okay
alkaline ionizer water machines are one
of the greatest scams of all time
there's a lot of great scams and that's
one of them
those metal plates corrode
and in the past before medical meme
information got everywhere like it's
pretty much getting everywhere now where
people are actually like on all this B12
and they're doing all these things now
and taking care of themselves all that's
been Pro medical meaning for for decades
right in the past when people were doing
the ionizer water machines they went
mental
and got sicker
because of the metal plates corroding
is one of the greatest scams of all time
one of them there's a bunch of them but
that's definitely on the list
it's terrible
and then people doing those machines and
then blaming medical medium for getting
them sicker when they're drinking tons
of that ionizer water that alkaline
ionized water and they're going to get
so sick
their brains that's metal metal
particles leaching out of those
those plates with electric with
electricity attached to those metal
plates corroding them over time
insane
that tips to scale the wrong way
it's exhausting
been saying it for years some
medications can be useful in crisis
situations this is interesting
I've done water shows in the past
talking about this I'll do some things
again when I can
but right now we're in the 20-day
medical meme brings out there big one
challenge guess what it's free
so how to get your stuff
get the book free at the library
some medications can be useful in crisis
situations such as injuries or severe
infections
I'm not anti-medication
I am not anti-medication
for a lot of reasons some of it is
useful
there are times when they are truly
necessary I say it here
what we need to be aware of is how
long-term use of pharmaceuticals end up
saturating brain tissue and dampening
the central nervous system's ability to
perform and we're not fixing the
original problem we have to work on
fixing the original problem
when we're not given answers from the
medical industry about how to heal
chronic illness
are symptoms and conditions continue far
too long and we may find ourselves on
medications for extended periods and I'm
not shaming blaming or judging anybody
with the medications possibly making our
conditions worse on top of it medical
research and science don't even know
what the cause of chronic illness is to
begin with
so they also don't realize they could be
making the condition worse from the
medication
one thing to keep in mind
is that sometimes multiple medications
are prescribed by different doctors
creating a stronger Brew than anyone
intended that can alter or hinder
your brain's ability to function
optimally if you're actively relying on
medication I respect that
says it here I do you can still work on
healing your brain and protecting it
from the dozens of other brain betrayers
here in part
three
boom diddly boom
you guys
that was really intense by the way did
you find that kind of intense
half time
[Music]
robot oh robot anybody
is anybody doing the robot
we we're doing the robot
[Music]
I like the robot
I like it am I embarrassed yeah I'm
embarrassed
all right let's go
embarrassing yeah it's embarrassing
do I care no
I don't mind embarrassing myself I don't
care all right you guys
we're having fun um here we are I got my
ingredients in front of me
try doing that holding your breath
no don't try doing that I'm sorry don't
try doing that only around it's a bad
idea because that's what I do
don't do what I do
because I do things that are Reckless
I work 20 hours a day and get a few
hours of sleep that is not wise it's
actually not good at all
quarter peeled lemon that's a lime
lemon
quarter peeled lemon
that's going in first
I'm gonna cut it
yep
quarter lime peel
lime
I peeled it you guys saw I peeled it at
the beginning
borderline peeled
okay
what's next what's next quarter cup
chopped green onions
man
these babies are Sharp
they're sharp that's some strong
strong use
I've got totally packed fresh cilantro
cilantro anyone
oh my God I love the smell of that onion
the green onions
love that smell it just hit me
such a great smell
and a half cup of cilantro here
do you know when something like the
aroma
the aroma something smells so good
all right what's next
we got
two raw medium asparagus stems
Spears
get it right
whoa
there's two nice ones there these are
kind of like still small just letting
you know these aren't the real big ones
all right what's next half a stock
celery
oh hang on
all right
I'm stock celery
let's get that in here
I don't think that's funny at all
half an apple
foreign
that's a really nice apple right there
this is going to be so good
I love the pharmaceutical
exposure shot
a friend of mine said why are you taking
the pharmaceutical exposure shot like
what's wrong with you are you on
Pharmaceuticals
no I'm not any I'm not on any
Pharmaceuticals no not on any it's
taking the shot I said I don't know did
you read the book it's a lot of exposure
there's so many Avenues of exposure
popping some apple in here
we go
if you're new here and you don't know
about the mm1500 or 900 it's 20 off
right now but guess what
that's not the special thing that's
that's amazing
the special thing is
is the money saved
not because of the 20 off the money
saved because of the fact that squeezes
so much juice out
and I endorse these guys because of it
because if it saves you money it saves
you money I love how the pulp comes out
like this
right
I saw a comment on YouTube
um
I think it was legit was it Roseanne was
it Rosanna I can't remember but
I think she was talking about how
there's influencers out there pushing
the spinning basket one
yeah
yeah totally the spinning basket one is
takes a lot of produce and you lose a
lot of produce and people aren't wealthy
or Rich enough or have access to co-ops
and access to infinite amounts of
produce coming their way where they
could just keep on pushing it through
that machine
people who are chronically sick don't
have all that money to throw away so
that's what I love about the mm 1500 900
because it's squeezing more juice out of
it that's the whole point and it's
preserving the nutrients because it's a
cold pressed masticating machine because
when you're sick you need that when
you're chronically sick you need a
medicine maker not a you know a
flamboyant
spend a ton of money on produce every
minute kind of machine
Carrie Pearson says the mm Omega juicers
are the best save so much money and
you're saving money not just not just
because the discount right you're saving
money
because of the produce you're buying
less produce oh my God
matters
yeah
all right
guess what
I got a shot glass right here
fantastic
I did something right
[Music]
see you later Pharmaceuticals
bye bye
any recent exposure I may have had
I'm kissing you goodbye
[Music]
so good
it's incredible is you can sense how it
it actually can work
because I don't get experiences like
that when I just drink the juice the
green juice
[Music]
because it's about what it is the
phytochemical compounds working together
we create so much
destruction and Death on this planet
Earth so much toxic waste
you have to have a balance somewhere
there has to be something that exists on
this planet that you can grow from your
food that can
Levy against it
and that's what I love that's where the
compassions wisdom
and knowledge about what we can use to
battle what we need to battle
bartender
give me another
bartender I'm not mad or anything I just
want another
Carson says I took ADHD meds
since I was a child I had terrible side
effects and symptoms when I finally got
off of them I tried everything to heal
but the only thing that worked was the
medical medium information
eternally grateful
God love you
God bless you
that means more to me anybody knows
that's the whole point
truly making a difference in people's
lives because no one understands
[Music]
no one understands what it's like
they don't understand what it's like
to be struggling and and have no answers
um
someone wants to tell you that they are
happy you're off the ADHD medications
and you found medical medium too
um
somebody wants to tell you and they are
clapping their hands Dr asking why are
you clapping your hands because you're
proud of that person
yes I am proud too
Dr Nesbit is very proud
of
of you for getting off this meds and
finding medical medium information
Dr Nesbitt where's Beatrice
she's indisposed what does that mean
she's indisposed in the moment
I never understood that I was indisposed
um anyway Dr nesbitt's here he said he
took a day off today he's not doing
surgeries today
it says he's thinking about micro dosing
what
no he's joking
he doesn't think it's a good idea he
just likes whiskey
hardcore whiskey is his favorite what's
your favorite brand
I'm not going to repeat that brand on
here I don't want to give anybody any
ideas thinking that it's good for them
Dr Nesbitt says that he's proud of
everybody here just keep that in mind
that he cares
yeah no I know I know they like you they
still like you yep
even though you're yeah they look they
have doctors they have doctors too
it's okay if you're a doctor Dr Nesbitt
yeah
yeah I told them we were board certified
psychiatrist and a surgeon
Dr Nesbitt says that he will gladly
um
be offering psychiatrist needs to anyone
if they're a chicken so you have to be a
chicken and an order for Dr Nesbitt to
give you
um
therapy as his Psychiatry therapy
yes
you work on humans he does surgery on
humans all the time is his waiting room
is filled with humans and his surgical
table he works all day on is filled with
humans but he only
gives
psychiatric help to chickens
yeah he says he only talks to chickens
he'll cut people open and he'll he'll do
all kinds of surgeries on people but he
loves to work with chickens uh
psychiatric wise so
yep in Greece is nothing better than
chickens he's hoping he's got a question
to ask you guys is it a question or a
demand
he's insisting on something he says that
can you please not eat chickens or
chicken or chicken fingers he says try
not to eat chicken fingers or chicken
breasts Dr Nesbitt don't get too excited
about this they're not gonna stop if
they like chicken they're probably gonna
still eat chicken and I can't tell them
different so just just calm down
he says he's been wanting to say this
for a long time but he's hoping
everybody stops eating chicken
um
what about Peggy and Donnie the Donkey
he says that for Piggy's sake I don't
know if you guys know who piggy is but
piggy is a friend of Dr Nesbit piggy for
piggy sake uh Dr Nesbitt asks if you
stop eating pig and ham and bacon
Dr Nesbitt people are going to do what
they want to do and uh that's just it we
have a message for the vegans
yeah he says the vegans
um they're eating too much vegan cheese
out there
he says the vegan cheese he says that he
was doing a surgical operation on a
human and he found a hunk of vegan
cheese
uh inside
their abdomen
what
says yes he pulled a piece of vegan
cheese out of somebody's abdomen
and he said that one of the nurses ate
it
Dr Nesbit that's that's like a terrible
joke
he says no it was a perfect piece of
vegan cheese
it was still wrapped in plastic from the
store they swallowed the vegan cheese
with the plastic on it so the nurse said
there was nothing wrong with it and it
shouldn't go to waste and she ate the
vegan cheese in darkness we gotta go
Dr Nesbitt says that
Dr Smith has a crazy sense of humor by
the way you guys I'm not kidding
um Selena yes it's the mm 1500 I am
using indeed today the mm-900 is also uh
my favorite as well
Lorraine you didn't like that joke from
Nesbit
all right but all I did I liked it lots
of laughing faces
um get on the medical medium newsletter
please if you guys can download the free
grocery shopping list because we're only
on day 14 of a 20-day brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge go to
medicalmedium.com and get on the
newsletter another light blast is coming
soon too so you might want to get on the
light blast newsletter too at
medicalneem.com because we will be doing
another light blast
and even Dr Nesbitt is going to attend
that light blast as well
um go watch the blood draw video that
was posted on reels today on IG if you
can and
um what else uh check out my telegram
messages I left one saying I'm sorry
if you haven't already listened to it
check out medical medium podcast if you
can can I just say one thing can I just
say one thing is that okay just one
thing okay
um Dr Nesbit agrees that I should say
this
all right
look at that one it's okay
Dr campus says document says we can tell
you
medical medium podcasted Apple podcast
there's no advertisements and no
commercials
it's unbelievable it's the only podcast
of
its stature
that doesn't have that
I know we're just being stupid
we can make a ton of money and we don't
do it by giving people free come no
commercials and no advertising I know
okay so as far as it goes um imposters
look at imposters by the way people who
say they're medical medium
people who say they're Anthony William
and that they want to do a consultation
and they DM you and so forth and
everything and they want money from you
and everything else imposters there is
they use my name and they use my profile
that's what imposters do please report
post imposters to medicalme.com on this
spot in my web on the website where it
says you can you know it's an imposter
uh
all right
I will see you guys
bye guys oh I'll see you tomorrow day
15. let's finish this thing up we got
five more days no six six more days
let's let's finish this thing up
tomorrow