they rob
and steal any chance for you to heal
they rob and steal
any chance for you to heal
the dealers the professionals that don't
know why anybody's sick
all the different product dealers they
rob
and steal any chance for you to heal
but you won't know that until you're
really sick
and then you'll know and then you'll
find out
if you're lucky if you're one of the
lucky ones
that figures out somehow
some way it's your opportunity to heal
has been taken from you from the world
of guessing games in alternative
medicine
don't know why you're sick don't know
why you got the hashimoto's
the fibromyalgia the ra the neurological
lyme
the ms tingles and numbness the aches
and pains
the body aches the body pains the ear
ringing fluttering popping heart
palpitations
heart arrhythmias and migraines and
anything else
too and what happens is the guessing
games
and the games played on people in the
industry in the alternative industry
about try this no do this kombucha tea
will fix it no bone broth will fix it
no apple cider vinegar will fix it no
nutritional yeast will help
now try this product that product and
they rob and steal any chance
for you to heal we're live we're live on
youtube we're live on
facebook you guys we're live on tick
tock right now
which is really cool we're live on
clubhouse too
so i'm excited we're talking about some
cool things right here because
you know i talk about the traps but the
traps
are real they're pieces of wood
they're wooden sticks they've been
sharpened right so they have the point
a hole is dug in the ground for you
yeah and those little sticks and and
those
sharp sticks are in that hole pointed up
and you come walking and then they put a
little cover on it with some bushes on
top
and you come walking around you're like
well wait a minute should i try this gut
health product
powder let me do that wait should i try
oh i'll try this new apple cider vinegar
it's got mother in it
that's the way let me try that and
you're coming over and you're about to
step up and you go right in
and you're now stuck on those those
sticks they spear right through you're
like you're a tiger
like a tiger the industry has to catch
you they run ads
24 7. did you guys know that
did you guys know that they run ads 24
7. ads ads ads for the podcast adds ads
i'm not saying there's anything wrong
with that
i'm just saying the traps are set
they're set
the ads are running 24 7 on all the
different channels everywhere else you
can possibly imagine
try this probiotic that'll fix you
that's the answer try this microorganism
product that will fix it right there
try this clay that will work try this
charcoal that will work
try this colostrum try this deer antler
try this neem
try this kombucha tea try this bone
broth try try try try try the robin
steal
any chance for you to heal we're live on
youtube
live on facebook live on tick-tock we're
live on clubhouse
letting you guys know and i'm making
fries i'm making fries you guys
i'm excited about it too so i can't wait
we're gonna make some fries the whole
bit
um so why is this important why does
this matter simply look good to see it
why is this important how come it
matters
it matters because when you're not so
sick
you don't know it you don't know it if
you're not so sick right
you won't know it but you'll be trapped
in those snares eventually
and eventually get too sick that's
how it happens to everyone and maybe
you're somebody that's not sick but you
just you just care about what you're
doing you care about what you're doing
for your health
you care about how you're taking care of
yourself right so all these things
really
won't take you down they won't take you
down
but you know what i've noticed you guys
you know don't
know what i've noticed on tick tock you
guys know what i've noticed on facebook
youtube right clubhouse
it's like you got all these health
experts out there right
all these health experts and they all
all mirror the same crap
they all do they all mirror the same
crap and they're funny
not funny it's the same stuff the same
stuff
unless they steal something from medical
medium without citing it back
right but you know what the funny thing
is is when they steal
something from medical medium
they're really hurting people because
they're not saying hey here's the other
good pieces
here's the other good pieces of the
puzzle we don't have to play the
guessing games we can
there's other pieces right but
it's good to be back on tick tock i just
thought welcome back on tick tock
back on tick tock and but i got to tell
you guys
when all these professionals out there
which i support many of them right
because i want health professionals to
be out there but they're all
mirroring the same stuff
they don't want no one wants to be out
of the club it's
one big club it's one big
club is what it is that's what it is out
there
it's one big club okay don't don't step
out of line
nope don't step in a line here no yep
here's a probiotic don't step out of
line
here's a good health product here's a
protein powder don't step out of line
protein you need your protein you need
your protein don't step out of line
okay nope nutritionist that's fine don't
step out of line
here's your acv don't step out of line
nope nope
right here's yeah here's your corella
don't step out of line here's your
charcoal don't step out
don't step out of line that's how it
works
it's just everybody mirrors the same
stuff you need your protein you need
your balance
diet you need your moderation you need
your fats you need your fats you need
your fats
don't step out of line they all mirror
the
same thing it's one big
ugly trap it's the wild west
is what it is it's one big ugly trap
don't believe me fine don't believe me
that's okay
because what happens is you end up
getting sicker
down the road and you're stuck in that
trap
and that's when it matters that's when
it counts right there or if you're sick
you're sick and you get stuck in that
truck michelle l good to see you
i see you guys coming on um we're live
on tick tock we're live on youtube we're
live on facebook we're live on clubhouse
and i'm making fries and i'm talking
about something really critical to know
they'll rob and steal every chance and
any chance
for you to heal that's what they'll do
they'll teach you to fat yourself to
death that's what they'll teach you to
do because
we're already fatting ourselves to death
we're already
fatting ourselves to death and but they
want to teach you
more and more fat yourself to death more
that's yourself to death more
right that's what they want to do
protein your kidneys to death how about
that they want you to protein
your kidneys to death as a plant-based
person i'm not just talking about animal
protein person
plant-based person okay
it's that's what's happening i see a
comment on there
medical medium club is the best so what
it is is
there's this big club out there
big happy mob out there
they all sing the same tune they all do
the same thing
and they all advertise the same crap
and it's just one big ugly
club out there and they got those pits
dug out for you
and you're walking along
and you're down there snared you're
snared
and then your cupboards are filled with
all of their crap
protein powders gut products left and
right
mct oil whatever it is just filled with
crap
and that that's what it is right but hey
why should i care why should i even care
right like why should it even matter why
should i put myself
out there because i got
an understanding since i was young right
spirit of compassion said to me
you're gonna understand the suffering
and the struggling whether you
like it or not and i was like i just
want to be a kid i don't want to know
any kind of suffering
i don't know why i don't want to do any
kind of struggling
and i don't want to be connected to that
i don't want to be connected to when
someone
has been to their fifth doctor and their
sixth
seventh doctor and they've been to their
tenth their tenth specialist
and they're hurting and they're not
getting answers
and they they don't feel good and their
depression is taking over
i don't want any part of that i remember
being young remember when i was young
and i was like
i don't want to be any part of that i
don't want to be
a part of that i don't because that
land is scary land scary land spirit of
compassion said
you have to know what people go through
you have to know what they're struggling
with you have to know what they're
suffering with
you have to know what it's like to be in
their shoes i don't want to be in their
shoes
i don't want to be in their shoes i
remember having
arguments and spirit of compassion when
i was young
10 years old 11 years old saying the
spirit of compassion i don't want
nothing to do with that
i don't and soc said
you have to you have to that that's
that's you have to work for the light
and you have to make sure
no matter what that you understand their
suffering and their struggles
and you get it and you get it and you
can sense it you can feel it
you can smell it you just know it and
you know it inside your soul
and then it's about protecting everyone
and that's what it was about so all
these years it's about
protecting everyone how can i protect
you i got to teach you about the blood
draws
because you guys are getting your blood
sucked out of you
to death right you know like i talk
about the medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
exactly the medical medium podcast and
our podcast the blood draw
bloodletting podcast episode right
and that's what's happening i'm holding
up my book because i got some french
fries here
and i'm going to make french fries in a
couple of minutes you guys so we're
going to have some fun
um so and that's what they do they'll
just still just do
things to just suck the blood right out
of you and i've talked about that you
guys they only need this much blood but
the industry
takes all the blood from our children
right you only need that that much blood
okay and you can get literally you
wouldn't believe the profile so you can
get off of that alone right you only
need that much blood
but they theft our blood that's what
they do and all alternative medicine
bought into it
alternative medicine believes you need
tons of blood
in order to run a test but they knock
out your immune system
they lower your immune system the
industry lowers your immune system
that's what they do
okay in hopes that someday you get so
sick you just rely on all their drugs
all their drugs exactly the alternative
medicine world
they're not innocent either they're not
innocent either
really important enough okay i want you
to have your doctors and your
practitioners i want you to have the
support system you need but you've got
to know how to protect yourself too
because people get sick and then next
thing you know the alternative medicine
world is playing their guessing games
and everybody i know you guys all love
your teeth right
you guys love your teeth m sky good to
see you ichota good to see you
right i know you guys are on tiktok good
to see you guys too
everybody loves your teeth right yeah
you want to keep your teeth clubhouse
you guys want to keep your teeth
you want to keep your teeth did you know
that apple cider vinegar will destroy
your teeth
okay will destroy your teeth it'll just
it'll just oh chris good to see you
chris
you're just one day your teeth will just
all fall apart
just start falling apart okay
isn't that funny no it's not funny right
and and and it's not about you know it's
not about the loving people that want to
sell a wholesome product it's not about
that
no i mean people they have compassion
they want people
there's good people selling products
that you know that
people are using that aren't great it's
good people in the caffeine industry
meaning not the caffeine industry the
mom and pop caffeine world right
i was talking to one person the other
day and they said you know your whole
hit on chocolate's been really hard on
me because
you know aw i'm sitting here we're like
sustainable
we're fair trade with our chocolate and
you're just hitting us hard
talking to somebody i know the other day
and i said
and i go okay i get it right i said
listen people are gonna eat chocolate no
matter what
you'll have plenty of chocolate to sell
okay people are gonna eat it
medical medium can't stop anybody from
eating chocolate come on let's face it
i can't stop anybody from eating cacao
there's no way in hell
caffeine industry and the chocolate
industry is a monster
and everybody's going to be addicted to
that caffeine until they die
right maybe not you guys right lorraine
l good to see you
and so but what happens is it's about
since i was young
yeah since i was young it was about
protecting you guys
because they rob and steal any chance
for you to heal
and they teach you how to fat yourself
to death on top of it
and then the guessing games are like
bullets and they're like knife jabs
when you're sick and even when you're
not
you know so um no caffeine and chocolate
for 60 days
that's really really really cool right
there on tick tock
you guys i'm holding this book because
this is the new edition right here
and well anthony what are you selling
what are you selling aw liz good to see
you
death by a thousand cuts what are you
selling anthony you can get the books
free at the library
just get it free the library if you want
yeah you can get it on amazon or a
bookstore or whatever
and you know what it does it pays for
making the book yeah
pays for all the everything to go to
actually printing the book
when you buy it off of something but get
it free at the library the free library
um i'm making the the problem is with
with like
like coffee and all the different
caffeines you got is a psychoactive
drug gotta keep that in mind right and
i know it takes the innocence out of it
i know
chocolate is so innocent in so many ways
right
it takes the innocence out of that but
chocolate's got the caffeine in there so
it's a psychoactive drug
and if you're gonna heal if you want to
heal it will get in the way that's all
it maybe not one time here and there but
it will
get in the way and there's no holding
back because that addiction is strong
right that's why everybody's on their
chocolate every week they're on their
chocolate smoothies they're throwing
chocolate and everything right on
tick-tock you guys
chocolates in everything yeah i saw
matcha yeah matcha the same thing the
caffeine right
and what happens is like the whole
osteopenia thing that's from all that
caffeine
osteopenia osteoporosis the caffeine
takes you down that road
right so look i could hold a blind eye
to it all
i could sit back pretend it's not
happening we can do that
we can sit back we can pretend it's not
happening we can pretend
nothing's happening how about that
nothing's happening you guys how about
that
right how's that sound does that sound
good wanna do that
when uh people say raw chocolate is good
but like you said
it's all bad well that's how it is
you know the drug dealers they'll say
they'll say chocolate's good
the drug dealers yeah because in the end
that's what it is it's a psychoactive
drug right
so it's really addicting and
lorraine else said chocolate is so hard
to let go
it is right cacao powder is smoothies
too yeah that's that's all
that's to brainwash you guys i'm trying
to un-brainwash
you right they got you brainwashed i can
go into all the different levels of
brainwash
protein protein protein protein powders
protein fat your brain wash
um chocolate chocolate chocolate
chocolate smoothies chocolate in your
smoothies cacao cacao
what happens is they train us to become
high chasers you guys on tick tock
they train us to become high chasers
chasing that high
gotta chase that high i'm gonna chase
that high i gotta keep on chasing that
high that's what it is
we become high chasers and they teach us
that young and then the alternate
movement takes it on
because they're drug dealers too and you
know but look look
pretend it's all it doesn't exist none
of it exists
who cares play the guessing games don't
don't drink your celery juice because
it's so bad for you like
you know like the industry tries to
basically trick out
trick out everybody and they put hits
out there to try to stop celery juice
right
just don't do anything good for yourself
exactly right
don't do anything good for yourselves i
just saw a whole bunch of people got
kicked off of facebook just now
so i just saw a whole bunch of people
got booted and it's like don't do
anything
for yourself protecting yourself right
don't know about these pitfalls don't
know about these snares don't know about
these
these problems and then we live our life
and we get beaten down without us
knowing
right i mean that's what happens
freezing on facebook it's freezing on
facebook because facebook's freezing it
out
um that's how they try to drop out 200
300 people at a time
400 people 500 people at a time um
so the whole thing you guys know medical
medium's been censored it's censored
everywhere
just everywhere you can't even put you
can't even put um
you can't even post medical mediums
sometimes and they just do
they censor it right don't show it to
everybody
but that's a whole thing you know
but if you're in the other club you're
fine the other club is
just go with the business like
it is but that's not having the person's
back
now you could be look you want to put
cacao powder in your smoothie i still
want you here
learning and i still realize you're
gonna have that addiction
so i still realize you're gonna have
that addiction right
so i do realize that but
i i want you at the same time to at
least know there's a way to protect
yourself
you know soon he's in good to see you
glad you guys are coming on
um guys you're coming on tick tock
that's great so we're having a good time
today i'm making fries
we're live on clubhouse facebook we're
live on everything youtube
practically we're live on tic tac right
now so it's really fun
so the bottom line is you guys do i have
your back or do i give up do i have your
back or do i just
sit back and just just worry about
myself
do you want me to do that now i could
worry about myself 24 7.
i could get into myself 24 7. just what
what is what does aw
need to do let's do aws life the whole
thing and all that stuff and
but you know that's just not that's not
good it's like i got to make sure
i got you back in a whole bit um look if
you're on facebook and you got booted
off
i should have said this earlier you can
go to tick tock you can go to youtube
you can just watch me on youtube right
now which is great because you
you get an awesome view on youtube right
here too you guys
so the bottom line is that's a pretty
harsh thing for me to say
right they rob and steal any chance for
you to heal
even if they don't know what they do
even if they do not know what they do
right you know not what they do right
even if that's a situation
but the bottom line is how
can i protect everyone the best they can
right and at the same time
you guys learn how to protect yourselves
so you become your health expert like
that's what it's always been about
you becoming a health expert your own
health expert
right so that's the key you're back good
to see you back okay good i'm glad
you're coming back amazing
amazing so the bottom line you guys
is this all right and um
we live in a place where it is like
been thinking about the matrix a lot
right and it's just a fun fun thing to
think about
a lot of people really they're they're
they really believe in that matrix right
a lot of people do
right and it's a pretty cool concept
it's a pretty cool theory but there
kind of really is a matrix going around
in the world of health there really is
and it's this place where there's so
many things
holding us back in it that we don't
realize that are happening
and then we get brainwashed in the
process right the protein deal
that brainwashed us that that totally
gave us the big brainwash in 1933. i
talked about that you guys
where it was to convince everybody that
protein means
everything it just means everything okay
and that that's been ingrained ingrained
in our psyche that's a big brainwashed
out alone all on its own
right and so it's like a mob is what it
is
and then science of research they're
part of that mob because they're a paid
for
mob in health right and they confuse us
because it's like this it's like
two plus two equals four jet fuel is
comprised of
this code it's pro it's comprised of
this math
you know it's it jet fuel is fossil fuel
you know what they do is they actually
synthesize it they actually
work it right they have all the science
so that so that literally you can have a
jet fly
right and there's all that but then so
we think well science knows everything
see that jet fly across the sky right
look i can call my friend right now on
my phone whatever
that's science science has it all down
and so we're convinced
that science has it all down in
in health especially with the surgeries
you need a heart valve replacement right
we can do it now
we can do it and that's what's
incredible out there right
so we can we get convinced that science
has it all down
but when it comes down to chronic
illness it's far from the truth
and then that leads us into like a whole
you know chasing chasing chasing highs
chasing uh dreams chasing everything
we're chasing those science and research
smoke and mirrors the smoke and the
mirrors we're in this one mirror room
and then one smoke room in one mirror
room and that's what we're chasing
but the bottom line is how can we
protect you guys
how can we give you guys answers so you
know why you're sick
and how can we give you the tools and
what to avoid when you think about it
that's everything
that's everything i'm gonna start making
some fries and we're gonna talk about
some cool stuff
we're live on youtube facebook clubhouse
and tick tock i'm going to put this down
for a second
so um i have steamed potatoes i'm taking
them out right now i'm going to cut some
fries i'm going to get them in the oven
and we're gonna make the ketchup
how about that so
i got some potatoes over here springing
them over
so these are steamed potatoes you can do
this without them being steamed but you
gotta
you know you gotta keep the lower heat
on the oven
so you're really baking the potato fries
right but i like them steamed so i could
put them in have the oven hot
make the fries really good aw thanks uh
savita says aw i am so grateful
for giving me my life back your
information saved me i mean that's what
matters
never heard that ever ever heard that
in the other in the other uh parts of
the alternative medicine world by the
way
years gone by if one practitioner
back in the 2000s early 2000s one
practitioner got
one person better it was a miracle
they'd be
heralded as like a god that's what
happened back then right
now we're in a place where you know
we've learned about so much information
now for medical medium it's spread out
so people are healing a little bit more
like why to stay away from gluten it's
35 years of mm work
why to stay away from this back in the
old days of the health movement it was
just about stay away from processed
foods that's all
processed foods right i'm going to put
some fries on here i'm cutting some
fries
as we speak i got some potatoes here it
was all about
back in the old day in alternative
medicine
it was all about just stay away from
processed foods
that's all boxed foods boxed cereals
sugar cereals right it was all about
stay away from
all that it was there was
nothing else nothing else in the health
scene nothing else
that's all it was i mean think about how
incredible that is right
it was just about that um
so i'm making some fries right here
and there are thousands of healing
stories
with the medical medium information
someone's gonna say of course well aw
you're you're gonna be tooting your own
horn about
medical medium information why wouldn't
you because you're a medical medium it's
like
i'm not tooting my horn i'm tooting the
horn of spirit of compassion because the
information came from spirit of
compassion so what i'm doing is i'm i'm
just
i'm happy it's been working all these
years
so that's what it is you know i'm happy
it's been working all these years so i
got some fries going on here
um
so what you do is you take the potato
and
these are still hot so they're a little
sticky right
take the potato and you can do it a
couple different ways you can do it like
this
just cutting these fries like that
these are a little bit more of the steak
fries and then you can cut the other
fries where they're not steak fries so
that's like a steak fry
a lot of people like those better that's
what i've noticed over the years they
like the steak fries right
you know it's kind of like there's
there's more meat to them so that's what
people like i'm just putting them on
on the pan right here
so i'm just dropping these on the pan as
you guys can see on tick tock that's
what i'm doing clubhouse that's what i'm
doing
and we got some good stuff to talk about
so what have you been taught to do
throughout the years you guys
you've been taught to do the bone broth
which has the vinegar in it
i call the bone broth the fat broth
that's what it is
it's the fat broth and
that's a hard one it's it's it's hard to
heal
when you're doing the bone broth because
that pancreas and that liver of yours
is under so much stress when you're
doing bone broth
you know and but yeah you'll you know
people like oh this is how people
you know can get better it's like oh it
is it it's not
it's not the thing is with bone broth is
if you're choosing not to eat anything
else and you're just doing bone broth
you're you're now basically doing a mono
diet for the moment
and yeah you might see some benefits in
the moment but in the end it's not
the way to go because you'll see more
fallbacks over time
the whole vinegar thing in the bone
broth is really really not a good idea
too
vinegar is is such a health destroyer
and the reason why some people feel like
they get a boost from bone broth
is because of the steroids involved
so you get faked out so a lot of
alternative medicine
is a fake out just so you know so i'm
putting some fries on this
on this sheet here a lot of alternative
medicine is a fake out
so what happens is that when the cow
is gone to slaughter right
doesn't matter if you say well no our
practices of how we kill our cows is
different
we don't terrify the cows we don't
we don't walk them through that moment
of death this isn't an anti-animal
protein campaign
i'm i i support animal protein people
and i support plant-based people so i
just need that disclaimer out front
right now for you guys
so it's just important to know but i get
it there's there's practices
where we we don't walk the cow corral it
to the to the you know slaughterhouse
right and the cows are all freaking out
right we we have practices it's like
nice cow we're petting the cow or
petting the cow and then we hit the cow
on the back of the head
okay so we got these practices where
it's more humane
right i've heard that from a lot of
different um from a lot of different
industries with it all right
but the deal is is with that is no
matter what the adrenals still
explode so when you kill the cow
the cow's adrenals explode so the whole
all the information of the cow's
adrenals draining
all that all that epinephrine into the
body
this medical medium information
originally i taught that for years and
years
right and where that adrenaline goes i
mean we're talking about
huge adrenals cal adrenals are huge
where that adrenaline goes is inside the
bones not just inside the meat
inside the bones okay
so when you're doing the bone broth
a big part of that adrenaline surge goes
inside the bones
more so than even the meat okay
and so when you're doing your bone broth
you're getting a steroid high
we're high chasing again we're high
chasing again
and high chasing is an important
understanding
because they rob and steal any chance
for you to heal
and puts you on a high chase on top of
it
so now you're having your bone broth you
look at this bone broth it's good this
bone broth is good i'm having it i'm
having it
and you're getting this steroidal effect
the steroid high is what you're getting
that's how it works
and no one's gonna know that
no one's gonna know that chris linnell
went to a health practitioner
and get more sick since one year
read all your books eat
your recommendations follow the
protocols
the energy supplements and getting
better and stronger and younger every
day
thank you for giving me my life back
love you for the job
you are doing chris i'm honored thank
you for being here
and i can't tell you how happy that
makes me
it makes me happy to know you're getting
your life back
i mean doesn't that matter does that
matter you guys does it
because the industry that robs and
steals any chance for you to heal
doesn't care if you get your life back
because guess what you rely
less on the industry you rely
less on the industry is what happens
health with liz
good to see you see you on tick tock
right now because
i think you got booted off of
put it off of facebook do your books
address
balancing female hormones
yeah they do because what happens is if
you don't get your adrenal strong
like medical medium adrenal snacks right
all that information there
if you don't get your adrenal strong how
are you ever going to balance your
your hormones how's it gonna be possible
you can't balance female female hormones
unless your adrenals are up to par you
know why because once you lose that
hormone blend in your adrenals
your hair falls out as a woman and
caffeine is a big part of that a big
part of that one
big part of that and so
if you don't if you don't address your
adrenals
then your reproductive hormones that's
part of your reproductive hormones
your estrogen it's your adrenals
so um yeah i addressed that in medical
medium
new addition and cleanse the heal
so that's fun to heal right there it's a
new addition okay that's cleansed appeal
and that's the new addition to medical
medium
if so what happens is you're having your
bone broth someone recommended it
practitioner recommended it right you
got your bone broth going
you're noticing you're getting a boost
that boost
is because you're getting a steroid high
you're getting a big boost of
epinephrine okay
and it can actually even numb out some
pain
temporarily for the moment and then it
comes back
but like any addiction because then you
get addicted to the cow's epinephrine
you get addicted to the cow's
epinephrine think about that
and now you're on this up and down thing
once again high chasing
just like coffee up you're up you're
down you're up you're down
matcha tea you're up you're down green
tea you're up you're down
right you're up you're down that's how
it works chocolate you're up and down
you're up and down you're up and down
okay but what happens is you're doing
the bone broth
and you're up you're down you're up
you're down
and all of this stuff robs your adrenals
eventually because you're up you're down
you're up and down
we're taught to high chase with
everything which constantly it's high
chasing
right and then the fat high chasing is
another one too
we get a high from all the fats just so
you know
dr fonda md good to see you dang i'm
addicted to these facebook lives but
can't watch them
since seeing patients in and out
you're working hard that's why you're
working your butt off doctor
dr fun you're working your butt off and
i know that
honor to have you just peeking your head
in right now in between patients
you're an amazing man um
so you guys we're taught all the time to
chase highs
so then you get all the alternative
functional medicine guys and all the
alternative podcast guys and you get all
these other things out there
and they're all just teaching women and
men they're teaching women
to chase highs that's the game that's
how it's played
and when you chase highs you're gonna be
buying their products too but
they teach women that too okay and men
right so it's all about
this high stuff noel shepard good to see
you an incredible incredible person good
to see you
um and the whole thing is
is when you're chasing highs that's when
you lose yourself you're sick and you're
you're
you think you're getting better but
you're not you think you're getting
better
but you're not they rob and steal any
chance for you to heal
you think you're getting better but
you're not it's how it works
that's how it works you feel a little
better from dumping all that fat in you
whether it's animal protein fat whether
it's plant plant fat
you feel you feel a little better and
then you're not
and it's this sick cycle is what they
they're teaching you this high cycle go
up you go down
you go up you go down you guys know you
guys know what i'm talking about right
you go up you go down that's how it's
done
and that's like any addiction you know
the fat addiction is real you guys
that's a real addiction
yeah people healing with compassion on
tick tock people protect their
addictions and
keep them sick absolutely right
and so plant fat absolutely see that
right there k
k on um tick tock yeah plant fat
there's a plant fat high you get so
that's there too
the more fat you do plant fat nut seeds
nut butters
all the avocados i'm not saying you
can't have avocado or nuts and seeds you
guys that's the whole point it's just
that you're gonna do it anyway
i have to go so far over to protect you
guys
so that you guys will even think
about it for a little bit right meaning
i have to say
i have to tell you guys cautious of nut
butters right
the almond butter the peanut butter the
walnuts the pumpkin seeds the sunflower
seeds the hemp seeds
the oils the coconut oil the olive oil
right the sesame oil the sesame seeds
the tahini okay
i gotta actually like look out for you
guys and i have to say you gotta be
careful with all that
because all that does is pump adrenaline
it creates this adrenaline surge
and i'll tell you why the more fat you
put in your body
the more your adrenals have to release
epinephrine to thin out your blood
so you don't get a heart attack yeah
your blood could get so thick your blood
could get so thick and so thick and so
thick
right danny says how do we break these
addictions
to fat coffee and chocolate we'll talk
about that too
um let me get these fries in the oven
right now
let me do that get some fries in here
here we go got some fries going popping
them in
i got it set for 350. they're in the
oven
okay gonna put these potatoes away
i gotta make some ketchup pretty soon
i got a i got an episode on medical mean
podcast at apple podcast
right it's the coffee matcha tea
chocolate episode incredible
episode information to how to break the
addiction okay
so we'll cover we'll go back seaweed
hero good to see you
let's just go back to the bone broth for
one second so we get this high from all
those steroids
that's how it works tremendous amount of
adrenaline is in those bones
right and if you are to do if you are to
do bone broth and you're like you know
what aw
i don't care i'm doing my bone broth i
don't care what anybody says
take the vinegar out please because
you're just you're just losing calcium
in your own bones
so as you do your bone broth and there's
vinegar in there you're
destroying your own bones because of
that vinegar
at least you're gonna do it no matter
what you're destroying your own bones
just letting you know
so take the vinegar out like keep that
part out
and that's something to that's something
right there that's like a takeaway
that's important
david says so how do we break these
addictions i'll let you know right there
like one
the one way it's on the yep it's on the
coffee
i as i told you just a couple minutes
ago you guys it's on the coffee episode
um chocolate episode matcha tea episode
um and yeah that's there's great great
withdrawal
techniques in there so okay anyway
all right another way like look another
way to break addictions two is getting
the things you need
that's a whole important thing on its
own getting the mineral salts you need
that's a celery juice right there
cleanse the heel i talk about how to
break those addictions right there so
all the different
healing techniques cleanses and
protocols so let's start making some
ketchup
we got more to talk about so um we're
gonna do some tomato paste
i got some right here it's great tomato
paste
so pop that open got a little bowl right
here too
so uh
i'm gonna do about three ounces of
tomato paste in here
get a little bit in there like that
a little bit of apple juice put some
organic apple juice right here
and you gotta watch out you don't want
your ketchup so runny so you just
can add a little as you go along there
we go we got some ketchup right there
um i'm gonna put a little bit of lemon
in here too
a little bit of lemon in there i'm gonna
put a little bit more
of the tomato paste
this recipe is in my book
the new edition you guys
fries with three dipping sauces and
we're doing ketchup
so i'm gonna i'm gonna add some garlic
powder in here
a quarter teaspoon of garlic powder
right
good to be here live on youtube live on
facebook live on tick tock it live on
clubhouse too
add a little bit of onion powder
into this ketchup right a little bit of
cayenne into this ketchup i don't know
if you guys like stuff spicy but i'm
gonna put a little bit in
whoa whoa lorraine i think i put too
much in
lorraine l i think i put too much in put
a little bit of um
oregano now if you're sensitive with
spices okay if you're sensitive with
spices you don't have to spice
everything like crazy all right so you
don't have to spice everything
so so heavily you can be really light on
the spices if you're
a little sensitive you know the
intestinal tract stuff going on and
put a little bit of oregano in there
and put a little honey in here too one
teaspoon of honey
there we go that was pretty close to a
tea probably a little bit more
i'm gonna mix it up so i'm making the
ketchup
you guys see on tick tock making the
ketchup right here
i had a phone call coming in you guys
i hope they call
yeah yeah i know i'm just feeling like
feeling like crap today
feeling sick i was about to do a post
about
it i was about to say how medical medium
and his celery juice is making you sick
uh-huh yeah
what do i no it's not the perfumes and
colognes it's not my perfume
no no it's not my scented candle that i
lit last night
no no why are you saying that it's the
celery juice it's medical medium
it's all his bs and i'm sick of it and
i'm going to write a post
let's just try to take the medical
medium down it's about time
uh-huh yeah no it's not the new medical
treatment i just got
like last month i told you it only made
me really sick for a little while and
then i seem to bounce back
no it's a celery juice i keep on telling
you that
the peanut butter every day i put two
tablespoons of peanut butter in my
smoothie bowl so what
yeah i put cacao in my protein shake
my protein powder it's not my protein
powder we need protein
yeah we need protein uh-huh
yep collagen yeah i do like a tablespoon
of collagen powder every day i got it
from that real like
i got it from that alternative website
it's not the collagen i have my coffee
drink
yeah i picked it up from the place i get
it every day
did i sanitize my hands before grab it
after grabbing the coffee
from the takeout person no why should i
do that
who cares what
yeah i've got a package from yeah
package came in from the delivery guy
yeah i just grabbed it and i put it
right on my bed
uh-huh what do you mean like it's bad to
put the package right
from coming off the road from the
delivery guy grabbing it
and putting it on my bed and then
putting it on my kitchen counter
what do you mean that's that's
bad i can't catch anything from that
i'm telling you it's a celery juice in
all the medical mediums bs
yeah he's getting too much power we've
been yeah i've talked to a bunch of
other friends and we're trying to like
say crap
about them um it's not the new cosmetic
treatment i got
no and it's not the real new
relationship i'm in
no that the person i'm with doesn't have
any bugs at all
so what yeah they get acne yeah the new
person i'm with gets acne
that's that's a bug what is that it's
strep
more medical meaning bs again
i don't care about the toilet seat at
the public place because it's clean
they have people that clean the public
bathroom there so i can just sit on the
seat i don't need a covered seat
i'm telling you it's his celery juice
yeah i ate
i eat out all the time me and my friends
we go eat out all the time
uh-huh yeah i had that stomach bug
thing that came on when i ate out but
we didn't think it was food poisoning
because nobody else got it at the table
it's medical medium celery juice uh-huh
yeah so what if i took an antibiotic for
a couple of days
my doctor said he needed the antibiotic
anyway because my microbiome was off and
then he gave me a gut powder
and some and some probiotic it's medical
medium
he's the reason why i have problems i
tried the celery juice i'm sick
i'm sick from the celery juice
yeah i got some new clothes in the mail
what do you mean
he says there's fungicide on the clothes
that's bs there's no fungicide on my new
clothes that i got yeah i got the lip
filler
well what's wrong with that
medical medium says there's nothing
wrong if that's what we want to do if we
want to get lip filler
he says though that could that can still
become like you can still feel sick from
it sometimes
i feel fine i'm telling you it's a
celery juice
yeah my functional medicine doctor told
me to stay on a high fat diet do as many
high fats as i can but stay away from
all sugar
and the minute i ate one piece of fruit
from medical medium i got
sick i'm telling you it's why i was at
the dentist
last week because of his fruit and his
celery juice
mostly his fruit because fruit ruins her
teeth
i did my apple cider vinegar shot uh-huh
i did my apple cider vinegar shot yeah i
i do it every other day because this
other functional medicine doctor told me
to do my apple cider vinegar shot every
other day
he says it's good for my gut yeah
the neighbors yeah they spray pesticides
every other
week did was i out there in it yeah it
smelled like perfume the pesticides they
smell like perfume
i just did this and just walked through
it
i'm telling you the celery juice is
making me sick that's what it is
pizza yeah i had pizza with my friends
last weekend
i had the vegan pizza with the vegan
cheese
uh-huh was it gluten-free no the crust
was corn
medical meme says corn is bad this is
ridiculous
he's he's a fear-monger and we have to
stop him
we have to shut him down let's report
him
and keep on reporting him canola oil
i don't know what has canola oil i was
given a bunch of supplements there's
alcohol
in them it i'm writing a post today
about how celery juice
is like killing us and how it gives us
like blisters on our body
i'm writing a post uh-huh and then i'm
gonna even say he's a terrible person
yeah why not he goes against the
ionizers the alkaline
eyes and eyes my friends have the
alkaline ionization water machines and
said medical meaning one against them
and so they put out a bunch of bad posts
yeah
chocolate i'm gonna have some now this
has stressed me out big time
i'm gonna have chocolate okay bye
you guys i made some ketchup right here
um and we got some
fries in the oven let me take a look
those fries are cooking up i'm excited
about these fries actually just so you
know
anyway look you guys here's what happens
out there okay
like have you guys seen any of that or
no
i see a lot of l-o-l-o-ls
so sad but true yeah
it's crazy and you think is this we're
all we're all taught to chase the high
right you're you're being you're being
taught that chase the high in every way
you can
that's how it works your functional
medicine doctor doesn't want to get rid
of their chocolate so they're going to
make sure you're on chocolate your
functional medicine doctor whoever with
your
md functional medicine whatever it is
and i want you to have your doctors
that's not it
but you got to know when to say no and
got to sit no one to say yeah and you
got to know what's right for you
you gotta know right you gotta know how
to protect yourself in any way i talked
about antibiotics forever i talked about
new medical treatments forever i talked
about all these things forever
and then you feel like you get shamed
you get
shamed into everything right and you get
that whole shame thing happens too if
you know the truth
you know the truth you know you get
shamed on for knowing the truth you
can't go against the grain
god forbid you go against the grain
right and
marianne says he cracked me up big time
um so
sweet anne says i honestly never thought
about it until you opened my eyes
the goal is to keep your eyes closed
that's the goal of the industries of all
all the industries right so your
practitioner
and it's this isn't a pick on this isn't
a practitioner roast
right now you guys on clubhouse too this
isn't a practitioner roast
that's not what this is okay i know so
many doctors and practitioners you guys
it's unbelievable okay
and for years it's not a practitioner
roast but what happens is your
practitioner your nutritionist your
dietitian your
counselor your uh md your functional
medicine doctor your chiropractor
they're on chocolate they're on their
coffee they're on their caffeine they're
on their bone broth they're on their
whatever
they're doing whatever and they're not
gonna they're they're gonna make sure
that they're doing their acv
they're doing their protein powders
they're on a high all day themselves
right chris right you seem fine to me
so they need they need to keep that with
you too you need to make sure that your
your eyes can never get open that you
never become like
really woke not the fake woke you know
the whole fake woke
right like the fake woke right
you're not allowed to have the real woke
how about that
the real awakening not the fake woke but
the real awakening right you know
what micro yeah educating myself micro
dosing too exactly
the whole micro dosing scam i call it a
scam
you know and that's what it is i know
this pisses off everybody all the stuff
i say and do
it always has since the beginning it
always says just like when i told people
right stay off of gluten going all the
way back stay off of wheat
right all the way back since i was a
child stay off a wheat and people would
be freaking they'd be freaking so you're
taught to poison yourself
on a smaller level with micro dosing too
so it's all about
the moderation micro dosing it's this
major scam i saw it in tick tock exactly
it's a major scam
so you're taught to poison yourself with
the micro dosing what about all the
lectins tomatoes
that cause leaky gut who says who's that
there's no science that's there's no
science that says tomato causes leaky
gut
aspen aspen i'm glad you're here on
tick-tock
okay it's a really good question okay
but
um there's there's science that actually
can see a tomato go in your body
sit inside your intestinal tract and
cause leaky gut do you know a leaky gut
is
leaky gut is actually a real per like a
perforation a
real poke in your gut where there's a
hole through it
and then when you have a hole through it
guess where you end up you end up in
icu with 105 temperature with sepsis
so the leaky gut theory was all wrong to
begin with
that was the whole thing no one knew why
anybody was sick so it was like leaky
gut leaky gut leaky gut are you kidding
me if you have leaky gut you'd be like
sepsis you'd be pissing out blood
and dying if you have leaky gut fast too
real fast within a week if you have
leaky gut
see how the misinformation works this is
how the misinformation works
it's just it's it's rampant it's rampant
the one thing i can tell you right now
if you can get past the whole spirit of
compassion thing
you will find the answers here okay if
you can get past
the whole spirit of compassion like the
dude hears a voice since
age four if you can get past that
if you can just get past that somehow
you'll have the answers you need
and you'll be unstoppable it's just you
you've got to get pat
that's a thing too like because there's
so much spiritual racism
against me tremendous amounts of
spiritual racism
like the spiritual racists are the worst
right and they're just they're spiritual
discriminators they're spiritual racists
and and they hate the fact that i hear a
voice and
have got all this incredible advanced
medical information has saved so many
lives right
but if if you're new here and you can
get past the whole thing that he hears a
voice
then you're you're open to all this
incredible information
then you're open to it you know and and
that's all fit
and i tell people look if you have to
numb out the fact that i hear a voice
right and these books are written by
that voice if you can numb that out too
if you need to numb that out just
just to make sure you get these answers
so you can heal then numb it out so you
can get these answers so you can heal
numbing out it's sorry you're not gonna
hurt my feelings gotta make some salad
too right now
make a little toss salad i got a bowl
right here
i don't want you guys just eating fries
on their own
i'm gonna move those fries around hold
on a sec
i'm gonna move those fries around a
little bit
so all right now they're looking good
they're looking good make a little salad
i'm not against animal protein i'm not
against
plant fat and plant protein plant
protein
is greens leafy greens that's plant
protein you guys
i'm not against animal protein too if
you guys are animal protein eaters
but i'll i'll help you i'll help you
learn
how to eat your animal protein the right
way so you don't
get sick so you can stay healthy so you
can get healthier and people are
stealing that information
i keep on getting so one of my friends
in the industry keeps on telling me oh
my god podcast doctor
podcast doctor's still stealing your
information podcast doctors still
stealing your information
it's like the podcast doctors reading
your medical medium books not citing you
and
doing his podcast and stealing your
information talking about mercury all
the time now when he never knew anything
about mercury
talking about lowering your fat a little
bit if you're animal protein
right all of it not citing right not
citing
it's just it's incredible
and you know what's funny because
there's a phone call coming through
that's right
i got another appointment you guys
hey i was just telling everybody about
you yeah yeah
yeah you you know when you're telling me
how the podcast doctors are stealing all
medical medium information
they're stealing it and they're not
citing it yeah i was just telling
everybody about that
you know what's funny i'm gonna haunt
them for the rest of their life
yeah because they know
they did something terrible they know it
in their consciousness they know they're
stealing
medical meme information they're trying
to make it their own
to get ahead in the world uh-huh yeah
and they have to live with that for the
rest of their life i'm gonna haunt them
to their grave you know what happens
when you get older you when you get
older
you know you did it you know you did
something wrong and you didn't come
clean with that
yeah that podcast doctor that's right
down the road
he's going to be thinking about me every
day because he steals the information
and he knows he did something dirty that
podcast doctor
did something dirty yeah
and knows it in his heart and in his
mind
i take up real estate in his mind every
day yeah
a couple of podcast doctors do this
uh-huh and i'm gonna haunt them
in their brain until they die when
they're on their death bed
uh-huh they're gonna be thinking about
how they screwed me over
yeah and they screwed everybody else
over because they didn't lead them to
where the information comes from so they
can heal fully
yeah uh-huh yeah i was telling everybody
on here now about the podcast doctor
doing that
mm-hmm yeah somebody even says
selita says that's so true i noticed so
much info is coming
in the podcast doctor uh-huh that's
right
that's right i know i know
yeah you have the top podcast doctors in
health
uh-huh yeah yeah
just stealing information uh-huh
yeah they know what they're doing it and
yeah all right i gotta go because i
really have to talk to these guys gotta
talk to everybody here
you can't take up all their time
um and all they're doing is hurting the
sick people
they're hurting the sick people people
who are sick people who have been to
doctors like that thing is you guys you
guys have no idea of the history
of some of the podcast doctors out right
now i actually know their history
because you know why
hundreds and hundreds of their patients
came to me
all through the 90s the late 90s
the early 2000s the mid-2000s
their patients were coming to me okay
after being antibiotic to death with
their lyme symptoms
literally losing their lives from that
podcast doctor
yeah you guys have no idea
and now that now that how things work
and in the past on how the path it's
just
incredible because you couldn't even
believe it
so many women you know what they call
you know they call them spoils of war
would you like to be a spoil of war a
woman that's been totally
totally jaked over by the industry and
certain
certain doctors in certain industry
standards totally screwed over where
your life is now
just in in ruins you're just you're just
a statistic you're just a spoil of war
from mistakes made and then the podcast
doctors could sit up all high now and
just be talking all this alternative
information as if they know things
meanwhile nobody knows how they just
they pass it off as oh those are just
spoils of war who cares if
10 000 women got so sick from
my stupid mistakes susie said i thought
i read information from a podcast doctor
information that i knew was yours it's
all it's all the time now it's
unbelievable you guys
michelle travis says i'm a 30-year
critical care nurse
whoa veteran i'm fighting for you
and aw and spirits information
incredible incredible
guys i'm making a little salad here this
is green leaf lettuce
you guys in clubhouse i'm chopping up
some green leaf lettuce i'm honored
you're here in clubhouse you guys
because i know you guys
are probably on the run running around
you got your phone on
we got tick tock live we got facebook
live eachother is healing
children what's going on chode is
amazing um
the problem is that they take bits and
pieces
and then twist it into other things so
really people aren't getting the truth
and here's what's interesting to you but
at the same time
people are getting they're being
sustained with their sickness because
they're using medical media bits and
pieces
so they're getting they are getting up
ticks say
but yet yeah they're getting up ticks
and if they're not really sick they get
a big
uptick using a medical medium piece of
information right
but then the rest isn't there in case
someone's
you know sicker and they can't make it
all the way right
i don't know if that made sense i was
trying to make sense on that
but we're live you know we're live
so i'm making some salad i got a little
cilantro in here too
i'm chopping up um
i don't like the pre-record stuff unless
i really have to
you guys like i like to keep it live all
the time i don't know if you guys notice
that
and it goes back for many years i was
working so hard teaching so many
practitioners and doctors
uh about health and patients that became
doctors that they started working on
their platforms before mine
um out there too and they started
writing books before i got a chance to
put the books out so
little tidbits got out escaped every now
and then like that too
not a whole lot but a little
a decent amount actually so i'm going to
do some tomatoes right here
back to that whole thing tomatoes
causing leaky gut that's really a sad
misconception a tomato can't cause
a leaky gut doctors don't even know what
leaky gut means really
so let's check those fries hold on you
guys
i'm making a little salad while i've got
this fries going up
cook it up then you cook a little bit
more i'm going to turn the heat up now
to it's 350 but i'm going to put the
heat up a little bit higher you guys
so i'm going to dip let's go to 375.
let's do that okay nice
let's chop up a tomato what i do is i
always take the top of the tomato off
i don't know how you guys like to do it
i mean i still eat that
but i like doing that and then i like i
like cutting these little
like nice little wedges here like see
i'm making a small salad that's what
this is usually the salads are this big
you guys
right you know the salads are like this
big this is a little one right here
see
i know you guys are used to me making
the real big salads it's just a little
salad on the side right here
so i'm cutting up these little pieces of
tomato popping them in here
it's got cilantro and green leaf lettuce
so far
i don't want you guys to always have
your french fries with no
greens i do want some greens are you
guys eating enough greens let me know
let me know what's going on over there
you guys doing enough greens
you guys doing your spinach on clubhouse
you guys doing your spinach
tick tock you guys doing your spinach
okay
how many greens are you guys do are you
doing your leafy greens ever
and i understand some days you just
don't have them you just didn't get to
the store
vibrantly nourished good to see i
stopped eating tomatoes for years
because i was told they were bad for me
no more tomato fear thank goodness
thank goodness amazing
just chopping up some more tomato you
guys
so i'm putting two tomatoes in the salad
right
every time i hear somebody's on
diatomaceous earth particles i i
i get the scariest feeling inside
laura says i am eating spinach soup and
your signature salads every day now
amazing
that diatomaceous earth particles that
just wreaks havoc on the intestinal
lining
just so sad when i keep on seeing this
misinformation out there
um so we're making a little salad let's
put a little uh red onion in there
fries are almost done
we're gonna do thin slices look you guys
can have hunks in there i'm gonna do
thin slices if that's okay
you love the spinach soup selena amazing
lorraine says like eating volcano rocks
you must been talking about diatomaceous
earth something else
we're going to thinly slice this onion
right here
it's the red onion onion games i'm gonna
play some onion games any second right
here
right it's gonna hit my eyes
some onion games
put a little onion on top of the salad
thin nice
uh sliced nice and thin put a little
lemon on top of here too
you guys i know you're gonna eat all
your fats every day because put a little
cucumber too
i get it everybody's eating their fats
right it's not that you can't have a
little avocado or some sesame tahini and
stuff it's just that we're taught to
do both animal protein and plant fats
animal fat and plant fat every single
day and if we're plant
based we're taught to just pound the
plant fats and fat ourselves to death
and if we're
and if we're animal protein we're taught
the same thing right
problem is with tomato sauces is you
know you're on a pizza
you got all that oil in the tomato sauce
right
then you're out or that pasta with the
cheesy pasta
you got all the gluten from the bread
and the pasta and everything so that's a
whole nother thing all on its own right
so i'm gonna i'm gonna thinly slice some
cucumber here thin slices you guys
chicken parmesan you got the cheese
got the cheese on there with all that
oil and the sauce
right okay
tomatoes take the blame they take the
blame
would you guys want the blame on you
for everything that goes wrong for all
these other things you guys want the
blame on you
i don't think you guys want the blame
right i just don't think so
um like i was talking about the blame on
the celery juice
right still to this day there's always
somebody that puts out a post
trying to take mm down right it's
hilarious
about the celery juice or something else
or reporting to get you know reporting
constantly to get me censored more and
more and more
looks great all right let's check out
those fries that's a salad going on just
a little salad okay you can have some of
it you can have a portion of it you
don't have to have all of it
i like having salads i like to do lots
here so let's take a look
it's another couple minutes over there
so you guys i just want to talk about
the blood draw for a couple seconds
it's important because i keep on seeing
it all the time hey i just got all my
blood work done and i'm low in vitamin d
hey i just got my blood work done and
i'm low in calcium
it's like you just got all your blood
taken out of you
now you're definitely going to be low in
everything so that's something to really
to really um keep in mind i'm going to
put the ketchup in this little cup right
here
to get ready for the fries
learn how to protect yourself with the
blood draws
i can't tell you how i you guys know
i've talked about this before and i
don't want to
to bore you guys on this but women are
the blood donors
sick women they've been brainwashed and
taught to donate blood
just so you know so that that's who
donates blood it's women that are sick
struggling women that their health isn't
good
and that's who's that's who is taught to
donate all the blood right
not strong men that aren't sick not even
strong women that aren't sick
i know that there's some of both that
donate blood don't get me wrong there's
strong men that donate blood there's
some
there's strong women that donate blood
but sick women are the ones that are
actually taught
they're being brainwashed to donate
blood and i'm not against
donating blood that's not it but but
when you listen to the medical mean
podcast at apple podcast the blood draw
episode you'll learn how to do it
carefully and protect yourself
i'm not against it totally not totally
right my sister is a phlebotomist she
said she has to take that much blood to
get
uh serum that's not true angie marie
that's not true i've had phlebotomists
on here say that's not true
so i've had lab technicians on here
already that all
like the last couple of months and
that's not true i talked to doctors that
know about the stuff that's not true
um yeah they only need it they only need
a dot a dot of blood
and they they they only need a quarter
vial really if they want to play around
with anything
with it quarter vial each vial right not
full vials they don't need
80 milliliters 70 milliliters 140
milliliters
they don't need all that it's just what
it is it's not that your sister's
wrong it's your sister's misinformed
that's what it is so your sister's a
phlebotomist but she's a phlebotomist
that's not been given the correct
information that's all
it's not that she's she's right for
the misinformation she has she's right
about the misinformation she just
doesn't know it's misinformation
the system's broken and what they're
doing is
they're vamping women kind right now
that's what they're doing
women are the ones that get the blood
tests every day
it's women men men i
every time i talk to like a family and i
talk to you talk to
um a woman in the family and she's just
like well yeah my husband doesn't really
get too much blood drawn ever it's like
he got blood drawn like three years
ago five years ago um i get my blood
drawn because of my cfs because of this
because of that i get blood drawn
because of my fibroid i get blood drawn
because of this i get blood drawn
because of that
and um and i also my doctor wants
regular blood work from me ever since i
had my babies
regular blood work you know all of that
right so what it is is the system
vamps women kind i really believe
from information that i've
heard from powerful people in the world
and information from spirit of
compassion
that there is there is a dirty dirty
dirty dirty dirty dirty
system around bleeding women to death
to a slow death there is a dirty system
set up on that just letting you know
it and it's not the doctors doing it the
doctor isn't doing it
so and it's about literally draining
women
of their of this precious resource
in draining sick women of this precious
resource the system's not just broken
it's it's
it's it's yeah courtney it's scary so
scary and
that's how it's designed right so that's
one of the ways
there's there there is a movement out
there that people don't realize
yeah um you seem fine to me chris chris
my blood was drawn because the wind blew
yeah marissa aw stands up and empowers
us women
marissa i'm honored honored you're here
thank you for being here um
and but but there is there is a
scary thing happening that's doing this
for women in their
and and robbing their doing this to
women and robbing their blood
the blood supply knocking down their
immune systems
experimenting with their blood okay
all of this this is a precious resource
and it's not
tree it's treated like trash your blood
is just
trash and then one of the brainwashing
techniques that's happening out there
is you you should do this you should
donate your blood or
you should get your get your blood draws
because you're just you're
you're getting rid of old blood and then
fresh blood
fresh blood is like clean it comes out
clean and your body produces fresh blood
that's not how it works
that's not how it works that's a trick
so there it's a
bloodletting trick too i'm not saying
don't donate blood we need we do need
donations for blood but they don't use
all
the amount of people donating blood and
the fact that
they only need a fraction of that in
hospitals
where does all the rest of it go just
pretend they throw it all away then
they're throwing away millions of
gallons of women's blood
millions of gallons are thrown away
michael says too many red blood cells
have to get
well that's the technique instead of
knowing what's wrong with the person
instead of knowing how to fix them
instead of knowing why too many red
blood cells is a viral condition but
they don't want to
do any science research studies on that
and figure out how to fix it
so they're just still yeah they just
want to take your blood so it's done
to get these fries out you guys make a
little room for them too
what's going to do um
got some fries right here i don't know
if you guys can see this a little bit i
think so right
so let me get a little plate for this
it's a nice bowl right here so i'm gonna
get some fries in here now you can get
them as toasty as you want
you'll see that this one right here is a
little extra toasty see that you guys
that one right there is a little extra
toasty right
now there's no oil on this on these
fries just so you know that keep that in
mind
there's no oil on these i don't advise
you to use your hand like this and just
grab them like this
i just have for some reason since i was
a kid i could handle intense heat with
my hands
like really really
intense levels of heat with my hands so
i'm just saying so i don't
don't don't do what i'm doing right now
like i can't even
like this doesn't even bother me but
someone else they'd be
they'd be like crying probably so just
don't do that
and i've been known in my family since i
was a kid
that my hands can handle the heat
big time just let you guys know that's
something in my family that's well known
so but don't do that whenever you do
okay check out these fries
i just want to show you guys on tik tok
what do you think
you guys youtube facebook what do you
think
can we air fry the potatoes sophia m yes
you can
definitely it's just that i wanted to
use the oven this time
and not the air fryer so don't these
don't these look good or no right and
then
the salad with it and then you got the
ketchup right here
so you take the fry and you put it in
the ketchup right
dip it in a little bit of ketchup on the
fry what do you guys think
and then in it goes
oil free you just learned
oh whoa that's spicy i put some cayenne
in there
just be careful on the cayenne i like it
spicy
i like all that cayenne okay and skye
this is spicy be open hearted good to
see you too i saw you
um yeah but that's really amazing
and here's what's cool it's not a high
chase
it feels like a high chase i'm happy i'm
eating some fries and ketchup right
but i'm getting glucose and then the
salad is going to give me mineral salts
see how it works you guys i'm getting
glucose in the salad that's going to
give me mineral salts right
isn't that incredible the recipe is in
book one
you know why it's not a high chase you
guys there's no oil in there
to make your adrenals spit out all this
epinephrine to keep your blood thin
because the oil going in there's no high
chase here this is actually an enjoyment
this is just
fun this is fun
incredible it really is that's the
recipe right there
it doesn't look like that does it
um it's medical medium new edition
and you guys remember like there's
protocols in the back of this book
some in the actually in the front of
this book too there's proto protocols
through this book with
supplements and dosages to conditions
and you know a friend of mine was
telling what supplements do i like
i haven't talked to them in years i'm
like are you kidding the dimmer g
that's the magnesium glycinate from
vimergy
m sky when you steam first and then bake
you get
crunch on the outside and full yep
fluffy potatoes on the inside
em skye that's what i did you guys
you guys um here's the vimergy stuff
that i always recommend
okay i'm not sponsored but v is victor i
m
e r g y dot com their supplements are
unmatched
austin knows i think austin uses bemidji
from what i remember
um and so the books have
supplements protocols if anybody ever
wanted to venture into supplementation
and protocols to learn how to heal
i mean the information is there i just
don't talk about
you know everything else i talk about
everything else that's the whole point
so anyway magnesium is important
so many people need magnesium it's
ridiculous it's so critical
they rob and steal any chance for you
guys to heal
that's what they do and keep that in
mind
the industries including the alternative
industries that's what they do
it's sad but true it's a big club out
there
they all mirror the same old
and that's how they do it
and then they secretly drink celery
juice
behind the scenes many of them do
i'm letting you know okay i want you
guys
to heal not be high you hear that i want
you guys to heal
and not be high anyway i'm heading off
to tick tock
not take that little tick tock again ig
and tick tock i'm heading off to both of
those you guys
so i'm excited so just give me a couple
of minutes to straighten things out i'm
gonna make some fries again
hopefully i do a better job next time
that's always think about i'm going to
be on clubhouse again too so i'm going
to click on clubhouse in a little bit
i'm clicking on tick tock a little bit
and i'm going on ig and we're going to
have some fun
because i feel like i'm in a good mood
right now because i'm not on a high
from this i'm on a happy happiness from
having some fries
because i'm hungry today i'm gonna eat a
fry clean up the mess for a few minutes
then we're going on ig
and tiktok and clubhouse i love you guys
you guys take