we're making banana ice cream we're
making nut milk we're making wheat grass
we're making baby food puree food right
and we're making salsa
with this machine so this is gonna be
really fun you guys I'm actually excited
about this is the mm1500 you guys know I
work with the mega everybody was always
asking me well what about baby food and
what about nut Butters and what about
nut milks I'm like you know what
let's do it all let's do it all let's
make some banana ice cream what I like
to do just a little tip on this freezing
banana thing I like to kind of keep them
whole I have it set for ice cream so I'm
popping some banana in here right now so
there it goes
foreign
oh yeah so let's make some baby food or
puree I'm gonna run some steamed yams
through here take a look so that is the
puree baby food yams you could do
carrots you're gonna do some wheatgrass
right now so I have right here the end
cap for the wheatgrass this is the 1500s
known to save you money because it's got
that celery end cap you can't extract
this kind of wheatgrass juice from other
juicers I know I've seen it out there
you're looking at how dry the pulp is
the wheatgrass pole other juicers they
don't do that it's got its own little
strainer on top of it I'll show you this
which is incredible about the juicer the
mm-1500
making some Walnut milk right here and
what I'm going to do is add water in
here
now these are soaked walnuts just so you
know the nuts are soaked overnight yes
that's what I like to do when I'm making
a nut milk now this machine really
pulverizes you can actually take this
the froth over here and you can actually
take that off so you do a little bit of
a mix to it
so I'm making a salsa right now so I'm
dropping tomato and I'm dropping some
onion in here I put a lime in here too a
little bit of cilantro
drop in some jalapeno in there now so
what you do is you take this part here
you mix it in here like this
so what I'm doing is I'm mixing this up
this one's a little hotter so what I'm
doing right now is I'm making a walnut
butter
it's like sticks of butter
but Walnut butter butter you buy they
add a ton of oil there wasn't four
ounces of oil added into this it's the
mm 1500 and that's what it does eighty
dollars off and you know what's
incredible about this right now
80 off and you get a free cleanse to
heal book with it which is really cool
so I'm excited about that all on its own