it can be exciting i'm making the heavy
metal detox smoothie
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie and i'm making a
celery juice too because that's a
healing tool for toxic heavy metals as
well
helps to prep them help helps to
dislodge
them helps to carry them out with
everything else you're doing that's why
the cellar juice is so important
so adhd autism that's what we're talking
about
i'm going to do a little demo too in a
minute talking about the brain
i'm going to read out of the new edition
which has helped
so many children and adults
with adhd and autism and
this is the book that blew the roof off
of autism like
the whole world of it all adhd and
autism this is the book right here
talking about the midnight the midline
cooking out
and talking about the metals inside the
midline canal okay
so if i can get my words straight today
but that's what i love about having it
live
all the time and unedited cool
so we got that right there um i got the
juicer in front of me at the
heavy metal detox movie i'm going to
make got everything in front of me too
barley grassies powder the spirulina the
vimergy that's the stuff that works
in my opinion from what i've seen and
what i recommend friends and family i'm
not sponsored
got the wild blueberries right here big
bowl got the cilantro
got the dulce and got these oranges you
see these oranges
do you see the size of these oranges
they are not gmo
these are not gmo these are incredible
michelle l my god was just reading that
chapter
autism you were incredible look at the
look at these oranges right
these go into the heavy metal detox
movie you got bananas right here too
i'm gonna read the autism chapter a
little bit in there
so i'm excited sundy hi uw
i love your new book full of so much
wisdom and truth
love you love you man my son's adhd and
autism get
better with cj and heavy metal smoothie
i am forever grateful for you
um sunday thanks for being here thanks
for being on that's the best news ever
dr fawn md good to see you the man
what a great medical doctor you guys if
you're looking for medical doctors out
there
searching for medical doctors if i
needed a medical doctor i'd be knocking
on his door
um so anyway going to read a little bit
too
so let's go
whether you come to this elevated and
expanded edition of medical medium
as a new reader or as a seasoned
follower of the book series which i know
many of you
about the book series and you got the
books right know this
there's already a track record
established
of the power of healing this book has
provided
and that track record that track record
is the real deal
and it has healed a lot of people this
book and that track record is
huge worldwide and that's why i'm
constantly asked to do the tv shows and
the docu-series and documentaries that
just don't have the time
and and for a lot of other reasons too i
want to keep you know staying
in touch with you guys like this in this
level is because the amount of people
that healed around the world
it's garnered a tremendous amount of
attention and
this book has got us there people from
around the world
who've tried everything medical research
and science had to offer
have found this information to be a
sanctuary and that's what i love about
this book you guys
it's been that sanctuary dr sherry green
incredible another amazing medical
doctor um
and if look if i needed a medical doctor
knocking on doctor sherry
green knocking on dr fawn
they found that it has allowed them to
rise out of the ashes just reading a
little quote at the beginning of the
book we're talking about autism adhd
we're live it's the way i like to do it
youtube
and facebook um it's what don't like to
edit anything i always love it live
so i'm going to read a little bit we're
going to get into this so i just want to
give you guys a rundown if you just got
on here okay i'm going to make the
celery juice which is a huge
part of healing you guys this
is a healing tool to celery juice i'm
using the healing machine
that's what i call it this is you know a
medicine tool
okay and that's what i call it too it's
the mm900 hds that's the one
that um that licensed my name to the to
the company of megajuicers.com
it's on my directory too you can find it
there um or just the megajuicers.com
just go straight there but that's the
mm900 hds
and it saves people a lot of money
people love the juicer
i know a lot of you guys have it i got
i'm going to make this heavy metal detox
movie and i'm going to show you guys
some other stuff too i'm going to talk
about the brain a little bit
with autism so i hope hope you can see
that good
going to talk about the brain with
autism
so we got that to cover i got some
mercury in my hands i don't want you to
ever do this do not
ever put mercury in your hands god
forbid
i'm letting you know so don't do that
don't do that with mercury whatever you
do
don't uh this is fake mercury
but still don't ever do that okay so
we're going to do a little talk on that
too
um lorraine l she's here
um so melinda which is the best book to
buy
so link is in the description this
is medical medium revised and expanded
you got to know it's revised and
expanded
okay uh new edition medical medium
secrets behind chronic and mystery
illness and how to finally heal it's got
a powerful track record
an unbelievable track record healing
millions worldwide
i'm going to read a little bit out of
there and
you just can't say that people aren't
allowed to say that
you know you can't just say oh all the
books you know helped heal millions
worldwide
you can't do that and you can't say oh
sold so many copies of the book it's
it's popular you just can't say that
either people say things like that but
you'll see a gold emblem right here
millions millions of copies
sold around the world medical medium
series
and this book has an incredible track
record also
plague info in here so plague info
okay really important to know about the
plague
about info needed it's in here
you guys if you just got on i know
people are just getting on everything
making the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie and
making some celery juice we're going to
do that too
we'll get through this okay let's read a
little
let's get into this
all right right so
specifically adhd and autism
are born primarily mercury
plus aluminum that settles in the
brain's
midline cerebral canal which divides the
left cerebral
hemisphere from the right okay
just wanna talk about that and lo and
behold we
have a brain i'm gonna bring another
brain over here too but i just wanna
show you here
all right that's half a brain in my in
my demo
all right and the midline canal
you'll see right here good old midline
canal
right there okay and i want to show you
and that's adding the other half of the
brain
in there okay so the other half
and so that midline canal goes right
down the middle i don't know if you can
see right down the middle there
so right in the center that midline
canal
dividing the hemisphere with the right
hemisphere
okay and in that midline canal
is where the metals gather
when you're a child right from the
beginning
and what gathers in there is mercury
and aluminum that's what gathers in
between that good line canal
really important to know so taking the
other half of the brain off right there
i want to show you i'm gonna read a
little bit more
okay the mercury and the aluminum can
also be in other
areas of the brain other areas of the
brain sprinkled about in smaller
deposits
some even inside the emotional
center of the brain all right
so the metal doesn't have to be in the
midline
right but it but that's where most of it
gathers
especially young um as a child as a baby
and then child and then there's also
metals
that get sprinkled about in the brain
too and that happens as well
um you guys just got on here just doing
a little demo
on the brain talking about the new
addition
talking about autism adhd gonna make
celery juice
to make the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie so you can have
deposits sprinkled all over the brain
there's a couple of deposits right here
you see
these are big deposits and that's not
what it looks like that's just for the
model so you guys can see that the shiny
deposits right there
let's keep reading a little bit and in
the emotional center of the brain is
where a lot of metal
can also sprinkle about which
makes things difficult all on a whole
other level
it might occur to you that it's hard to
build up significant
exposure to toxic heavy metals in just a
few years
of a young life like where did all the
metals come from
where do they come from how does it
happen
you know people think about that like
how does my baby have metals
how is that even possible how does my
child have metals
this doesn't even make any sense right
okay mercury however is a neurotoxin
that slips
under the doctor's noses
mercury slips under
the doctor's noses
really important to know right there
most doctors
are oblivious oblivious
to which medical treatments they offer
that contain
mercury we'll just do this
pharmaceutical here
what mercury i don't know about any
mercury
what mercury there's no mercury in this
pharmaceutical right here
um all right
let's keep on going here so most doctors
are oblivious to which medical
treatments they offer that contain
mercury
and if they are aware of it they're
either in denial
yeah afraid to break traditional
protocol
or they believe in the treatment and
that belief overrides their common sense
about the nature of the toxic heavy
metals
medical communities are due for a
massive wake-up call
about obvious mercury contamination
there's no mercury no more
doesn't exist what that was what
hundreds of years ago mercury
that's not anywhere it's everywhere
mercury is a great instigator of adhd
oh is it ever and autism too
especially in children in the 21st
century
why why or
how is it possible we have so much
mercury now
in the 21st century how's that possible
how is it uh mercury's toxic it was gone
a long time ago
mercury is also responsible for most
seizure disorders
seizure disorders responsible for most
seizure disorders okay until mercury and
aluminum are addressed the conditions
will continue to affect
millions of new kids each year how's
that possible
millions of kids each year
not 50 years ago
this year last year
it's very easy for a baby to take in
toxic heavy metals from her or his
mother while in the womb
yeah and for a father to pass along
toxic heavy metals at conception
that's because the parents have likely
accumulated mercury over the decades
and so did their mothers and fathers
before them and mercury tends to stay in
the family bloodline generation after
generation
which i got something to say i got
something to say you guys
i got big time in some cases for
centuries unless specific
steps are taken to remove it um
i just got to read that one more time
like i'm like i'm trying to think here
i'm like scratching my head about this
right about this i'm like scratching my
head over here
all right so that's because the parents
have likely accumulated mercury over
decades and so did their mothers and
fathers before them
and mercury tends to stay in the family
bloodline
generation after generation
um so
every time someone's sick and they have
a problem doesn't matter what it is it's
genes
everybody just says genes so the medical
industry
and health professionals around the
world they'll just say it's genes right
research in science will tell you it's
genes mercury
is passed down generation after
generation after generation
after generation and
no one wants to ever look at that got to
put a
blind eye to that oblivious to it and
call it genes
that's what's wrong your genes went bad
won't talk about any mercury god forbid
your genes went bad genetics are not
behind adhd and autism and i tell you i
i swear to god
every time i hear a doctor coming
straight out of med school brand new a
hot dog like oh i just got out of med
school so i know everything
i know why millions of women have
suffered i know why hundreds of
thousands of women have
have lost their lives to lyme disease
they don't know any of this stuff
they don't have any any experience right
they coming out they come out
they come out with no experience okay
and they're just like no genes are
behind adhd
gut health is your adhd or genes
or autism is from a from your genes
stephanie lynn the genes are the
predisposition
the mercury and other things are what
triggers the genes to become
active problematic see that's a
hypothesis that's a
that's a theory that's theoretical is
what that
is and that's that's also to keep
on the gene narrative so that's what
they need you to think
that your children's genes are bad
and that means your children's
children's genes are going to be bad and
that means
you're a bad mom or someone's a bad mom
because you gave your child
bad genes because
that's that's and then then medical
medium information 35 years ago put the
mercury out
the mercury truth and then that spread
around
and now they mix it they mix it because
they take bits and pieces medical medium
information
the good stuff and they mix it with the
garbage it's still your genes
well maybe mercury's actually creating a
gene problem maybe it's
triggering a gene problem they can't see
that there's nothing under any
microscope and i've talked to scientists
i've talked to the best doctors around
the world
there's nothing anyone can ever see in a
microscope
that shows a gene being triggered by
mercury
but i i'm happy you're here and i'm
happy you're you're you know giving me
all the info that you got
it's important little wolfie my son has
autism we are doing the heavy metal
detox movie for two years saved my son
now looking in our eyes talking playing
start at school learning his red cheeks
healing
he was allergic to bananas now healed
incredible little wolfy incredible
it's the best thing ever so uh dr faun
md says that's how doctors think
especially their young
and aren't affected yeah what happens is
that
you got young doctors right you're a
seasoned doctor right you got the young
doctors coming out and they're they're
they're told science knows everything as
soon as you get out of school you're
gonna know everything
and what they find out years after
experience and years after experience if
they
if they allow the info to come in they
find out that science research doesn't
know anything about chronic illness
and that they also find out that they're
just left with a couple of theories in
their hand of why people are sick which
is cause unknown
genes the body attacking itself because
of genes
and that's pretty much it or
they start getting spiritual you know
you get some doctors they're like i'm
gonna start going the spiritual route
start doing some yoga and whoa i think
i'm creative i think my patients are
creating it with their mind
that's what it is i think it's all about
mastering your mind and that
that's what it is because we don't
science research doesn't know why
everybody's sick so it must be all
mental
that's what happens all right
so
the cerebral midline canal talking about
that you guys i got to make the heavy
metal detox smoothie i got to make some
celery juice
i got by the way this is this this
juicer is incredible
just want to let you know before i
forget it's 50 off
so for the moment anyway um on
megajuicers.com it's the
mm-900 hds but it's got to be that one
it's a celery juicer that's the one
that's great
i told you guys um i'm working with
these guys
i licensed my name to them because they
made the best thing i've ever seen for
celery juice
the brain's midline is located directly
between the right and left hemisphere
cerebral hemispheres of the brain this
midline
looks like an open canal
so it looks like an open canal so i
don't want to drop this but you see that
open canal up at the top that blue line
looks like an open canal
the midline looks like an open canal but
instead of water running through it a
channel of
electrical energy does that midline
canal you guys
has electrical energy running through
this and this is really an important
thing to know
right so your brain is electricity
that's what it is and it's running on
mineral salts
not just salts minerals trace minerals
so it's running on a whole group of
trace minerals okay
neurotransmitters they have those trace
minerals within them
it keeps them strong neurons
also have those trace minerals and
glucose you got to have the sugar
you got to have the glucose you got to
have the glucose for the brain you see
what that is glucose glucose glucose
we're live
youtube and facebook so
you guys what happens is that
electricity runs also through that
midline canal
a stream of it does runs through the
that's what happens so let me get the
brain back okay
and you got the brain right there so
right
in between right in between this part
and that part
you guys see electricity runs
right up and around that
so i want to give you that little demo
let's talk about this we're back to
the new edition if you guys want to know
what we're talking about if you just got
on here medical medium revise and expand
it
the book will blow your mind and help
you heal
and that's not not it's already has that
track record of
healing people worldwide it's not just
me saying no the book will help you heal
kimberly miller your info has saved my
life i cry tears of joy
being able to have a second chance of
life that that
that means more to me than you even know
i mean
truly truly means the world to me it
truly does
so let's go a little bit
a little bit more all right it's not yet
documented in medical
research that this canal forms an
electrical charge that makes an
energetic connection between the two
hemispheres you guys research in science
doesn't know a lot
about the brain i mean they got great
mri technology
that i love out there right it'll see a
dark spot gray spot
white spot it'll find a gray area that
can be identified as a growth or a tumor
mris are great in so many ways okay
but there's little little known about
the brain
really little known about the brain so
um
let's go a little bit more into this
this electrical charge that runs through
the midline
okay makes an energetic connection
between the two cerebral hemispheres and
allows information to be exchanged
between them
so in that midline right there right in
the middle
right right in the middle of the brain
information is being exchanged between
left and right
hemisphere so this is an important piece
of information to know
this exchange of information is powered
by neurons
and the true nature of this connection
may never be discovered by medical
research
and science maybe a hundred years from
now
children have free flowing midline
canals
and i'm sure a couple of you guys are
like well wait a minute how would he
know
research in science don't know well
that's funny because research in science
is taking medical medium information out
of this very book
after it's been published and they use
it so medical medium information has
never been proven wrong
it's been it's it's not been
contradicted by me
okay it's been like it always been for
35 plus years since i was a child
and science research has taken from it
over the years
and they take it after i've lectured
about it or published it in this fashion
children have free-flowing midline
canals free-flowing
mid-line canal canals that's what
children have
it's what allows them to learn how to
communicate with other people
and with the metaphysical realm have you
guys ever heard of children
being like well i see an angel or i'm
talking to an angel or
mommy i see something you know
or imaginary friend or invisible friend
or children that see and hear more
right that midline canal is free-flowing
including the you know angels things
that adults
don't see fairies angels
uh mystical things you know in the
garden
where mommy didn't see it but but but a
three-year-old sees it
when toxic heavy metals enter this
midline canal
which is supposed to be open and free
they block the electrical and
metaphysical
energetic transmissions between the
cerebral hemispheres
so when metals block that midline canal
when metals block that midline canal
it breaks up the electricity it breaks
it up
between communication between left and
right hemisphere
guys if you just got on here i got to
make a heavy metal detox movie and i got
to make some celery juice so we're
moving we're moving
we're moving along talking about adhd
and autism
this challenge is the child's brain to
develop alternative ways to make that
exchange
happen adaptation set in and the child
unconsciously begins
accessing areas of her or his brain that
most of us
never use at least not until we're older
metaphysical and electrical energy
struggles to find its way
into uncharted territory electrical
nerve impulses begin igniting neurons
and firing up neurotransm
neurotransmitters onto brain pathways
that aren't supposed to be explored
until after the person breaches
adulthood so what happens with children
when metals block
that midline canal electrical impulses
have to go in different places so
so what happens is that midline canal
that's that's half the brain right here
left left hemisphere right
and that midline canal i've shown you
there
when that fills up with toxic heavy
metals
electricity can't flow free anymore
so it has to re-route itself
and when it does it's going down
different neural pathways
synapses it has to cross the synapsis
and go into a different neuron root
see
sarah i was just reading this exact
paragraph of the book
everybody should get the new book hey
sarah thanks
revised expanded new edition awesome
awesome
autism is essentially more advanced and
complicated
form of adhd it's a more advanced and
complicated form of adhd
see i know the medical system wants to
just put a label on something that's
adhd
no that's autism especially originally
right
that's bipolar
that's there's no in between of all that
no that's adhd
that's autism that's bipolar
i had a few i had a few extra oranges
before before i started
that glucose is really good feels good
so autism is a more advanced
and complicated form of adhd toxic heavy
metals are
present at higher levels in the midline
cerebral canal
and gathered in uneven layers this helps
explain why there's an autism
spectrum which wasn't there to start
with
they didn't have the autism spectrum
okay
that wasn't there but this explains
why that developed
with the with the syndrome displaying
different
okay intensities depending on the child
it all has to do with the amount of
heavy metals in the canal that's the
whole thing
it all has to do with and the amount of
heavy metals we're gonna make the heavy
metal detox smoothie
and in the positions that they've
accumulated so where are the metals
where are they
what part of the brain is the metal in
what area of the brain
that all that is it frontal lobe
where is it all this matters is it by
the pituitary
where is the metal is in the emotional
center of the brain
where is the metal in the brain and that
determines also what's happening too
okay
it all has to do with the amount of
heavy metals in the canal and the
positions they accumulate with autism
versus adhd
the additional layers of mercury
interfere even more greatly
with the metaphysical and electrical
energy communications trying to cross
the canal
the small amounts of toxic heavy metals
sprinkled throughout the brain
also have an effect there too so the
metal in the midline canal and the metal
that's sprinkled around the rest of the
brain can all interfere
because i'm reading the revised and
expanding you guys should have the book
if you don't have the book tell people
you know the description is in
description i mean the link is in the
description
go to amazon.com target barnes noble
uh yeah
to understand adhd and autism
imagine the grand canyon you guys in
book depository too you could find a
book
book depository so you ready to
understand adhd and autism imagine the
grand
canyon there's a symbiotic relationship
taking place in
and around at the grand canyon right in
the u.s between
physical and metaphysical elements
there's the water running through the
canyon
right the wind rising up out of it
the electrical fields from storms and
the earth
and the light and the heat of the sun
all of it combines just so
to make the canyon a visible
energetic and spiritual force
the brain's midline canal is like the
grand canyon
in the u.s in this way so many elements
interacting at once to make it work
just so it's just like any canyon really
around the world
a lot of different canyons around the
world with water running through and the
rock on the sides and everything now
what if something altered this pristine
environment of the grand canyon
what if someone started dropping cars
into it
and metal barrels into it you see where
i'm going
everything would change see the grand
canyon is the midline canal
in the brain that i was showing you guys
and metal barrels question mark
yeah everything would change wind
patterns would redirect themselves
because they would hit
the metal barrels right
the sun would reflect at different
angles because it would be hitting the
metal barrels no longer reaching certain
areas
but lighting up other nooks and crannies
that hadn't
seen sunshine for thousands of years
even sound within and around the canyon
would change
the whole frequency of the place would
be different as the elements adapted
this is what happens when toxic
heavy metals enter a child's midline
cerebral canal
we see the child behaving in ways we
don't expect because
her or his brain is adapting to the
extra materials blocking internal
communication
it's learning to access different parts
of itself
so that's what happened so i'm going to
make some heavy metal detox smoothie
midline canal like i was showing you
guys okay
right the brain okay midline canal right
in the middle
just like the grand canyon if you put a
bunch of stuff in the grand canyon cars
and metal barrels
everything's gonna change about it
energetically electrically
okay all of it and that's what happens
when all that metal
gets in that midline canal of our
children and it does
and it does all that mercury does
okay all that aluminum does
so much more info is in there just so
you know so much more information is in
this chapter the adhd
um an autism chapter so much more
information you guys i mean i'm just
scratching the surface really
jamie lynn davis hey glad you're here
anthony's info has brought me
back to life if you have any chronic
pain give his information a try you will
improve and i do
talk about chronic pain i do talk about
tinnitus vertigo
body pain fatigue everything in here
epstein-barr related stuff
lupus fibromyalgia multiple sclerosis
all of it you guys joanna thank you what
juicer do you use
it's the mm-900 hds so
mm-900 hds omega juicers.com
and it is 50 off right now
it saves people money it saves me money
i've heard other people say that because
they're juicing less celery
i'm gonna juice some celery for you guys
and make the heavy metal detox smoothie
the pulp comes out dry uh maria
hey what's going on
honored you're here
see you guys let's do uh let's do a
couple things we'll do a little juicing
real quick and then we'll make the heavy
metal detox moving divine light and it's
important to know the updated supplement
list because
things have changed in the world exactly
okay i don't recommend zeolite for heavy
metal detox
i don't at all they changed they're not
the same
even the one i recommended was only
because dulce was not
available at the time supplement
companies have their free will and they
change things all the time
um you know and and that's that's why so
i don't have any loyalty supplement
companies because
because they know that they could change
but i recommend the ones that i use that
aren't changed that are good anyway to
do the we're going to talk about that
this is the juicer that i love you guys
like i said it's 50 off
people ask me about what you know i
don't show i show the juicer for a while
and then everybody
will ask like which user do you use what
juicer do you use
oh you know what i'm doing i'm juicing
without putting out a boulder
all right that's what i love about live
performances right there
that's what i like but you know what
i'll have it this way any day then
editing everything sentence by sentence
just letting you know all right
let's go
[Music]
that's what makes the videos good right
[Applause]
wait what else is missing oh no
i forgot to plug the juicer in
[Applause]
wait where's my glass where i'm gonna
actually put the juice in i don't even
have that
sharon phillips i was screaming the cup
[Applause]
you know what you know what i've noticed
on youtube is everybody edits everything
to the point of each line it's like
hi my name is anthony williams all of a
sudden it's edited to the next part
i'm talking about this it's edited to
the next part that's how youtubers do it
right
and i just don't like that i think
that's that just means like
look just be
this you know
[Applause]
susan walker this truly is the best
celery juicer
i've tried many and nothing
and also get the nutritional value and
the celery works
like this in mega so nothing works
better than the omega i know it's not
just the omega though
it's this juicer right it's the mm-900
hds
it's not just it's not just a mega
juicer but go to megajuicer.com they got
the celery juicer mmm 900 hpf
50 off becca white i'm so glad i found
my
way back to you i bought your book two
years ago i was so overwhelmed
with your information that i couldn't
handle it i've
been fighting lime since 1998 whoa since
dear lord i'm slow i'm slowly getting
better thank you so much
for your commitment to help um save the
health of people you are amazing
i'm honored you're here i totally
understand you know it's just sometimes
it just takes the
the right time in your life i i totally
get it
sander a same thing happened to me a few
times you mean you didn't put the cup
underneath it pura vida i've done that
plenty of times
[Applause]
i've done the same thing juiced without
the glove glass underneath
patricia bennett
dr fun md
bloopers reel yeah hey no i like
bloopers you saw the one on tick tock
right
where i was trying to make a heavy metal
detox smoothie but i was trying to make
it for real
but i was doing it with you know little
music and the whole thing just fell
apart on me
i couldn't even get the banana right i
dropped dropped the uh
the blender honestly it was a disaster
but you know what
i published it i posted it because
i mean what are you gonna do
i can't cry about it so i may as well
just
post it see you guys i'm making some
celery juice
right now this is the mm-900 hds if you
just got here it's the celery juicer i
use
um favorite favorite celery juicer
favorite juicer i've ever had
no he is saying to stay away from
corella you're correct
correct pirella's a disaster
it's a disaster i've seen so many people
bowled over so sick to death
barfing their brains out be barfing
their brains out
and not just that because it's got
bacteria in it many
many of the batches they just they just
for years that's happened but that's
just not one
that's one reason another reason it
doesn't get metals out
it doesn't get done it doesn't
i like things that work that's why so
many people
appealed on medical medium information i
like things that work
[Applause]
yes you can juice other fruits and
vegetables with this juicer it's just
that it's incredible for celery
in the end you can juice anything you
want with a juicy it's just that amazing
with celery
[Applause]
[Music]
dude
what a lot of people do is um
there's some serious mlm marketing going
on with that zeolite
okay zeolite never got people better
over the last 20 20 years
25 years okay it died in fact and what
happens is people bring things back in
here they bring
things that actually died years ago that
just didn't help anybody and they bring
it back in
and they match it to medical medium
stuff so someone doing celery juice if
you bring in some zeolite
you'll think the zeolite is actually
getting better when the celery juice is
getting you better
someone brings in zeolite into when
someone's actually
getting rid of those processed foods
learning to keep eggs away and they
bring in their zeolite
they start getting a little better and
they think the zeolite's getting them
better
some people bring in the zeolite when
you're doing the heavy metal detox
smoothie and that's what marketing is
doing so the pyramid scheme right now
with
with with the zeolite is you bring it in
with anybody who's doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie that's a trick
that's what they're doing so the heavy
metal detox smoothie has been healing
people around the world for years
without any zeolite and i don't
recommend zoi and i don't i don't
recommend it at all
and and that's the whole thing like what
does anthony williams say well he
doesn't recommend it for a reason
it dehydrates you and it reduces your
electrolytes to the brain and people
with neurological problems
i don't like zeolite and so um
and the zeolites now out now what i is
what i don't like
so the whole point with the zeolite
thing and what happened is
that they're trying to get everybody to
do zeolite
with the heavy metal detox smoothie the
mechanical heavy metal detox smoothie
and that and then they'll just say oh
you're getting better well it's their
zeolite by far it's our zeolite
uh okay sure yeah that's sure zeolite on
its own you take away everything get rid
of all medical medium tools whatsoever
get rid of them all get rid of cellular
juice get rid of the heavy metal detox
smoothie get rid of every single heavy
metal deep
get rid of every single version of
medical medium tool
right get rid of all the different
things like everything i've ever
recommended to stay away from whatever
just get
and then you know and then what you do
is you bring in all those things that
are recommended to stay away from
you bring those back in you bring your
zeolite in you bring your water ionizer
in your alkaline
ionizer water machine you bring in
nutritional yeast you bring in your
vinegar
you'll go
keep your caffeine and keep your
nutritional yeast in keep
keep keep the the bone broth in keep the
colostrum in
keep the collagen in keep the water
ionizer machine keep the zeolite in
keep the charcoal in keep the crow in do
all that
keep all medical medium tools out
whatsoever keep celery juice never do
celery juice never do cucumber juice
never do spinach soup never do the
healing broth never do the heavy metal
detox smoothie
don't do any you know whatever don't
don't listen to the medical medium
information and you do all that other
stuff
watch how fast you go downhill like
everybody went downhill
all those decades in health communities
because what happened was i don't know
if you guys remember
but 15 years ago 10 15 20 years ago you
were sick
you stayed sick nobody got better in the
communities
they went to hundreds of doctors and
nobody got better medical medium
information broke the fine
broke that whole thing that happened
and got people better and that's what
happened for the years of work have done
and what's happening here
while agreeing anthony when i started
following mm
i needed a walker had boat rocking
feeling 24 7 diagnosed with multiple
sclerosis and was so sick
i've recovered so much and don't need a
walker anymore while agreeing i'm
honored
incredible i'm so proud of you by the
way so proud of you just so you know
so the trick is bring in this old
garbage
that never got people better on its own
on its own
bring it in with something that's
getting the metals out of people
or bring it in with someone doing the
celery juice and then say
the pyramid schemers say it's the
zeolite it it's really actually
disgusting what they do and then they
have 50
60 100 people marketing and doing it
like i can't compete with that just
it's crazy susan walker i use the best
deal like going in 2004 and i went
downhill completely susan
it happened to everybody it happened to
everybody with zeolite but they they
brought
this back by incorporating it into the
medical medium community
and that's what they do it's actually
twisted really when you think about it
you're not the only one
that literally went downhill from
zeolite
and that's the problem and and that's
what happens
i recommended this one gentle one many
years ago
because of hoping i can get some metal
out of an intestinal tract
and and i stopped because it changed
everything changes
and there's a whole bunch of bad ones
out back then too and at the time
be open-hearted yes i tried z-light also
didn't help me either
that's what happened um i read your
comments by the way you left a comment
on youtube right
a couple comments just really cool um
you know like like
that that's exactly what happened and
that happened to everybody but here's
the trick
now they got social media they got
marketing uh
literally an army of people with mlm
trying to get it into the medical
meeting community they sit there
commenting
all day you need the zeolite with the
heavy metal detox smoothie
it's actually like it's disturbing i
mean
yeah do what you want you can do that
you guys want to use you like do you
want but i'm just telling what happened
dino started live scene and mm info with
eczema
patient and he started to heal faster so
an eczema patient and he started to heal
faster
because the reason why i don't have the
lysine right here i want to look for it
and i know we got stuff to do you guys i
know i know
i don't know where my lysine is but
anyway let me pour some celery juice
so so it's really kind of
so yeah stop all your medical medium
everything including medical medium
stuff you didn't know you're doing
because medical medium information
brought it out into the world in the
last 20 25 years of the health movement
30 years
and you've already adopted if we remove
all medical medium information even
stuff you don't know you're doing
that's medical medium right if we remove
all that
and you just bring in all the old crap
the water ionizer alkaline ionizer the
zeolite
bring it all in the charcoal bring brim
the bone broth broth bring it in bring
it all in and keep medical medium
information out and make sure you do
your eggs again and everything else
and just go downhill you'll end up like
everybody
that was 20 years ago and 15 years ago
where no one in them
in the healing communities were getting
better and and it was just doctor
shopping guessing games and everybody
was
literally devastated with their
conditions that was before spirit of
compassion really taking root and taking
root
with information i mean seriously
i got some celery juice here
that's a big one by the way that's a
really big one
so made some celery juice i showed you
guys let's make the heavy metal detox
movie
let's do that all right
um it's honored to have you guys here
really is
let's get two cups of wild blueberries
in there
do that now in the
two cups in here celery juice is a
complete electrolyte
it helps to loosen up toxic heavy metals
but
also what it does is a complete
electrolyte
it it stops the rust of toxic heavy
metals
inside the brain it stops the corrosion
inside the brain putting about two cups
in here
okay it stops the erosion that's one
thing it does too
right celery juice also feeds neurons
really important to know guys i want to
put some cilantro in here
right get a little cilantro in here too
little dolls
this is the medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie i'm making right now
put a tablespoon you can put a teaspoon
in there if you really want to that's
fine too
put like what seems like a tablespoon
it's probably like if they crunch down
it wouldn't be that much
i got that in there i'm going to pop in
some orange
right look at these
caracaras right these red navels what do
you think
right squeeze some orange in there let's
do that
you can put the orange in just don't put
the rind in
okay look here's how it works with this
heavy metal detox movie this is this is
what really has helped people
not a phantom zeolite not a zeolite that
goes
in your stomach and out the end and
dehydrates you
this is hydrating it's built
to last in your system to travel far
each ingredient runs off of itself
kind of like a football team or a soccer
team
passing the ball to each other to get
down the field
that's what happens here you got the
cilantro working off the spirulina you
got the spirulina working off the barley
grass you get the barley grass working
off the dolls
to make like a wrap out of that
but yes i'm gonna pop some bananas in
did you guys see nicholas's healing
story the autism story
his autism story with his healing with
uh
on ig got the wild blueberries
i'm putting two bananas
in here details matter
and i'll show you what the details are
right here
you got the banana which has the
potassium
which is an electrolyte all on its own
right that's an electrolyte all on its
own
okay critical for neurons very important
for neurotransmitters is potassium
so that's in here but most importantly
the bananas in here because glucose
you can't bring nutrients to cells
to the brain without glucose the brain
will die
to start dying five minutes after it
loses its glucose your brain runs on
sugar
your brain has to get fed sugar
or it dies there's nothing else to say
it doesn't get sugar it dies after about
five minutes
that's what happens okay and when you
get your blood drawn you lose all your
electrolytes you lose your glucose
and when you do a blood donation you
when you donate your blood
they take a pint you know they take 500
you know 500 milliliters which is
unbelievable really
unbelievable that you go into mild
hemorrhagic hemorrhagic shock
so if i if you guys if you guys if
you're chronically ill i don't
recommend donating blood whatever you do
because you lose all your glucose to the
brain
you and i got a podcast coming talking
about it but if you want to donate blood
and you're strong and you can you're
resilient and you've got a constitution
then i would still you know give them
only half that amount
and come back another time to donate
again it's not like i'm against donating
blood it's like
you give them 250 uh
milli milliliters you give them 250
milliliters is what you give them
so let's go a little bit more on this so
i got the bananas in here i put the
orange in here you guys
now let's get some spirulina here so the
vimergy spiruline is the one i trust
right now with my family my friends
people always feel like what does he do
like what does he do
showing you guys what i do so i put a
teaspoon of spirulina in there
right some emergency v is in victor i am
as in mary ergy
pasta one thermogee.com i'm not
sponsored
so i'm going to put some barley grass
juice powder in here too
teaspoon janette i was donating blood
often when i
got the sickest yes because the immune
system gets removed
so here's how it works i know we're
covering a couple different topics
that's a white blood cell right there
okay that's red
red blood cell okay white blood cell
when you donate blood you're getting
you're getting mild hemorrhagic shock
because they're almost taking
their i mean when you think about
they're taking 500 milliliters
okay and that's a lot
just so you know um and when when they
take that much they're taking
your white count with them and when you
they take your white
count and then they take your glucose
they take your glucose right the very
thing that feeds your brain
then they take your mineral salts like
the celery juice i just made right they
take your mineral salts okay
they're they're they're robbing all that
white count that paroles your
your body to stop viruses and then you
end up getting sicker and sicker blood
draws do the same
and we got to be careful you got to do
less blood at the doctor's office you
got to tell them half files i'm going to
do
a podcast it's coming this week coming
up
and i talk about the blood draw in in um
what to do like in the new additions
just so you know so
important seen people lose their lives
go down he'll go downhill with their
chronic illness they keep on getting
five vials seven vials 10
vials 12 miles and they just lose their
life they stay sick for the rest of
their life
or they they die or if they have cancer
they just suck the life out of them with
all the blood draws and they take their
immune system while they have cancer and
literally the system
is is is very much responsible
to people losing their lives that's how
it's bad
um so that's that's the thing here so
let's get this smoothie rolling we got
some orange in there i just put some
more put a little bit more i got bananas
in here
cilantro they work off themselves
uh elizabeth no no not normal
blueberries
only while frozen yes a fret a fr
or freshly picked wild blueberries
otherwise wild blueberries raw
powder from beemergy correct that that's
what i would do
um regular blueberries aren't gonna do
it they have to be the wild blueberries
there's a big the details matter to get
someone better you use the regular
blueberries you don't get better you
know you use
a bad spirulina you don't go as far you
don't you use it's just this is how it's
been not that i've
ever seen always see megan is it okay to
eat
fruit while my sugar is high it's the
fat that's the problem
so megan you do what your doctor says
ask you know ask your doctor
but if if it was me and i had high sugar
i would lower my fat
and then that lowers your sugar meaning
your a1c
it lowers that sugar profile it brings
it down you gotta
read the diabetes chapter you can take
it to your doctor if you want
to revise and expand it that's the book
though don't get confused and grab the
first edition
that's out there the link is in the
description
let's start this up get rolling
you can get the book in the library too
if you want
uh making the medical eating mental
detox movie
how do i get to your podcast deborah
i'll tell you a second
yes
so beverly asked can i get the new book
on amazon yes you can
amazon is where to get it amazon us
or the amazon other places um and then
there's another question how can i get
to your podcast deborah you had that
question
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
there's 17 docu series style episodes
there's no advertisers there's no
commercials
i did that on purpose and it's a top
podcast in health
and and there's so much information
the episodes are in there and and and
what you want to subscribe because i'm
coming out with a new episode this week
you also want to check out the
meditations in there
and also all the different neurological
symptoms anxiety episode you guys know
right
the the caffeine matrite coffee
chocolate episode i mean there's so many
episodes
brain fog episode b12 episode potato
episode everybody's afraid of potatoes
right
all of that um
so and i'll even show you what it looks
like
i just happen to have this handy okay
that's it can you guys see medical
medium podcast at apple podcast that's
what it looks like
yours truly is sitting there because i'm
at your service
and i want you guys to have free
information
as much as i possibly can
so i'm just pouring the heavy metal
detox smoothie you can you can get a
spoon and get the rest out
you can totally do that if you want
right out of the right out of the
container there it's a medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie
put that right here you guys the thing
is with this juicer
the reason why people save money and the
reason why i'm saving money
is because it's a small amount of pulp
for a lot of juice now i showed you how
big that was it was over 32 ounces
and it's dry the pulp is dry and you
can't get that with any other juicer
and that's why i love the juicer because
that's
half the celery i buy half the celery i
buy
so instead of buying two cases of celery
like i used to have to
for the week or whatever it was now i
buy one case right because i juice a lot
of it 32 ounces to 60 ounces
the juicer is 50 50 50 off
okay so that's it and strain
the celery juice that's the key always
strain the celery juice that's the best
thing to do
keep that in mind right there straining
the celery juice
be open-hearted that's so interesting i
didn't even know that given blood or
blood draws
were such a big deal great info uh
such a big deal i'll just give you a
quick rundown on that okay
um critical to know when you're
chronically ill when you got any kind of
condition the
condition can worsen and worsen and
worsen
from blood draws and then as you get
sicker from your blood draws
then they draw more blood it's a trap
that eventually takes people out
um and it's really really sad it's the
biggest problem in the medical system
that's not even being looked at or
addressed they can send half files
to the lab and they'll accept them if
the doctor sends them
so that's something to keep in mind i
personally if i got any blood drawn ever
if
i wanted to it would be two to three
vials half full half full vials that's
what i would do
and then if your doctor wants to order
more tests divide them up and ask them
can i divide them up and come back
another day
and get another two vials or two half
files and then you run that metabolic
panel or you run that thyroid panel
or you run or you run your cbc like can
i get my cbc another day
which will take another two or three
vials half files please and you come
back another day
this way your immune system there's
enough of it in your bloodstream
to keep you from getting virally sick
because that's what happens
you get more susceptible to the flu you
get more susceptible to chronic fatigue
syndrome epstein-barr you get more
susceptible to any condition you have if
you have
endometriosis pcos if you have fibroids
any condition
anxiety depression lupus multiple
sclerosis
eczema is any condition you have worsens
from blood draws they take too much
blood they remove your immune system
your glucose in your and your
electrolytes
um and so much more is coming in the
podcast so the podcast that's coming
this week
the episode medical medium podcast at
apple podcast you guys should go there
later and check it out but that new
episode is going to be packed more with
the information but
it's not for the faint of heart i'm
forewarning you
some of you may want to just not hear
the the episode
um if you got if you're sensitive
because i'm dropping a bomb
and you're going to have to have your
seat belts fastened and you're going to
have to have your lemon balm tea
that's raspberry leaf right there but
your lemon balm tea
traditional medicinals i'm not sponsored
it's just a tea that keeps natural
flavors away
because i've never seen natural flavors
in this company's teas
yet or anything natural flavors is msg
which kills the brain
so anyway the point is you guys is that
episode coming at the medical media
podcast
apple podcast is not for the faint of
heart it's
just like chemtrails was not for the
faint of heart just giving you the 4-1-1
on that
[Music]
um so anyway did some celery
did have metal detox smoothie divine
light me too and also there's so much
info in anthony's books we really want
to always get back to that
them and read them again that's that's
amazing also because when time is passed
and we experience more we can see
more things than before yes that
that's really what it is incredible
so
anyway you guys look i'm heading off to
ig and tiktok i'm going to juice again
i'm going to make another heavy metal
detox maybe i'm probably going to mess
up again
and just start juicing on the counter
and spill it all over myself
and the floor um because we're going to
do it live
bottom line and
it's been great having you guys here
okay and you've seen the heavy metal
detox movie done and everything else
you guys know i love you and i love all
that you're doing and i stand with you
and
through your journey and i believe in
you and
i want you guys to keep on healing keep
on moving forward
and um i'll see you there at ig you
coming with me or what you guys come on
over to ig if you get kicked off ig
because it's got a glitch go to
tick-tock live i'm doing them both at
the same
time just like i'm doing youtube and
facebook right now live
um yeah the books have guidance in them
so you can heal
so you can get what you need out of
there so you can get better
it's not just food or foods or food talk
or anything it's
information these are medical textbooks
so
all right you guys love you