okay and they're going to be talking
about
seven heavy metal detox cleanses
seven heavy metal detox cleanses gonna
talk a little bit about the different
levels today's the day the books are
released brain saver right here brain
saver protocols
I promise you this
they will go down in history as the
greatest
Health books of all time I promise you
that when you hold one in your hands
you'll feel it you'll know it you'll
know it when you read them
they're epic books
and if someone says oh he's biased
because he wrote the books uh
I'm just like you guys
I'm a messenger I got the information
from above
I put them in the books
I can judge them
I'm allowed to
I could judge the books just like you or
anybody else
and hands down
you will be so blown off your seats
I promise you that
because they're that good
you guys uh happy to be here I have the
brain saver books in front of me right
here okay and I'm gonna open them up in
a second how are you guys doing
incredible to be here in this moment in
time I'm honored to know you guys I'm
honored to be here I'm honored to
deliver this information I'm honored to
be the messenger
regardless of the price I have paid
along the way and still do I am honored
to be here
and I'm so excited
and that's just to say the least you got
your books 1200 pages of pure goodness
incredible mark
amazing you're so excited you got your
books incredible
so Ashley says hello I'm becoming a
brain surgeon your work is amazing and
will continue to flourish in the health
field that's incredible and and we need
brain surgeons because a lot of people
have stuff inside their brains they have
stuff inside their brains that grow and
so
that's an incredible incredible
um
I mean as surgeons are gifted too it's
just amazing I love hearing that so look
you guys
I'm on here you're excited hi there you
got the books incredible
so all right let's go you guys let's
talk about it a little bit I got the
brain saver
and I got the brand saver protocols in
front of me you guys see them right
there okay
so I what happened yesterday when we
were doing the live is I was reading
some of the symptoms and conditions but
there were so many symptoms and
conditions that are in the books that I
kind of like only got through some of
them so I just want to ring off a few at
you now and see what you guys think and
maybe you guys have some of this and
maybe you don't or maybe you don't even
know it
when we go into it a little bit more
heart palpitations
okay non-neurological heart palpitations
neurological heart palpitations there's
a big difference right there that's how
incredible that's how advanced the books
are
where there's a little bit of both I'm
gonna put these right over here
there's a little bit of both of that
that people have and nobody knows this
that there's neurological heart
palpitations and there's
non-neurological heart palpitations heat
sensitivity so many people have heat
sensitivity
okay
hepatitis I even have that in here
herpes simplex hsv1 hsv2 how many people
have the cold sores so many people have
all the different cold sores the mouth
sores right
HIV got that humidity sensitivity how
many people have they're really
sensitive to humidity
hunting hens disease
hyperhidrosis hyperpigmentation so many
people are dealing with hyper
pigmentation that's a big one right
there impulse control issues
so impulse control issues inflammatory
myopathy so many people have that they
didn't even know it and they have
inflammatory myopathy influenza right
inner ear disease that's important so
many people have that insomnia
right in intracranial hypertension so
hypertension
that's cranial not just hypertension
somewhere else in the body but cranial
hypertension
that's a big deal irritability itching
and burning when no rash is present how
many people are dealing with itching and
burning with no rash present
jaw pain mystery jaw pain right
joint pain it's another one right there
learning disabilities and disorders you
know anybody with learning disabilities
the only children with learning
disabilities
left neglect
that's another one too liver spots how
many people have liver spots do you guys
know anybody with liver spots
Long Haul C
right also known as long C you guys know
what word I'm talking about
Long Haul flu
loss of face face movement loss of smell
loss of taste how many guys have dealt
with loss of taste loss of smell right
low vision you guys know anybody with
low vision you know has nothing to do
with whether you have glasses or you
wear contacts it's just low vision even
whether regardless of that the low
vision problems people have lower back
pain any of you guys dealing with lower
back pain mystery lower back pain
lupus that's one right there Lyme
disease Mania
marijuana withdrawal that's interesting
because a lot of people don't want to
smoke the marijuana because they they've
maxed themselves out by they've done it
for years or they just want to be freed
from it
I'm not judging anybody here I'm just
saying they want to be free from it so
there's there's actually marijuana
withdrawal in here
mecfs melasma
how about melasma so many people are
diagnosed with that or dealing with that
you guys know memory issues memory loss
Meniere's disease right so you get dizzy
you get the vertigo and it's like
Meniere's disease
meningitis migraines Mind Body syndrome
that's something a lot of people are
dealing with right there
anybody is saying everybody's saying
look I got this I got that I see you on
Instagram and everything you're saying
this and I see you guys there right you
guys there on Facebook YouTube you're
like hey I got this I got that
it's probably in the book I'm just
reading just a few things mitochondria
myopathy mononucleosis mood changes and
mood swings motor skills disorder
multiple sclerosis muscle pain
mysterious muscle pain how many of you
guys have mysterious muscle pain right
I mean a lot of people do muscle spasms
mysterious muscle spasms right
muscle weakness a lot of people muscle
weakness where they feel like they're
they're weak in the muscles like they're
just they can't do anything okay
muscle weakness
muscular dystrophy
uh
um myelin nerve sheath damage
myocarditis mystery fears and worries
mystery hunger narcolepsy nausea mystery
nausea
neck pain mystery neuralgia neuritis
neurological fatigue
neurological gastroparesis neurological
fatigue is a medical medium
term
that's taken over by research and
science they actually took the medical
medium term neurological fatigue and now
they're using it out there
without the medical medium you know
being cited we know how it works
neurological Lyme neurological symptoms
neuromuscular disease neuropathy
Neurosis numbness many guys are in in
how many people are dealing with
numbness right I mean people do you know
women and men obsessive compulsive
disorder that's OCD
neuralgia optic nerve atrophy so many
people have optic nerve atrophy and they
suffer with all these different symptoms
it's brutal epic neuritis orthorexia
interesting orthorexia here in the brain
saver books
other specified feeding and eating
disorder
overeating pain in the back of the head
mysterious pain inside or around ears
how many people get the ear pain you
guys have that like the ear pain how
many people have that
pancreatitis
pandas right panic attacks paralysis of
facial nerves
hmm who who do we know out there that's
got paralysis of facial nerves even a
famous person right
paralysis of facial nerves
they might want to get this book
so it keeps on going on parasites
Parkinson's disease
um peristaltic issues personality
disorders
Pika eating disorder right p-i-c-a pika
polymyalgia
popping in the ears who gets the popping
in the ears you guys how many people get
popular I'm just I'm just taking a
couple of minutes and just reading some
of the symptoms and conditions in the
brain saver books
so Pika yep p-i-c-a
it's eating eating disorder
post polio syndrome how about pots you
guys are dealing with pots out there did
a little video on pots
pressure and chest that whole mystery
pressure in your chest
tightness to chest it's another one all
on its own right I healed my mystery
nausea with mnm info amazing
so
psychosis PTSD
psychedelic mushroom withdrawal
that's a big one right there and I've
known people talking to doctors and a
lot of doctors where they got patients
that have done so many psychedelic
mushrooms they can't break free from
them and they just start losing their
minds like losing their minds and they
need a withdrawal process
psychosis
PTSD ptss
pulling sensation in the face
so facial
pulling sensation
that's a big one right there
pulling sensation in the nose where you
feel like your nose is being pulled one
way or another like it's being actual
pulled and a pulling sensation in the
eyes where you feel like your eyes are
being pulled
forehead too
pulsating Sensations in the head anybody
have any pulsating Sensations has you
ever known anybody to have that or you
feel a pulse where you shouldn't have
one where it shouldn't be like why is
this pulsing right here or why is this
pulsing now how come I'm living with
this pulsing condition
recreational drug withdrawal
the recreational drugs
repetitive strain injuries
restless leg syndrome restlessness ra
you know rheumatoid arthritis right
neglect
ringing in the ears roving pain
sadness sarcoidosis
Scar Tissue on the brain schizophrenia
sciatica sad seasonal affective disorder
seizures
a sense of not digesting well where it's
like I'm not digesting my food I just
don't feel like I digest my food at all
you know this is just these books are
just absolutely phenomenal for people
groundbreaking information and we're
going to talk a little bit more about it
too just incredible
shingles Sjogren's syndrome sleep apnea
sleep issue slurred speech
are you like your speechless
and it's not because you're tired
spasms speech difficulties stiffness
stiff person syndrome burning stomach
how many people have the burning stomach
out there I've seen that over and over
and over
stomach flipping when you're not nervous
or it's a nervous feeling like your
stomach's always flipping right you see
that out there
stomach pain stomach problems how many
people have stomach problems
just about everybody in the United
States never mind globally
Strokes
Sun sensitivity
it's a lot of people that are sensitive
to the sun sun spots
swallowing difficulty where they have a
difficult time swallowing regardless of
what it is food or not
so I'm just saying you guys I'm just
running through the some of the symptoms
and conditions in the brain saver book I
still haven't gotten to the end of the
list
so
I'm going to talk about
one thing here which is interesting back
to the medical medium frame shot therapy
now I promise you
the medical mean and brain shot therapy
that your mind is going to be blown when
you use the brain shot therapy
so it's 30 shots
but what's incredible is the brain
shot therapy cleanse
that's exciting now I'd say cleanse is
there's different levels so there's the
cleanse with cleanse is I want to talk
about that a little bit
so I'm in the brain shots and I know I
talked about this yesterday because it's
that incredible you got the different
brain shots
that's the exposure shot right there now
be prepared so here's the thing between
yesterday when I was talking in today
and I'm talking right about it all
today I'm just trying to give you guys a
little heads up
that when you Embark and Venture into
these brain shots prepare yourself
because people are not used to getting
results right away in this world
they're not in alternative medicine
people and conventional medicine people
are not used to results immediately
they never they never expected so when
you do the brain shot therapy
brain shots
it's going to surprise you so I'm trying
to prepare you
because
people don't get results
right away
but they do when you're doing the brain
shot therapy
so when you Embark into these brain
shots
get ready so it's not a surprise I don't
want it to be a big surprise for you I
don't want you to do it and be like what
just hit me oh my God
I want you to know that
this is quick acting relief it happens
so actually be ready for it and be
prepared prepared for it so there's the
pathogen exposure shot talked about this
a little bit yesterday toxic fragrances
fragrances exposure negative energy
exposure
mold exposure EMF and 5G exposure so I'm
just going through some of them but I'm
going to move out of the brain shot
therapy
well actually let's talk about the
different levels there's seven
brain shot therapy cleanse levels
so the first level is entry level
so if you want to Embark into that or
try that you do the entry level
second one is
basic so it's the basic brain shot
therapy cleanse
third level is simplified brain shot
fourth level is intermediate brain shot
therapy cleanse fifth level is
performance brain shot therapy cleanse
sixth level is Advanced frame shot
therapy cleanse
seventh level is high powered brain shot
therapy clouds
and remember what I was saying before
even if you're just doing them singly
like you're not doing the brain shot
therapy cleanses but you're doing the
brain shots
that when you partake in those
be prepared to actually feel something
what happens in alternative medicine no
matter what you do where you go
getting instant quick
results or relief is not something
that's heard of out there
but this is the medical medium stuff and
this is the brain saver books
so look out
and
we're in brain saver right here and
we're braid saver protocols
so the whole thing about with brain
shots what are they let's clarify that
right now I'll give you a little window
into what they are just so you know
here's the mood shifter right here if
you see you see a glass
that glass is filled with roughly around
two ounces that's a shot glass
so they're brain shots because they're
small quantities
of medicinals
medicinal food
and then what happens is when you
actually turn it into the shot through
the recipe that you have here in the
brain saver book
it looks something similar to that I'll
show you another one right here just so
you're not confused
this one's the energy shifter right here
there you go
so keep in mind that's like a two ounce
shot glass is what that is
now I'll show you another one too
here's a craving shifter right there
so what I mean quick acting relief I
mean if you're somebody fighting and
struggling with Cravings somebody that's
struggling with cravings and dealing
with anything like that
and you do the brain shot
you get the instant relief
so it's a big deal
if you're dealing with frustration if
you're somebody that's
gets heated up easy
you get angry that's the anger shifter
right there
that's a two ounce shot glass
so these are the medical medium shot
brain shot therapies and medical mean
brain shot therapy cleanses with seven
different levels so I'm just kind of
so I see you guys some of you guys got
questions about it you're like well what
is that
so I'm in the medical medium heavy metal
detox section right here
a brain saver
now what's incredible about the heavy
metal defects first of all medical beam
information the heavy metal detox
smoothie that's been out there and the
heavy metal detox cleanse medical medium
that's been out there has saved a lot of
people's lives it's helped so many
people around the world
in the brain saver books
takes us to another level which is
really exciting
so not only is this filled with
information detailed comprehensive
information
about toxic heavy metals what happens in
our body and how it works
the information you've never heard
before
but there's seven heavy metal detox
cleanses
in the brain saver books
so I'm just showing you guys
in different levels
so the first level is the entry level
the heavy metal detox cleanse second one
is the basic heavy metal detox cleanse
the third one is simplified heavy metal
detox glands
fourth one is intermediate heavy metal
detox cleanse fifth one is performance
heavy metal detox cleanse six one is
Advanced heavy metal detox cleanse
seven seventh one is high powered heavy
metal detox cleanse so a lot of people
have different levels of toxic heavy
metals different areas inside the brain
different places a lot of people
have toxic heavy metals in the emotional
centers of the brain
so they're having a lot of different
mental health issues because of it
they're struggling
their mental health is actually you know
in a place where they're actually
struggling every minute every day every
hour so many people not just depression
and anxiety but
that plus other things too compiled into
it so
when you're talking about the
high-powered heavy metal detox cleanse
that's a whole other level too so many
people it's Advanced heavy metal detox
smoothie and an extractor smoothie so
let me go into that a little bit
and then there's advanced track
extractor smoothies so
there's something in these books called
the extractor
it goes with the heavy metal detox
cleanse
so when you experience that so I'm
trying to get you guys
just
familiar with what's happening inside
these books because it's a whole other
level these brain saver books
and I want healing to happen quicker for
people I want people to get results
quicker
a lot of times what's happening now so
the world is changing and that's the
thing with what's going on with the
medical medium book series is as the
world gets more corrupted
with poisons and toxins on a level that
we've never seen before
and everybody's just like a frog and a
pot of boiling water
because you're kind of living in it you
get the exposure you don't know it and
it gets worse and worse we have to do
something about it so
what is offered in the brand saver books
is to move that needle no matter what it
takes
and medical meme information has already
done that for people but we're coming on
in history in the next
five years even now and moving forward
that
we're going to be up against so much
more with our bodies
so much more corruption in the
industries
so much more exposure with pathogens
that we have to keep up with it and we
have to make sure that everybody has a
chance to move the needle
so it's really an incredible exciting
moment in time right now for the brand
saver books and all medical medium books
I mean I always recommend having them
all
having a lot your your personal library
at home filled with all the books but by
no means do you want to not have the
brain saver protocols and brand saver
books okay so letting you guys know
what's going on there
so if you just came on I'm just reading
some of the comments too as you guys are
here if you just came on we're talking
about the brain shot therapy cleanses
which is mind-blowing on its own
seven levels of heavy metal detox lenses
were talking about the advanced heavy
metal detox cleanse and we're talking
about the extractor smoothie too
part of the heavy metal detox cleanse
this will blow your mind I can't wait
for you guys to hold these books in your
hands and see what I'm talking about
here
I'm really excited for all of you
you love your mm personal Library
incredible Lisa you just received the
books Alexandria
amazing
so
give you a quick rundown on the books a
little bit if you guys aren't familiar
with it
there's over 300 symptoms and conditions
in these books many of the symptoms and
conditions explain in detail now there's
an eating disorder chapter
that's on a level no one is ever going
to expect really it's mind-blowing so
that chapter alone is just
lots of incredible information so I want
to give everybody a little window into
the book there's a blood draw chapter in
detail of how to protect yourself with
protocols on how to protect yourself
before you go for a blood test
protocols for how to protect yourself
after you had your blood test or blood
drawn
so that's a big big plus inside these
books all on its own
and I've talked about it if you're new
to Medical medium information you might
not know about what happens when you get
your blood drawn
and how it weakens your immune system
and that your bone marrow has to go in
overdrive to produce immune cells and as
we get sicker and have mystery symptoms
our doctors and Specialists they order
more blood so they want more blood drawn
so now you're into a lot more vials of
blood then you lose more of your immune
system and then your bone marrow has to
go into overdrive again
and then your condition worsens
so medical meme information has been
about doing it right
teaching your doctor
about your blood draw
making sure that you can protect
yourself at the same time and in the
brain saver books there's a blood draw
protocol
for before you have to go and get your
blood drawn and after you get your blood
drawn
and so that's a huge deal on its own
Michelle L says I had so much blood
drawn I can't believe it
but it's incredible to know about the
information in here for blood draws
so there's that all in its own
anyway you guys just wanted to let you
know the books are out today
they are ready there are they're being
shipped out from what I hear
so
when you get a chance check them out
brain saver brain saver protocols and
I'll see you guys next time