right here youtube live facebook live
we're talking about the immune system
medical medium podcast i released the
episode
okay blood draw bloodletting vampirism
one of the most important and critical
episodes ever
out there so you might want to listen
when you get a chance
someone said well wait a minute why
didn't you let us know before
aw like why would you hold us out
this many years and all this time
and not tell us about the blood draw
problem tell us that we're losing our
immune systems
that's because i was telling you guys
i talked about it all over the place i
have spoken about it and everybody would
just
glaze over you know you talk about it no
no my doctor knows what he's doing no no
roll eyes roll over no no no
finally watching everybody get sick sick
sick while they're trying to get better
better better
i'm like you know what i'm just gonna
have to scream
at the mountaintop exactly michelle dang
aw
we're gonna talk about the immune system
we're going to talk about what that
means when your immune system leaves
when you get your blood drawn
and so when you get your blood drawn
okay and it comes out of those veins and
arteries we're going to talk about that
a little bit going to talk about the gut
a little bit too of why there's so much
confusion about
the immune system's all in your gut no
it's not
it's not it's not there
and we're going to talk about why and
why that even happens
yeah probiotic companies want you to
think your immune system's all in your
gut
of course they do gut product companies
which
basically are running the gamma all
they're doing is banking
banking banking they want you to think
just your immune system's all in your
gut
of course they do and then they want you
to think neurotransmitters are in your
gut too
they want they want you to think that
neurotransmitters in your brain
or in your gut now no they actually get
created in your brain tissue by your
brain
but they'll tell you anything to sell
you gut products so i got to give you
guys a little window on that but medical
media podcast at apple podcast have you
listened
to the episode it's that medical meeting
podcast apple podcast have you guys
listened to it so you can protect
yourself it's so important it's
critical that you hear that episode
so important so keep that in mind
um because that that episode blood draw
okay bloodletting vampirism is the most
important one
um yeah michelle yeah gut supplement
empires absolutely that's what it is
and you know they'll do that they'll try
to sell your gut health
products they'll try to sell you your
probiotics right i know
probably all you guys are on a probiotic
but take away
the celery juice get rid of it get rid
of
more fruits herbs leafy greens get rid
of it get rid of all the tools get rid
of all the tools i've been working on
for 35 years teaching people how to do
because people didn't eat fruit
get rid of every single berry because
everybody said there's too much sugar in
berries all those years
all those years too much sugar kept all
the fruit away get rid of all the fruit
get rid of the heavy metal detox
smoothies get rid of the good
supplements the high quality stuff the
good spirit lean get rid of everything
right and just get rid of everything and
take your probiotic
take your probiotic take your apple
cider vinegar
take your nutritional yeast take your
charcoal and you go
now you're at 20 lime doctors oh it's
all in your gut now you're at
30 lime doctors now you're at
specialists and that's what happens okay
and what turned all this michelle miller
yay
good to see you you know what happens is
that
you know the medical medium information
is
it's changed all that that's what life
was before
the first version of medical medium okay
that was life before it was hell for the
chronically ill
it was hell when you had fibro it was
hell if you had anything
back before this book came out and then
the information disseminated all around
the globe
doctors and practitioners are using
little tidbits all through the medical
medium books
they're incorporating them so people
stand a chance in hell to heal
and then they also muck it up with all
the bad stuff
but we're going to talk about you guys
listen to michelle says bone broth
collagen
what is that collagen bone broth
colostrum probiotics fermented foods
yeah stay on all that don't do one thing
medical medium
i can hand pick all the medical medium
stuff that you don't even know is
medical medium right
if i go through your cabinets go through
your refrigerator i'll be like what are
you doing
you know what's going on here oh you're
doing that well that wouldn't be here if
it wasn't for my work ten years ago
okay well that wouldn't be here either
if it wasn't for my work 10 12 years ago
that wouldn't be here if it wasn't for
this book right here let me get rid of
this that would be here now just go on
everything that used to be here
colostrum collagen bone broth fermented
foods
apple cider vinegar charcoal whatever
make sure you're on all probiotics
beyond all that
take away all the medical medium stuff
for 35 years that changed health
take away all that and everybody will be
where they were
it was terrible it was terrible i mean
what was happening back then
jennifer my brother-in-law had too much
iron in his blood he had to go to blood
letting station every 30 days
the low-grade viral infections can do
two things
they can get into the spleen and now you
have an infection and now
this chronic infection and you're
cranking the iron they get into the bone
marrow
you're cranking the iron they get into
the liver you're cranking the iron
and then you get that aspect of it or
the livery viruses what they do is they
get into your system and you've got low
iron
you've got low low iron and that's the
difference pathogens see different
things
michelle miller says i wouldn't be here
if it weren't for you anthony i'm
honored so good to see you i'm so glad
you're here
and again it the bloodletting station is
just a band-aid but it doesn't fit the
problem
completely understand and there's things
we got to do to fix the problem
you guys i'm here i'm going to talk the
reason why i have the dummy with me
all right the reason why i have the
tick-tock dummy with me is because i
want to show you guys a couple things i
want to talk about why it's important
to listen to the episode medical mean
podcast at apple podcast the blood draw
episode just share it with every friend
you have you know share it with
anybody you know please please share
share share so you can help people
because
people lose their lives from too much
blood drawn they get kicked down from
too much blood drawn they lose their
immune system from too much blood drawn
and it just it just you know that's just
what i mean somebody will say to you the
reason why i'm talking i have the dummy
here
is the reason why someone's going to say
to you yet your immune system you're not
going to lose your immune system if you
get your blood drawn
you're not going to lose your immune
system if you get your blood drawn i'm a
nutritionist i'm telling you that your
immune system's all in your gut
i'm a health coach and i'm telling you
that your immune system is all in your
gut because we just parrot everything we
hear and see
i'm just no i'm a doctor i'm telling you
immune systems all in your gut
well all that comes from gut health
companies that sell crap and
gut health uh probiotic companies that
sell stuff and it's pseudoscience it's
pseudoscience
real science doesn't even believe in
that science that's pseudoscience it's
gut health
companies create this pseudoscience so
they can somehow have
something behind their gut product that
spreads and gets out there
and then you're going to be like well
the immune system's in the gut it's not
in the gut
and i got the dummy here because i want
to talk to you guys about this stuff
paige i almost died from a huge blood
draw
oh my god oh my god it's just
exactly exactly i'm just glad you're
here paige and you know
better you know what's up you know how
to protect yourself you must listen to
the episode right
you must listen to the the blood draw
episode um
medical medium the link is in
description you guys share it with
everybody you know okay
even if they don't like me i don't like
that guy he's the medical medium
you know i don't like them whatever
listen to this episode you don't like
them fine but
listen to this episode because it can
protect you your family save your life
you don't have to like me um to save
your life
kathy do you gain immune cells with
transfusion
great question the immune cells they try
to work
they try to work when you get an
infusion okay so
so when someone else's immune cells are
in the blood and you get the blood but
it doesn't normally line up that way so
it doesn't work that way
sometimes sometimes they're well first
of all they diminish over time and then
your your immune cells take over so your
immune cells take over your bone marrow
produces more immune cells
and then but but your immune cells can
live in that blood they can live
in the blood of another person right so
so then when you get your blood
transfusion your immune cells that
that develop fill that new fresh blood
okay and then the old immune cells
that were that were basically um
stationed for that other human being
they don't work the same way in your
body as they would work in someone
else's body even if the blood type is
the same
but still doesn't matter blood
transfusions are are important or
critical and they still give you all
these other things that give you glucose
they give you
they give you iron they give you all
these other things
leanne i had a huge blood draw in
december and then crashed
in a big way in february two rounds of
the advance 369 saved me thank you
anthony see
look how important the blood draw
information is
and if i wasn't censored and suppressed
okay where you know the platforms they
kick everybody off my platforms and it's
lucky i even have anybody on here now
any of you guys you're not just booted
off
like on ig everybody's just booted off
and
if it wasn't for the censorship you know
this stuff would get
out even faster to save more lives but
it's it's hard to get it
out into the world um so but the good
news is i
put some of that blood draw information
in the medical medium
new edition and that is going to be out
there millions of people are going to
have this in their hands so that's the
good news at least there's a way
freedom of the press there's a way to
get
you know that this freedom of speech in
the book to get it out
and they're not burning books yet so
they're not burning books yet they're
definitely
suppressing everybody in different ways
but they're not burning books yet so we
can still get the information out there
and you guys are
spreading and sharing the information
too i talk about blood donating blood
donations
in this episode okay so medical mean
podcast at apple podcast link is in the
description do
not miss this episode whatever you guys
do if you're new here
please listen to it okay it's at medical
even podcast at apple podcast
so i talk about pregnancy withdrawing
blood how to rebuild your blood i talk
about blood donations how to do it right
how to protect yourself if you must
donate and if that's what you want to do
i talk about how
how to do that how to protect yourself
which is important
christie moore michota's healing yes i
know i was
wondering though after the podcast we
lost our immune system when blood gets
taken
so in order sorry in other words we lose
our immune system
during our periods too right it's much
different
much different because you're not
bleeding as much blood in your period
and that's a natural process in life
having a needle go into your vein okay
and drawing out a large amount of blood
is not a natural process at all
so that's the difference okay because
your immune system floating around your
bloodstream
is doing its job right and your immune
system
that's in your reproductive system is
doing its job
but there's that's the natural process
you lose
some blood but you're losing more than
blood through your menstruation cycle
you're losing the lining of the uterus
the shedding of the lining of the uterus
you're losing that
okay there's also mucus that comes out
with the blood
and the fluid with the blood too
so it's not as much blood it's it's not
even a fraction of blood
and that's the difference okay and that
right there
also weakens the immune system of women
that's the other point too
so so menstruation is when
your immune system does drop so that's
what happens with women
their immune systems drop during
menstruation and then as it drops during
menstruation they get their acne back
they get their migraines back they get
symptoms
all this other thing that happens okay
and so um
80 of the immune system runs to the
reproductive system to protect the
reproductive system when you bleed
a little bit with your uh with your
cycle but you've got to listen to the
podcast i talk all about it
um but when you lose too much blood
during a cycle then it's a concern
why is it a concern why are the doctors
worried how come
when you're losing a lot of blood during
a menstruation cycle
right where it's abnormal and you're
like oh my god i'm just i'm i feel like
i'm hemorrhaging or something i'm losing
so much blood
and now the doctors are really worried
well guess what
they're not worried when they take 70
milliliters
80 milliliters 140 milliliters 240
300 milliliters that's 30 tubes 30 vials
of blood
300 milliliters they're not worried at
all taking out of you at all
you go donate blood they're going to
take 500 milliliters out they're not
worried at all
120 pound female chronically ill goes to
donate blood who doesn't feel that great
overall
she donates blood she loses a pint of
blood they're not worried there
no one's worried but the minute your
cycle you're starting to lose a little
too much what they're like
scared crap the doctor's like oh my god
we have to you're losing some blood
but they don't care when they draw it
all out if you see the difference these
are just
these are just some of the difference dr
faun md he's not saying to not
do blood tests he says let them take
less
exactly and if you hear the podcast
you'll know why and how
it's important to know i'm not saying
don't get a blood test but the system's
broken
and i'll give you a little demonstration
with the white blood cell
when we tap into those veins okay
we tap into those veins we're taking
your white count your red count we're
taking your cbc
cbc see you later bye cbc
bye gone we take your cbc and that's
what happens here
okay if you're wondering why i have all
the goodies here i got a chocolate chip
cookie here i got a half a hard-boiled
egg
i got a chicken piece of chicken and i
got an
ice cream on a stick we're going to talk
about that in a second
um so you lose your immune system when
you get those big blood draws
and the blood lab doesn't even use a
fraction of that
just not even a frat i mean such a small
amount
you throw it all away or it goes off
somewhere else on the black market
so and our immune system doesn't build
fast it doesn't build fast it doesn't
build back in one day
doesn't build back in three days when
you get a blood draw even five
vials a blood draw you're waiting weeks
to get your immune system back
so then if you've got some kind of viral
issue or some kind of
streptococcus bacteria if you've got a
little bit of that
some for some reason right a little bit
of strep bacteria in your system to say
is why i have the dummy with me say you
got chronic sinusitis
so chronic sinusitis well that's
streptococcus bacteria
lodged in your sinus cavities causes
scar tissue get people get surgeries
because of it they don't know it's
strapped but that's what it is
so you got your streptococcus bacteria
lodged in the sinus cavities well what
happens is your immune system
okay your immune system's keeping
everything at bay
keeping everything good right and you
start removing your immune system
now you're set up for a new
streptococcus infection and now you've
got a bad sinus infection three weeks
later but don't know why
that's just one example immune system
doesn't rebuild in just a week
it could take four to six weeks it could
take three to six months depending on
variables who you are
what kind of condition you're in if you
already have a weakened immune system
and if you've got some fibro and some ms
and you've got
eczema psoriasis and you got ra and i
talk all about this in the podcast and
guess what
you're already dealing with a weakened
immune system that you have to fix and
heal and do all the right stuff and
learn
talk about the new edition check it out
okay
and sonja i recently had a bone marrow
transplant
and have statistics that show my blood
building through my weekly draws this
includes wbcs neutrophils platelets bone
marrow will replace
lost blood because it desires
homeostasis all blood cells have
lifespan and are constantly being
replaced with new young healthy vibrant
cells
okay so
also i knew what each tube was being
drawn for which tests
with which color tube to the
phlebotomist only fills them half full
i like celery juice and don't trust big
pharma but this is
not but this but this take is not it
um a couple things first of all just so
you know
right so when someone has cancer okay
and they're getting blood draws
constantly losing their white count
that attacks cancer cells and
the bone marrow issue that you're taking
the bone marrow with producing like
often replenishing your blood so quickly
is not true
even science research will tell you when
you donate blood
you're four to six six weeks out for
your red count to come back
just letting you know you're four to six
weeks at least
so science and research like the head of
science and research
okay dictates that with a blood donation
you're four to six weeks out of getting
your red blood cells back up to par
just giving you that one right there to
begin with
that's at least four to six weeks okay
of course you're gonna get white blood
cells popping out of your spleen
immediately that were stored in your
spleen right when you
get a right when you get um any kind of
procedure
or blood drawn or um
or anything like that okay so but the
thing is is that
your bone marrow has to go on overload
to produce those cells
and it doesn't produce them all
perfectly
because you have stored cells in certain
places right you have them stored in
your spleen
you have them stored in other areas of
the body and those are your reserves
now you're lucky if you're seeing
anything like that
but then you got somebody with lyme
disease and they're getting their blood
draws
okay and they're getting worse and worse
and worse
and neurological symptoms are getting
worse and worse and worse
and you're getting somebody with c with
with me cfs and their symptoms are
getting worse and worse as they're
taking seven vials 14 vials
28 vials 30 vials okay and their
symptoms are getting worse and worse and
worse finally they're bedridden
because their immune system has been
removed and
they're low-grade viral infections that
give them all their different symptoms
aches and pains tingles
numbness fatigue twitches spasms burning
skin
brain fog eye floaters vertigo
is getting worse worse worse worse okay
and people like that they can lose
everything
okay you should listen to the podcast
episode to hear all the information
really important to know but don't
assume
that our our bone marrow just replaces
it all every time we draw it out
um that's not true it's just not true
it's not
because each person has a different
story so
most people with autoimmune have a
weakened immune system already so what
does that mean
weakened immune system because they're
already diagnosed with an autoimmune
condition
and if they already have a weakened
immune system that means we have a bone
marrow issue to some degree
where we're not producing what we need
to
need to produce on the level we need to
produce to keep up with what's happening
inside the body so you got to keep that
in mind
so anybody with any kind of autoimmune
condition at all
that happens jim says in my experience
if the blood is dark purple
almost black it would not hurt to lose a
couple few tubes
of dirty blood refreshed with clear
eating habits
agree not good to draw blood with
cancerous conditions
fasting can save you your life as long
as the cancer
is not too advanced um
so first of all they're not doing two
vials jim so
it's not doing two vials that's not
usually what happens
you get sick you don't feel good it's
five vials you get sick you don't feel
good at seven vials
get sick you don't feel good it's 14
vials then you're at now you're at a
specialist and it's 20 vials
that specialist after you're burnt out
that specialist and that specialist
burnt out you six months later
after you've already dumped about 20
vials three times with that specialist
now you're off to a new specialist but
he doesn't care about all the blood work
you just had so he's going to pull
another 20 vials
and another 28 vials and another 40
vials okay
this is killing women this is killing
women
so what happens is they'll draw 20 40
vials out of a 120 pound female
they'll sin they'll draw the same amount
of blood out of a 250 pound
male okay so you got a female that's
sick with chronic illness
could barely function severe chronic
fatigue 122 pounds
and they'll draw 30 tubes out of her and
you've got a 220 pound male
and they'll draw 32 30 tubes out of him
and so you know there's there's a lot of
problems that need to address it's not
as simple as how you got some dark
you got some dark blood it'd be good to
draw it a couple of vials
fresh blood coming in the reason why
it's dark is because
the liver is toxic number one and the
blood is dehydrated
that's why so if your blood comes out
dark purple
dark dark dark color red really dark
that is the chronic dehydration so
just giving you that information so you
can protect yourself
all on its own it's chronic dehydration
and a dirty liver
you can pull out that blood all you want
fresh blood just doesn't come in and
you're all fine
your liver is toxic stagnant sluggish
and dirty and your blood's dehydrated so
you got to go into hydration and then
you gotta go cleaning up the liver and
fasting doesn't fix everything
it doesn't uh and there's a big history
to that
okay and uh fasting doesn't fix
everything
i've seen fasting hurt people too it's
not just fix
them deplete them and hurt them so i've
seen
fasting do that to people you know
deplete them
they lose all their neurotransmitters
all their electrolytes
they lose it all and i never recommend
for
central nervous system conditions like
neurological symptoms for people to fast
long at all so
any kind of fasting long term while
you're dealing with neurological
symptoms
can be disastrous and dangerous so
there's a lot of
a lot of problems with a lot of that
stuff it's like
yeah there is something you said about
fasting emergency
cases small amounts of time but it's
another things that
you're fasting long term and you just
don't understand how the body works it's
a whole other thing too all on its own
look i'm not saying that you don't have
some good info somewhere that's not it
but we're talking 35 years experiencing
i've seen everybody fast under the sun
i've done long-term water fast because i
wanted to do it spiritually
okay so i've done really long-term water
fasting
really long-term water fasting not
because of a condition
because spiritually doing it okay and i
did that
okay but i was strong as an ox when i
so when i did long-term water fasting
for fun
i did it while strong as an ox
and not only strong as an ox for
spiritual reasons
but i would i when it comes down to
people they got neurological symptoms
they got cfs
they got bad fibro they got multiple
sclerosis they got lupus they got aches
and pains they got other problems
that are not just that they got
they got depression anxiety long-term
fasting
not not good little short clips here and
there one day
but doing it right two days doing it
right if there's a really good reason
for
it um but anyway
it's all good stuff so uh
okay you guys i'm talking about the
medical media podcast apple podcast
check out that episode
um we're gonna talk about some other
things really quick right here too so
um let's go into that so here's the
here's how it works okay your immune
system is not all in your gut
just we got to clear that up right now
okay because that's the new thing
missed information that's trendy that's
always
out there because money is behind it you
just gotta know every single trend
out there that gets out there and it's
pounding its way out there like your
immune system is all in your gut is only
done
or sold or propelled by gut health
companies and probiotic companies and
that's how they do it
and they find some pseudoscience in
order to do that pseudoscience is just
science they pay for
to back up their little claim that this
product is good for them
and then they go with a theory and they
don't even have the science to prove it
and you just go with a theory the immune
system is all
and you're good you say well there's
trillions of microorganisms in the gut
so if there's trillions of
microorganisms in the intestinal tract
and the colon
small intestinal tract and there's
trillions of microorganisms
then we that's that's where the immune
system is but that's not your immune
system
in fact far from it okay your immune
system is
first of all in your bloodstream that's
your number one place so when you get
your blood draw
you lose your number one most important
immune system now why is it in the
bloodstream
it's in the bloodstream to protect what
right here it's in the bloodstream to
protect your
brain okay that's why that's why your
immune system's in your bloodstream
it's to protect your brain critical this
is why
someone you hear about this all the time
i hear about this all the time too do
you hear about this i got to tell you
jane says people go seek someone that
has proper credentials like a doctor of
an acupuncture a chinese medicine
functional medicine practitioner and a
doctor of natural naturopathy
not this person who has no medical
background or extensive training in
nutrition
pathology anatomy you yeah you think
you're probably really smart to say that
too i bet huh
it's really great you see the
cardiologist that's on this book right
here this number one new york times
bestselling book
do you see that cardiologist that's on
here and the other doctors that are
actually in the books do you see that
there's clinics there's doctors all
around the world using the medical being
books did you know science and research
plagiarizes the information out of these
books it was published here first
fact i don't know if you like that
science research has taken all the
information from the medical medium
books
uh how do you feel about that right
that's that's another thing too plus 35
years experience
and guess what that's really funny
because
guess who's come to me all these years
the most powerful people in the world
okay because they went to 50 doctors
they had
you know hundreds of millions of dollars
they couldn't get answers from their
doctors the best specialists they flew
around the world to see
but they had to come to me for answers
huh
really interesting real really
interesting
and that's just one thing all on its own
plus there's millions of healing stories
around the world of people getting their
lives back
huh it's another one too think about it
and um but i i look i respect what
you're saying okay you're saying hey
don't listen to this guy listen to a
doctor okay tell that to someone who's
chronically ill and they've seen 10
doctors
20 doctors 10 neurologists specialists
and they don't have answers
but medical medium information in books
actually reversed their condition and
healed them you know
yeah so there you go jennifer said oh my
god i just listened to the podcast wow
incredible incredible um
so anyway but um look haters
like to hate um and it's okay
what are you gonna do okay you guys so
here's the thing
but you know what's funny we know what
haters will do they'll take medical
medium information and we'll use it
they'll use it
watch watch the hater actually be
concerned about how much blood is drawn
at her next
blood draw watch that watch how when
they're taking seven tubes or 14
tubes and she's getting the blood drawn
from her watch
how that hater jane watch how she's like
um
can you guys do like half files um i
think you're taking too much blood here
watch her take medical medium
information and then
try to piss on medical medium as she's
taken as she's taking the information
that's what people do
pressing prince good to see you right
there uh pressing prince if skeptics
just really sat back and listened to all
your info
i'm sure they would notice how much
sense you really make you are amazing
and you have so many people that love
everything you share and have truly
made a seal pressing prince thanks so
much pretty cool
amy mm healed me doctors did not
i mean but you know what happens that
person
never got sick enough right so that's
how it works you guys
that's how it works they never got sick
enough they haven't they probably just
got a little sick
and then they went to a couple of
functional medicine doctors that gave
them some tips
and some things that were probably
partly on them because functional
medicine uses medical mean
information now they never did before
the publications of the books
but they use it now right and so a lot
of different practitioners and doctors
they use mm info
so they're probably just skating by okay
they don't need to go too
far through healing they don't have to
really take it too seriously
because they're not really that sick and
but if they get
really sick down the road they'll be
back here you know spirit of compassion
told me
a long time ago when i was young that
you know what even the skeptics still
have to try to
find the truth and the answers in the
end if they get sick enough
and they're stuck on mattress island
then they have to just swallow their
pride
realize science totally screwed them
over and didn't have the answers
and then they have to find their way so
yeah
look anyway let's talk about this a
little bit more you guys
so your your immune system is in your
blood oh
so wait a minute that's interesting
because um
most of your immune system is in your
blood but i guess you'll just
go trust someone some other person
because how can you trust me
you'll trust some other person that
doesn't know your immune system is in
your blood that's interesting right
this is unbelievable you'll trust
somebody that doesn't even have a clue
let's just draw lots of blood out of you
every single month
let's drain you dry and blood let you
anyway the immune system's in your blood
and there's a reason for that
and it goes through all the different
blood vessels to protect your heart so
that's another thing too
so that's your little heart right there
okay
and in those blood vessels and those
tiny arteries
blood vessels right you have your immune
system
it's critical that's what protects you
from getting blood
poisoning because that's why your immune
system
system is mostly in your blood to stop
you from getting sepsis to stop you from
getting
blood poisoning that's the key that's
another really important part right
there so
um another thing too blood going through
your heart
has to has to have a strong immune
system
so you don't get infected valves so you
don't get infections to the heart
so the reason why our immune system is
in in our bloodstream
ninety percent of it the most majority
of our immune system is in our
bloodstream is so you don't get an
infection in your heart
and you don't get an infection in your
brain two places that you
have to know that are so important right
there okay and then
the second most important place your
immune system is
after that is your liver so there you go
see your liver
that's the second most important spot as
your liver and that's where the immune
system is
okay the second most important spot your
immune system is all right
third most important spot is your
lymphatic system but that's a third
okay second is your liver and i'll talk
about the lymphatic system for a second
to you guys your lymphatic system is
only as good as your liver
keep that in mind all right so and it's
only a small amount
of lymphocytes in your lymphatic system
so that's not the majority of your
immune system
and but what happens is that the liver
is has to stay healthy for your
lymphatic system to be healthy so when
everybody's trying to cleanse their
lymphatic system what they're really
doing
by accident sometimes some of those
different things they do
is it's oh hey i want a juice hey i want
to do some juicing now
and try to cleanse my lymphatic system
when they don't get it their juicing
is helping to cleanse their liver and
that's how you get a lymphatic system
more healthy it
has to be the liver because you can't
just you can do all the lymphatic work
you want you can get all the lymph
massage
you can get all the d you can do
everything you can possibly do you can
be a runner
okay and you can like i love to run you
can be like a runner
and that's what you do you run 15 miles
a day
you're like okay just ran 15 20 miles
i'm good
i got my lymphatic system moving because
i'm exercising but if your liver's
dirty your lymphatic system never cleans
up does it matter if you're a runner
does it matter if you're an athlete
doesn't matter if you work out every day
if you don't
keep the liver clean your lymphatic
system can never
clean it can never get cleaned up
lymphatic system is the second blood
filter in the blood lymph filter after
the liver so the first one is the liver
after that it's the lymphatic system so
everybody's like oh my lymphatic system
is the most important thing you know
it's all lymph lymph actually no
no it's not it's liver liver liver
that's your filter when that filter gets
dirty your lymphatic system
is just trashed that's how it works you
can't keep up with that lymphatic system
ever
unless the liver is addressed so that's
important too so
you can be doing like all the lymphatic
stuff you want but when you're eating
like too much
like chicken and cookies because
chicken's too high in fat
when you're having your ice cream bars
you're needing too many eggs you're
having your eggs right
when you're eating things that feed bugs
and feed pathogens
okay and they clog up the liver too and
you get a lot of different exposures to
the liver so you got like
air fresheners you're breathing in goes
right into the liver scented candles
right into the liver
right you know whatever it is you just
absorbs right into the liver
different chemicals different toxins
cleaners all that difference of clones
perfumes right goes right into the liver
and so when you have that that perfume
you're spraying that perfume the minute
you breathe it in ends up in the liver
first that's where it will end up
you'll end up in your mouth you'll
swallow it goes down into your digestive
system then right up the
paddock portal highway highway right
into the liver
and so what the critical thing to
understand is
is that there's all the lymphatic hubbub
because
everybody's trying to sell some kind of
lymphatic thing too so it's like gut
lymphatic gut guts everything immune
systems in your gut
lymphatic immune system is not in your
gut you can be 85 years old
you know anybody that's like 85 or 80 i
know people do you know anybody that's
90 and they just eat whatever i know
people
have eaten whatever they want pizza ice
cream every day
anything they want right they just eat
it
and they're eating it every day and
they're 80 years old and their gut's a
mess i know people that eat chocolate
cake every day with lard
all kinds of soft drinks drink wine
champagne every day
they're out playing tennis their their
gut is
trash their gut is filled with every bad
microorganism that's
feeding off of all that crap and garbage
and the alcohol and everything
right you guys and then and then but
they're not sick
and you get somebody you get somebody
that's on this clean keto diet
somebody's on this clean vegan diet
clean
plant-based diet you get somebody's 24
years old
and they're on this clean diet they're
staying away from bread they're staying
away from
and they're bedridden right you got
somebody who's 45 years old 55 years old
they're playing tennis they're filling
themselves up with lard and chocolate
cake while they're playing tennis
and they're filling themselves up all
with all this garbage and junk
and they're fine they're on the tennis
court nothing wrong with them
you know hey party everything's good
they can drink champagne
they can do anything one he's got these
22 year olds for 24 year olds 26 year
olds they can't they never even finished
university finished college
they were so sick they had to just go
home to mom and dad
and they had to lay in bed and they had
to see 20 doctors and specialists and
then what happened they were blood
leaded
then they were bloodletted okay well
honey you've got to go see this new
doctor
and then let's draw another 18 tubes
another
16 tubes right right and they're then
they put them on this no sugar diet they
put them on these somewhat healthy diets
to get rid of processed foods
but this 55 year old right is playing
tennis
chucking down chocolate cake doing
tequila shots at night
with her his friends guts a mess filled
with all kinds of crap you think there's
good microorganisms in that gut of that
person no what it is is they don't
happen to have a virus
or a pathogen or the right kind of strap
or hhv-6 hhv-7 simplexes
or they don't have enough viruses
shingles ebv
wreaking enough havoc yet in their life
and a 22 year old can be loaded with
epstein barr and it's totally taking her
him down
boom down and they could be on a clean
diet unless they know what to do unless
they know
how to clean it up unless they know how
to take care of themselves and
and and know what protocols to use you
know
and know how it works mm is just not
about
some celery juice it's not just about
food it's about
important protocols you know it's about
the right kind of vitamin c that's the
micro see right there that i use
not sponsored it's about having details
and knowing
how to use things you know and that's
important we can play gut health games
all we want but if we don't have the
right stuff
you know and then we get in trouble and
that that's what happens you know like
here's the cat's claw that's the vimergy
cat's claw right there
that that i love love the vimergy cats
club because for lyme disease
that's what i taught doctors that use
for the last 35 years it's cat's claw
and there wasn't a product like this out
at the time just wasn't a product like
this
good out there would have to get the
dried cat's claw i remember 25 years ago
i'd have the dried cat's call in my
office and doctors would be calling me
up be like for my patients do you have
any more of that dried cat's claw
tea do you have any more of that i'll be
like send it out to you i'll get it out
to you
and it's like but we didn't have
anything like this you know like the
vimergy
um it's important to know so that's
critical right there are the b12 energy
b12
so gut health is this blanket term right
now to sell
to sell products and then to lie to
people
you know it's like your immune system is
all in your gut it's a theory
it's not actual truth there's no truth
they haven't figured it out
scientifically
it's made up but it's made up for the
gut health companies you know
and meanwhile you can go on like the
merry-go-round and you're looking for
help and you're
you're at the next doctor and he's got
you off the wrong foods
he's got you you know doing different
things he's got you on gut health
products you might improve because he
gets you off of some gluten
and some dairy products or some
processed food
but then you know then you know you get
a little better because you're not
feet you're not feeding too many
pathogens
maybe the doctor gets you off of gluten
so now you're not
you're not you eat some gluten right
you're not eating gluten and you're not
feeding the bugs inside your gut
right you're not feeding the bugs inside
your body okay
that's another thing too you're not
feeding your shred for viruses jennifer
says now 50
had to eat better than everyone since 14
then how to drop out third semester in
college
did some shots during during
just to ease the mental pain finally two
years ago began to heal with you
you know you know that's amazing and
look i've been saying this for years
no one talks about all of the college
students
that never finish college nobody talks
about them
margaret valentine glad you're here no
one no one
no one talks about them thousands upon
thousands i remember when i used to see
people right
and doctors would send all their
patients to me and and
um needing help there were
just droves of college students
that never finished college not because
they didn't want to
they couldn't go out with their friends
anymore and drink they couldn't get
their studies done
they were all home in bed and
that's what it was it's still like that
now more than ever before
nobody talks about it right but someone
would come on here like a naysayer like
a hater like
when i just read that comment earlier
earlier and they'd be like don't listen
to him
listen to a doctor he's not a doctor
he's not a whatever never said it was a
doctor
and you know and and it's amazing though
right
that's somebody that doesn't know that
hundreds of
hundreds of thousands of college
students never finished college
and they saw every doctor under the sun
at 22 years old 20 years old 18 years
old 19 year old that's somebody that's
so disconnected
to what's really happening in the world
of chronic illness and people's
struggles in people's trials somebody's
so disconnected to say that
it's like it's just kind of funny when
you think about how disconnected they
are
christie my dad has been using cat's
claw and his
hip pain has subsided significantly yeah
the one thing i love about the cat's
claw the vimergy cats claw and
this is the one i recommend for my
family and friends i'm not sponsored
but it's just the best stuff ever and
this is the one for all that because
what happens is you'll get
viral symptoms out there right you'll
get like viral pain
viral nerve pain people with lyme
disease of all neurological pain
neurological symptoms from viruses right
i told you about that you guys
it's in the medical medium the lyme
disease chapter and the medical medium
new edition just so you know
most important book you can have in your
little book library at home right
um most important book and uh
so the catskill is critical for knocking
down books liz lindsey says oh yeah that
happened to me in high school got mono
and never recovered went to college but
dropped out because of chronic fatigue
the doctors and everyone thought i was
faking
lindsay i just want to tell you
something okay i understand
i really do and i can't tell you how
many students told me
over the years 35 years of this how
they they were told they were faking it
right people went through hell and back
but guess what
the media will never write a story about
it no one cares
it's happening every day now more than
ever
it's just you get sick and disappear
you're you're worthless that's what they
all feel like just get out of here go go
let's sweep you under the carpet what go
see a doctor you're not better yet
you're not better yet go to a doctor
what do you mean you're still dizzy
like what do you mean you're still dizzy
right it's like
um it's unbelievable what do you mean
you still got fatigue
what you didn't you didn't fix it
science knows everything go see a doctor
science says every answer there is
just go see a doctor get it fixed now
college student get it fixed now
university student
and it's happening by the thousands and
thousands now actually hundreds of
thousands and
it's happened all through the years and
no one knows
no one's held accountable no one cares
it's sick and this is part of how the
system's totally broken
so broken um jill says how much cat's
claw should we take i got dosages in the
book
ask your doctor take it to your book
that's your doctor um
what do i do it's another story like me
personally
i don't have anything to worry about i'm
not sick
but i take it because i can you know
it's like
when you know when you know too much
about
what's going on you know too much about
everything i mean i might end up in a
public bathroom somewhere
right where it's like you just you're
just stuck out and you're
out somewhere and you're with some
friends or some family and you're like
well
nature calls man you know now you're in
a public bathroom
anyway so i just take you know i i
always take these things but
what i do is i take two dropper fulls of
cats call a day personally
i that's what i take every day i just
take two two dropper fulls
sometimes i'll take a break for a little
while um
april says cat's claw makes my joints
hurt
um well did you ever have joint pain
before or that's the
only time so no joint pain no body pain
joints never hurt at all ever i just
want you to be your own detective right
so i'm just that's why i'm just
mentioning this right um
so nothing ever hurt before and then you
took the cat's claw and all sent your
joints hurt
or do your joints hurt periodically
because you already have a problem and
that's why you're taking cat's claw or
trying to find the next
new thing to help you heal and all that
just really important question right
there
the other thing is did it have alcohol
in it
was it a bad brand what did it have
citric acid in it did it have
additives in it there's a ton of bad
ones a ton of terrible ones
if it is a good one right if it is a
good one
it also kills bugs so if you're somebody
already with jim joint pain and with
some issues and what fatigue and all
these other things and you take the
good one what i would do if it was me
ask your doctor what he wants to do and
listen to him
but if it was me you know i would do
smaller dosage
personally smaller dosage and
that's what i would do of the best one
there is and that's what i would do
but ask your doctor what's great for you
um
so yeah so anyway you guys give you a
rundown if you just got on here let's
talk a little bit i got my celery juice
right here do you guys mind
are you okay with this you okay with
this so
i just want to take a sip my throat's
getting dry
i love that celery juice
so good so good
um when you drink your celery juice
where can i get the cat's claw
v is in victor i am as in mary ergy
dot com they got the best supplements
there are
hands down in the world that in my
opinion from everything that i've
researched
with supplement companies what they do
talking to all the different
owners of supplement companies i've
talked to almost every owner of
supplement companies because
i want to know what you really do so
then i can recommend it to
people i care about um so anyway
and i have a lot of supplement questions
in the books too there's the new edition
supplement answers for questions so
give you let's give you a quick rundown
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
if you guys just came on don't miss the
opportunity
of listening to the blood draw
bloodletting vampirism
episode whatever you do i'm casey cat's
call my naturopath
said it was all compromised so he says
don't get it
um you know you know it's hard
it's it's it's hardware i get it there's
a lot of
a lot of these dudes right they're in
health
and they're in a bubble they're in a
bubble
and i don't blame them for being in a
bubble where they don't know about
how many lives were saved because of
cat's claw about the
40 years of lives that were trashed and
thrown away with lyme disease and
how many women lost their lives with
lyme disease and other conditions and
how cats claw when it when it got
to people it saved their life
and and still still does right
but i'm not i'm not shaming the dude
and i'm not disrespecting the dude
it's just i know that a lot of dudes a
lot of naturopaths that reach out to me
a lot of different doctors that reach
out to me they they'll even say many of
them like look i've been in a bubble i
see my patients all day long but i don't
know what happened out there in the
world i don't know what's going on and
i don't know what to trust on the
internet and i'm too busy in my own
practice to know what's going on out
there
and they miss they miss the boat ride
for their patients
so they'll say to a patient hey cat's
claws are all bad out there
don't get any cat's claw and but they
don't even know what the cat's claw has
done for people or what the hell
people have been through and how it's
reversed neurological conditions for
people and
i don't blame the dude at all or
anything
and i just know that so many guys they
live in a bubble and i totally get it
but listen to your doctor if he says
don't do cat's claw
don't do it okay listen to your doctor
and don't do the cat's claw
that's what i recommend austin i got in
a big argument with my wife
about the mm info and she doesn't buy it
i do it's changed my life it's not an
unusual thing to happen austin so let me
just
first of all i'm sorry i'm sorry if i
caused any trouble
poor guy you don't want to get into a
fight with your wife
and there's nothing worse right so um
so um just know that i'm sorry for uh
being a wedge in between but i'm proud
of you
for doing the information truly i'm
proud okay
and uh and i want you to heal and i want
you to know that there's
just like the blood draw information
medical medium information
is always ahead of everybody else and i
know you know this just
but it's ahead of everybody else that's
why i'm able to drop
bomb after bomb so medical medium taught
the world that epstein-barr was behind
the chronic illness today okay and
shingles behind chronic illness today
and now and no one knew knew that no one
knew
you guys they only thought ebv was mono
and it went away
and that was it okay reactivation of
epstein-barr
causing chronic illness today medical
medium reactivation of fc bar
causing the plague to last longer
medical medium just that's just some
things
epstein-barr causing hashimoto's they
found a link to it
medical medium published first so it's
i'm always ahead of the curve
the information is never contradicted
it's never proven wrong
and only proven right it just is
if i don't talk about it no who is
i gotta like let you guys know like the
accomplishments of medical medium
information
um so
mark o'neil my clients are taking cat's
claw
and healing it's real absolutely
absolutely so that's the bemurgy cat's
claw that's the one
that um i recommend to my family and
friends people always want to know what
do you recommend to your family and
friends right
there's a lot of people on curcumin okay
so i'm always like
i tell a family member what are you
doing with that curcumin like that one
there that doesn't have the quality in
it that doesn't have what's supposed to
be in it and
and then i give them the rundown and
everything and i say no that's the
curcumin so it's like
it's always like i'm telling family and
friends about the energy supplements
um
listen to the beginning here and i talk
about iron a little bit so listen to the
beginning of this
this uh live youtube live facebook guys
i like doing it live
um i've been recommended never to do
anything live i've been recommended to
just you know
candy coat what is it can't uh
candy coat everything or something you
know recommend like everybody else does
on youtube
they don't do it live they just always
always like
cookie cut it is that it they cookie cut
it and you know
you're a number one year 10 times best
seller anthony mr william you should
never do a live performance
mia the very end of your blood draw
podcast blew my mind
it's it's mind-blowing it really is
thank you for listening
um diana medical medium protocols got me
of 10 years of synthroid got me off 10
years of synthroid
after a thyroidectomy incredible
incredible diana incredible
really is and that that means everything
it means everything it really does it
really does
but yeah you guys leave a couple little
tidbits
a couple more little tidbits um me too
clp me too
me too my husband fights with me about
it
[Laughter]
you guys i'm really sorry i really am
seriously
but like i always say though i'm at your
service i'm at your service
monica what's the brand name for the
cat's claw it's vimergy it's v
is in victor i m as in mary e
r g y it's the best cats called there is
hands down out there in the world
there's a whole bunch of reasons why
someday i'll do a live on
supplementation that i take with my
family my
uh loved ones that i recommend um
but um but yeah and and talk about the
details but yeah it's of emergency cats
club
by far hands down um that
it's just if it's the best it's the best
i don't know what to say it just
is anyway um and for so many cool
reasons
so you guys podcast listen to the blood
draw podcast
share it with everybody you know please
so they can heal um i'm heading off to
instagram and tick tock okay
you guys you guys are the fun crowd okay
you're the fun crowd where i could be
relaxed
and talk to you guys on tick tock
and instagram i start throwing mud
i start throwing i don't know all i know
did you see what happened on tick tock
and instagram where i had i had to do
the dog imitation
did you guys see that where i had to do
the dog imitation because
you know science has always got us like
right waiting like a dog waiting for a
bone did you see that
i'm hoping i stay calm on instagram and
tick tock today
but i doubt that will happen all right
you guys
because it's a different crowd they're
the they're the crowd that
like to agitate where's your science
who are you he's not a doctor where
[Laughter]
are you guys uh there are so many haters
on these platforms yep
elizabeth all right you guys i love you
i'm heading off to tick-tock in ig in
just a few minutes i'm gonna drink a
little celery juice
clean up this mess make a new mess i
love you guys