hello I'm Anthony William thank you for
joining the
webinar and being here this is such an
amazing time and I'm deeply honored
you're here hyperthyroidism
hypothyroidism
Hashimoto this is going to be a fun one
we're going to talk about a lot of
different things all around that you
should have your book by now if you
pre-ordered it you should have it by now
this is an unbelievable time I am so
excited I am so excited
if you uh read it more than once read it
more than
once um because there's there's a lot of
hidden little jewels and gems in there H
little diamonds that are in there and
sometimes you know if you're you know if
you're you hey you might get distracted
with your phone or something else why
you're in the middle of the book and
skip over a part that's so critical or
important and not realize it it it's so
easy to happen that way cuz we live in a
world of distraction So reading it again
you might all of a sudden hit that spot
and be like whoa wait a minute what or a
couple of different spots so I don't
want you to lose anything that's in
there um so uh hopefully some of you
have started reading it already and
maybe you guys haven't but I'm excited I
can't wait for you to dive into it we're
going to be talking about a lot of great
stuff here like I said before I'm
honored that you're with me on this
webinar right here um it's an important
webinar it's an important time and you
know knowing the truth about
something um is that powerful is truly
that powerful and it means it means a
lot of freedom it means a lot of freedom
you know not every truth has Freedom
attached to it you know you've heard the
saying oh there's still okay who's truth
this truth that truth what is a truth is
it not everybody claims the truth and um
but what happens is is that the reason
why truth is so confusing in so many
different ways is because truth is
backed by things that makes
it kind of a a false truth so truth gets
backed by things it gets backed by
medical funding you know with lots of
strings attached it gets backed by
internal Kickbacks and persuaded belief
systems and private panels of
influencers and health field pay offs it
gets backed by trendy traps and
different interest groups it gets backed
by things and that's why it's could be
truthful some of it out there in the
world of Internet information about
thyroid or books or experts working on
it but there could be pieces in there
missing there could be pieces that are
skewed like the thumb on the scale
because it has stuff attached to it the
information in here doesn't have any
contamination attached to it so the
information you have in front of you is
clean it's clean it's not attached to
something that's conditional something
that's conditional that might have
altered it or made it just right so it
fits into the world
today that's not how it should be you
need to know the truth about your health
you need to know the truth about your
thyroid you need to learn these things
it's so important to learn these things
it is so important to know
what the truth really is with healing
and your thyroid in general with
anything and so that information here
comes from a pure place untampered with
Place Advanced Clean Source a higher
source and that's what the information
is in here and that's what it is you
know painstakingly I took the
information down from my source um day
in day out day in and day out and made
sure it was in there just the way my
source wanted it to be and um and so
this doesn't have the thumb scale on it
this doesn't have the dollars behind it
this doesn't have things that make make
it and shape it into something that fits
just right so that all the interest
groups out there in the medical Fields
both conventional and alternative are
happy no that's not what this is about
this is about making you happy this is
about meaning making you better not just
not about making you happy making you
better make giving you that freedom a
false happiness this is the freedom that
we
need and um and to and to be a part of
it together blows me away to be a part
of it together blows me away seriously
it really does so we're talking about
Hashimoto today we're talking about
Hashimoto we're talking about
hyperthyroidism we're talking about
hypothyroidism we're just talking about
we're going to just Bop around and talk
about a lot of different things there's
cool stuff going on with all of it um
I'm going to start a little bit with I
think I'll start a little bit with
history a little bit with history just
about Hashimoto in general you know when
you get diagnosed with
Hashimoto you should think okay well I
have something here meaning meaning
science and research is there they're
there they know they get it Hashimoto
science and
research there's nothing scientific or
research about Hashimoto yet yet I'm
just going to tell you right now that's
what one of the saddest parts of it all
is first of all it's discovered back in
the early 1900s how by a physician
putting his hand on a patient's throat
and feeling that there might have been
some
inflammation and that's with thyroiditis
was that was the birth of thyroiditis
Hashimoto thyroiditis there it is that
was the birth of it that was the birth
of it and the only thing that's come out
of it since then the only thing that's
come out of it since then which is a
theory a
theory okay is the discovery of an
antibody discovery of an auto
antibody that Discovery okay but but not
knowing what Auto antibodies do you guys
not knowing what they do not having any
clue any idea aidea just
theoretically believing that an auto
antibody is creating inflammation and
attacking your thyroid that was just a
theory that was a theory because it was
the safest one to go to which backed
science and research the reason why it
backed science and
research it backed science and research
because it put the blame on you your
body that was the safe fault for science
and research is a perfect safe fault
because science of research never wants
to admit they're behind the times or
they're in a non-discovery Zone they
hate it they hate it they hate it they
hate feeling or knowing that the
billions of dollars and the trillions of
dollars that have gone into science and
research about anything they hate
knowing it hasn't amounted to
anything they hate that and so they have
to take theories and they have to make
them law law law of the land which only
hurts you law of the land that only
hurts you and that becomes false truth
that becomes false
truth that's what that becomes and then
it becomes law of the land a fake truth
a false truth becomes law of the
land so Hashimoto is this so this only
other thing that came out of Hashimoto
in science is there was this discovery
of of of a random Auto
antibody with no identification of what
it does or where it even goes where it
even goes what it
does nothing nothing just a
theory attached to it it must be why you
get
thyroiditis and that's how bad things
are that's how sad things are and that's
where we are with the most advanced in
in in in thyroid and somebody one of you
might be out there saying well no not
true there's all these triggers and all
this other stuff we're going to talk
about triggers
we're going to talk about
triggers but but and you'll see there's
a list of triggers actually that I put
in there you'll see it the list of
triggers but they're just triggers
they're not the cause they're just
triggers they're just triggers just like
anything just like any kind of
trigger just a trigger so so the theory
was the only thing that came next after
all that 10 and something years here we
we are what year is it now and look two
things came out of Hashimoto's
thyroiditis two things a guy feeling
somebody's thyroid which named it
Hashimoto's
thyroiditis and a guy 50 years later a
guy 50 years later a doctor 50 years
later finding an auto antibody but not
having a clue to what it does so it was
a madeup
theory compounded
that was basically well this is probably
what it's doing let's do this it's the
safest way out let's create the
autoimmune fallacy the autoimmune Theory
the autoimmune theory of your body
destroying itself cuz you know why it it
sets it protects science and research
till the cows come home till the cows
come home it protects and protects and
protects and protects like you don't
even know because it's your fault that's
your body being faulty and since they
still don't have answers to what causes
anything it becomes your genes now and
you'll see a little genan section in
this book read that read that baby like
three four times that Gene
section you have to Deb brainwash
yourself it's so critical it's so
critical to Healing it's so critical to
the conditioning that
occurs so this is an important step this
is an important
step right here where we are in history
right
now this information is an important
step in history right now this just
isn't just a book you
know is isn't a book to do anything like
further my career or anything like that
it's not that's not what it is you know
it's a funny thing someone even said to
me ah you
authors this isn't a memoir this isn't
you know yeah I'd love to do something
silly like uh a whole book on on the
medical medium starting from when I was
birthed to to now and in a whole you
know level of the painstaking crap I've
gone through my whole entire life
hearing Spirit it'd be a fun book
meaning to
read it would just you know further my
career on that way
and that's not what these books are
about I put a little touch the origins
of of of me in the first
book but what it's about is getting you
the truth and the information that's all
I care about I I'm not going to be able
to cover the whole book in this webinar
but we're going to cover what we can but
I had I have to give you the basis of
the understanding of the
two the two discoveries is all we have
for thyroid meaning the two discoveries
that's signs and research have that
everybody's holding on to literally like
it's like it's
everything a mystery Auto antibody that
no one knows what's going on or what
it's doing putting the blame on you that
your body's attacking itself and
destroying itself and destroying the
thyroid and at the same time the
discovery of hasimoto to begin with some
guy some guy felt a swollen thyroid back
in the early
1900s and let me tell you something I do
respect and appreciate both of those
very
things as much as I sound like I'm
talking down about it I'm talking down
about the fact that it becomes law and
nobody just even has a clue or debates
it or understands any of it nobody in
the professional world of medicine or
anything and just move just keep on
moving
forward and then you don't get the
answers you need you don't get the truth
you don't you don't get any of that
we're going to talk about Epstein bar a
little bit Epstein bar gets into the
thyroid and that's what causes Hashimoto
we're going to go into it a little
deeper today but you'll see the new
experts that recently took information
from book one the origins you know book
one medical medium they took information
because spirit and I published how it
works with Epstein bar and the thyroid
and everything like that and they took
it and they sprinkled it on their
websites and they sprinkled it in and
out of their their other kind of books
now thyroid books sprinkle it in and out
because they don't want to be left out
but they call it a trigger because they
just don't trust in the fact of what's
going on because they're so married to
the laws the two laws a guy in 1950 in
the 1950s that found an auto antibody
but doesn't know what's going on so the
theory became it's your body attacking
itself and then of course the guy
Hashimoto felt the thyroid and felt it
was swollen they don't want to leave
these
laws but that doesn't really protect you
sure you could clean up the diet maybe
get your numbers a little better on the
thyroid but that's not the answer either
entirely this is serious stuff we're
talking about this is serious stuff this
is no
joke this is no
joke
so um by the way you
know have your tea have your herbal
whatever you need I got mine right here
because we're going to go deeper into
this and we got we got a lot of time
we're going to be doing this so I'm
going to be sipping some tea along the
way being this is live it's uh you know
might get a little dry throat from
talking so much but thank you for just
listening and holding on tight fasten
the seat belts is what I'm saying if
you've already done that because already
you should have the seat belt fastened
for just what we're talking about just
what we've been talking
about we should already have them
fastened all right so talk a little bit
about the
history of hashimotos the swollen
thyroid now
originally in the 17 1800s late 1700s
early 1800s originally right around that
time there was there was a goer
developing this was from iodine
deficiencies in certain areas of the
world goers and that was from a real
true 100% you know iodine
deficiency that was different than the
thyroiditis always different than the
thyroiditis that was creeping up come
around the turn of the
century right around the late 1800s all
these food experiments were happening
that not even people know when they know
about the Green Revolution and they know
about all that kind of stuff that was
going on in 1950s and how food was being
you know um monog grown and sprays were
being you know uh the whole thing with
pesticides and everything there were a
lot of different experiments pre
1900 all in the late you know in the
1860s 1870s 1880s tremendous experience
experiments I mean lots of them
tremendous amounts of them I mean due to
food they were dropping off canisters at
every Farm whether it's small Mom and
Pop to a little bit bigger to
everybody's backyard to farmers markets
dropping off cans of contaminated
materials to BL and put
on everybody's food that was growing in
that time 1860 1870 this is
completely hidden hidden in the in the
world because people can't handle this
they just don't want to they didn't want
to know then they don't want to know
now these were experimental insecticides
the
earliest these were experimental
antibiotics before the birth of
penicillin in the
1900s and it was experimented on our
food really broke our immune systems
down like never before in
history it also fed a harmless bug a
friendly little bug that was never
against us ever which was Epstein
bar Epstein bar it was a virus that
actually only worked in our favor it
destroyed enemies and it helped us it
was a friend not a
foe it was a friend a friend friend to
our immune system it protected us from
disease it was a bug actually it had not
a mean streak in it on any level but it
was tampered with and it was fed poison
and it was beaten
down and by 1900
it was getting into some thyroids was
creating the first
thyroiditis the first thyroiditis that
wasn't just an iodine
deficiency it wasn't just a
goer and it got into the thyroid isn't
this fun isn't this fun though I'm still
have I'm having too much fun I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm having too much fun I just
I waited for this this book to come out
I just waited we waited we waited okay
all right
so the virus became a little bit more
meaner developed a little bit
more of a meanor streak it wasn't in
everybody it wasn't spread it wasn't
spread to everybody it wasn't getting
too far there weren't a lot of
cases of this thyroiditis it was
rare But as time went on in the
1900s the virus changed and it mutated
ated and a few more strains developed
and by 1940 women discovered they had
symptoms for the first time in women's
history of the symptoms they had which
seemed like very which seemed very odd
and strange medical community was
completely baffled 100% had no idea what
the hell was going on there were
neurological symptoms there were the hot
flashes hot flashes in the first time
first time ever real recorded documented
hot
flashes up and down temperature
fluctuations
fevers aches and pains
fatigue hair falling out hair falling
out hair didn't fall out before then
hair didn't fall out before
then there were you know hair loss the
brittle nails all the different
symptoms and medical science was
completely
baffled and what was happening was the
epin bar virus was growing into
something different growing into
something
different and more cases of thyroiditis
were developing more thyroid problems
for women more cases of thyroiditis were
uh was
developing
and Medical Research Medical Science
didn't know what to do besides they were
already in the process in the late 40s
and mid mid to late 40s they were
already in the process of developing and
working on hormones they're working on
hormones they were in the process this
was the perfect perfect match ever
before in history the perfect match by
1950s so many women were literally
lining the doctor's
offices the ones that were
wealthy they were told they had a they
they they had a problem the ones that
weren't wealthy were told they were
insane that's how medicine worked back
then by the way that's how conventional
medicine worked this is an alternative
medicine alternative medicine was a
beautiful thing back then no doubt
conventional medicine was an absolutely
hot mess a complete disaster at this
point so when very wealthy rich women
came into the doctor's office the
doctors are like well you know you do
have something going on and now since
big Pharma gave us all these hormones
here let's let's make sure we apply
these because we think you have just
hormone problems and they were really
steroidal these hormones that they were
giving these women which led to some
suppression of some of the symptoms but
not a lot of suppression at all in fact
even worse symptoms in many to most
women at that point but it was
completely birthed the hormone movement
at that point of it's your hormones it's
your hormones women that were poor that
went to the doctor that got to the
doctor and they were on the lower class
scale at that time frame in history they
were told they were
nuts just hysterical crazy lying
bored so and um and maybe hormonal too
depending on who the doctor was so this
is what was going on in this time frame
medicine was was
disgusting and you know and so but what
was really happening was Epstein bar all
the women that were born in 1900 1905
1904 1894 1898
1910 by the 40s and 50s 1940s and 1950s
they were 40 years old 45 years old 50
years old so it seemed like it matched
the change of the of of
menopause so that's why the hormonal
thing just really kicked in as being the
the the the tell all for what these
symptoms were but before that women in
their 40s didn't experience that women
in their 50s didn't experience that
before that this is a firsttime thing in
history the change was never a painful
toxic kind of
thing meaning both emotionally mentally
historically but it was the Epstein bar
creating a whole new barrage of
symptoms and thyroid problems were more
common too more common which leads to
where we are today where the experts
today are like well the thyroid is
causing most of all this now yes and
you're going through a change and the
thyroid is causing most of these
problems now because it's all kind of
seeming like the same time frame but not
really because women now in their 20s
have thyroid problems 30s have in their
20s and early 30s teens have thyroid
problems so that's also kind of a
baffling aspect of it all but they're
just it's all just thrown into hey it's
autoimmune in the bodies attacking these
young women
early on the basis of that false Theory
to begin
with so right now today we're in a place
where Hashim Oto we think we have the
answers when we don't we do now what's
in your hand it's
there but we're still in Antiquity land
until we drop a the body's attacking
itself and going after the thyroid and
these Auto antibodies are there to
destroy the thyroid and if we can get
out of that land then we're out of
antiquity
land but we're not going to get out of
there because that married law is still
in is still going to impregnate and
still going to saturate every single
expert from here on out that's coming
out except you as an expert you it
won't you're getting the
truth you know when it says the truth in
the subtitle of the
book when it's anything medical medium
then it's the darn
truth you need to know the difference
between that and the truth you see and a
lot of other self- health books you need
to know the difference this is the
difference you're hearing it now you're
going to read it it's important to
understand this isn't me boasting this
is about taking Health seriously and
really getting better this is about
really making a difference with the
people around you you yourself if it's
just you yourself then that's that's
that's all I need if it's people around
you great that's wonderful it's people
around them wonderful if it's getting
the message out wonderful whatever it
is whatever it
is
Hashimoto is a stage of Epstein bar
after Epstein bar leaves the liver
Epstein bar leaves the liver and it
heads to the
thyroid and Hashimoto thyroiditis is a
stage hypothyroidism is a stage it's
just the same thing it's the virus
leaving the liver going into the thyroid
that's the Epstein
bar and the Hashimoto is a little bit
more heavy dut Beauty version where it's
not just keeping at a hypothyroid but
it's all the same a lot of people with
hypothyroid end up hashimotos later
because the thyroid was in the the the
thyroid was in the stage of the Epstein
bar sitting in there working on the
thyroid so over time it then
became seeable as far as antibodies
being pre present in the blood
work but that's also a lot of times you
can have Auto antibodies and it's not
even present in the blood works so you
can even have that with hypothyroid
doctor won't even know cuz blood tests
aren't aren't so easy to read which
you'll see there's a guest tests guest
test chapter in this in this book
thyroid guest tests talking about how
why and what why it's so difficult and
why a lot of doctors now and
practitioners are guessing and just
saying well you need to go on thyroid
medication you need to be on thyroid
medication even though your numbers look
good or they look borderline you'll see
why when you read that
chapter and so what is going on with the
auto
antibody well as you'll also read the
auto antibody is designed by your immune
system to go after only one thing a
virus it has tagged a virus it has
tagged a virus it has
found it's not going after thyroid
tissue the virus goes after thyroid
tissue the virus inflames the virus
itself inflames and this is not known
till this day it is not known yet in any
in any
place in any place where we got the
research of Science and we got the
experts it's just not known
yet will they ever learn down the road
it depends because breaking the
autoimmune Theory means admitting you
don't science of research doesn't know
what's wrong with their patients yet it
admits that and that it's not the
patient's fault and it's not your body
attacking itself and that's not going to
be something easily admitt ever by the
medical research department or in even
experts that put out books because it it
it it it it outdates their book
instantly in the thyroid
Market think about it that's serious you
put out a book you got something you
believe in but you can't drop a theory
to get people better to move forward
because it it it cancels out what you
did in your work so how is it ever going
to change think about that right I mean
that's difficult and I don't blame a
practitioner or a Healer or a doctor
that's written a book that has outdated
thyroid information I don't blame them
at all it's like it's like your work is
all there and then you're like holy crap
I can't let those theories down because
it means it it outdates my book the work
I put into and that's why it's that hard
to get people
better that alone is that what that's
that's that's why it's that hard to get
people
better so the auto
antibody the auto
antibody goes after the virus itself and
only the virus the body is brilliant
your body is brilliant your body is such
a healing machine oh my
God lord it's a healing
machine like no
other your immune system is like no
other it sends out soldiers it creates
soldiers called Auto
antibodies not Auto as in destructing
you and hurting you or whatever no no no
no is going specifically after the virus
and even if research and science
discovered this they probably
wouldn't put it out
there because it means they have to open
up such a huge can of worms about
Epstein bar and they have to give
Anthony upstein and Dr bar
credit and then they have to find billi
ions of dollars and do research on
Epstein bar they so don't want to go
there because it takes billions away
from investing into genes and genetics
which puts the blame on you once again
so how are we ever going to get that
truth out there well we're going to get
it out there you guys us we're going to
get it out
there takes a little time got to have
patience but that auto antibody goes
exactly after the virus and only after
the virus it's there to break down that
virus go after
it and even when it's not detectable
on on a blood test or through blood
blood profile even if it's not even you
can find it even if you can't even find
it your body's still going after that
virus even when you're in just hypo
instead of just
Hashi it's going after the virus it's
designed to go after the virus it's
actually programmed to go after the
virus it's it's
tagged to go after the virus it's
looking to only tag the virus
itself the virus is what causes the
inflammation inside the thyroid the
virus is what causes cigar tissue the
virus is what causes uh thyroid nodules
the virus is which what causes any kind
of cyst or any kind of tumor inside a
thyroid all from the Epstein bar there's
different varieties you'll read about
those two
and is this information
helpful it's beyond
helpful because when you know your body
is doing the right thing and you know
it's going after something the right way
you can heal fast and
faster knowledge is power when it comes
down to this it comes down to this
knowledge is incredibly powerful I can't
even say it enough incredibly
powerful I can't even say it
enough so let's talk
about symptoms a little bit H
hypothyroid symptoms what you're
experiencing when you're experiencing
hashimotos or
hypothyroid those symptoms aren't the
thyroid causing it and you're going to
learn that there's very few symptoms the
thyroid actually causes from bonking out
on us from getting affected by Epstein
bar in anyway very few symptoms some
temperature fluctuations is pretty much
it I think maybe a couple more I put in
there but that's
it well there's a lot of people I I know
somebody's mind is blown there's a lot
of people and I'm going to explain this
that's why there's a lot of people they
get their hormones balanced just right
for the
thyroid they get rid of even I mean
their Auto antibodies don't even show
but they're still dealing with lots of
symptoms they always have they're still
dealing with the fatigue or they're
still dealing with something else or
they're still dealing with some
different symptom they're still dealing
with weight gain whatever it
is because it's not coming from the
thyroid and I explain in symptoms and
conditions list you'll see where a lot
of these symptoms are coming
from I can't believe I can even say that
that means you got the
book
and that that's that's amazing so
understand that Hashimoto and
hypothyroidism the symptoms are not
thyroid
related but they're liver related other
things related they're viral related
they're about being
viral I've had people without a
thyroid have all the same symptoms
nothing went away nothing changed
or they had their thyroid killed off all
the same symptoms they had their the
hormones up to par the hormones were up
the
level all the same symptoms same thing
with somebody with hypothyroid all the
same
symptoms sometimes a thyroid medication
can suppress and I talk about that in
here it's a steroid so it can suppress
some symptoms and they put a lot of of
thyroid medication in you the reason why
is cuz you're they want to keep those
numbers up because the liver keeps on
sucking up that medication sucking up
that medication sucking up that
medication and keeps on absorbing it
finally the liver maxes out and it's
like I can't absorb anymore and then
finally you get balanced meaning they're
like okay you don't have to really
change your your your thyroid medication
amount because it seems to be level in
the bloodstream that's cu the liver had
to fill
up and with all that steroid compound
floating around it can sometimes
suppress symptoms viral symptoms and
sometimes it doesn't you'll read about a
little bit of that to
too
so what happens is just like it happened
starting in 1940s and 1950s all these
symptoms
occurred and the blame was on hormones
only like the change the menopause men
had had these symptoms they didn't
complain it was a stoic time back then
and Men weren't allowed to complain they
were scared to death to tell their
doctor they had a
symptom they were also scared to death
of telling their workplace because they
would be
fired let go seen as unusable or not
usable or not or useless symptoms were
not a good
thing if a man had hot flashes it was
totally
just canceled out as work
sweat and just shaken
off a man a man had to be stoic back
then in the greatest
sense and couldn't have a
complaint were allowed to complain now
you know men are allowed to complain all
day long they're allowed to feel their
emotions
and contemplate and wonder who they are
and whatever they're allowed to do that
they weren't allowed to do that then it
was seemed it was it was
odd it was
odd he had to roam with the pack survive
in the
world no time for complaining about any
kind of symptom thank God women were
bold strong and said I don't care what
it takes I need to get my message out I
don't care who what where knows it
doesn't know it I need to go to the
doctor I need to let the doctor know
there's something going on here and
thank God for that because it has helped
it has
helped but the the hormone time period
was birthed at at that point and then
eventually it just fell into thyroid
later on after that and then of course
down to thyroid and the hormone period
it's just thyroid and the hormone period
time now where we're just it's it's PR
per menopause and thyroid but what is
not understood with all the per
menopause symptoms and menopause
symptoms and postmenopause symptoms is
those are all epin bar symptoms those
are all viral symptoms and yes there's a
thyroid problem that has occurred
because that's a stage of when the virus
gets from the liver to the
thyroid the thyroid is just another
victim in the batch of symptoms that's
occurring the thyroid is just another
symptom that is the big big big thing
right there that's
it that's the big boy right
there and
that that's ignored meaning research and
science don't want you knowing that even
if they
knew they
don't it's just one other
thing it's just one other thing
happening it's one other symptom it's
one other part of of all of that but
it's not the cause it's not the cause of
the aches and pains the fatigue the
brain fog the confusion the
lightheadedness the vertigo the tentis
the the uh hot flashes the mood swings
the brittle nails the hair falling
out it's not a part of that it's
not and that's a big thing that's a big
thing that's why I'm even pausing
because it's just it it's it's
unbelievable what's going on in in in
the medical world right now and what's
happening and how it's things are seen
and understood we're still behind
chronic illness is still behind
look I totally love research and science
love it love it love it it just it's
just not there with thyroid disease and
thyroid illness and everything about the
thyroid it's not there
yet
hyperthyroid hyperthyroid is the epin
bar going into the
thyroid and accelerating tissue
growth because it's attacking the
thyroid so feverishly that the thyroid
protects itself and develops a little
bit more tissue this is a protection
meth mechanism for
you the bulging eyes for Graves and
hyperthyroid that comes from fluid
buildup from having the virus fluid
build up specifically behind the
eyes it's not the thyroid necessarily
causing bulging eyes the thyroid problem
itself is not causing the bulging eyes
this is fluid buildup behind the eyes
this is something research science
doesn't know either yet understands that
symptom yet
entirely
somebody can still gain weight with
hyperthyroid because they'll also have
another variety of Epstein bar which is
the one that slows down the
thyroid meaning that's the one that sits
in the liver allowing the liver to get
super super sluggish causing the weight
gain
so what happens is if the liver has a
lot of viral material in it so it has
two varieties of viruses or even three
some people have even more they have
different kinds of viruses but if they
have two varieties of the Epstein
bar the liver really gets sluggish and
slows down so even if someone has the
hyperthyroid virus and it's in the
thyroid creating a little accelerating
the tissue growth a little bit which is
more hormone
production they also can have the other
Epstein bar inside the liver that's also
inside the thyroid but it's inside the
liver really really really slowing the
liver
down which then affects the
thyroid but it's the liver being the
problem it's the liver being the symptom
that's the problem the liver is where
that's at it's not the thyroid in the
end but it's the liver that's actually
causing that and that's a whole another
thing the liver is causing
literally dozens and dozens of symptoms
because Epstein bar sitting inside the
liver causing symptoms and causing
problems for the thyroid and for other
things in the body cuz the thyroid like
I said is just this other victim it's
just this other thing that's happening
it's another part of what's being
problematic and when somebody gets a
thyroid killed off there's still thyroid
tissue working and there's still thyroid
working and when someone gets their
thyroid removed you'll and you'll read
about that how that works someone gets
their thyroid
removed there's still thyroid tissue
always left producing
hormone but what
hormone is the most important hormone
you're thinking T4
T3 no they're the least important
hormones there's two undiscovered
hormones that you're going to read
about that are really important to
thyroid
healing
now um so let's go into a couple of
other things here let's go into a couple
other things that we need to go
into we're going to talk about the role
of the thyroid a little bit this is fun
this is fun we're going to talk about
the role of the
thyroid now the thyroid its function is
a lot different than we think we think
it's the metabolism function we think
it's just for controlling weight it's
it's we think we we don't science
research believes that the thyroid does
a whole bunch of the T4 D T3 means
everything meaning it basically sustains
our
life and it's these the ultimate
metabolism hormones too keeping weight
off and everything like that and by the
way that's just not true there are so
many women that have either normal
numbers or they have or they have um
hormone replacement they have the
thyroid medications and they're still
gaining weight like crazy because like I
said before it's the liver and it's the
virus inside the liver that does that
just like when someone has two viruses
like I said with hyperthyroid that's why
hyperthyroid people they they tend to
gain weight too and just so you know
people with
hyperthyroid there's more people with
hyperthyroid gaining weight meaning
overweight hyper thyroids than there are
people underweight
hyperthyroid very important to know very
important to
know that that's a critical critical
point to know by the way but boy they'll
make it out like different they'll
completely make it out different to try
to prove a point that they have a theory
that they have so they'll make it seem
like no no no then you're you're the
only one that's gaining weight with
hyperthyroid that's how they'll act and
be it's unbelievable research of science
will they'll just you're the only one
everybody else they're all losing weight
they can't keep their weight on with
hyper thyroid and you're the only one
gaining weight with hyperthyroid you're
just an anomaly oh okay just here's your
medication see you off on your
way no no no no there's more people much
more it's like 70% of people with
hyperthyroid are gaining weight and
they're overweight and they're dealing
with weight issues 30% are either normal
with their weight or losing
weight and that's even that's even not
even right meaning in the sense that
that 30%
um 30% is complicated it's complicated
it means people still stay the same
weight most of that 30% and then they
gain weight later is what I mean they
gain weight later so it all depends on
where the person is in their time
someone could have hyperthyroid when
they're 30 and have their weight stable
or even lose a little but for some
reason here they are later on gaining
weight and and before any kind of iodine
treatment radioactive iodine or any kind
of kill off or anything else like that
or any removal of thyroid or anything
like that and then they're gaining
weight before any of that even happens
that's another thing none of this is
they don't document all this all the
different variables and what
happens so in essence most hyperthyroid
people don't have a weight loss problem
they have a weight gaining problem one
time or another
eventually
because the amount of thyroid having the
other thyroid virus I was talking about
the other Epstein bar not the one that
accelerates uh hormones and tissue
growth in the thyroid that you'll read
about with hyperthyroid but the other
one that slows down the liver which
slows down everything the other one
sitting in the thyroid and that slows
down the
liver
so um so let's go into what the thyroid
does what does it really
do what does a thyroid really do I mean
that that's another thing too well first
of all it's like the second
brain it's your body's data
center it's not the metabolism
manager that everybody wants it to
be it cataloges everything it's it marks
everything it cataloges
everything its goal is to create
homeostasis throughout the body but
homeostasis throughout the body balance
throughout the body it's the complaint
center and you'll even read about that
the this is really funny the complaint
center that's where every organ every
gland in the whole body can send out a
complaint to the
thyroid but what's it sending out a
complaint for so that T4 and T3 can do
anything no no no no it's not sending
out a complaint so that T4 and T3 can
save the world within the body that's
what I'm trying to
say it's not doing that these other two
hormones that are undiscovered by
research and
science
okay these other two hormones that
you're going to read
about they are radio frequency
hormones because research and science
only looks for one kind of
hormone a special chemical that
determines if it's a hormone or not
meaning a a different kind of there's
different kinds of hormones
some that aren't just the the blatant
steroid variety what I'm saying is the
only
hormone the only hormone variety
research and science has documented so
they know what they're looking for is a
steroidal based hormone that means we
have all these different hormones in the
body all these different hormones but
they all have a steroid touch to it they
all have an identification of steroid
but there's this whole group of hormones
in the body in general in all kinds of
places that I'm going to have to get
information from Spirit along the way my
source and get it to you but there's a
whole bunch of different kinds of
hormones that aren't steroid
based so they're not identified in the
lab because the lab is only literally
programmed with data to find a
steroid-based
hormone these hormones are radio
frequency hormones cu the body is way
more complicated than anybody knows than
research and science has ever discovered
radio frequency
hormones they're not a steroid compound
attached to
it there's there's no chemical compounds
in the steroid Department that are
really Affiliated or understood with the
radio frequency
hormone and the radio frequency hormone
has chemical compounds but they're not
going to be understood as the regular
steroid the regular steroid that
everybody knows about which is
everything T4 T3 which is progesterone
and and estrogen which is testosterone
which is all the different hormones
which is you know all of that the sex
hormones all of that they are steroids
the adrenaline hormon
steroids
steroids well that's what they are so
they're identified like that in the labs
but radio frequency hormones are not
discovered
yet and the thyroid has two of them that
play a bigger role in our thyroid health
and our body's physical health than than
no one even can imagine
yet and so these frequencies get
delivered to different parts of the body
to keep it balanced delivered to the
liver delivered to the pancreas
delivered to other glands and
organs and that's the powerful real
role of the
thyroid so if the thyroid gets d
damaged if the thyroid gets
hurt if the thyroid gets injured by
Epstein
bar the thyroid is still going to send
out those radio
frequencies cuz radio frequencies are
powerful in the thyroid to the point
where you only need a little bit of
thyroid tissue left you're still going
to have a lot of radio frequency coming
out of those little pockets of tissue
even if your thyroid scarred and damaged
and everything
else
and the liver stores a tremendous amount
of interesting chemical compounds that
help out the thyroid when a thyroid
calls out for radio with the radio
frequencies and the adrenals
overcompensate as well the adren
adrenals can even mimic T4
T3 in its own way can do all kinds of
things for us to give us to give us
backup hormones the thyroid works with
every organ and every gland and this is
a big deal and this right here we're not
there yet as far as research and science
T4 T3 play a role in our health but a
small one T4 T3 really just helped the
immune system stay balanced which is
important don't get me wrong it is
important but other things keep the
immune system balanced too other thing
other things in the body keep it
balanced and so
T T4 T3 help with temperature
controls so you don't feel cold in the
morning or you don't feel kind of like
there's a little bit temperature
off but that's pretty much
it your thyroid sends a 911 call out to
the liver for backup for storage of T4
and T3 if your thyroid needs it it sends
an 911 call through a radio frequency
hormone the Undiscovered radio frequency
hormones to the liver to
get the liver to convert some T4 to T3
and also to get some T3 to begin with
and T4 going out of the liver if
needed that's the power of the thyroid
that's one of its
roles and it can do that even if it's
injured even if epine bar has invaded
the thyroid
the adrenals can create T4 and
T3 and even a little bit of radio
frequency R5 and R
six has
backup so this is important
information okay let's take a sip I'm I
am I I don't know you guys but I'm going
to take a sip here of some tea bear with
me that's a mix of peppermint and lemon
Bal it's very good very
good okay so um let's go into symptoms
let's talk about symptoms a little bit
let's do that that that's kind of
fun um weight gain liver the liver
causes weight gain um the liver becomes
toxic over the
years um uh builds up little fatty
deposits even if it's not diagnosed as a
fatty liver yet and and that's the very
basis behind weight
gain mostly the basis basis behind
it metabolism
metabolism that's really just the liver
once again um make sure you read the
metabolism
chapter whatever you
do you can't forget about the metabolism
chapter so make sure you you look into
that one um hair loss
hair loss that's adrenals that's that's
that's cortisol that's adrenals that's
adrenals being in you can be under
stress for three four years five years
in your life you could be drinking
coffee being stressed out um not taking
care of yourself getting really
deficient but the adrenals play the
largest role in hair loss hair thinning
not the thyroid the adrenals
do and you can read more about it you
know more kind of cleaner version in the
book I'm glazing over it right right now
meaning that symptoms hair texture
that's straight
deficiencies that's one of the things
straight
deficiencies
insomnia insomnia is a neurotransmitter
problem usually Epstein bar and Epstein
bar creates deficiencies just eats away
at at our um vitamin storage
bin slows down the liver um all that
stuff so we we get less vitamins less
conversion with vitamins less
methylation that's all that's that all H
happens with um Epstein bar inside the
liver insomnia neurotransmitters due to
neurotoxins you can read and you can see
neurotoxins that do a really good
explanation in there of neurotoxins
dermatoxin
byproduct so make sure you get into that
sometime brain fog concentration
neurotoxins once again floating in the
bloodstream coming from the liver coming
from an Epstein bar floating around um
toxic heavy metals also either in the
brain brain that are also oxidizing but
feeding viruses causing neurotoxins to
cause more brain fog more confusion more
concentration that's not a thyroid
problem that is not a thyroid symptom so
I'm comforting some of these symptoms so
you know what's not a thyroid symptom
too chills that's not a thyroid problem
that's a viral problem someone coming
down with Hashimoto with serious serious
fatigue and chills it's blamed on the
Hashimoto no it's not the thyroid
causing problems because the virus is in
the thyroid it's the virus in general in
the body causing the problems causing
the chills causing the fevers causing
the fatigue causing the neurological
fatigue that's the Epstein bar that's
the chronic fatigue syndrome Epstein
bar what science and research is good at
though is renaming things they've
already named chronic fatigue syndrome
you know five times I don't know what it
is now they'll probably name it another
five times just to keep us
distracted
um cold hands and
feet cold hands and feet is liver
circulation because of the liver and a
lot of toxins in the liver namely many
could be viral puffy face puffy eyes
lymphatic system and liver once again
liver being clogged
up and that's edema that's a mild edema
and then regular edema if a doctor can't
find kidney problems or heart problems
which which is which is easy to find
with what we have in research science
thank God and that's what I love about
research of science is they have so much
that is helpful that I do love in so
many ways and surgeons I love surgeons I
love everybody committed to bettering
people's lives and we have so many great
things and I've talked about that over
and over again you guys don't need to
hear that again from me you know I'm Pro
I'm Pro uh Pro doctor Pro surgeons Pro
Specialists Pro experts too you know
even know I I say what I say about you
know in the thyroid World in other world
it's just a chronic illness is falling
short so I do I do say that everybody is
kind of behind the times in that area of
course that that that I stand by been
chronic illness is where it's all
falling through um and has been for
decades and decades so the puffy face
puffy eyes that's liver lymphatic
sluggish liver problematic
liver so these are just some of the
symptoms um and you can see other
symptoms too that are that are in there
that are you know of what's going on
that's a that's another thing now
medication I want to talk about
medication a little bit of medic
medication is is a funny thing um you
know talk to your doctor with any of
that um you know your practitioner
whatever if you want to play with your
medications you know a lot of doctors
these days are definitely open to
playing with medications they're open to
reducing them in case you're getting a
side effect from a medication they're
open to uh changing them sometimes too
um so they're they're they're they're
open to to a lot of different things
some you know I've seen a lot of great
doctors where they learn about Epstein
bar they learn about the thyroid they
see their patient getting better doing
anti-in bar protocols I've seen this
because they're doing stuff out of say
the medical medium book or
something and um and the doctor
minimizes the medication for them along
the way they feel better um and so
there's a lot of different things you
can do with medication but one thing
about thyroid medication it does make
the liver sluggish so if someone goes on
thyroid medication because they have a
hypothyroid say in their 30s or in their
they're in their 20s so if if you've
ever experienced that if you know
somebody or maybe it's you going through
it what happens is that if you're on
that medication for 20 years you're just
given that medication for Life what
happens is the medication ends up
slowing down the liver clogging up
causing weight gain sometimes it's not
even the upstein bar somebody's life is
going good where they're not triggering
so easily their Epstein bar
and you know there's not a lot of
terrible things happening or stressful
things or changes in their life like big
breakups and heartbreak and divorces and
um things that we go through in life
that everybody goes through in life you
know all the normal things that cause
stress Financial stress everything else
the triggers the triggers and you'll see
the trigger section there so if you're
not going through a lot of triggers if
you're not someone that's going through
a lot of triggers things could all be
going smooth you got this very mild
hypothyroid because the mono you had
that you may not even know you had
really mild it could be like I talk
about a medical
medium that could just literally be
giving you you know the exposure of a
very mild epine bar in the liver it's
not doing much then it goes to the
thyroid causing the hypothyroid in your
20s or 30s it's not doing much it just
sits in there it's not doing much and
you don't have a lot of triggers things
are going smooth life is going great
and next thing you know it though the
medications end up clogging up the liver
over time by the time you're get into
your 40s you're noticing weight gain you
can't control and then that gets thrown
into hey you need estrogen testosterone
you need all everything rebalanced you
need progesterone you need all your you
need all your hormones looked at because
then the hormone thing gets thrown into
but really what's happening is you got
this liver problem from old Epstein bar
sitting in there so long and you got all
the medications built up from your
thyroid medication and that happens to
millions of women where things are kind
of going smooth they're not getting too
many triggers too many upsets in life um
and uh just maybe some of the basic
upsets or basic triggers and you know
the upstein bar hasn't really Advanced
too far causing too many symptoms and
then the thyroid medication builds up
and builds up and builds up in the liver
from 20 years of thyroid medication
which is bottles after bottles of
thyroid medication being stored inside
the liver and then finally weight gain
comes on then it's blamed on hormones
it's blamed on per menopause it's blamed
on menopause and if then if they get any
kind of triggers at that point in your
life so if you get a trigger in that
point in your life now it's years later
you're in your 40s you're in your early
50s and you're getting triggers now
something happens divorce stress or any
kind of other you know or any kind of
thing trauma or anything well then the
virus can amp up a bit causing other
symptoms fatigue brain fog other things
and when that happens then the doctor
say well definitely menopause per
menopause symptoms and this was the
mistake made in
1950 this was the mistake made in
1950 and I talk about it here in thyroid
healing but I thought I would you know
talk about it a little bit also in this
webinar
um so uh so
basically we don't want to build up that
much medication in the liver either over
time so we do want to play with
medication if we can I mean if you're do
meaning if you're doctor's open to it
you can talk to your doctor and see if
he's open to it and you do the protocols
that um that Spirit KN have outlined in
the book for knocking down Epstein bar
and what's happening is with these
protocols inside the book it's about
knocking down Epstein
bar that's what it is and that's that's
the key and it's some some of the
supplements too are to revive the
thyroid from Epstein bar damage because
we want to protect the thyroid so it can
keep strong and keep our radio active
frequencies and everything else going on
but it's about the foods not to eat you
know you do the best you can you take
one thing at a time try not to get
overwhelmed and you do the best you can
you take out some of the foods that feed
the virus that you can back down and
that's what happens with a lot of also
you know diets out there is they take
away some of the foods or a lot of the
foods that do feed Epstein bar but they
don't know that that's what they're
doing and then they call it the thyroid
fix but really what's
happening when they do get results they
don't know why they have the wrong
reasons of why they're getting
results it which is fine as long as
someone's getting results but you need
to know why you're getting results you
can keep on it stay on it so it's
nothing creeps up and comes back 10
years down the road 5 years down the
road or something else happens you want
to really get rid of the epsteen bar and
clean it up you really want to revive
your thyroid but you want to know why
and how and that's that's what we're
trying to do in thyroid healing so that
once you take out those foods that feed
the virus and and and cause the virus to
cause more symptoms and whatnot once you
you know you're using take out the foods
that don't help and you're using foods
that do help revive the thyroid you're
using foods that do help knock down
Epstein bar then you're moving forward
but you know why you're moving forward
you know what you're after you know what
you're doing and you know why you have
the auto antibodies and you know why
things are going on that matters so you
don't pop off course one day on a
different
Trend or you're on the same Trend and
you're but now you're not getting
results and you don't know why a year
later that's because it wasn't really
specifically for what the real knowledge
is which is about knocking down Epstein
bar which is about knocking down the
viral load it's viral the Epstein bar is
not a trigger and that's what happened
that's what happened if you read a note
for you at the beginning of the book
read that note you don't have to read it
now but you know or anytime but when you
get a chance read that note that the
note for you I I wrote that note for
you and in that note it's important to
understand um some of the things that I
I put in there because it it it'll help
it'll
help it's because what happens is
that the information for instance like
book one getting Epstein bar out there
about how it got into the thyroid they
got a lot of people upset out there they
got a lot of professionals upset so what
happened was they started using the
abene bar thing you know but they're
using it as a they're putting it in the
trigger basket which is the wrong place
they're putting it in a trigger basket
it's not a trigger it's not a trigger
it's the cause of Hashimoto it's the
cause it's the th it's the cause of
hashimotos it's the cause of Hashimoto
symptoms it's the cause of hypothyroid
it's the cause of
hyperthyroid it's the cause of thyroid
cancer it's the cause so um it's
important to know that
and and being you know back they're just
you know when they're trying to protect
themselves and they're taking our
knowledge here and then kind of
manipulating it so it works in their
favor but doesn't work in your favor
entirely that's just that's that's how
things get messed up and screwed around
with or skewed around with that's how
that you know that's how that
happens and um and so just keep an open
mind when you read a note for you so you
can kind of say that's why he's saying
all this it's part of why he's saying
all
this so that's a really
important important fact
so the deal is with the supplement
section look supplements are always
overwhelming take it one day at a time
the supplements there are geared to
killing off Epstein bar they're geared
to helping the nervous system recover
from Epstein bar symptoms they're geared
with they're geared to helping you know
heal damaged tissue in the thyroid take
it one day at a time I you could work
with your practitioner and healer and
doctor and friend whoever you have you
know you can work with them on the
supplements you can take one at a time
if you're afraid of supplements
altogether hold off and just work with
the
foods if you're somebody that loves
supplements or doesn't mind taking
things and knowing what you're taking
whatever you don't mind what you know
you love knowing what you're taking what
it's for then you know then go into it
the way you feel you need to go into it
so baby step baby step baby step baby
step well that's what I would do is baby
step and if you're confused about what
kind of vitamins because different zinc
and it's true I've seen zincs out there
where I've tried where I've almost I've
spit it out and I couldn't believe what
went in my mouth because it had so much
citric acid in there it was like poison
it had it had so much preservative in
it I couldn't believe what entered my
mouth I've tried all so many different
things out there and I I would squirt
this zinc from a reputable company just
right in my mouth and and it would burn
a hole in my mou throat and mouth
because it had it had an ounce of citric
acid just in there oh my God and so for
that reason I I I put a note in there
saying go to my directory I don't sell
the supplements on my directory I'm not
in the supplement you know business or
anything like that I don't sell the
supplements but go to my directory so
you don't go to the store and buy the
zinc that has all that citric acid in it
or something like that and it's like
that with with with all supplements
meaning you just got to be cautious with
whatever so I put I put a note saying if
you want the ones that I trust that will
you that make that list or whatever then
go to the directory at at Medical medium
and did that to protect you
um and so uh so when it comes down to
supplements you know work with your
ition you might have a practitioner
that's really really liberal with
supplements really liberal and they're
just and they're just like no okay
listen I want you on this I want you on
that I want you on this this this this
this this is great and then you and you
might have practitioners already have
you on a few of those supplements so
they're like okay no this is great you
can do this you can do this so you just
you know you you you take it one step at
a
time
um but just
know that you're moving yourself to
healing and if you're afraid of
supplements in general and you don't
like them or don't have any money you
may not have any money at all I run to
people they don't they can only get the
book If even and they can't afford a
supplement so then you just work with
your Foods try to pick a few identify a
few foods from the book and maybe try to
do one of the recipes you every little
bit counts but I'll I'll tell you this
I'll tell you this and this is important
in this webinar knowing the information
that's even in that book helps you heal
it helps you heal read the great
mistakes chapters the great mistake
chapters read those because they help
you heal the autoimmune mistake the
metabolism mistake the gene mistake and
it goes on and on and on the mystery ESS
mistake just read
those because they help heal knowing
what's going on knowing what your
thyroid does knowing what happens when
your thyroid is not working all all that
helps you heal having this knowledge
helps you heal that's a big part of it
that's a really great big part of
it a huge part of it there's people
already that have healed from book one
medical medium their thyroid issues and
that's just from one chapter in medical
medium one chapter on thyroid in the
book medical medium that's all I did was
one chapter this is a whole book on
thyroid but there's just one chapter
and they heal their
thyroids and and and I'm not just
talking about one or two people I'm
talking about hundreds of people and
hundreds of people have healed their
thyroids from just that one chapter and
knowing information that count it and so
that's what's happening here and you got
a whole whole book to read through so if
you if you need to be slow on
supplements if you need to be kind of
you know slow on the subs or slow on you
need to be slow on the
foods then take your time then take your
time then just knowing the information
is going to help you take one day at a
time but you'll get to the foods and
you'll get to some of the
supplements you'll get to some of those
supplements that are really helpful
there's a whole thing on iodine in there
how iodine Works Sea vegetables and so
forth because there's a complete
misconception out there about iodine
iodine is a disinfectant the reason why
some people with hashimotos have a
reaction if they put a whole bunch of
iodine in them because they actually in
this in this reaction is considered
negative and you don't want a huge
reaction but it's considered negative to
practitioners and doctors so they say oh
stay away from iodine it could flare
Hashimoto what iodine
does is it goes after the virus meaning
it actually is a disinfectant it kills
all bugs all pathogens you put a
pathogen in a Petri dish and you stick
iodine in there and guess what the
pathogen
dies you put iodine in your throat and
you got Hashimoto's and it's saturated
with Epstein bar that has that that that
thyroid with Hashimoto is saturated with
with epine bar and you put you put
iodine in there and you're going to get
you're going to it's like shocking the
thyroid because it's killing off so many
bugs you don't want to do it that way
but you can't be afraid of a little
iodine and a half a teaspoon of
Spirulina or a little touch of iodine
and some dolls or a little bit of
kelp because you don't want to be iodine
deficient with Epstein bar you don't
want to be iodine efficient with any
kind of thyroid disease or thyroid
illness or thyroid
problems so that's something be to
consider you know read that whole area
read that whole that whole area
carefully so um that's a whole another
kind of thing
and now you may Wonder there's an
insomnia there's a sleep
section A sleep section in thyroid
healing I'm going to take another sip of
tea bear with
me you may Wonder why that's in there
like is it odd is it out of sorts it
actually the opposite insomnia and
sleeping problems is blamed on thyroid
more now than it ever has been in
history maybe you've already experienced
that because you're sleeping problems
and then wait a minute your thyroids off
as Hashim Modas that's why you're not
sleeping I hurt it every day I hurt it
every single day out there over and over
and over again well I've had sleeping
problems my doctor thinks it's uh it's
the
thyroid IT it became the easy out
symptom any kind of sleep problems
that's your
thyroid so I had to dedicate a section
with multiple chapters in the sleep in
the Sleep World in the Sleep Department
in the thyroid book I had no
choice because yes it's a symptom but
it's it's it's now there's so many
people and you may be experiencing that
are having sleep problems in general
having sleep problems for anything for
to to having sleep problems one way or
another whether it's restless legs or
just having sleep problems or they're
having whatever it
is and it's being all thrown in the in
the thyroid basket if it's not diagnosed
with lime which is a whole another thing
whole another story on down the road
I'll have to put a whole book out on
Lime to set the record
straight I'm definitely going to have to
do that I did a chapter in book one
medical meeting but I have to do a whole
a whole book on it and I know that I'm
I'm dreading it I'm dreading it cuz when
it gets controversial when anything gets
too controversial you just get nothing
but Stones thrown at you you get
pitchforks and knives and Tor you know
torches you get all that starts
happening cuz when you put real truth
out there you know what happens which by
the way is there any way any anybody
there if you like thyroid healing can
you put a review on Amazon for spirit
and I Spirit would love it um I like it
because the spirit likes it because it
can help people
it can truly help them because they'll
know there's there's some good
information in this document there's
some good information that's healing for
people so if you can I know you're busy
and you got busy lives and it's a pain
in the butt but if you can just put any
kind of review you feel um uh on Amazon
uh for thyroid healing we would be so
grateful grateful grateful because
there's going to be an onslaught of also
torches and pitchforks because of
because of how controversial this is
because when you when you show the truth
and you show the body's not attacking
itself and you and you try to get the
truth out there there's also this this
small army of people that just hate that
and they end up just you know throwing
stones and rocks so if you can do that
that would be so appreciated I can't
even tell you and I hate asking anything
of you I swear to God I hate
it because you know I know you're busy
and I know you got so much going on in
your life and just know that I care and
I totally understand
that um but when you have the truth in
your hand it's going to help you in
every way possible in every way possible
it's going to
help so the Sleep Department needed more
it just it just needed more I mean sure
there could be chapters on every single
symptom that's in there that Spirit can
provide additional information but in
the Sleep realm it's being packaged into
thyroid and it's not a thyroid problem
sleeping is not a thyroid
problem but sleeping can be anything
from stress cortisol adrenals viral
issues like Epstein bar the liver being
unhappy the liver being sluggish the
liver being completely burdened um
sensitive nervous systems
neurotransmitter issues all these
different things is our sleeping
problems from different varieties of
stress from different varieties of worry
from subconscious worry from
subconscious stress from all kinds of
things could be your sleeping problem so
so I had to put a good section in there
because they can't get all picked off as
just thyroid so it had the record had to
be set with sleeping so I hope you
enjoyed that there's a chapter in there
a very small one of why bad dreams are
pretty good for you you might get a kick
out of it I know it's t you know it's
it's I know it's taking it's going a
little bit on the spiritual side of
things and um but it's it's
powerful because what happens is we heal
through our bad dreams it doesn't mean
when you have good dreams and only good
dreams that you're never healing or
you're a bad person that's not it at
all I just said every now and then if
you ever get a bad dream one every 10
years one every 30 years one every 20
years is's a reason for it that's your
body healing if you get a bad dream
every night there's a reason for it I
get a bad dream I get bad dreams I do
some
healing I do some healing I get some bad
dreams here and there I've seen so much
in my life and I've been through so much
in my life and with this gift and
everything
else that yeah I have some bad
dreams but that's how you let things
loose and let things out and you heal in
different ways different parts of
healing you don't have to have bad
dreams to heal in all kinds of different
ways you don't have to have bad dreams
to heal your thyroid but just letting
you know since we were talking about
sleep so much in those chapters that I
thought I would throw that little tidbit
that Spirit has taught me so much
out and I hope you enjoy it I hope you
enjoy
it when we get diagnosed with
something it it can hit us really
hard you know I when especially when
when we're younger too when we're
younger I mean I've seen so many people
in their early 20s and late 20s get
diagnosed with with a thyroid condition
and they feel like their life is
over and and even their spouse or their
fian or their boyfriends or their
husbands they just can't they can't hack
it I've seen this happen so many times
I've seen so many
breakups so many
breakups because it was just scary for
the boyfriend or the husband or the or
the uh fiance it was just so scary that
their
25-year-old partner you know has this
thyroid problem so what next and then
when you look into thyroid problem and
you look into Hashimoto of the body
destroying and it's attacking itself
it can make a a person run away from a
partner and this is one of the most
disturbing reasons I feel is part of the
misinformation trap that's out there
I've seen
couples completely alter their Destiny
and completely split up when they were
very happy together because of
information that floats around in the
internet and other books like for
instance like Hashimoto is being the
body destroying itself which is wrong
it's about the body attacking itself and
causing all this harm and how where
things can go if it's not under control
and all these things and I've seen
people run from each
other and young women just lose partners
and have to and and just and and wallow
in in agony over that their
diagnosis and it's
heartbreaking and I I I've seen this
with women in their 30s men and women in
their 30s
happening and um and even seen it with
women in their
40s the divorce suddenly happens during
the Hashim Modas
diagnosis I've seen
this and so this is from misinformation
out there that's what this is putting
fear into women and into and into uh the
system in general that creates these
imbalances what I'm saying is if you've
been diagnosed young or you're you're
young now and you're diagnos with with
Hashim just don't fear it don't get
scared don't think your life is over
don't think you're dependent on hormones
for the rest of your life don't think
that you're going to have problems for
the rest of your life don't think any of
that you've had a little bug in you a
little viral issue that you've had that
frankly most people have in their system
doing something one way or another that
we all live with that you can clean up
and break down and help and
restore and get your life back mentally
emotionally and
physically and you can take control so
if your moms and you have a daughter
this is something you can tell daughter
that's going through the same things
it's not because mom had it now the
daughter has it and it's genetic that's
not how it works that's not how it
works and then your child's going to
have it because it's genetic no that's
not how it works that's another big
round of misinformation that's out there
that's one more thing I just wanted to
tell everybody here about before um the
webinar ends and I just I just wanted
everybody to know this and it's
difficult when you're young because
you're starting your career you're
trying to look for a career you're
trying to figure out school you're
trying to figure out what you're doing
maybe your job maybe you love your job
maybe you're doing things and you get
given this diagnosis and you got these
symptoms you don't understand them you
fight you fight forward you heal up you
you take what you deserve meaning good
health and freedom and you grab that
freedom you deserve it and you take that
and you hold it in your hand and you
keep that as armor and you fight for it
and you do what you need to do and I say
that for anybody in any age it's just
that the younger people I noticed they
suffer more mentally and emotionally
when they're not feeling well
and and and it's just it's unbelievable
with with what younger younger people
have to go through and of course I feel
that way with everybody no matter what
age if you're my age or older or
whatever your age is I feel that for
everybody but I notice that the world
has changed there's a chapter in there
about creating your illness how we don't
create our illness I'm noticing that the
young people are falling tra in prey to
a Consciousness that's developing a
trendy trap of how if you're sick with
Hashimoto and you're 25 that means you
must have wished it on yourself that
means it's bad karma that means you
created it and that's why that chapter's
in there to clarify that so make sure if
Mommy if you got a daughter and your
daughter's thinking that because she's
getting diagnosed with hypothyroid make
sure she reads that
chapter because there's so much
misinformation out there once again
about that alone it's poisonous
destructive and it just does so much
damage to our
children and even even us it does damage
to us too so we need to know we need to
know that we need to know
that and if you're one of those that
thinks it's all in your head for some
reason no it's not all in your head okay
your symptoms are real and we're
addressing them you better believe it
we're addressing them the thyroid
healing that's going to help you address
them the book's going to help you
address them you take one day at a
time and you keep a light heart one
thing about Epstein bar is it becomes
useless meaning it it breaks down it's
weak and once you know the power that
you have it breaks down even more your
immune system goes after it even more
and does what it needs to do once you
know what's going on in your system and
you know what's creating your Hashimoto
you have more power to heal it than ever
before in history in any before in your
life's history any any any ever
before in your own life's
history you have more power to break it
down clean things up move forward and
heal have patience some epine bars
they've been around a long time in your
system you might have had a lot of
triggers so it could take longer because
of your triggers that's okay you still
can heal and still will get better over
time and sometimes there's healing going
on well all the time there's healing
going on but sometimes the delayed
effect of saying getting rid of all the
symptoms and maybe you get rid of six
symptoms out of 10 some of the symptoms
that lag a little later are from made
maybe damaged nerves that need to heal
heal they need longer times to heal so
nerves need longer time to heal or other
aspects in the body liver needs a longer
time to heal just have patience your
body's working on it and healing and
you're working on healing every single
day every single day you're doing this
and all the knowledge is packed inside
this this book all the knowledge and all
the truth in there you hold on to it
okay and you work on healing and you
move forward and you move forward
because your body is healing your body
is working hard it loves you
unconditionally and you can read that in
the uh in the autoimmune great mistake
your body loves you unconditionally it's
not designed to destroy you it's not
designed to attack you that's not what
it does it works on your side it works
in your favor it's not against you I
promise you
that and you need to know that that's a
big part of the truth about how things
work that's a big part of the truth
about how things
work
thank you for having patience to to to
get through this webinar with me
seriously thank you for having the
patience I love you for it and I'm
honored you're with me here so I'm
trying to think if there's anything else
that I could kind of cover I mean I know
you have the book now but but if there's
anything else I'm giving you even
tidbits that that you know that are are
wherever I can get them from um from my
experience and from Spirit and
everything giving you tidbits now of
anything that can be helpful cuz I want
you to to get as much help as you can
and help as you need I covered the
supplements a little bit I covered the
um Foods a little bit now what I did in
this book is I put a a couple of things
about what the food does and what it's
doing for you when it comes down to
dealing with any kind of thyroid
condition and underlying viral problem
that's actually causing a thyroid
condition I'm I'm or and causing other
symptoms and all kinds of other all
kinds of symptoms I I put you know a
little bit of
information with each
food make sure you you look into that
make sure you read that just don't get
the food and don't read that because
it's important to kind of know that that
food is doing something for you that's
another thing that reboots and restores
the immune system and helps clean the
mess up that's inside it's just that
there's information in food and if you
know what that information is something
happens with the immune system system as
it uses the food so so when that food
goes in you it's going in you with an
intention your thoughts your
Consciousness connects to that that that
intention of what the food does for you
anyway your immune system binds on grabs
on to that intention of what the food's
doing for you and literally the food
even works better for you and even
better so that's why I put those notes
there about every food that's why I did
that
um just you know take it one day at time
take it one day at a time if you feel
like you're getting overwhelmed it's
okay take a little break take one day at
a time whatever you need to do and um
just have a little patience like you've
always had and if you've been sick for a
day in your life or know someone who has
you already know that you've you've you
have patience within you or someone also
that that's been for day in their life
they know you know they have patience
within them and have some compassion for
yourself have some compassion for
yourself your body is not destroying
itself you can heal your Hashimoto you
can do more than just heal it you can do
do more than just get the numbers
straight you can do more than just get
your symptoms better you can really get
past this whole thing and keep it
concrete and hold it strong and then go
back to this book and get information to
keep you stronger and stronger along the
way so you don't get relapses 10 years
down the road and everything else
because the information out there's
flawed so this can really move you
forward and get you to where you need to
be and take one day at a time keep a lie
heart pat yourself on the back every day
just know that I stand behind you I'm
with you and I love you dearly pat
yourself on the back have compassion for
yourself cuz you know what compassion
does it rebuilds your immune system
compassion rebuilds your immune system
system you got um a sick child and
you're compassionate towards that child
to rebuild your child's immune
system if you got a friend who's sick
you're compassionate towards that friend
you're rebuilding that friend's immune
system maybe they'll do that for you too
maybe they won't that's okay still be
compassionate and you be compassionate
to yourself to build your immune
system do some prayers when you can in
any way that you like or
affirmations affirmations about your
body healing you know your body can heal
you know it will and you know you have
the power to do it and you know you have
things in your hands to make that happen
now no matter what keep strong in every
way every shape and every possibility of
staying strong and if you feel kicked
down and a little bit beat up you know I
dedicated this book to
you I dedicated this book to you and
that's the dedication in this book
okay and I did that and I did that for a
great reason for a great reason because
if you've been kicked down you've been
tossed aside if you had trouble healing
or maybe you already
healed maybe you didn't heal yet
whatever it
is okay I'm with you and I stand behind
you
100% And so this book is dedicated to
you and it's dedicated to you healing
please know that in my heart of hearts I
stand behind you I love you thank you
for being here at this
webinar and um just you know we're
always going to be putting out
information and I'm always going to be
doing things to make sure that you heal
no matter what let's stay in touch all
of us in every way possible I'll see you
on Instagram do some Instagram stories
Instagram anything go on there and check
them out meaning check the stories out
and if you got one feel free to put one
in you know if you don't want to put one
in don't worry but everybody's putting
them in these days
and just you know just get inspired it
inspires me every day when I see that
and
um yeah okay okay all right um I'll let
you go I love you guys I hate letting
you go I'm te eyed and getting kind of
emotional my voice is going to start
cracking I love you and one day at a
time take care
bye-bye