this call is presented for information
purposes and is not intended to provide
or be a substitute for medical advice
diagnosis treatment or prescribing never
disregard medical advice or delaying and
seeking it because of any information
provided through this call neither
Anthony William nor Anthony William Inc
is a medical doctor or other licensed
Healthcare practitioner and provider
consult with a licensed healthc care
professional before altering or
discontinuing any current medication
treatment or care or starting any diet
exercise or supplementation program or
if you suspect you may have a health
condition that requires medical
attention the information provided
through this call is not guaranteed to
be correct complete or up to date and
should not be considered a promise of
benefit claim of cure legal warranty or
guarantee of results to be achieved the
information provided does not
necessarily reflect the opinions of
Anthony William or Anthony William Inc
mentioning a product or service during
the call is not intended to indicate or
imply that Anthony William or Anthony
William Inc recommends endorses supports
sponsors or is any way affiliated or
associated with the product or service
Anthony William Inc is the only party
permitted to record this call and
reserves all copyright and other
proprietary rights associated with the
recording and its content Anthony
William Inc may use copy and distribute
the recording in whole or in part alone
or with other recordings or information
and in transcript form for advertising
or other purposes any use of the
recording or its content without the
prior written consent of Anthony William
Inc is strictly prohibited hello I'm
Anthony William and I'm excited I'm
grateful I'm honored I'm happy that
you're here ready to take on this
powerful information that can help you
forge forward
with that protective armor that I always
talk about that protective armor my
life's purpose has always been that you
get ansers to protect yourselves your
family you know to have that truth to
have that knowledge to protect your
loved ones your dear friends and and
your neighbors anybody that's important
in your life and and that's that's
important you know if this is your first
time joining my webinar or heard a radio
show or read any books or anything of
mine please know that I dedicated my
life life to provide real answers for
countless people for decades and much of
the information has been proven over the
years as the years have gone by it's
been proven even by science of
information that have brought to the
table and so much of it that I've
brought for us hasn't been yet
discovered by research or science and
it's still years years down the road in
ahead but I always want you to have that
information now I don't want you waiting
it doesn't make any sense to wait you
know and there's something important for
you to know is as you listen you may see
that sometimes this information that I'm
sharing with you will seem the like the
opposite of what you've heard before
when it comes down to Something in
health or something in cancer or
something like that but don't be alarmed
there could be good reason and very good
reason why it's the opposite to protect
you so keep that in mind as you're
listening to this and going through this
and sometimes you'll notice that the
information could be similar to other
sources but there's subtle and different
critical differences that make the
difference there's critical differences
in the information and you might not be
able to see that right off the bat and
say oh well oh god I've heard that
before no there could be a subtle
critical difference because it matters
because information as it goes down the
line gets messed with
as it goes down the line the Common
Thread with the information you're going
to get today is that it's the truth and
I'm not talking about truth that has
been altered truth that has been tainted
truth that has been
skewed along the way I'm not talking
about that kind of truth that even the
best the best well-known experts are
speaking out there but don't realize
there's something in there that's not in
your best interest the information
you're going to get is not
repackaged and it's not recycled Theory
made to sound like something new you
know this this information you'll hear
doesn't come from interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks yeah persuaded belief
systems and private panels of
influencers and health PE health field
payoffs or even trendy traps that are
both in conven
and alternative medicine that are both
in conventional and alternative me
medicine seriously you know when I say
that I still can't even believe it but
it's true and I've seen it and I've seen
it over again this information I'm
sharing with you is in your best
interest you need to know that that's
important it's in no one else's best
interest it's not in any of those groups
I just mentioned okay it's very
important because those groups come
along with with even the best
alternative information that people and
experts are sharing and it doesn't mean
it's in your best interest anymore even
though the heart's all there and it's
all there in the sense of you know the
the inspiration is all there the passion
someone could have behind it best your
best interest matters see the
information you're going to get here
comes from a clean Source a Pure
untampered Source that I've been blessed
with and have had access to since Age 4
a higher source a compassionate source
that many of you have learned through
reading my books or have heard or
experienced oneon-one with me all
through the years okay so fasten your
seat bels and I hope you enjoy the show
and I mean fasten those seat bels for
really because we're going for a ride
we're going for a ride many people have
recently been asking me a lot you know
what what are my thoughts about cancer
you know I see it all over the place a
lot of people ask me in different you
know ways and online and everything else
what do you know what do I know about
cancer and what are my thoughts about
cancer well you know so it was time that
I actually I actually covered this like
I've covered dozens and dozens of
ailments and different you know
illnesses and diseases and conditions
with Advanced information I think it's
important to just you know get some
cancer information out there too uh that
could look be additionally helpful for
the information that's already out there
in the world either way but it's
important information and my personal
experience with cancer you guys started
at age four when I discovered my
grandmother had lung cancer so I was the
one and actually saw that she had lung
cancer and many of you probably know
that story and how it went but it but
that was my first personal experience
and since then though through the
decades I've actually seen cancer in so
many different people cancer that has
developed in so many different people
along Ong the way and I've taken it
extremely personal because of my
grandmother number one and number two
because of the nature of it and what we
go through in health and everything else
so I'm going to provide key pieces to
cancer that you should know and of
course Epstein bar which has a reason
for why we're doing that today too which
you'll you'll you'll figure out out
along the way as we talk about it and so
we're taking this serious today we
really are cancer and EBV cancer and
epsteam bar we're taking this serious
you know so when I diagnosed my
grandmother of lung cancer at age 4 I've
seen a lot of people just in as a child
I'd be in a busy place or being a movie
theater and be able to know if someone
had cancer in the movie theater and
whatever kind of cancer and variety of
cancer now the good thing about the gift
the wonderful good thing about the gift
that I've been given is you get to know
what's behind the cancer what's really
the starting point when did it start how
did it start in someone what was it see
medicine today you guys medicine today
just focuses on cancer once it's been
created once something's been created
once something's developed and
manifested that's what cancer research
is about it's about that point cancer
research really isn't about anything
before that and if it is it's about
something entirely wrong which we're
going to talk about and I could say that
and it's going to be a mindblower that
there's a fa there's a piece of fabric
about the study of cancer today that
isn't really
correct and so the the information has
to be out there about really how does it
start how can a cancer cell become a
cancer cell how can a cancer cell grow
how and what and why what's really going
on and that's what we're talking about
today I mean we only have a certain
amount of time of course so I can't go
on and on and on about hundreds of
different varieties of cancer and all
the different research that's out there
today and the whole bit and we'll do
more of these we're going to do more of
these along the way so we cover more and
more but we're going to cover key
critical critical points that are so
important and information that is so
important so I just want to give you
that whole
background now let's go into history
just a little bit now there I'm sure
there's some cancer experts that are
actually just listening to this for sure
now and different Physicians and
different professionals and different
people all around and people that aren't
even doctors that are that are experts
in cancer because they've experienced it
or they've known somebody or anything
like that or they just researching
constantly and I get that so if you know
some research you know that cancer we've
been told cancer goes back a long way it
goes back years and years and years and
years before us so that's what we've
been told Cancer's it's really old it's
old in our history it goes back farther
and further like for instance you may
hear that cancer is a thousand years old
and then you may hear that there's
people with cancer that you know are
2,000 years ago maybe they found a mummy
with cancer okay and then you may hear
that just 500 years ago
okay or you know go back to 400 BC all
right when the word cancer was was
created it's a Greek word so that word
was created that's a Greek word cancer
for a sickness in the body so you would
think well cancer started really early
because 400 BC that's when cancer first
started so and you're going to hear
eventually and you're going to hear
eventually that you know and I ican an
ican has cancer and they got it under
study you know somebody they found in
ice 10,000 years ago 12,000 years ago
next to a mammoth and they're going to
say well you know science research going
to say well cancer goes back as far as
woo the time of the mammoths and you're
going to hear
that but I have to be straight with you
guys I have to be straight up all right
and remember I told you to fast of no
seat belts there's reason for this for
this trip for this ride there's
reasons see we've been had that's
misinformation cancer is Young extremely
young in history and I'm going to talk
about how and why and what see you have
to understand something when the term
cancer in 400 BC around 400 BC they're
around that time frame when the Greeks
came up with the term cancer they were
talking about a tumor but they weren't
w't talking about cancer cells in a
tumor they weren't talking about
malignant cancer cells in a tumor that
word was developed for benign
tumors for benign
tumors that's where that word was
developed it was also developed off of
Just sickness that grew whether it even
wasn't a tumor it didn't even have to be
a tumor for that word to be used when it
was first invented is first first that
word was first you know
pronounced so that means if someone was
dying of some type of toxin or illness
or something back you know over 2,000
years ago the word cancer was applied
all the
time all of the time it was applied
tumor no tumor um being able to see a
disease or not it was applied so you
need to understand that this is really
important
okay any kind of tumors that were even
found in the 1400s 1500s 1600s weren't
cancerous could they have killed someone
yes growing the wrong way growing in the
wrong place absolutely growing up
against an organ pushing up against a
vein pushing up is very easy back in
that day for anything to pretty much
take you
out and but
these
tumors weren't the cancer we speak of we
see we talk about today at all now why
is this why isn't this corrected
anywhere why isn't this corrected with
the experts why aren't they correcting
it because they don't know better I'm
sorry to say and there's a reason for
this it's not their fault not their
fault at all the reason why no one's
corrected with this is because medicine
today has to put the blame on you it has
to put the blame on you you need to know
that's how it's all been set up okay and
hang on hang on hang on this is going to
be okay get some tea out get some tea
out okay maybe some some lemon balm tea
or some relaxing tea because this is
hard this is hard to digest maybe some
peppermint tea cuz with you know it
helps you digest food so we'll get the
helps your digestion improve we'll get
some peppermint tea
out see the fault has to be put on you
same thing I talk about all the time
with autoimmune disease we're we're told
that the body is attacking itself that
the body literally is destroying itself
with any kind of autoimmune disease
that's incorrect information as I've
talked about many times there's
pathogens that are the cause of the
damage being done or the inflammation
that's occurring the body produces an
antibody not to destroy the body or hurt
the body body on any level but to go
after the virus it's not autoimmune see
that part isn't even corrected yet but
the blame is always it's not corrected
out there except I was the first person
to actually get it out there now it's
starting to get out there thank God and
it will be proven I promise you this but
the point is is for you to believe that
it's always your fault so no matter what
so whatever kind of chronic fatigue or
sickness or disease or illness or rash
or disord order it's it's it's just you
and this is how it's always been set up
so if the truth came out the real truth
and you knew that you weren't
responsible for your cancer or cancer
just didn't afflict you it didn't
naturally afflict you just came on to
you because that's the way it's been for
thousands of years which is the wrong
information if you knew the truth that
it was somebody else's fault and if the
world knew that things would start
falling apart the things would start
falling apart in medicine and research
and everything else so the pattern for
medicine is always going to be heading
in the direction it's your fault you got
bad genes your body's attacking itself
and destroying itself you're creating
your problem you're eating too much
you're not taking care of yourself
you're doing whatever whatever it is
it's going to point there in
medicine but with
cancer Cancer's an early epidemic really
early I mean not early start just
recently early is what I mean that's
what I'm trying to say here it's
recent it's
recent and it's not as far back going
all the way as we think it is so when
did the first real cancer start to
develop into cancer meaning it left just
the word itself and turned into a
malignant cell a cancerous cell a cell
that became destructive or a tumor that
became filled with malignant cells and
so forth when did that all start right
in the late
1700s the late
1700s that's when the first cancer
started that alone is important to
understand for so many reasons that's
when the first cancer started and those
cancers weren't the cancers we're
dealing with now today they weren't
those
cancers they weren't in fact in the late
very late 1700s there was only basically
one variety of cancer
docile slow to the punch not problematic
barely problematic and then by the 1830s
1840s a couple of other cancer varieties
stemmed from it still
doile but a little bit more aggressive a
little bit more
worse the first cancer started around
the Industrial Revolution the Industrial
Revolution which gave that was the birth
of chemistry that was the birth of the
chemical world this is when cancer
started understand that it started when
man started playing with chemicals
started playing with chemicals in the
lab chemistry
that's when it first started and those
chemicals were were created and worked
on and being the chemical world was
being built the industrial world was
being built we were burning things in
the air we never burnt before we were
playing with different things we were
synthesizing synthesizing different
things different chemical compounds
different agents that we were we were
playing with we were mixing
metals and we were learning how to use
chemistry for the first time in history
really learning how to use chemistry for
the first time in in history and we are
learning how to do things with it we are
learning how to play with metal with it
to change the structure of
metals and to even do more than that and
we were burning chemicals and burning
them and they weren't the chemicals we
have today which is why the
cancers weren't so bad the cancers
weren't so bad at this point now of
course in the in the you know 1700s and
1800s we had all kinds of different
tumors and we had different varieties of
tumors and they were getting worse
benign tumors different illnesses
different sicknesses to that point but
cancer itself cancer itself and the
cells of cancer wasn't in its you know
great day at that point at all but it's
the birth of the basically the
industries it was the birth of the
chemical playing around with chemicals
and the
industries okay and here's the deal now
as we go today now where we are today
there are a lot of different varieties
of cancers now we know that you know
that not telling you anything
new and but what there is there's a lot
of different
variations of why someone gets a cancer
to what degree they get a cancer to what
degree so all kinds of different
variables lots of them okay now science
and research doesn't care about the
variables so Medical Science medical
research doesn't care about all those
they don't care about all the different
variables we're not there yet you know
as far as science and research goes no
one cares about all the different
reasons someone gets a certain cancer
and someone else doesn't or someone gets
a certain variety of a mutated version
of a Cancer and someone doesn't or
someone gets sick in a certain way with
the cancer like someone it kills someone
but doesn't kill another person all
these different variables and there's so
many in the mix and to what degree
someone gets cancer and who gets the
cancer and because the reason why it's
all all Man Behind cancer to begin with
I'm not talking about uh any bad people
you know that are trying to help people
and help care people of cancer and help
I'm not talking about that I'm talking
about I'm talking about all the
different things created of why we deal
with cancer now exposure talking about
solvents all the different solvents were
exposed to all the time and the chemical
agents all the different chemical agents
were were thousands of chemical agents
all the different pesticides herbicides
fungicides
rodenticides um insecticides whatever
all those different
ones radiation exposure not just
radiation different types of radiation
different types of radiation exposure
all the time and that's just a fraction
of it then there's something else see
someone has to have two things there has
to be two things that someone has to
have in their body to create the
possibility of cancer there has to be
two things in someone's body you guys to
create cancer even though there's all
these different solvents and these
different agents and different heavy
metals different pesticides different
radiations varieties of radiation
different um you know
nanotechnology and everything else even
though that's all there there's
chemicals falling out of the sky even
though that's all
there there has to be two things that's
one thing that's one group that's one
thing but you have to have something
else you have to have a virus you have
to have a viral nature inside the body
it has to be a virus inside the body or
viruses inside the body so there are two
things someone has to have in order to
create cancer two things they have to
have chemical agent of some kind which
is a toxic of some kind and they have to
have a virus that's the two things and
then you got the possibility of possible
cancer you know and if you know unless
you do things like get toxins out of the
body unless you do things like knock any
viruses down then you then you never get
cancer even if you have the virus and
the toxins if but if they get out of
control more tox toxins accumulate more
toxins build up more toxins you know
pile on top of it of itself and build up
in different organs different places of
the body and the brain and the and even
the stomach stomach holds so many toxins
it goes into the lining of the stomach
wherever these toxins are liver
everywhere pancreas you name it and then
the virus the virus is is is increasing
in numbers if it's proliferating if it's
growing and that's the other factor it's
these two
things and that's the difference of what
you're going to hear there's another
difference all in its own so there has
to be a toxin there has to be a virus
the variations are endless though to
what virus and what virus
strain the variations are endless to
what virus and what virus strain and is
the virus mutated what kind of virus is
it
mutated and how many toxins someone has
do they just have a few heavy metals and
a little bit of radiation do they have
different varieties of of of you know do
they have all kinds of different
things did they have you know carpet
chemicals you know going through their
body you know from from carpet cleaning
services are they getting their home
sprayed are they eating only
conventional produce Non-Stop and only
that but if that if someone H has to be
forced to eat conventional produce
non-stop I understand you know it's more
affordable in so many ways for so many
people but there's things you could do
to still clean up the pesticides while
you have to eat that way and you're
still getting benefits from those Foods
that help counter that but the bottom
line is and what I'm trying to say is
the endless variations and then how
strong the person's immune system is so
how strong the person's immune system is
matters too that makes a huge difference
so each person is different everybody's
different okay everybody's different
someone can smoke
cigarettes for 50 years and not develop
lung
cancer someone could never smoke
ever but they happen to breathe in a lot
of hairspray over the years over the
decades you know to try to get their
hair looking prettier a certain way so
they just spray and
hairspray and someone breathe in
Hairspray and for some reason they get
lung cancer someone not spraying
anything gets lung cancer and didn't
smoke a day in their life
life I mean I've seen people smoke a
lifetime not get lung cancer and not get
any cancer any cancer because one of
those things that I talked about the two
things one of those things wasn't
there it wasn't there apparently they
had the they had the toxins they were
able to smoke for 50 years 60 years 70
years they had the
toxins that's the one thing remember and
the other thing
the viruses they didn't have they didn't
have the viruses they didn't have a
virus that's why old man Johnson never
got lung cancer and never
died that's why old lady McFarland she
never died she she
smoked maybe she got a little something
else maybe she got COPD when she's
92 but but the Cancer's not there and
I've seen that I mean I've seen that for
decades
happen because there has to be two
things there has to be two things and
the variations matter including even
stress including stress because
adrenaline doesn't help either
adrenaline can be really noxious can be
really
toxic and really difficult to deal with
cancer research like I said is based on
cancer that's manifested already it's it
that's what it's really based on
it it it always has been it's about okay
that's it there it is let's biopsy it
let's cut it out you know let's do what
we got to do I mean whatever I'm not
saying that that's bad or good everybody
has um choices they make and directions
they go to how they handle a situation
and how they deal with it and some
people you know they get surgery some
people don't some people get chemo some
people just get radiation there's a
whole vast differences to how many
people in what they do and can't clinics
have gotten a lot better they have
gotten a lot better it's not like the
Dark Ages you know and and that's true
they have improved in so many different
ways they've reduced and lowered
variations of chemotherapy they're
working on targeting targeting what
chemotherapy works with what cells and
so forth and so there is there's there's
definitely differences that have made a
difference in people's lives and and and
I stand behind science and research 100%
you need to know that one of the things
that happens is when I talk about how
science research hasn't discovered this
or they don't understand this or maybe
something Trinkle on down the line
that's not in your best interest it
doesn't mean I don't believe or love
medical research and Science and I don't
stand behind it and love the people
behind it and what they're doing you
need to know that it's important but but
you also need to know the other side or
the piece pieces of it to fill in
so you know with the pesticides and the
herbicides and everything else we have
going on and not just that the different
metal and all the different toxins and
the
solvents that's one aspect of it and
then you have to have the viral present
that's act that's the other side of it
now why why will that create cancer so
back to this why will that create cancer
because the virus has to have something
to feed on it has to have a fuel it has
to have something it can
eat something that it can
consume and you might be a a biologist
or something right now listening and
you're like viruses don't eat anything
no that's not true that's misinformation
they even teach in
school viruses eat that's how they
produce they eat they can't produce if
they don't get the food they need and if
you don't have a virus in you then you
don't have to
worry I mean but chemicals and harmful
substances don't do us any good and
could give us other health conditions
and problems and cause all kinds of
variations like tumors that are benign
like the tumors back in the day in 400
BC when the word cancer was created and
it was a benign tumor it wasn't
cancerous cells that we deal with today
because that's a new thing new thing in
history but the but but the benign
tumors back in 400 BC were filled with
heavy metals especially back in the day
in the Rome day in the Greek you know
all that that day back that time in
history and Greece all that time in
history what was going on there was
heavy metals were saturating the
waterways everybody was using heavy
metals like never before in history and
there were some toxic substances for
certain varieties of of minerals and and
chemistry starting nothing like it did
in the dustrial revolution but it
created toxic problems such as tumors
that weren't
cancerous and those tumors have to feed
too but cancer cells need they need the
very toxins I was talking about before
they need those toxins in order to
survive in order to eat in order to turn
into something in order to turn into
something a virus cell a viral cell is
not a cancer
cell it's not a cancer
cell nope not yet it's not a cancer cell
so a virus cell has to eat and what it
does if it's eating a poison it has to
eliminate it and this is where we're
going to go into more information so
fasten your seat bels again I know I
probably drive you crazy guys with that
one but you know get ready get your you
know get your herbal tea out whatever
you need and the whole bit it's
important CU we're going in we're going
into some good stuff here um so a virus
consumes a toxin a solvent a pesticide a
heavy metal a plastic a feran a dioxin
DI dioxins dioxin the age of dioxins is
upon us that's one of virus's favorite
foods for cancer producing a dioxin
itself doesn't
necessarily create cancer if you
saturate a rat in the lab with
dioxins the rat will have viruses
there's there's no question the rat will
have viruses within it to feed off the
dioxin to create a
cancer so and I mean pesticides like DDT
too all those are still in our
environment I talk about that so many
times and if you you know I can't cover
everything right now I'd love to talk
about DDT for an hour I can't you just
have to keep on looking into all my past
shows and things I do but but what
happens is once that virus consumes a
toxin it remanufactures it's a
remanufacturing indust industrial
machine itself is that tiny viral
cell and it remanu factures the toxin it
changes the chemical
compounds of the chemical structure the
biochemical turns it into a biohazard
worse than it was originally turns it
into a biohazard in a worse
State okay than it originally was to
begin with and then it releases it into
the body's
atmosphere as something far greater in
strength and
destructive okay far more aggressive to
to the
body this new toxin saturates an area of
tissue especially if a virus happens to
be near an area of tissue such as say if
a virus is near or in the
thyroid so as it's eating the food it
wants it releases it so that would be a
thyroid
cancer so as it releases the
toxin in an area a tissue or or um you
know an organ more cells
die around it from from that toxin
because the cells are being poisoned so
when the virus
remanufactures and it releases that
toxin into tissue and this information
isn't out there this this is a big part
of the information that's not out there
and it's important for you to know write
down your notes cuz I don't want you
forgetting and I don't want you missing
out and once that that that toxic
remanufactured Poison's released back
into an organ or into some tissue and
not just floating around the body if
it's close to an organ or anything like
that more cells die in that tissue they
die of a stink of
death basically what that means is is
that virus's poison kills cells it kills
cells those cells actually are dying
differently than when cells naturally
die and create toxins so as cells
naturally die and create toxins in our
body on a healthy level that's different
these cells were poisoned to death they
were living cells and now they're poison
to
death and there's a decaying process and
they're very
toxic okay and then that that can even
be released throughout the
bloodstream which lowers the immune
system and the immune function which is
part of all this and a lot of these
rotting cells can also stay in that
adjacent area with whether it's in a
thyroid in an organ or
anything but these cells have a
signature attached to them now they have
a
signature because of the poison that it
was that from the virus the virus put a
chemical compound on these Po in these
poisons
and so there's a
signature these dying decaying cells
prompt an additional viral response so
more viruses are coming more viral cells
are
coming and when they come these viral
cells they engage in an area where the
first viral attack was for instance say
on a
thyroid so they engage in that area
where these first cells were done
dying the viruses then consume more
damage dying cells that were first
contaminated
originally and they
remanufacture the toxic dead cell
material okay now we're remanufacturing
again we're remanufacturing something
that was
remanufactured the poison initially that
got into the cells that killed it was
already remanufactured once this is an
important very important understanding
but when the virus starts to eat those
dead decaying cells that have the once
already remanufactured
poison the virus remanufactures the
poison again the living virus cell
remanufactures the poison again that's
what it does I'm going to tell you
that's not good so it remanufactures
those toxic dead cells this is a process
that doubles the toxic strength it
doubles the toxin
strength
so as the new viruses digest and release
the remman once again remanufactured
poison again it's in double strength
double trouble it's in double strength
double in strength it's synthesized like
a little chemical Factory
synthesized and just give you an example
of of when you when you take chemicals
in their basic structure structures you
mix them you you spin them you spin them
in the big Vats in the chemical
companies I won't name the companies but
you spin them you work them and you you
do the whole process and then you take
that you take a portion of that not all
of it you take a little portion and you
add it to another batch and you do this
whole mixing and every this whole thing
occurs it's almost like each vat of
chemicals gobbles up a small amount they
keep on passing on to the next one and
it gobbles it up then they take a
portion of that it's called reverse
Homeopathy in a way reverse Homeopathy
for destructive Natures not for healing
the body but for building destructive
Warfare chemicals and so forth and and
insecticides and skull and crossbones
crap you name it it's that so this is
kind of like that that's an example it's
similar in some
way
so basically it's like I'm saying it's
similar to the chemical factors
factories creating more more potent
versions of a chemical compound
synthesizing now if this process
continues the
poison gets stronger and stronger it can
quadruple in strength
and then get even stronger and don't get
scared don't get worried this isn't a
this isn't a scary show this show is a
powerful show to give you an
understanding you never had before so
you can do something about it and really
protect yourself like really protect
yourself not just stupid protecting talk
like really protect yourself good stuff
really good stuff is you know it's
important to know all this so the poison
severely
mutates and then what happens is the
viruses start to adapt for that new
poison so the viruses are eating these
denatured cells these death these dying
cells that are in a little tissue a
little organ tissue they're they're
eating these cells that have already
been remanufactured even once or
twice and they're eating these
cells and the viruses themselves can't
even handle the level of toxin they
created to begin with the virus can't
even handle the level of toxin that it
had created it's too much for the virus
itself the original virus that started
out it's way too much and you're hearing
for the first time in history anywhere
right here how how a virus mutates cuz
no one else will tell you cuz they don't
know there's no lab there's no chemical
La chemistry lab there's no biology
place there's no you know immune expert
out there that knows it it doesn't exist
I'm just letting you know I'm not trying
to do that to be cocky sounding and
eggomatic that's not it at all it's
because if I don't don't give you the
point and you just probably think this
stuff's online somewhere and you go out
looking around and you to find some
other interesting little tidbit of
information and you just lose lose you
know you lose
this that's why I say what I say
so the deal is the virus itself gets
poisoned in order to not let the virus
die which a few of them end up dying
from that noxious poison from that toxic
poison a few few of them do die viruses
and you say hey that's great that's
perfect in that situation it's not
perfect because the virus is quickly
adapt a virus quickly adapts it has to
adapt and in order to adapt it has to
mutate it has to
mutate that's what the virus has to do
has to change gears has to change gears
fast because
viruses the majority of all viruses
don't want you really getting hurt in
the end they want to live forever and
live free and live happy they don't want
to hurt you in the end just like the
retrovirus HIV retrovirus it it's never
there to kill anybody retroviruses don't
kill anybody it's other things that kill
people that's what happened with the
whole AIDS epidemic all all long all
along people aren't dying anymore of
AIDS because of new AIDS drugs people
aren't dying anymore of AIDS because the
fear of of God and the fear of dying and
all that's been been dropped back
because because and that's a big part of
why people died so much as they thought
they had a death sentence that would
kill them in two days because that's
that's how it was purported out there
misinformation it hurt so many
people but retroviruses and all viruses
they just not all viruses I'm sorry
viruses that are more just stealth more
natural-based um they have a lineage in
our history so the vir you know a virus
can get this poison in its system get
this poisonous system and die but but
but the viruses quickly learn from
another virus that died it quickly
learns and so it actually
adapts and once it adapts it can handle
a higher level a level you know six a
level you know
higher of poison so as it eating the
dead cells the human cells our cells as
it's eating the dead cells out of a out
of some tissue out of some connective
tissue out of an organ out of the liver
out of the lung wherever cancers go and
wherever cancers start and all these
different things it's eating all this
and get that dead cells it's
remanufacturing once again and it's
getting stronger and that stronger
material kills a few more viral cells
that come along and try to
engage and then more adapting occurs and
more mutating of viruses have to amp up
and the viruses
become a different type of virus and not
a virus that can make you feel super
duper for sick necessarily viruses you
don't even feel you're not feeling
anything going on you're barely feeling
anything there's nothing even going on
you're just living your life all is
good
so so basically that adapting
occurs and the virus has to become
something different So eventually the
virus goes to another stage where it
mutates so destructively or so
differently
because of the level of toxins that were
constantly remanufactured over and over
and over
again it had to change its game to the
point where that Viral cell became now a
cancer cell the viral cell is a cancer
cell that's when it became a cancer cell
and nowhere in medical history do they
know this part yet they know that
viruses could be a cancer cell they know
that some viruses create cancers they
finally know that now guess what I knew
that as a child I got that information
from my source as a child before it was
even out
there but they know that now but they
don't know the process of how it gets
there and the reason why they're not
going
to is because that virus isn't your
fault that you have it if you do if if
like they say 50% of the of the world's
population is going to have cancer in 20
years
versus you know the other 50% not having
if the rates are going to be that high
it's not your
fault that you have that virus and it's
not your fault you have those chemicals
those chemical compounds those
destructive compounds those toxins it's
not your fault it's somebody else's
fault believe it or not and it points
back to the
industries and if it gets out that none
of this cancer was your fault at all and
someone else is fallen and he gets out
there then there's hell to pay and
there's trillions and trillions and
trillions of dollars in Damages look at
it ASB bestus cancer misilo look at ASB
bestus cancer okay they got a $30
billion fund sitting out there for just
one cancer an industrial cancer asbest
by the way
asbest es bestus doesn't need a virus
that's why I didn't add it to all the
toxins and all the the the poisons I
talked about it doesn't need a virus
aestus on its own can create an aestus
cancer it's literally its own breed its
own breed completely separate from 99%
of all the other cancers which guess
what are viral cancers 99% of all the
cancers out there are viral cancers you
guys except for asbestos cancer but look
there's a$ 30 30 m billion sorry $ 30
billion
fund for people who've been afflicted by
asbestos cancer right right well because
it was somebody's
fault but if we were told that it took a
virus and it took all these different
host of chemicals right down since the
industrial re Revolution the
corporations and the industries and
everything else going back since 1799
since 1817 the birth of the industrial
re Revolution would have to come up with
funds of billions and billions of
dollars it would equal trillions and
trillions and especially since it's
going to carry on for decades and
decades and decades and more people are
going to get cancer and sick of can sick
with cancer and die and all these other
things that suffer with every in the
future unless they learn information and
protect themselves really and watch the
back and because more and more that's
going to happen it wouldn't just be some
asbest fund of 30 billion
it would be in the trillions higher than
the country's country's debt of 20
trillion do that we have now which is
the country's debt it would be higher
than
1920 trillion do can you believe that
yes it would be higher than that so it
has to be your fault it has to be your
fault something that is in your jeans
cuz you got bad
jeans jeans play a role in a lot of
different things don't get me wrong but
it's not why someone gets cancer that's
why the Brock 1 Brock two Gene with
breast cancer that's why the majority of
women with breast breast cancer don't
have the Brock one or Brock two Gene but
what happened is the misinformation has
to get out there they have to feed it to
people because if you know the truth
someone's going to take the blame down
the road someone's going to find out how
the first Epstein bars and the first hhv
6es and the first different viruses
started back in the early 1900s and who
started in where someone's going to find
out another $5 trillion right there a
payback someone's going to find out I
saw the chemical companies which
chemicals and everything else that's why
you can't really get a straight anything
out of anybody so they do it General
dioxin they Compass it into one package
so no one gets the blame no one takes
the blame you say oh dioxins could
create cancer it kind of do on a rat so
you know but that's about as far as it
goes
so
let's let's let's keep on going let's
keep on
going so here's the annoying part the
cancer
virus can do something it can create a c
meaning now now a cancer cell so the
virus can create a cancer
cell all
right and when it does this here's
here's what's annoying it releases a
chemical out of it a chemical that
saturates the human cell in the adjacent
area that was poisoned originally with
remanufactured toxins over and over
again so it can actually deliver now a
chemical a biochemical it can the cell
can produce a chemical and shoot it out
into adjacent human cells in a tissue in
an organ in an adjacent area and it can
do
this and turn a human cell into a cancer
cell and that human cell is going to be
different than the viral cancer cell and
this is something science of research
has not discovered there's a subtle and
critical difference in every
tumor and every lesion a cancerous
lesion in in any bone cancer there's a
subtle difference there's viral cells
that literally pose identically as the
human cell cancer so there's a cancer
viral cell and a human cancer cell that
pose identically to each other because
science hasn't been able to divide them
yet they haven't been able to open up a
tumor and know which one's which and
know which one's which haven't gotten
there yet that's another 20 30 years
from
now but that's what happens right there
so a human cell turns into a cancer
cell and the cancer cell the the the
virus turns into a cancer cell first
obviously and so it creates a human
cancer cell and they communicate and
they start to share the foods they like
they sh they start to share
communication for what that cancer likes
to eat yeah what that cancer likes to
eat which we're going into a whole bunch
of other stuff so I hope you're enjoying
this this ride um you know and you're
not upset or anything else just you know
just maybe some like I said lemon balm
tea is one of my favorites because why
it's one of the most powerful
anti-cancerous teas that I love so so I
love the lemon balm but Peppermint's
good too just to you know relax overall
as well Chom meal is okay so whatever
you got in your cupboard let's do it so
let's go back into this let's go back
into the different factors and
everything else so as more cells gather
in tissue and and they they can actually
poison more cells so we need that before
multiplying occurs we need a poisoning
to occur so the virus is poisoning more
good cells they're dying it's
remanufacturing again it's
remanufacturing stronger and stronger
like I said before the human cells are
dying turning into cancer
cells but multiplying has not occurred
and this is why people may just have a
lesion you know a really bad lesion on a
liver doctors don't know if it's good
bad cancer or not unless they do a
biopsy and some many times they're still
not even sure to be
honest
and so as this is occurring so this can
also create a whole bunch of different
carcinomas there's not just one
carcinoma obviously it's a really
popular cancer and there's different
varieties of mutated forms of carcinoma
and it can and remember variations
matter with all the different poisons
what poisons were involved was it old
DDT was it a pesticide was it herbicide
was it a fungicide from buying new
clothes at the shopping Mark was it uh
was it anything was it detergents was it
was it conventional detergents I won't
may name the names but all those
conventional deter detergents you know
you see commercials for that easily
could spawn on and feed a virus and and
create a Cancer all these different
toxins and chemical warfare that we're
up against so what occurs after a while
is a tumor can start because the cells
the human cells that are cancerous now
they're staying alive more than they're
dying so more than they're dying off
they're staying alive because cancer
cells at the beginning can naturally die
off they can naturally die
off they can't just like a virus because
the virus FedEd
information and so but the reproduction
of the poison is so toxic so dangerous
that's saturating more and more cells
and the cells start to accumulate while
alive and mutated and they group
together and they start forming a very
microscopic
membrane
extremely microscopic vessels kind of
like blood
vessels really small and it starts to
connect them all together kind of like
like kind of like when you go to a tree
and you saw all the different veins on a
leaf but more so than this kind of like
a
beehive kind of like that too and it
starts to connect with having an ability
to feed itself what it needs feed itself
the poison it needs feed itself the food
it needs to stay
alive and it so it groups itself but as
it groups itself it groups itself and
encapsulates a whole bunch of viruses
too that are also
mutated they become one
but what has to grow out of it is
angiogenesis well angiogenesis you know
you know that that's not nothing new
angiogenesis but I'll tell you something
new
angiogenesis okay are these different
blood vessels that are coming out like
tentacles so the tumor can grow and mass
reduce and take it take in more tissue
or even Tak in more cells through
angiogenesis viruses tend to try to
deliver human cells up the veins of the
blood vessels the
androgenesis um viruses start to become
from the outside of the tumor Delivery
Systems Delivery Systems and adrenaline
is a big part of this if you're under
too much stress You're Going Through
Hell all these different things are
going on in your life adrenaline can
help open up the the the the tentacle
the androgenesis and science has no clue
about these parts and I want to give you
the four warning on these different
pieces and it helps Drive cells up that
the that the viruses are bringing up
virus can bring cells up and also
deliver them up in different ways up
this these tiny blood
vessels and the
adrenaline prompts the blood vessels to
open up even wider it's why people who
are under enormous stress and don't take
care of themselves and have any
anti-cancerous foods and all these
different things can
can come down with a
cancer so as this is happening these
tentacles and blood vessels are are
reaching out the tumor can grow the
cancer can
grow but it's going to need more fuel
and more food and that's where that's
where the important stuff really comes
in to try to stop cancers try to reverse
cancers try to prevent Cancers and it's
foods and how foods
work and
that's where we're going to go into
we're going to do a little food time is
everybody ready for that we'll do a
little food
time and actually actually before the
food time let's go into a little bit of
Epstein bar let's go into a little bit
of viral time let's do that now in order
to keep a virus happy technically you
really have to be feeding foods that
viruses love that's another factor of it
so not only do you have chemicals and
poisons and toxins and all these
different things that are in your system
that you can get from all all these
different solvents and every all the
exposure I talked about but you can also
be eating all the wrong foods and
viruses love the wrong Foods now if you
feed the vir if you don't Fe feed the
viruses the wrong Foods anymore and you
just have the toxins you might not get
cancer you might even be able to stop it
it's the food component that falls into
the whole thing too the real bad foods
that actually falls into it but Epstein
bar which doesn't really which is really
somewhat of a doile virus and it's not
really supposed to create cancer as
anything it gets fed all the things it
wants and you know it there's different
strains of Epstein bar I talk about it
in you know all the time you guys you
know you know you've heard all my
different shows I won't go deep into it
but he talk about the 60 different
varieties that I've found um over the
years nobody knows about different
mutated varieties I mean I remember just
seven years ago uh talking to a chemist
and and and a biologist and an
immunologist talk talking to all three
of them because it was about a patient
and I was explaining about um about
their patient and my client and I was
talking about you know the the different
variety of the mutations of Epstein B
and they and they they couldn't even
believe it now you know some guys just
like yeah you know what I believe that
viruses probably do mutate and it's it's
it's actually for some reason people can
digest it better now it's amazing how
time has to go by it's sad it's really
sad though that it has to go by like
that so what happens is you got the you
got the uh you got the virus cells virus
cells viral cancer cells tend to also
teach the human cancer cells what to eat
like I was talking about what to like
and that's why a tumor can grow bigger
and bigger if it has a lot of mutated
human cells in that tumor it'll start
getting an appetite of what that virus
likes like for instance an Epstein bar
loves dairy products and loves
eggs and it loves all these different
foods we're going to cover in a little
bit but let's talk about Epstein bar
cancers carcinoma it's all Epstein bar
cancer every carcinoma is Epstein bar
it's a variety of Epstein bar that's
been mutated and can create
cancer and that's all the carcinomas now
if you have epine bar you don't have to
worry it's not about you're going to get
cancer or not no so you can do things so
that you don't get cancer you can do
things so you can stop cancers you can
do things and that's what this
information is about Epstein B
is literally responsible for all the
carcinomas it's responsible for every
prostate
cancer it's responsible for every
leukemia some
leukemias have heavy metals behind them
but you need the virus remember what I
talked about before you have to have a
toxin and you have to have a
virus all the
leukemias are Epstein bar children's
leukemia Epstein bar with heavy metal
preferably
Mercury and um it's all the prostate
cancers all the breast cancers I repeat
all the breast cancers Epstein bar I've
been saying that forever and now it's
information that's finally starting to
take that information just starting to
surface but I promise you I've been
saying that forever I'll go all the way
back in time on that one um I was the
first one to say that the first one I
believe um and I say that
because it's important to know the
information and and the differences and
everything else breast cancer Epstein
bar 100% lung cancers most lung cancers
are Epstein barus lung cancer no it's
not Epstein
bar that's what I talked about before
thyroid cancer is Epstein
bar all liver
cancers Epstein bar some brain
cancers Epstein
bar very important to understand so
that's just the tip of the iceberg right
there tip of the iceberg right now um
it's starting the word for HPV is
starting to get out where HPV
creates creates um cervical cancer
creates it creates different cancers
ovarian cancer creates um and you know
and that's that's out there now and it's
HPV
but HPV is always
present but it's Epstein bar that
creates ovarian cancers all the ovarian
cancers all the cervical cancers all the
uter uterine cancers that's epine bar
that creates us cancers it's just that
the more epine bar you have in the
reproductive system which a lot of women
have a lot of epine bar in the
productive system um the more HPV
because the immune system is lowered in
the reproductive system the reproductive
systems immune system is dropped down so
you can have higher
HPV if you're killing off HPV by eating
healthy and doing all these wonderful
things and everything and you notice HPV
is going down or a doctor says hey you
don't have HPV anymore chances are you
knocked down your Epstein bar at the
same time and had no
clue and that's how it works
there um I'm not saying HPV is this
great friendly virus that causes no harm
at all it can cause Scar
Tissue but that's not the scar tissue
that's behind the Epstein bar
reproductive cancers it's this important
bit of information I'd like to get
across um
so let's let's let's keep on going we
got we got some stuff to talk about the
different viruses let's talk about hhv6
real really quick hhv6 creates kidney
cancers that's a human herpes virus
hhv6 all the h7s the eights oh look um
saroma okay that's a herpes virus but
but science research knows that one too
that that's a herpes virus but there's
also hh9 10 undiscovered 10 undiscovered
hhv1 undiscovered hv12 I talk about my
herpy show those are all cancer
promoters cancer creators all the
different mutations of
hhv6 actually create a lot of different
cancers heart cancers cancers of the
heart cancers of the stomach Epstein bar
can create cancers of the pancreas
hhv6 K kidney cancer that's one of its
biggest heart
cancer um different types of connective
tissue cancer for hhv6 different brain
cancers for hhv6 and its mutated
forms so it's really the herpes viral
Family as that unit of all of them from
cyto magal virus which is kind of doile
but could create a
Cancer and these these the herpes family
is mostly responsible not entirely most
responsible being that other piece that
you need to create cancer along with all
those tox we talked about
before now in order for a tumor to grow
it needs to draw food it likes so if
you're still living in a toxic situation
you're getting doused with lots of
dioxins of different varieties different
kinds Fernand in the air you know
chemical sprays maybe you live someplace
and they spray all the time try to get
the schedule so you don't get sprayed
and hit all the different names if you
want a weed killer you go you get a bug
spray a wasp killer and you go and get
your can of wasp peel and you're
spraying it if this keeps on adding up
along with makeups that aren't
natural as long as creams that aren't
natural in certain ways um hair care
products hair dyes all the different
chemicals and solvents and different
varities perfumes perfumes are one of
the worst perfume
companies would literally have to Fork
over billions and billions of
dollars if the truth really got out to
how to separate these chemical compounds
where they originate from where they get
them from and how it
works like I said before like I said
before it wouldn't be an asbest fund of
you know of 30 billion if you add it all
up it would be way above the country's
um you know the country's debt of 20
trillion so what do these cancers really
like to eat besides all those poisons I
just mentioned there they need the if a
cancer becomes a tumor and it's a mix of
human cells and viral cells it's going
to need the food you're eating it's
going to need the food you're eating
eggs are number one number one on that
list
eggs now I look I would love an egg just
as much as anybody else I talk about
that so many times people are happy when
you make them
eggs and I get it if it's you got
nothing else to eat and that's all you
got to eat then we you know work on some
supplements and I get it you know if
you're trying to take care of yourself
and eggs is all you got I get it I'd
rather have you do something else like
brown rice over eggs if we could maybe
get brown rice and I realized that brown
rice is a grain and some of you are like
oh he's not ahead of the curve oh here
we go again he just blew his whole thing
his whole show because he's talking
about grains and uh but but brown rice
doesn't feed a cancer it won't feed a
cancer I'm just letting you know
whatever your belief system is on a
grain that's not the one that feeds
cancer but I will tell you I will tell
you this that corn does feed cancer and
that information is correct out there
been saying that forever GMO corn will
feed cancer without a doubt GMO canola
oil I wouldn't even I I I would probably
even steer clar if you're worried about
cancers or something steer clear from
them but eggs that's the top of the Heap
right there and that's recommended all
the time to everyone what every kind of
illness right now these days eggs it's
good for you it's got the Omega-3s all
that but no egg material and eggs
hormones and natural organic eggs
hormone-free eggs still have hormones
eggs are a ball of natural hormones from
the chicken I'm not talking about
injected hormones talking about organic
natural hormones and those feed cancers
like nothing else does and they drive
right up the tentacles right up the
endogenesis right into or right into
precancer cells which are virus cells
turning into some kind of cancer right
in and it drive they just consume it
they love eggs viruses eggs a whole bit
it's why you could beat your Epstein bar
anytime you can kill your Epstein bar
anytime you just get the V get the
viruses under control knock them down
bit right beat him down and talk about
it on the show on the um the upstein bar
show so so you got to look out for that
dairy products are another thing that's
number two dairy products milk forget it
goats milk forget it cheese forget it
okay kefir forget it yogurt forget it
any anything else I forget cream and
your coffee forget
it and coffee is not even great you got
it dealing with a cancer coffee UPS up
the adrenaline gets the adrenaline
pumping and then if you got cream in
your coffee you could be feeding some
cells so it's just not even
good I mean if you're really not worried
you don't have anything going yeah you
can enjoy a cup of coffee I guess why
not but the bottom line is it's the
foods that I'm talking about get driven
up
into the tentacles and get into it and
here's another thing that you got to
know about protein protein feeds cancer
now you're probably getting ready
getting the stones out and we going to
throw stones now break glass break
Windows if you need to break windows
then don't don't do that no if you need
to kick kick something kick something
kick a can kick a can down the
street but protein feeds cancers cancers
learn how to eat protein because here's
why protein doesn't digest so e easily
in us heavy amounts of protein it
doesn't digest easy so it doesn't break
down and it gets it gets into the liver
it starts to collect in areas of the
body and it grows toxic and it creates a
toxin so protein undigested denatured
protein because becomes denatured for a
multitude of reasons and it releases a
chemical chemical that that cancers love
to feed on so if you're into whoo all
protein nothing nothing but protein
nothing but protein you're in the wrong
game you can have some protein and
there's great protein sources quinoa is
a great protein Source it won't feed a
cancer a black bean is a great protein
Source won't feed a cancer a spinach
spinach leaf great protein Source a few
different kinds of seeds hemp seeds
incredible protein Source you know I you
don't need probably a lesson or a
teaching on that there amazing protein
sources potato Believe It or Not doesn't
feed cancer it won't feed cancer but
you're probably thinking well there's
sugar in potato sugar feeds cancer no
here's the deal the wrong sugar feeds
cancer and in labs they have proven that
corn
syrup genetically modified corn syrup
can feed cancer can actually accelerate
cancer but they have yet proven because
they can't and they never will never
will that fruit and fruit sugar feeds
cancer the reason why is because they'll
never have the sugar and fruit
accompanied with all of that color the
antioxidants all the phytochemicals that
stop and kill cancer they'll never have
the study with that instead they'll
separate
fructose and still even fructose by
itself won't feed a cancer I don't care
what botch research and I'm going to go
back to the very beginning remember this
here's how studies work so you know how
studies work when someone funds A study
in medical science both conventional or
alternative they don't want to know
their money was
wasted so when somebody has a big idea
like a belief system so say St there's
there's a big doctor that has a belief
system and they want to prove it and
they get funding they finally get
funding it's a big break for them and
they don't want to be
humiliated and they get this huge you
know huge hunk of money to try to
determine if their Theory applies the
people who fund
it don't want to lose that money that
person will never be funded again if
they can't prove what they were trying
to prove this is how this has been a
history this is going back in history
over and over again I'm just telling you
right now this is the beginning of
medicine so what happens is all right
that the theory will come out one way or
another as being proven but fruit sugar
in a piece of
fruit with all of its biochem all of its
amazing
phytochemicals to actually stop
cancer that will not feed cancer what
happens is so when you eat plain old
corn syrup and plain old cane syrup and
you're eating cane syrup and corn syrup
and you're doing a lot of that and it
happens to be in chocolate cake and
other things there's a combination of a
lot of things that feed a cancer that
can make that corn syrup make that table
sugar feed cancer It's a combination of
all of the wheat which is a different
grain wheat is a different grain than
the other grains genetically altered
wheat combination of that all the canola
oils maybe the lard maybe the fats
because fats also feed
cancers higher fat diet you're on the
faster a cancer can Thrive because fats
take out the oxygen out of the blood it
reduces the the oxygen out of the blood
oxygen kills cancer kills cancer
cells so when your your oxygen is lower
than it should be and those tentacles
are drawing up nutrients and they're
drawing up nutrients and they're drawing
up less oxygen than ever before because
you're on a high protein high fat diet
you got a better chance of not slowing
down a cancer so if your diet is you
know eggs in the morning and you know
and protein in the afternoon and nothing
but protein again in the afternoon
protein in the evening and there's not a
lot of room for what does stop cancer or
kills cancer which is fresh fruits and
vegetables and leafy greens and there's
not enough of that in there it's not
going to be enough to stop a cancer so
easily that's not going to be enough so
that oxygen diminishes the more higher
fat you have in the bloodstream it shuts
down the oxygen levels drops it down
systematically it drops it down uh
dramatically and so what happens is when
that occurs your cancers aren't getting
oxygen and Cancers Don't Like Oxygen so
they like the fact that there's lower
oxygen that's why exercise and you know
and and fresh food does matter fresh
fruits and
vegetables because of the oxygen levels
that occur in the body and when you thin
out the blood a little bit Naturally by
lowering the amount of fats you have
like you don't have sausage and eggs for
breakfast or you don't have a big of
butter on top of some wheat pancakes
with some lard in the pancake if you
don't have that then your blood will be
thinner more oxygen will get in areas
that cancers could be developing to shut
it down and stop it so it's really
important too so right now in the world
of cancer Sugar's the enemy Sugar's the
enemy as far as the information that's
out there right now but I want you to
know that that that line is blurred corn
syrup yeah that that's not a good thing
Thing by no means for cancer too much
table sugar that's bad for cancer but
what's really happening is fruit's being
thrown in there and fruit shouldn't be
thrown in there because as I talk about
many times fruit fear is is a dangerous
thing when you're dealing with Cancers
or worried or cancer in the family or
something going on you you got to be
getting those blueberries those wild
blueberries you got to be getting those
strawberries those cranberries
especially those wild blueberries not
the regular if you need get regular
blueberries fine blackberries black
raspberries yeah sure you know there are
a lot of information out there now it's
that they're helpful and people are
using that in their you know protocols
for cancer but it's more than that it's
melons it's apples it's bananas it's
bananas really
helpful okay it's papaya it's
mango it's lots and lots of
tomatoes lots and lots of Tomatoes all
these are in incredibly health healthy
for fighting and battling preventing
cancer kiwis another one grapes and you
might think well grapes are loaded with
sugar actually the sugar and grapes is
combined you can't separate the sugar
when it's eaten from the phytochemical
the antioxidants that kill cancer cells
so what happens is when you eat a
grape the sugar is going to go up the
tent up the tentacle up the endogenesis
travel the blood vessel and it's going
to go into the tumor
with something that the tumor cannot
tolerate which is what's in the skin of
the grapes it's what's in that skin of
the grapes or in a
raisin and that's dimethyl Resveratrol
different subgroups of dimethyl
Resveratrol that aren't even calculated
or on any any you know the labs don't
haven't even figured it out that there's
all kinds of different stuff subgroups
from dimethyl Resveratrol all on its
own and goes up into the tumor and it
starts to kill the tumor starts to
trigger off an anti-tumor shrinking an
anti-tumor shrinking
chemical that is inherently in your
human cells so even though your human
cells might have been mutated to such a
point combined with the viral cell
mutating becoming cancerous and them
both joining and being inside of a
living tumor that's growing even with
that there's still something you can't
break that's in that human cell inside
of a cancerous tumor there's something
you cannot
break and it's information there's
information there's a chemical compound
that stays in that human
cell that can be triggered to start
shrinking a tumor
and it takes and it
takes exactly those kinds of foods to
help someone fight the fight along with
whatever else they're doing or choosing
to do in life whatever really good
Cancer Clinic they found or alternative
Cancer Clinic they found and everything
else but the foods matter they matter so
greatly and the same thing with the wild
blueberry it has these chemical
compounds these dimethyl these subgroups
off the dimethyl R veritol these
subgroups that trigger off that chemical
compound in a human cell that's been
already denatured and mutated to the
point where it's a cancer cell growing
into a tumor and multiplying and growing
and growing and
growing so fruits and vegetables are
critical if you can't handle any fruit
for some reason you're worried about it
then you just bring in more vegetables
then and more greens and maybe some red
bell peppers and orange bell peppers
bring in some more different foods if
you can bring in the turmeric that's
really
important all these are important
celer is important celery juice is
important very helpful I talk about it
all the
time heavy metals get out the heavy
metal detox that we talk about which is
the sparine as sparine is a great great
weapon as well barley grass juice powder
a great weapon and you know and look any
kind of anything I'm talking about in
the supplements next with I'm going to
talk about you can always go to my my
page I don't sell the supplements but
you can go to my page on my website and
know what the ones I like the ones that
I favor because I know how they help
people and so it's a directory to get
you the right so you know what you're
getting weak grass juice weak grass is
incredible there's there's um you know
if you if you have a way of getting weak
grass and juicing fresh weak grass
that's a that fights that helps fight
the fight because what happens is
there's phytochemicals and weak grass
that when they're drawn up into a tumor
or or absorbed by D Atri cells that
haven't become a tumor somewhere that
haven't even become a tum tumor or a
lesion that happens to be active with
cancer cells now and that we crass is B
phytochemicals that help to suppress the
development the
growth so all these are important
supplements to kill off your Epstein
bars we talk about that all the time and
in the Epstein bar show I did before got
to have enough zinc in your regimen okay
that's important the lemon bomb's
important nettle Leaf is
helpful vitamin C lots and lots of
vitamin C tumors lesions cancer cells
pre-cancerous cells virus cells hate
vitamin C absolutely hate vitamin C I
like the Lipo liposomal C that uh that I
always recommend that's the one that I
like there's a lot of different ones out
there I don't like a lot of them um
there's a really good one that I
recommend that uh doesn't have corn in
it and all the lipos Som Seas they all
have corn in it so that's not a great
thing so it's really important to know
that so if you're concerned you want
preventative or anything like that you
do a wheat grass juice shot there's a
company called Dynamic greens they grow
their wheat grass in a field just like
say grass-fed beef you know how
everybody likes grass-fed beef because
they like that
more and you know the wheat grass grows
in a field because you know it's better
that way too so that's a and then you
can't get a hold of the that you don't
want that product then just go into yeah
the health food store and get the wheat
grass juice you need right in the moment
but the bottom line is it's all these
different pieces so I'm going to run
across them it's about getting the right
leafy greens and different green
chlorophyll substances in you but that's
not old that's not new information
that's not and and I know that but
that's okay it was
new back in the early 70s all right when
Spirit was telling me this is what you
need to be on this is what you need B
this is what you need to get and getting
it was near impossible back then near
impossible but the bottom line the point
I'm trying to say is that everything's
that are fingertips now resources like
never before so vitamin C is really
important um I like IV vitamin C if
you're if you're concerned about cancer
possibilities talk to your doctor your
cancer doctor everybody about vitamin IV
you know vitamin C IV that's a really
good thing and that's been out for
helping people with cancer we know that
that's been out there but you can also
take a really good lipos C if you're
concerned which kills off Epstein bar
knocks down Epstein bar lysine is
important for knocking down Epstein bar
that's another one that's really
important um so adding all these
different things licorice is actually
okay too and you know you can take
licorice once licorice tea is really
good you can do licorice tea to help
bring down Epstein bar um that's helpful
in many ways one of the things is is
that there's this whole thing thing
going on about estrogen and estrogen be
creating Cancers and everything else and
then there are forms of estrogen mutated
forms of estrogen that we ingest and we
consume every single day we consume them
out of foods so they come out of foods
so we have to be careful um if you're
really worried about an estrogenic um
cancer then eggs you should never even
touch I don't care if they're grown in
somebody's backyard you shouldn't touch
them so you you can't in milk and dairy
products and everything else I would
keep even in animal products down to a
low if you're concerned about any kind
of estrogen causing
cancer but estrogen in its mutated form
it's not it's not a um the woman's
natural estrogen that's that's being
produced by her adrenals or her
reproductive system that grows cancer
it's outside estrogens it's an entirely
different estrogen but science and
research is not separating that right
now that's another problem we have um in
general I mean I mean just that's a
problem all on its
own but anti-estrogenic Foods I'm
talking about estrogenic foods that are
actually the toxic ones that are out
about that are in Plastics and
everything else you could battle those
with the right fruits and vegetables and
making sure that you keep you know the
eggs and the dairy and everything else
down but there's little things you can
do every day every day you can work on
knocking down any kind of viral issue
that you have with the right amount of
vitamin C the lys
and having enough zinc reserves those
alone are important to knocking down any
kind of herpes virus um in the herpes
family hhv6 that create cancers epine
bars that create
cancers sparina knocks down and
kills viral cells sparina can stop a
thyroid from getting cancer by killing
off Epstein bar and many other different
viruses like hhv6 and the sevens the
eights the NES the 10 11s the 12 you
name it and all all the herpes viruses
ceglar virus all of
them and the simplexes one two but the
bottom line is you can do these simple
things get the spirulina get the vitamin
C get the lemon bomm get the lysine you
know that just that alone getting the
zinc reserves up to knock down the viral
loads and then taking the foods that
feed the viruses out and bring in foods
like some Dand lion greens some MH some
kale lots of spinach spinach is an
incredible War Warrior for for keeping
down cancers in people's bodies and
knocking down Epstein bar and then all
the different fruits grapes bananas
apples peaches plums nectarines
cranberries melons mangoes papayas kiwis
right down the road right down the road
all those should be in your diet and you
shouldn't fear them or be afraid of them
but stay away from the table sugars stay
away from the corn syrups because most
of the time those corn syrups and table
sugars aren't going to be by themselves
you're not going going to go and get a
vial of corn syrup and just drink it
it's going to be in something else
that's
probably really helping cause a cancer
meaning corn syrup combined with
something that's nasty like a bad
cupcake so we know that as far as grains
go if you're somebody who likes them or
don't like them you know if you have
nothing to eat you're not wor quinoa is
actually not cancer causing it's not it
won't feed a cancer is what I mean it
won't feed a viral cell Millet won't
feed a viral cell a black bean won't
feed a viral cell a sweet potato a
regular potato won't feed a viral cell
so if you just lost your eggs and your
Dairy and you're like what do I eat now
you can have a potato that potato is
going to protect you a lot more than an
egg would any day
anyhow and if you're someone that's
doing a lot of lot of animal protein cut
it in half cut it in half so you can
make room for the things that actually
stop cancer which are all the different
Le leafy greens and the peppers and the
tomatoes and the onions and the garlic
Garlic's a great secret weapon for
Epstein bar epine bar doesn't die in one
day and either do the other herpes
viruses but you can knock them down over
time and avoid cancer in the future
avoid the thyroid cancer the lung cancer
the reproductive cancer the ovarian
cancer the uterine
cancer all right and you can avoid these
the breast cancer can be avoided
heavy metal detox and all the different
fresh fruits and vegetables and leafy
greens help to eliminate toxins and
poisons so that you can't feed viruses
and get end up with some of the cancers
like breast cancer so all these are
incredibly important factors what I
would do is you know listen out for more
stuff about the Epstein bar that I do on
on the radio shows and stuff like that
and I'll fill you in more more more of
that as well along the
way but I want to talk about a little
history for a couple of minutes though
about the epscene bar and some of the
viruses they took off route back in the
late 1800s early 1900s because of all
the different arsenic combinations and
all the different antibiotic Creations
that were starting pre-antibiotic
era that were all starting and they were
using they're testing new fungicides and
new antibiotics on food purposely all
through the late 1800s and early 1900s
so we were getting a tremendous amount
of early poison in that day which
actually fueled a very benign
non-destructive viral cell that grew
into something more over the decades
through the 1900s and that's why it's to
the point it is now and I talk about
that a lot on the Epstein bar shows that
I
do
um prayer is important keep that in your
heart and soul all right and pat
yourself on the back take it easy if you
know know someone suffering or going
through something know that you can do
so much you can do so many great things
and you can do so many good things and
we take it one day at a time and we
start getting the different supplements
and I want to go across while we still
have time a few more supplements
too and um there's some supplements I
like I love turmeric I love curcumin
that's great I love coenzyme Q10 I love
that I love ala okay for helping prevent
cancers helping people along with their
immune systems I do like bees it's one
thing that you'll hear out there is all
the bees feed
cancers but when you
minus the when you bring down the viral
load down in your bodies when people
bring down the viral load down and you
bring down the toxic load everywhere
else a B vitamin will not be harmful and
that is misinformation about bees it
just so happens they find B vitamin in
some cancer tumors and they have the
discovered that but they've also found
every mineral and many vitamins and
nutrients that happen to accidentally
get up there because the the cancer
tumors and and the cells don't want
those it just so happens those th those
nutrients get delivered they don't feed
the tumor and they don't grow the tumor
the tumors and the cancer cells they
just want to go through this vitamin B
the thing a little bit with you guys
while we can um tumors grow from all the
other things they talked about all the
other things that it likes and the
cancers like and the viral cells and the
viral cancers like that's what tumers
grow on they don't
grow on vitamin B by itself you know all
the vitamin B's by themselves they don't
and they don't grow on a mineral by
itself and they don't grow on a nutrient
or a vitamin by itself and all those can
be traces of all those could be found in
cancers because it goes up the the it
goes up up the chot it goes up the
androgenesis it goes up the tentacles
and it also goes into lesions it goes
into different different cancers and
different Fabrics of you know all that
and it gets into different connected
tissue cancers and everything else and
so as it's going up in there there are
traces that are found and a mistake is
made about how Vitamin B's are really
dangerous with a cancer it's not
accurate it's all the foods and all the
poisons that the tumor relies on
Non-Stop someone can avoid a little bit
of B12 or they could avoid a you know
methola but they're eating eggs every
day while they're dealing with a Cancer
and that's what I'm talking about
critical and subtle differences of
understanding this stuff that's
important so I just want to give you
example too I mean people literally eat
eggs all day long or every day three
eggs a day one egg a day and they're
avoiding a B vitamin that can help
protect their nervous system and other
parts of their body so they could stay
strong protect their immune system so
they could stay strong
so that's another aspect of of what one
of the misunderstandings is going out
there I mean you don't have to OD on the
bees you can take a little bit you just
don't want to go to fishing and never
take a B vitamin because you're afraid
it's going to feed a cancer you can take
a little bit of B
vitamins so that's one other thing now
in the herbal world I love a lot of
different herbs for fighting
cancer here's the thing every single
herb does fight cancer every single herb
has phytochemicals within it that does
and fight cancer it does suppress
stop slows down or fights or kills some
cancers every single
herb so I like Elder
flow um crysanthemum flower I love these
I even like
Elderberry Elderberry is great rose hips
amazing for really helping with
Cancers all right you Yaro berock root
dandelion root little bits of that like
some tea could be really helpful Yaro
that's another great one Mullen Leaf
it's another one too so all these herbs
are really helpful and really wonderful
so if you're a practitioner too and you
want to try a different herb ibrite
that's a great one and like of course I
said before nettle Leaf lemon Bal those
are great as
well so these are some of the herbs that
you can you know think about red root is
a good one too that helps and that's a
good one as well so think about those
and incorporating some of those but
fresh fruits and vegetables no matter
what Avenue you go whether you go
Chinese medicine or you go to just a
different alternative doctor or you go
straight to a conventional doctor or
whatever it is that you're doing or you
know somebody bring in the more fruits
and vegetables lower the animal proteins
a bit if you just can't do without the
animal proteins have them once a day I
stand behind that but bring in some of
these other foods that I mentioned today
and um so a little recap we talked about
how it takes a virus and it takes these
toxins to create a cancer but viruses
cancers are almost all all viral so when
you really look at it it's all viral and
that's something that's always been kept
in the dark and kept in the closet so
always remember that you know most I
mean literally most and I'm talking
about most every single cancer is viral
that's that's the whole point now um and
there's people like look just a little
reminder again there's people that don't
get any viral sickness like they maybe
experience mono from Epstein bar when
they're younger and then it goes away
and they don't exper you know they never
they don't have the chronic fatigue they
don't have the fibromyalgia that I talk
about all the time that that epine bar
causes and they don't have that but then
a cancer can still develop later on
because the viruses could be a little
bit different there's still all these
different Vari ities of Epstein bar
talked about and different varieties so
recapping different varieties of the
hhv6 different varieties of all these
different viruses and especially epsteen
bar the Epstein bar is in you know
that's the spotlight right now you know
that's the spotlight right now that that
I'm bringing that I've actually brought
to the world like if if you look at my
uh look if you want to know more about
Epstein bar you get the first book
medical medium but just so you know the
thyroid healing book that one right
there is is even taking it to a whole
another level too but I always say to
people look you need both you need
medical medium books so you can learn
about the viruses how they work how they
get into the thyroid the whole bit but
the thyroid healing book takes it to a
level that no one's ever seen and even
the first book no one's ever seen that I
took it to that level but this is a
whole another thing so I tell people you
have to have both and then I I also when
it comes down to cancers in the
life-changing Foods book um I mean I
have easily over 60 70 cancers 50
cancers um easy 50 that's for sure Plus
in there and and what foods help all the
different cancers so you know what foods
whether it's lung cancer liver cancer
whether it's leukemia whatever it is
what foods help too with all those
different cancers so you know I I do
have cancer information throughout the
books the thyroid healing book takes the
viral information even further than ever
before in history uh at least iCal
medium history of course and history on
the outside as well so it's really
important to understand so
recapping cancers are viral and that's
the whole point and and that's what's
been hidden and it's about how that
virus like I talked about earlier how
that virus starts and what it does it
bring it starts and then it roots and
then it turns into something more and I
talked about how you need the toxins
that's the other half of it but but yet
you know if someone doesn't have the
viral issue if they don't have the
Epstein bar the variety of Epstein bar
the mutated variety of Epstein bar out
of all the different 60 varieties I talk
about in medical medium book one if if
you don't have that going on and you
just have the toxins then you can get
you know kind of sick in a different way
that's not cancerous you can still get a
benign tumor you can still get a lipoma
a fatty tumor and you can still get all
these different things or or other kinds
of sicknesses too be from having you
know constant exposure to so many toxins
and and it's like I was saying before
just you know recapping on like the lung
cancer thing too is somebody could smoke
for 50 60 years and not get lung cancer
somebody else smokes for four years and
gets lung cancer they have to you to
have the virus has to be around and so
that all that's important to understand
um but you know keep in mind if you you
know to to Really you know hook into
some of the there's a 28-day cleanse on
medical medium book one on the book
medical medium there's a 28 cleanse
that's amazing for cancer really really
powerful for cancer and the reason why
I'm bringing this up and bringing all
the books up is because what what you
have to keep in mind to protect yourself
from these Cancers and to protect
yourself from ever getting them or if
you have them you know getting you need
that reinforcement you have to empty the
body of the toxins I talked about all
the leftover toxins we inherit and I
might not have expressed that earlier um
in this webinar about how we inherit
these toxins heavy metals are passed
down for thousands of years thousands of
years in our family line it's not genes
that take us down it's not a gene
problem our forefathers have mercury in
them our forefathers have led Mercury
nickel um aluminum it going back
especially Mercury that's that's
actually one of the oldest and so we
inherit these metals and then we inherit
DDT from the 19 1920s 1930s when DDT
saturated everybody and DDT doesn't go
away you pass it on to your you pass it
on to your children just right just just
from the pregnancy itself literally um
and and it starts there right in the egg
right in the pregnancy itself right
there and that DDT is passed on and that
DDT comes from being saturated same
thing with all the chemicals and all the
solvents and everything else and we're
passing down a tremendous amount of
toxin unlike ever before in history and
then it gets blamed on jeans because
remember it has to be blamed on you like
I said earlier it has to be blamed on
you and the blame has to go on you and
not the mistakes made not all the
industries including the medical
industry and all the other Industries
because you know that's the whole point
so it's going to be thrown you're going
to be thrown into the genetic game
everybody's going to be thrown in that
and I know there's first of all I know
genes are obviously real they're
valuable in so many ways and they're
valuable in science I'm not
debunking that factor but I am telling
you that they're going to also use genes
against you when they shouldn't because
it's not part of the equation in certain
areas and remember I tell you at the I
told you at the very beginning there's
subtle and
critical differences the critical
differences one is yes genes are
important to study in science and they
matter in in many different ways but
it's not why everybody's getting sick
with cancer right now it's not it's from
all this all these toxins literally
being passed down and amplifying and
adding more more like never before in
history the thousands of chemicals that
are falling out of the sky every day on
us and everything else and that's just a
fraction of what I'm talking about and
so and including the inheriting the
inheriting the amount of poison and then
the inher inheriting of viruses that
have grown in strength so if if you know
if your if your grandmother had breast
cancer it's possible yes it's not a gene
thing that occurs where now you're going
to be genetically you know susceptible
no it's the virus that could have been
passed down and it could it these
viruses have information they stay alive
and they have memory unless you kill
them unless you kill them and break them
down and work on it and that's what I
dedicated the first book medical medium
and I dedicated thyroid healing for
breaking down these viruses and doing
the right things to knock the stuff down
knock the Epstein bar down and and take
it out and push it out of the body so
these things are incredible all this
information is imperative to know that
we inherit these poisons we inherit many
of the viruses and so forth but there is
someone to blame and it's not you and so
when you lose a loved one with cancer or
something happens where someone had you
know a loved one has or a child has
leukemia it's not their body you know
children with leukemia have tons of
mercury much higher amount of mercury
they have the heavy metals number one
they also have the monov virus the one
that creates leukemia that I talk about
about in book one medical medium and
that virus starts out the leukemia
Factor that's the whole point and that's
what's going on that's why there's so
many different now leukemias that
they're figuring out they don't even
know what to do they just use they do
the chemotherapy for leukemia because
and then they're using also different
drugs like immunosuppressive drugs and
chemotherapy together because they don't
they don't understand that it literally
is the Epstein bar virus that creates
leukemia and and many of the children
they they don't know that part to that
agree yet and a recap as I said before
cancer is only judged on the merits of
its manifesting already turning into
something already being something and
not like catching it way before so when
you hear about you know cancer
preventative and everything else from
experts and all that if they're not
talking about what we talked about today
in this webinar if they're not talking
about the information we're talking
about how it really starts how the how
the virus poisons the tissue and
everything else that the remanufacturing
the poison everything else that you guys
now know the truth the real truth the
real truth when we say truth out there
it doesn't mean it's all truth or
exactly the truth and that's another
problem too and so we can get sucked
into it real easy so the thyroid healing
book when it says truth about Hashimoto
on that book it's really the truth about
Hashimoto not not information and
studies that had interest groups behind
it okay and Kickbacks and medical
funding and everything else that had to
make something come out a certain way
the cake just come out just right
because so much was at stake and and you
know angled a certain way it's like the
whole thing with the sugar thing you
know corn syrup can yeah can instigate
cancer cells but no one studied a piece
of fruit with the cancer killing
phytochemicals within the sugar combine
that's never been put to a lab or test
to show how it kills cancer cells so
then all Sugar's ostracized because of
it all sugar is is is you know is is is
is called wrong when it's really the
things that you know we need to actually
cure cancer help with cancer the in the
it's in there and so these
phytochemicals so it's all about the
studies being twisted and bodged and
everything else is said the very
beginning in the opening you guys and so
because of that when we deal with the
truth and thyroid healing says it's the
truth about Hashimoto you you're going
to have to you're definitely going to
have to have your cam te with you when
you read that book because you're your
eyeballs are going to just they're going
to pop out in a good way in a good way
as you're reading that and you're you're
going to be like oh my God and so you
need to understand all this uh So you
you're you're you got the armor you got
the protection so you're you're guarded
in a safe way you know the whole point
is look we have have to protect you
that's the whole point and that's what
I've always done since I was a child so
I want to talk about the foods a little
bit too a little bit more about the
foods chaga mushroom fantastic chaga
mushroom reishi mushroom that's another
thing that's great for cancers now and
that information's out there that is but
I still have to remind you of some of
the things that are out there uh and
some of the things that I've been using
before that information got out there
once again like the like the reishi
mushroom I'm going back since I was 8
years old I was telling people to use
reishi mushroom for cancer and nobody
even knew what that was or how to get it
it was unbelievable Corps um Lion's man
those are all great I want to cover
juicing a little bit more deeper um
asparagus juice now here's how the
juicing Works to really help with
Cancers preventing cancer helping with
everything so anything you're doing in
your regime whether you're getting
chemotherapy whether you're getting uh
you know radiation uh um you know
synchronized radiation uh blast the
whole bit that that we do they l they're
doing better with radiation now they'd
ever did before even though you know a
lot of people are against it some people
hate it some people like it it's it's
just you know it it's complicated every
bit about it everybody's different every
doctor's different every Clinic is
different too so wherever you're going
whether it's the natural clinics where
you're just getting nothing but
intravenous or you're getting um a
combination of a holistic Clinic that's
doing some chemotherapy plus other
things whatever it is juicing can fit
into any of those places to help you
either prevent cancer um if you or or
combat it or help reverse it or whatever
whatever you need so so in the juicing I
like a base in the juice the base
meaning it could be apple yes Apple
believe it or not okay CU I know that
you know that's shunned in so many
situations which it shouldn't be on any
level it I mean there's so many cancer
fighting properties in an apple it's
insane so a little bit of Apple celery
which is a secret weapon that should be
a strong base cucumber could be a base
too now if you can just do plain celery
as your base you can do plain cucumber
as your base or apple but here's the
trick now it's adding it's adding the
accents on top of this so what I like to
do for cancers is and real cancer
preventative as you do your you do you
know a good half celery juice you could
you know good 10 12 ounces or 16 ounces
of celery juice whatever and then you
run some asparagus in you only need a
few ounces of
you know the the addition so asparagus
is one of them asparagus is one of the
the greatest cancer Fighters out there
so always remember that so you can do
this juice where you're juicing your
celery you got a nice glass of celery or
celery apple or cucumber and then you
put in your asparagus at the top juice
that in and you get your 3 oz of
asparagus it's really potent when it's
Juiced and you get that mixed in your
juice that's a weapon another thing is
cabbage you can then get your base you
get your celery you get your celery you
get your cucumber or you just whatever
one you want in the base like I said
before and then you take you take that
cabbage and you put the Cabbage through
there and you get a good few ounces of
cabbage
juice and that is another secret weapon
you can choose red cabbage you can to
choose green cabbage and that's a great
secret weapon um broccoli Sprouts
they're very potent very sharp but you
can eat those you can throw those as an
accent in the juice any Sprout can be
put through the juice or a little bit of
red clover fenugreek um peases sunflower
greens all these can be together if you
really want or separate and you you put
those you get an ounce of that an ounce
of peich juice or 2 oz of you know red
clover juice sunflower green juice peich
juice is really powerful micro greens
get the kale micro greens radish greens
mustard micro greens people can grow
these too you can learn how to grow
Sprouts so you can you can totally look
up how to grow sprouts and run a little
bit in your juicer and micro greens go
great when you have that base of of
celery that base of cucumber that base
of of a little bit of Apple if you
really want to break up the taste and
then you add your micro greens some kale
greens some radish and mustard of course
you can put large kale in meaning adult
kale or you know older kale meaning not
the micro kale where it's the baby you
can you can put some kale in as as also
an addition in your juice some spinach
all those are incredible for cancers but
I'm giving you the different
varieties and what you can do um to
really you know have that juicing added
into it all and remember once again
don't forget all the different fruits
you can have in your diet the wild
blueberries are by far one of the
greatest anti-cancerous foods on this
planet Earth right here and um and you
know always remember that so that should
be in your smoothies the heavy metal
detox smoothie once again just throwing
that at you um make sure that's a a
piece of it all because you're pulling
out heavy metals and other toxins and
other dioxins never underestimate the
power of cilantro in the heavy metal
detox and you can do cilantro in your
juices too and when but when you do the
heavy metal detox the barley grass juice
powder and you know you got your
spirulina and you got your cilantro and
you got your wild blueberries and your
douls don't underestimate the power of
those those not only take out heavy
metals and the wild blueberries I said I
said that already they not only take the
heavy metals out but they take Plastics
out they take DDT out in the liver
that's been there long before you were
born meaning in your in your parents and
in their parents takes out all kinds of
things chemical solvents from carpets
from rugs from you know just anything
that you've gotten into you throughout
the years that is feeding the original
viruses that start up cancer and so
don't underestimate that the power of
that as well
uh always remember that so um and hey
look uh bottom line is when you get that
copy of thyroid healing in your hands
you're going to have more information
than you just ever thought existed and
I'm really excited about that I would
get medical medium because I got the 28
day cleanse which I love for cancer
always have it's it's incredible for for
helping people with cancer because what
it does thins out the blood gets oxygen
oxygen in places where cancer doesn't
want oxygen and that's what I really
like and so no matter what your diet is
you know whatever your diet is too you
can always do a 28- day cleanse to
really support yourself protect yourself
and have that extra extra bonus um you
know if you're dealing with Cancers or
anything like that keep your diet
relatively lowfat if you love animal
products like I said you know just you
know keep them don't don't be you know
don't do the bacon in the morning the
the eggs for lunch the eggs and tuna for
lunch and then you know you move and
then dinner time lots of chicken and
beef try to pick one of those things
just don't do the eggs of course and um
because you want your blood not so fat I
have nothing against animal products
it's just that you don't want the blood
so thick so thick and pasty that oxygen
and nutrients can't get phytochemicals
that stop cancer can't get to tumors to
cysts to lesions to tissue that needs to
repair itself and and that's really
important to understand regardless of
what experts say out there and like I
said before some of the stuff is going
to be something completely opposite to
what you've heard what you've known but
you know I've seen success for decades
proven success for decades and decades
with all illnesses so so we we like to
give people what they need for sure and
um look when you knock your viral load
down when you knock that Epstein bar
down that res that sits in so many of us
when you knock that down you knock down
other viruses that could be trouble um
you take take control you actually take
control and it moves you forward you
take control into a place of healing
that you didn't even know existed
meaning giving you protection for the
future your future self your future self
because you know we look at ourselves in
the future we don't want to see
ourselves sick we don't want to see
ourselves dealing with with a cancer or
fibromyalgia or ra or all these things I
talk about Epstein bar creates and
causes or Hashimoto or whatever it is
you know I you don't want to have to see
yourself sick in the future and so you
want to knock your viral loads down and
that's what a part of all this is too so
keep in mind um with all all of
everything I said today and um and yeah
we move forward and that's the bottom
line we move forward so I think this
concludes at least one part one part and
look we're going to be doing a lot more
than this so just please listen out
because we're going to we're going to be
doing more than this and going to go in
depth in other ways and other different
illnesses and everything else including
with what we're talking about here again
I'm honored you're here I'm honored
you're with me today you know when I was
given the gift it wasn't for me when I
when I was young when I was a child when
it was given to me it was for you guys
and I knew that then and uh and I know
it now and so anything I can do
providing any bit of piece of
information that could help you in any
way that's what I'm here for blessings I
love you take care and uh God bless
you