$19 right there amazon.com us
$19 for the protocols book that is
insane heavy metal detox cleanses heavy
metal detox smoothie all the information
in here all the different protocols for
all the different autoimmune and
neurological conditions man this is like
jacked up times a th000 this book is so
pumped up with all kinds of different
stuff in it so I just wanted to say
what's happening out there people are
getting neurological symptoms all day
long that's what they're dealing with
tightness of the chest tightness of the
throat Tinkles and numbness aches and
pains ringing in the ears ttis vertigo
dizziness jaw pain back pain head pain
head fuzziness and tingles all kinds of
different boom Facial Pain trigeminal
neuralgia I'm just naming a few things
this book right here the answer is in
here and this doesn't even include like
fibromyalgia ra and all kinds of other
different conditions thyroid problems
the whole point
what I'm trying to say $19 right there
amazon.com us Black Friday
58% off you guys have to understand like
how crazy that is ready brain saver
packed with information all of the
troublemakers we deal with out there all
the information in here all the
Troublemaker supplements people do that
hurt themselves with all these different
things that are out there like talking
about all the different charcoal and the
bentonite clay and everything else
people do the Pearl powder so by
carbonate talking about why to stay away
from all that stuff talking about how to
heal all of it in here incredible
symptoms conditions explained about why
you have a symptom what it is what's
causing it breast implant illness that's
just one thing this these books are
packed I'm just telling you right here
so $24 freaking dollar at amazon.com us
$24 I'm just telling you right now how
insane that is and what that means so
check it out get some for Christmas
presents for people you know get some
for holidays get people the answers so
they can heal because they deserve the
right to heal it's our god-given right
to heal our symptoms to heal our bodies
to reverse our symptoms and everything
okay this is brain saver right there and
that's brain saver protocols autoimmune
mental health neurological and then
depression the anxiety the OCD the
bipolar
depersonalization all the different
stuff that's happening with people's
brains right there that is critical
right here critical to help them heal if
you know medical medium books you know
they work if you know mm books you know
about the street cred you know about the
record the track record of what these
books have done in the last 10 years
saving lives people who never thought
they can heal B everyone everywhere to
everyone tried everything and they
healed that's what these books do their
Bibles out there to turn people's lives
around I'm not even talking about the
100 recipes in here I'm not even talking
about that these books are insane for
healing incredible they really are
absolutely incredible profound
information from above I just want
people to know it's the lowest price
that's ever been for these books it's
why I'm excited I wanted to do a live
and talk about different things like
supplement Sensitivity I want to go into
that a bit a bit if you guys don't mind
and some other things too but you have a
right to know that this is
$19 and this is
$24 okay get ready though when you get
these books realized there there's so
much information it's going to take time
to get through it all but you become the
expert once you have this kind of
empowerment in your hand and maybe
you're not sick maybe you're not even
sick so forget it don't even worry for
now get it when you get sick then get
the books when you get sick down the
road but if you're somebody that's
struggling and you have a symptom and
you have a condition and you might want
to learn about it or what the cause is
or what's going on you might want to
heal it please check these out right now
Black Friday the whole thing with the
sale on these books $19
$24 it's unbelievable let's get down to
business let's get down to the business
of making sure people know what to do
for healing how to heal I want to talk
about supplement sensit sensitivity
these first and then I want to move on a
little bit past that right there okay
and if you want to know there's
protocols in here what to do for
symptoms and conditions these books are
just jamming jamming I'm seeing you guys
come on so I just want to give you a
second at the same time
so we get
sick and we're
sensitive we get beaten down we get sick
and we become sensitive
and then over time we just start feeling
like we lose our
soul because when you get sick and you
can't climb out of it and you don't know
how to get out of it it does something
to us it makes us feel like what is
going on with my body why can't I move
forward why can't I heal you start
doubting yourself you start questioning
yourself you start questioning your own
existence and then you see it you open
the front door and you see people out
there gallivanting around you go on
social media and you see people best
life ever I'm having the best life ever
and you see people parading around
they're on the beaches they're in the
Parks they're doing Gatherings everybody
looks like they are fine out
there and bottled up deep
inside are these wounds in PTSD because
you've been so sick for so long you guys
know what I'm talking about so many
people have experienced this and then
when you start getting sick you start
getting sensitive you don't know where
to go what to do can I eat this can I do
this can I take this can I get this
supplement where where do I go what do I
do I've been to already those three
functional medicine doctors I'm going to
try this new one I've been to two
neurologist I'll go try this GP I've
been to this GP let me go try this
chiropractor I've been this chiropractor
let me try this acupuncturist let me try
this this person that person
nutritionist herbalist back to the
doctor again back to this back to the
emergency room back out of the emergency
room panic attack again boom heart is
skipping a beat do back into the
emergency room back here again back to
the GP back to neurologist and that's
how it
rolls and if they can't really
definitively Define your symptom
definitively describe your condition if
they can't get down to the bones of it
all and then you're just like what do I
do you go to this functional guy you get
loaded up with all these supplements
take my stuff my pram probiotics my
cleanses gut microbiome that's what it
is cell detox and you're there there and
you go to another person it's like oh I
got liver heat I got spleen heat I can't
do cold food can't do hot food oh then
you go to calist he's like oh hey you
got to do food combining you're
combining the wrong Foods together and
you're not eating right boom boom you go
this then you go to this guy and it's
endless that's what happens and you're
just like what the
hell and it sucks totally sucks for so
many people out there and they struggle
and they struggle they do they don't
have any foundational tools they don't
know where to start they've lost their
Foundation along the way they're in this
spare they're
struggling and they're living with their
symptoms and conditions and then in the
end their family might not even
understand them their friends might not
even understand them and they might look
just fine and look look just standy the
person can look good look okay but
they're dying inside they feel like they
might look okay from the outside but in
the inside they feel Doom and Gloom and
am I ever going to get out of this and
I've been to so many doctors and I've
seen so many opinions and I've seen so
many things in social media and I've
bought in this person's program and I
tried it and I've bought this person's
program in course I've taken this
person's class in course and now I'm
$22,000 Less in my pocket now I'm
another $1,000 Less in my pocket and
then the blood work thing all on its own
you go to this specialist they want
seven vials and you go to this
specialist and they want 12 vials and I
saw somebody leave a comment saying I'm
a blah blah blah nurse or I'm a blah
blah fonus and they were like there's no
such thing as taking more than a couple
of vials I've never heard of such a
thing and then everybody came on like
are you crazy I took I they took 7 12 14
40 vials somebody said 60 vials of blood
and then we just get knocked down from
there and then you find this other
doctor and he's like nutritional
deficiencies look at all this stuff in
the blood work and then look at this on
the allat look at all your food
sensitivities look at your IGG
Madness absolute Madness is what it can
turn into it's worth a swear I'll say
that you know why it's worth a swear
because I've watched it go on for so
long and it's about the person who's
suffering and struggling it's about
making sure that that person is heard
because it's there's never any time for
The Chronic wheel there's never any time
for the person struggling and swept
under the carpet so yeah I can deserve a
swear gets me emotional really
emotional I've seen it every day for
years and I've seen
people just get kicked down so low get
kicked down so low down down down down
down down down to the point where
they're rock bottom and they're just a
puddle of water a puddle of fluid on the
floor they got the bladder infections
the kidney infections the UTI they're
back on antibio antibiotics they got the
sinus infections they got the sore
throats all the time then they got the
ear
infections and the list goes on and then
the flues come rolling into town you see
I got immune system stuff in front of me
right now because guess what I'm so sick
of it I am so darn sick of it the flu
and the Sea coming into town RSB coming
into
town rolling in the holidays are coming
people are getting together for
Thanksgiving getting together for
Christmas and everybody's coughing and
choking their brains out and they're
sick and they're sick and then what
happens is when you get the flu like
medical meme information you get the flu
or you get the SE it knocks you down and
then the bugs rise up knocks you down
and then the bugs rise up
exposures knock us down then the bug
bugs rise up and then we have that
happen
too like right now I'm under a lot of
stress not sleeping that much doing a
lot of different projects and things
trying to serve the chronic Leo and all
the other stuff right and I'm doing and
plus regular life stuff that comes in
the way I'm cranking up my antivirals
antibacterials anti- whatever because
you know I don't want a flu com in my
way while I have two hours of sleep and
I'm run down I don't need the SE come in
my way when I have 1 hour of sleep one
night cuz I'm working on a bunch of
deadlines and I'm under a lot of stress
like everybody's under stress and I
don't need something Sweeping in like a
sea or a flu coming in and knocking me
on my ass I don't need that right
now because I know I see it out there I
got some friends and I know some other
people and they're hit with it and
they're hit with it right now and
they're just their throat swollen Galore
they're choking mucas for a whole 3
weeks and I don't want that to be
me but I know that inevitably so many
people are going to be affected by it
and they're already affected by The
Chronic sickness and symptoms that
they're dealing with every day you guys
have been through it you know you know
other people that have been through it
and you
know so today I'm talking about
sensitivities as well
supplement sensitivities and other
sensitivities so let's go into it a
little bit right now there are a lot of
people out there that are struggling
with neurological symptoms whether
they've been diagnosed with neurological
symptoms or seen as if they have a
neurological
symptom and they get just whacked
whacked some kind of exposure a lawn
treatment at a neighbor's
house pesticide spray drift coming from
mosquito spray wherever they don't even
know what it is diesel exhaust coming
from a truck that was running for a half
an hour near their
house any kind of exposure any kind of
exposure there's so many different kinds
and then all of a sudden something flips
them upside down maybe they got a food
poisoning and they don't realize it but
they got a food poisoning so easy
there's so many food born pathogens on
food every day out there in restaurants
and everywhere else it's easy to get a
food born pathogen and then it knocks
you on your butt and now you're
struggling and now you're in this weird
hyper sensitive mode your neurological
symptoms have clicked up you're in this
hyper sensitive mode your head feels
fuzzy you got the brain fog your nerves
feel kind of Itchy and Scratchy you
don't feel like yourself and you're
sensitive to everything sensitive to
everything and the last thing you want
to do is try to take a supplement cuz
you're scared to take
anything and you're in this place where
you're just super hyp
sensitive super hypers sensitive
and that place right there is not a fun
place to be and then you're scared and
now you're going to this different
practitioner and this different
practitioner and you should you should
see doctors and practitioners I always
have told people that from the beginning
everybody knows that but you go see
another person and you're just like what
do I do and they're just like well you
can try this or do this and then you try
something and you react your body reacts
you feel like something is off
something's wrong and your body reacts
and now you're afraid of everything and
then the OCD kicks it up a notch and
you're afraid of everything the OCD
kicks it up a notch then you're afraid
of
everything then the anxiety Rises and
then the depression hits and then the
anger goes up and then the anger comes
down then your anxiety Rises and the
anger hits the anger goes up anger goes
down then the sadness comes and sweeps
in then the depression comes and takes
over then you're depersonalized then
you're doubting Your Existence and
doubting your purpose then it's back to
square one over and over and over again
what I want to tell you guys there's
light at the end of the
tunnel there's light at theend end of
the tunnel people who have committed
really committed to wanting to learn the
information I get it there's so many
things out there and so much noise and
confusion it's easy to get lost but if
someone cracks into the information then
they learn
it the light is in this book the light
is in these books so they can learn how
they got sick why they got sick and you
may see tits and T tidbits and things
like that and tidbits out
there you may see
that and what happens is that when you
see that out there you'll be confused be
like oh he talks about epine bar here oh
this person talks about this or mentions
this but you got to learn the truth and
where it comes from because tits and
tats and tads and things and all that of
information out there don't compile to
what's in here and becoming an experts
critical let's go into supplement
sensitivities a little
bit there may come a time in your life
where you're hyp sensitive and you've
been burned by supplements and you don't
like it because you're super sensitive
you can't take anything you can't do
anything then that happens out there one
of the reasons why there's supplements
out there that have citric acid in it
they have all these different
undisclosed things like C citric acid
and they cause problems with so many
people Terra over there on YouTube
please talk more about sensitivities to
to stimulation sound motion mental
stimulation reading talking ET
absolutely what what happens is those
are all neurological
symptoms a sensitive nervous system can
make it so you're actually sensitive to
noise you're sensitive to the front door
opening if you have if you're living
with family and someone opens the front
door you're going to feel it you're just
going to feel it and you're going to be
really sensitive you're going to be
sensitive to a Full Moon you're going to
be sensitive to a storm a wind wind
storm you're going to be sensitive to
when the cold weather sweeps
in and you can be sensitive to when the
hot weather comes in you could be
sensitive when the humidity Rises
sensitive when the air gets too dry
sensitive when the heat's on in the
house when it's cooled out sensitive to
when the air conditioner's on in the
house when it's hot out you can be fine
for years and then suddenly you're
sensitive to everything and
anything fine for years
what happens is with a lot of Sensi
sensitive people it's the sensitive
nervous system syndrome is what it is
the sensitive nervous system
syndrome basically what that means is
anything and everything can just rattle
your vegus nerves rattle your trial
nerves rattle your frenic nerves rattle
all the nerves in your body and bring
you to a place where you're just you're
just you can't you want to jump out of
your skin
and you feel like you might even seizure
kind of feeling where you almost feel
like it's pushing you over the edge
where you almost can't stand it anymore
and you
just you just feel like you're losing it
sensitivities from sensitive nerves can
make us feel inadequate make us feel
like something's wrong make us feel
like we're not doing good at all and
it's a hard place to be a hard place to
feel I feel for anybody who's going
through any of that
I really do truly truly
truly
and when it comes down to sensitivities
when we get exposed to something and
we're really hyp sensitive something
triggers triggers us in our life and
we're sick now whether it's pathogens
creating neurotoxins medical M
information got to say
it with there pathogens triggering off
you know things with neurotox toxins
whether it's strep bacteria whether it's
toxic heavy metals whether it's
pesticides herbicide sprays
somewhere whatever it is we get
sensitive and these things trigger us
our our nervous system can get inflamed
from it and our nervous system can get
allergic to it so then now it's time to
heal so we go we try a supplement and we
feel like we
react we try to eat something different
and we feel like we can't handle it and
we react sensitivities that occur and
now we're stuck because then it becomes
this thing where we get wrapped up all
in it and rightfully so because it's
real the feelings we're having are real
they're not fake they're
real they're real true symptoms we're
actually experiencing even though
someone else hearing it might be like
what do you mean you can't handle some
noise what do you mean you can't handle
some hot some cold you you can't handle
the heater on here you can't handle this
you can't handle the blanket being too
warm you can't handle whatever it is you
can't handle something stimulating on
television you can't see a movie or
watch an action-packed movie you can't
do things that you want to do cuz the
nervous system got really hypers
sensitive and then it becomes this
vicious
cycle it's vicious
cycle and then it's like I want to heal
I want to try
something and then a lot of people end
up trying something that's toxic or
aggressive or not great for you they'll
try some Alkaline ionizer Water they'll
feel worse but don't know why they'll
try some bentonite clay they'll try some
kind of scratchy microbiome probiotic
powder they'll try some kind of greens
powder that has all kinds of stuff in it
nobody knew about like scratchy scratchy
stuff and their intestinal tract gets
irritated everything gets irritated and
the nerves get irritated because when we
eat things that aren't easy on our
system while we're hyper sensitive or we
take supplements that aren't easy on our
system while we're hypers sensitive we
react and then all of our nerves
everywhere fire up and they go on fire
all of our
nerves the Vegas nerves light up and
then where anxiety attacks panic attacks
itchy scratchy um all kinds of different
involuntary functions and jerks and
things like that weakness in the limbs
weird
vibrations itchiness you can't scratch
pinches on the body ticks and spasms and
I'm just naming a
few and we become very very sensitive
but we have to
heal we have to move forward and we have
to
heal we need a chance toal heal what do
we do the key is finding the right
supplements it don't have things in it
that aggravate the whole thing that
aggravate the whole
condition so I talk about taking
supplements a lot I do I talk about food
a lot I talk about supplementation a lot
I talk about meditations a lot I talk
about a lot of
things but when it comes down to
supplementation people who are sensitive
I
tell you start with one thing that's it
you start with one
thing and you can do something with it I
know people out there like I can't take
one thing I just can't take one
thing and then people need to understand
that you can take one thing you
can but it it takes just a little bit of
confidence A Little Bit of Faith a
little bit of understanding and an
acclamation process so so what happens
when people are on Rock Bottom with
their sensitivities they on Rock Bottom
with their nervous system conditions it
takes some
acclamation teaching the body that it's
going to be okay it's going to be all
right because we got receptors in the
neurons that are basically saying I've
been burned before I've been I've tried
this tried
that I've done this everything
hurts and so what you can do and here's
an example right here I got some beach
12 right here right that's the vimer G
B12 so I want to show
you okay what you can do is you take a
tiny drop right
here right tiny drop and you put it on
your
hand just like
this tiny drop right on your hand okay
just like that so I'm showing you guys
okay tiny drop just on the hand just
like this you could even go smaller than
that
okay and you'll let it sit there if
you're somebody with
sensitivities supplement
sensitivities someone who's been through
a lot nervous system
sensitivities that's one thing you can
start with right there you got your B12
you put a little bit right on your hand
and you can just dab it on there like
this you can do this once a day once a
day just like this your body starts to
acclimate it starts to prepare and get
ready for something that's going to help
change your
life change your body
systems change the
balance so it goes into a better place
and you do this once a day if you're
somebody hyper sensitive you do this
once a day
day you can leave it on there just for a
couple of minutes once a day when those
couple of minutes are up you do this can
wipe it right off that's
it what happens is your body's now
recalibrating rewiring your brain your
nervous system your entire body is
rewiring to that
B12 to that supplement now I like doing
this with B12 because B12 is fundament
Fally how we exist keep that in
mind it is fundamentally how we exist on
this planet we need B12 or we
die we have to either be producing some
of the B12 on our own in our
alium we have to be getting B12 from
some Source something out there or we
cease to live eventually our whole body
falls
apart Rob over there on Stitch is that
it twitch I was sensitive to liquid B12
last year I've since been able to
tolerate it more there's a light at the
UN end of the tunnel there is a light
there the end of the tunnel important to
know Michelle you said your B12 is your
favorite because what happens is that we
our bodies
naturally want B12 our bodies no matter
what our condition is no matter what
what our condition is whether we got
fibro whether we got lime whether we got
ra whether we got some other symptom and
condition no matter what it is our body
wants B12 it does Cara says I've been so
sensitive to all supplements in the past
especially b12 with years of applying
medical medium healing tools and lots of
patience though it's now one of my
favorite supplements vimergy all the
way so on this test what happens is I
like doing it on the hand okay I do it
again I like doing it on the hand so
it's this once a
day what this does It prepares your
Vegas nerves that are inflamed It
prepares your central nervous system
your brain your
liver which is the
converter of supplements and what I love
about B12 I'm not speaking for all B12
out there I'm not because I don't know
the crap that's in beach2 bottles all
across the land I don't care who says
what and they got the best stuff going
on they buy the lower quality they buy
the lower
tier I've seen it all out there that's
why I support vinm that's why I work
with them because of this fact that
that's what companies do out there and I
become friends with so many different
companies and Company owners out there
and all through the land all these years
in the last 20 plus plus 30 plus years
and it's been the same story we can't do
that aw we can't make it good enough
like you wanted we can't do the quality
you want we can't make it so sensitive
people can take it sorry it's all about
the Dollar Bottom Dollar the bottom line
and themy doesn't do that they don't do
that to me that's why I actually support
them like I do because they don't do
that I become friends with them too over
the years and they don't do that they
said I'm not they said they said aw
we're not going to do that we wanted so
good we want to take it for ourselves we
want people to have
this and so I can't speak for all other
like like b12's out there but what I'm
trying to say is the methab balamin the
stos silab balamin right this these
co-enzymes right here in this bottle so
what I like to do is put it on the hand
for people who are
sensitive and you put it on their hand
you do a little rub like that you'll
leave it there for a good couple of
minutes you could leave it there longer
for 3 or 4 minutes it's fine
and you leave it there and you do that
once a day and then this acclamation
process happens now if you're somebody
you're not you're not even sensitive to
anything you take all your supplements
you do all your stuff you eat what you
want you go out you party whatever it is
you can still do this because you're
sending a message to your neurons you're
sending a message to your liver your
liver is already picking up on this this
goes to the skin it's heading into the
liver already drawing it in from this
process but in such a minute
amount on a level that is actually
Awakening your natural ability to absorb
assimilate and methylate supplementation
because if you've been that sensitive
where you're in that place where you're
super sensitive you've been through a
lot exposures Galore this is a way to
get it to really go into your system and
get you rewired re acclimated redirected
your body wants the stuff it wants be2
because guess what we need it it's
critical critical critical critical that
people have it so I want to show
everybody that right there that
technique really
powerful
empowering
truly Angela over there on IG I got all
stocked up with vimergy today and got my
free B12 so you know then so um you know
about the sale then at vimergy.com so
there's a sale there if you get over
$200 of an order you get the free
B12 which is
insane but it's
incredible I don't want a sale to go buy
and not mention it because someone's
going to be like why didn't you mention
it because I it'll help me if I know
there's a sale anyway so yeah I'm glad
you did that that's incredible so that's
the B12 right
there So eventually what happens is
you're going to get to to a point where
you're like okay you're going to get to
a point where you're like okay that's
that's another bottle I use this one and
you're going to be able to
do one drop internally take a look at
that right so I want to show you a
close-up on that I'll just give you a
close-up on the one drop eventually
you'll do one drop
internally it's like this you guys see
that okay right and you add a little bit
water and you take one drop just like
that so I'm going to go and grab a
little bit of water
now and here we
go this isn't hot like super hot just a
little
warm one drop and you do this once a
day not only are you doing the
hand the hand
technique you're doing the one drop a
day if you're some sensitive that's how
you start each
day that's how you do it the nervous
system rewires everything rewires your
body takes it in your liver takes it in
you're methylating all of
it so that's
important to know that's one way to do
it eventually you move on and you're
like whoa you can take more you can take
a drop or full a day and you get to this
point and now things are happening in
your body you're getting stronger you're
getting past
sensitivities and you're now taking
one
dropper every day I mean it could be a
quarter dropper and that's where you go
and now you're taking one dropper every
day there it is Courtney ma says the
sale helps me so much that's
incredible and there we
go and we got one
dropper now what happens with
sensitivities this is an important
understanding right here because you're
so
hotwired your nervous system's so
hotwired you're so
sensitive you can react to something
else but you won't know what it is and
then you'll actually blame something
else do you know what I'm
saying you can react to this you eat
this you don't know if it's that you
don't know if it was the food you had an
hour ago you don't know if it was
something you ate yesterday you don't
know if it's a supplement you just took
you don't know if it's a supplement you
took the other day you don't know if
it's somebody who came over to visit you
you don't know if it was because you
were in a store and breathe in all this
fragrance you don't know if it was
because you were in the grocery store
and the protest manager was spraying
down some stuff and cleaning all the
racks and rails you don't know what it
is you don't know if it was The Toxic
conventional flowers at the supermarket
that are just blasting out the pesticide
as you walk by you don't know if it's
somebody's cologne you were standing in
line with but either way you actually
are having a reaction but you don't know
what it is and the first thing you might
do is just be like oh it was that one
drop of B12 I had oh it was that orange
I had you know oh ho maybe it was that
avocado I had or maybe it was something
else and that's where it gets really
difficult that's why
I beg of people to make sure they're
actually learning and understanding
what's actually in these
books how much you can learn and
knowledge you can take in so you can you
can protect yourself through all this
process you can climb out of this and
he so it's usually a really tough tough
ride up when you got all these
sensitivities it's a tough tough ride up
the ladder the healing ladder because
it's like I always said this is never
ever gets old this never
ever gets old three steps up two steps
back three steps up two steps back five
steps
up couple steps back six steps up one
step back back to three steps up two
steps back boom four steps back boom
seven steps up two more steps back
that's how healing
works and you're going up the ladder
that's how it works this never gets old
it's one of the most
profound powerful pieces of scripture
that are in the medical medium books all
these years three steps up two steps
back learning this is critical to
Healing you got sensitivities you got
supplement sensitivities food
sensitivities air sensitivities water
sensitivities you don't know if you're
coming or going and you're working on
your healing process you go three steps
up two steps back and that's how it
works as you're climbing
up yes and you're rising out of the
ashes this is all hogwash to someone
who's not sick
someone's not sick they're about what is
this unless there's some like a podcast
doctor that wants to steal the
information and then they'll there
another story they'll just listen
they'll get it and then they'll tell
their people and their people like oh my
God oh my God never heard anything like
it never knew we have low-grade viral
infections never heard of anything like
that never knew the flu can knock our
immune system down and something else
could
happen never knew heavy metals are
behind anxiety wow Dr blah blah blah
you're so
smart but the three steps up two steps
down Mac critical to know because it's
one of the most profound aspects of the
healing process so you have a shot to
heal learning that is
critical we take in the good stuff
sometimes it could feel like it's
knocking us back a little but then it
propels us
forward you do the right things and
healing is
like starts to move you do the best
things for yourself and you learn how to
do it and it's healing just like
w healing
just builds up and
then and then you're unstoppable and
then you
heal hundreds and hundreds of thousands
of people have done that they've done
the books listened to the podcast found
the right tools did the right stuff and
they look back and guess what it was a
dream being sick was a
dream kbu over there on IG can you talk
about breast
implants I can I can I
can um I just want to say there's a
breast implant illness chapter in brain
saver I just want to tell you first of
all of all this is critical to know this
is on sale
$24 never seen it at that price these
things are thick Bibles of
information but there is a breast
implant illness chapter in here that's
really really
mindblowing and I mean it's that
powerful that much information is in
here okay it's
incredible and I'm just making sure if I
can find it really quick
okay antagonist let's go let's go let's
go faulted testing there we go here we
are here we
are okay all
right it's in here it's in
here Takes a Minute these books are so
huge Texas lime disease headaches come
on eating disorders Cushing syndrome
depersonalization chronic
mystery guilt I can't believe that's in
here it's
incredible hypoxia bulimia burnout
atrophy breast and plant illness we have
found
it breast and plant illness is a term
for a broad spectrum of symptoms many of
them neurological important to know many
of them neurological breast implant
illness it's all about neurological
people need to know that you have to
know it's it's that is the same thing in
a way such as fatigue tingles numbness
restless legs heart palpitations
dizziness eye floaters brain fog anxiety
weakness of the limbs that's just some
you can have those symptoms because of
breast and plant illness people
suffering with breast implant illness
have spent decades trying to be
validated trying to be heard I'm just
scratching the surface it's a whole
chapter on breast ampl illness right
here so just just know that it's really
really
a powerful chapter
too so anyway I just want to talk about
the immune system for a couple of
minutes as well so lately what I've been
doing is I've been doing kind of like a
cocktail just grabbing a glass right
there okay so I've been doing some cat's
claw so I'm just putting in a couple of
dropper FS of cats claw right there two
dropper FS of cat's claw you don't have
to do this you can start out small like
one drop of something ask your doctor
what's right for you ask your doctor
what your doctor wants you to do okay
I'm just telling you what I tell my
friends my family two dropper
fulls there right okay um B12 let's pop
a little bit of that two dropper fulls
of the B12 in
there okay I'm starting to make a little
bit of a
mess and
then I'm going to put four dropper FS of
the propolis in here right now I can't
say enough about the propolis I'm just
letting you know cannot say enough about
this
propolis I won't go into it right here I
just want to show you what I'm doing for
my immune system during this type of
time of year so putting four of these in
here but I want to
scream I want to scream
propolis okay I want to scream
propolis
all
right it's all over the
glass there's putting four dropper fulls
of golden seal in here two
three four I can't say enough about
golden seal as
well so important all right now I'm
going to put a little bit of water in
here and I'm going to put some some
orange in here right now almost lost
that orange I threw it in an entirely
different wrong
direction and now we got it
right let's get an orange
cut yep I got my two dropper fulls of
cat's claw in here two dropper fulls of
zinc in here I'm putting a little bit of
orange why am I putting a little bit of
orange in in this one let's go into that
a little bit
I'm increasing the chances of making
sure that all the phytochemical
compounds and nutrients and cortin
that's naturally like in the propolis
and all the different all the different
incredible incredible nutrients that are
in these medicinals right what I'm doing
is put a little orange in there because
that orange is glucose you know what
that means glucose
delivers the nutrient to the
cell and that's the whole thing I love
about vimer to begin with they got the
flax
glycerin it's a whole another game it
helps to deliver nutrients to the cell
right and then I step it up I crank it
up I put a little bit of orange in
there so that the constituents so that
the phytochemical compound so that the
anthocyan so that the the polyphenols
everything in here and the enzymes and
everything else that's in there and the
co-enzymes all get delivered easily into
the cells into the organs they get
pulled into the cells and organs because
you're driving it in with the glucose
you have to have sugar in order to take
a nutrient into a cell you can take all
the supplements you want out there in
the world all the different things you
want in the world and if you don't have
enough glucose in your bloodstream you
won't get all of it in your cells that's
an important piece of information vital
to Healing all on its own
Bobby over there on Facebook it's a
whole party in that
cup it
is mixing it up right now just Naturally
by doing
this back to this piece of information
on how critical critical this is it
takes sugar glucose in your bloodstream
to drive a nutrient into your organ and
cells big reason why a lot of people
take all their supplements and they're
doing the intermittent fasting and they
got their glucose is really low and they
just did a workout they did a workout
they were on the treadmill they were
doing weights in the gym they were doing
their you know their resistance
training and they're taking all these
powders and supplements and they're
intermittent fasting and they don't have
enough glucose and the stuff isn't even
going into the cells they're becoming
deficient and they don't even know
it um cyy says hi what's the brand of
supplement is vimergy check out
their Black Friday sale right now if you
get over $200 worth of
stuff you get a free liquid B12 almost 4
ounces it's insane seriously it's vmer
GV is and Victor I am is a Mary E rgy
check the description the links in the
description links in the
profile so what I do is I put a little
orange in here you guys because I want
to drive these nutrients really deep in
into the cells and what happens is when
you're sick and you got neurological
problems if you don't have some glucose
bringing those nutrients into your nerve
cells carrying those nutrients into your
liver carry them into your
organs they're not going to go as deep
they're not going to go as far and
you're not going to heal as quick not
going to move forward as quick any want
me to send this
down so
good so
good potent and good
so so what I do is when I when I work
with my immune system I think about my
immune
cells that's what I think about I sit
down for a couple of minutes after I've
taken a cocktail like this an immune
cocktail like
this and I just close my eyes and I see
my white blood cells I know I've told
you guys this before but it matters that
you still try it it matters that you see
it I close my
eyes and I see my white blood cells
floating around and then I see something
incredible happening I see my white
blood cells devouring the golden seal
devouring the propolis devouring the
cat's claw devouring the zinc devouring
it all and getting strong and I see my
immune cells getting
strong we talked about sensitivities a
little bit talk about the healing
process talked about the B12 on the hand
watch this video we're live right now
but watch us from the beginning if you
missed it or you just rolled into
town it's all important
information and check out the books
because the books
are dirt sheep
on amazon.com us for Black Friday I
guess right now I can't believe it $24
$19 don't miss out whatever you do wild
blueberry dreams good to see you just
took my micro C haven't gotten sick
since April it's my longest streak aw
yeah love
it
micro right
there um I'm going to make a really
quick as we're just doing this a really
quick um vitamin C shock therapy medical
me and vitam C shock therapy Barry griby
girl says I already bought medical
medium books for my teacher gifts for
Christmas this year love
that love
that all right I just put some micro in
there I'm going to drop some honey in
here this is the um vitamin C shock
therapy medical me vitamin sea shock
therapy right there I'm going to put
some orange in here you guys see this
all
right orange
honey the micro C powder right
there that's not ascorbic acid you guys
see the micro SE powder right there
that's not ascorbic acid uh uh not that
stuff that Burns Burns a hole in your
gut nope not the stuff that gives you
the runs or diarrhea not the stuff you
got to worry about and that's a thing if
you're sensitive and you take the wrong
vitamin C now you're just like what do I
I do that's the micro C I just put some
in I got the honey I got the orange
let's go let's put a little bit of some
warm water in
here let's mix it
up boom that's some medical medium
vitamin C shock therapy am I forgetting
something and I'm going to mix that up
right
there two kinds of buffered vitamin C
see it's not a scorc acid thank
God and it's the only vitamin C that
ever came out the grape seed extract and
so
forth just incredible absolutely
incredible so that's the medical medium
vitamin C shock therapy if you look at
the books you'll find all the shock
therapies this is the pro this is the
pro um protocols book that has all of
them in there Kelly Burke over there on
YouTube aw can you please talk about
taking supplements like B12 zinc D3 and
iodine on an empty stomach this has been
something recommended by some
practitioners in the
community you can take them any way you
like and you can take them any way your
doctor prescribes
it but if you don't have enough glucose
in your
system then the supplements aren't going
to actually get deep enough into your
system it's partly why you see the
vitamin C sh
therapy there was orange put into the
vitamin C shock
therapy it's also partly why I was
talking about before I put a little
orange in the
immune little immune tonic that I made
cocktail but the good news with the viy
supplements because they're not in
alcohol they're alcohol-free they're in
the flax glycerin you do get some
glucose which is why they work work so
good it's why they work so good so if
you have to empty stomach them because
your doctor or your practitioner saids
so then that's that's fine perfectly
fine but if you add just a little bit
more of glucose in there you don't have
to do it this way maybe you had some
celery juice a half an hour ago you got
some glucose from the celery
juice maybe you had some lemon water an
hour before you got some glucose from
the lemon water so you're still in the
ballpark you're still okay
Don't Panic or anything you'll they
you'll still work it's just there's
people out there that just drink coffee
with no sugar in the coffee and then
they go take their supplements and it
never gets anywhere unless it's the
vimergy supplements and there's that
flax there's that flax glycerin and that
does help that that gets it in there too
so Frederick go says why does zinc cause
nausea for so many on an empty stomach
so first of all let's go into
that so
there's zincs out there they'll just
make you throw right up they'll just
make you throw right
up and that's why like vimergy changed
the rules with
zinc you go into the store you go into
whatever the health food store and you
look on the rack and you see the
different zincs and stuff like that you
take one it's got all that citric acid
in there and all this other stuff in
there you take it boom nauseous boom you
throw up so many people have just
vomited and vomited because of that the
liquid zinc sulfate the way it's done
with the flax glycerin and everything
else the way it's done with fmer is a
whole different ballpark but ask your
doctor what's right for you your doctor
knows
best and if you're really really hyper
sensitive yeah zinc just like selenium
can make you feel a little nauseous if
you're really really hyper sensitive but
the problem is a lot of other things are
getting you nauseous too keep that in
mind if you're somebody where zinc a
really good zinc like you're somebody
wear a really good zinc like this right
here gets you slightly nauseous then
that means you're getting nauseous when
you eat different things you're getting
nauseous when you take a different thing
you're getting nauseous when you do this
it means you got the Vagas nerve nause
nausea always
happening and someone who's sensitive
and they get the nausea then take it
with food take your supplements with
food is what I tell friends and family
you do what your doctor tells you but
taking it with food is what I tell
friends and family you guys incredible
this has been really really a fun time
I'm going to sip my medical medium
vitamin C shock therapy right
here check out telegram I'm leaving
messages you know like the Pride and
Prejudice
messages right and all the other
different um messages like the Maya um
Kowalski messages that I put there like
all the different messages I leave and
about chronic illness and what we go
through check out my newsletter get on
my newsletter if you can sign up to my
newsletter so you know when the next
light blast is so you know when the next
Stone collecting meditation is
collecting Stone meditation so you know
when these things
are be on my newsletter for the weekly
bulletin be on my newsletter so you know
about
sales that could really help you like
the over $200 and vimergy and you get a
free B12 cuz that is just actually
incredible and very amazing but either
way be on there when you get a chance
and make sure you follow me on
Rumble
telegram
right and YouTube if you can if you can
all right you guys um keep a light heart
we're going into the holidays pressure's
up people get cranky people have a lot
of different things
happen keep a light heart pat yourself
on the back have compassion for yourself
while you're going into the holidays arm
up your immune system arm up your
nervous
system love you guys
and keep in mind a couple of things too
okay wait what's this here with henna
says only medical medium information
worked when nothing I mean nothing out
there
worked that's that's incredible these
books are from Heaven they are saving
hundreds of thousands of people
worldwide and they are it's true and
they really are and the track records
there Lisa today I was was on a date
with my boyfriend going to the movies
spontaneously and we had such a lovely
time together all thanks to you Anthony
four years ago I was bedbound I will be
forever grateful you're going to make me
cry on that one definitely going to make
me cry on that
one for real Danielle only medical
medium info helped me heal severe sio
gut stuff low iron anemia social anxiety
food anxiety list goes on and on warms
my heart we know why we're doing this we
we know what this stuff is and I see
somebody every now and then they'll say
oh wait healing alopecia over there in
IG says your books are gold thanks to
your information I'm reversing
alopecia whoa and I'm helping other
people to reverse it too now doctors are
asking what am I doing to heal myself
and you tell medical medium and it'll be
like medical
medium no way
Danielle says it truly works the only
thing I did five years of alternative
meds and nothing worked nothing worked
it's incredible you guys and you guys it
listen it listen pardon
me excuse me pardon me for when I do
some of the humorous stuff when I kid
around or I joke around I'm doing that
cuz there's a bunch of people that are
on mattress Island that actually find it
funny I know not everybody finds it
funny I mean but but you have to you're
trying to help everybody um Mel melber
Prince says medical medium only thing
that has helped so many of my
illnesses I live for my new found life
because of you and spirit forever
thankful I'm grateful Spirit of
compassion although Spirit of compassion
does push my
limits and occasionally gets on my
nerves a little bit okay Nia green
Anthony my father passed away this
weekend dear Lord and even though it's
been extremely hard I have been using
many tools I've learned with you and
it's being super helpful um prayers
going out to you ni green prayers are
going out I'm so sorry you're going
through that sorry for your loss truly
um yeah I truly
am uh rusa says definitely worth the
swear definitely worth the swear
validates me thank you I felt this so
heavy lately where I can't even hardly
cope at The Madness of this
world I understand I
do and Brit Eden says thank you Anthony
for doing this for people you are such a
blessing to us all thank you for being
there
seriously and heal with Ana says medical
M you for Thank You For Fighting for The
Chronic Le we are so lucky you are here
for us we love you and know you care I
see sant's healing thank you for
everything aw even showing up for a
live while you got while you're up so
much against things truly no words
explain thank you s
santara see on IG one divide it says oh
my God you're funny and Audrey says zinc
shock therapy saved me this month it
saves friend friends and family I know
and so
forth yeah let's get me all choked up
here Adele says I was praying to God and
then talk that I had was about how to be
at service and then the response
arrived notification of this amazing
surprising live thank you for God
Anthony at so I want to say you guys I
know I choke around a lot I know I do a
lot of funny
stuff your Protocols are keeping me from
getting sick this year I work for the
light I think I saw that on IG but
please be patient with me I just I know
it's cheering up a few people that are
just their bed bound they just you know
the humor they like the humor not
everybody likes it I see people they're
just like he shouldn't do that he just
should just do the information and no
joking
around I do the best I can okay the best
I can Sammy the The dietitian right the
Rd Samantha she will be making
appearance soon enough she's been dying
to get on to the show and I wanted to
give her um an opportunity to talk about
protein and so forth and other things
she says I have it all wrong and she
wants to correct my
information loving healing says I would
always get migraines with some storms
coming through yes the nerve shifter
shot has stopped my migraines after 33
years by the way the nerve shifter shots
in
here 19
$24 amazon.com us tell everybody get in
for Christmas
presents incredible all right guys you
love love Alicia G says love your
telegram messages I will leave more
telegram
messages from the
heart Terrace say love the tell telegram
messages I will try my
best I know I leave them late at night
sometimes midnight sometimes 3: in the
morning 2: in the morning
um but I never sleep so it's okay I love
you
guys I will see you soon please take
care have a good Thanksgiving or have
just a good
week I love you guys