are you seeing it out there people catch
a bug they get sick they're coughing
they're lungs out they're really sick
they got fevers going up and down they
start to recover they go to a doctor
they get on an antibiotic whatever it is
they start to recover and then they stay
sick they think they're going to recover
and bounce back completely but they're
dragging or 2 weeks later they're doing
a little better and then it hits them
and they're dragging and they're going
down and what's happening out there
people are getting sick and then they're
falling into this chronically ill
trigger and now they're getting all
these different things like brain fog
and weird tingles and numbness on their
body and aches and pains and fatigue and
brain fog again and they just don't feel
themselves and now they're triggered
into something entirely different
because of the bugs going around right
now right now in New England in the
United States there's a stomach flu
neuro virus and it's pounding the crap
out of people right now up there and
it's heading through through the United
States and around the world and it's
giving people like insane di area and
gut disturbances and we're going to
cover that a little bit cuz I want to
talk about that like what does it do in
the gut like what happens there's people
all about you know microbiome what
happens if you get the neuro virus and
you got the stomach flu and it's ripping
through your guts and you're sitting
there and you're just diarrhea diarrhea
vomiting too and diarrhea diarrhea and
then what like what happened how's your
microbiome then is it all fixed is it
all great what's it like nobody really
talks about that they don't talk about
what happens when boom you get that
neuro virus and you got the stomach flu
and then is your microbiome is is that
going to get back to normal wasn't even
normal to begin with and is it going to
get back to normal eventually or is it
going to be out of B now for next
another 2 years until you get another
stomach flu so I'm talking about a bunch
of different things okay therez a lot of
bugs out there quick announcement to did
you hear the episode medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast black tongue
did you hear the episode the black
tongue syndrome so many people get it
there's a whole thing about it with
metals and everything else I talk about
in the episodes the medical medum
podcast at Apple podcast black tongue
I've seen people get the black tongue
and they're sitting there with the
toothbrush and they're like scrubbing
scrubbing and they injure their tongue
they're trying to do everything they can
they're rinsing with salt water they're
rinsing with mouth
rinses they're rinsing with everything
under the sun and they can't get rid of
that black tongue have you ever seen
that out there people get that and it's
just like it's coming it's going it's
coming and then sometimes it's just jet
black for a very long time right in the
center of the tongue going swiping all
the way down so check out medical Me
podcast podcast at Apple podcast please
listen to it when you get a chance it's
an amazing informative show about Black
tongue discolorations and so forth and
everything I'm sure so many of you guys
have had discolorations with the tongue
so it's good information very important
but I'm here to talk about our immune
system and how it's getting pretty beat
up these days with what people are going
through do you know anybody that's
coughing do you know anybody that's got
a sore throat and a fever do you know
anybody who's been hit with anything
that's going on because people have been
getting hit it's like a insurgence of it
insurgence of it happening right now
this is like one of those hot spots
we're in where it's just really starting
to pick up pace I hear it all the time
people are sick for a month with it
coughing out their lungs the whole bit
but then to add insult to injury there
is a Norovirus stomach flu hyper catchy
hyper catchy that's actually steaming
streaming right out of new England land
right now and it's going to be cutting
across the country and you know overseas
and everywhere else and that one really
sucks really really sucks so what I'm
doing right now is the reason why I'm
even here is because I'm saying are you
taking care of your immune system are
you taking care of your immune system
right so I have my family on this right
here just a safeguard I need a safeguard
my family and my closest friends you
know safeguarding them too and all that
so that's the total immune blend do you
have it and what's crazy out there is
what I'm seeing right now is all these
different supplements are coming out
it's like crazy right and they're
claiming all this stuff claiming all
this stuff but they don't work they
don't work and you look what's in them
it's like yeah all poor quality crap all
garbage whatever you name it and they
just don't work it's so sad that's what
I'm seeing out there you guys know I
endorse these guys this is vimer g v is
in Victor i m is in Mary E RG y I'll get
a closeup too on this right here this is
the to immune I'm living off of it to
protect myself cuz I can't get sick
right now with any kind of cold or
anything like
flu anything like that I use the term
cold but you know how there's no colds
anyway but it's this back in stock it's
back and stock so I give you a little
closeup on this before I move on because
we're going to talk about some stuff in
the immune system which is really
important so that's total immune blend
right
there there it is that's the vimergy I
don't know if you guys see it there it
is
very important critical critical um
resource right there it's got the time
it's got the Mullin it's back in stock
it's sold out like this when it came out
so a lot of people armed themselves and
armed their immune systems for what was
coming but I want to talk about even
more than that I want to go into like
what people are dealing with post
getting sick and what they're dealing
with pre getting sick because everybody
hasn't immune system problems and that's
that's a big thing right there all on
its own if you got a
symptom if you got any kind of symptom
if you got any kind of condition if
you've been diagnosed with a condition
if you're struggling with any kind of
symptom immune system right there
anything people who are dealing with
cancer immune systems broke down people
are dealing with all kinds of different
things like fibro and ra and lime and
anything immune system people that're
dealing with all kinds of aches and
pains and Tinkles and numbness and
vertigo and ringing in the ears and
dizziness and balance issues immune
system we have injured depleted
diminished immune systems and that's
what people live with every single day
if you know somebody and they're getting
things and they're getting symptoms and
they're
struggling yeah it's their immune system
it's struggling that's the whole point
it can't handle exposures it can't
handle the toxic heavy metal exposures
and then the herbicide and the fungicide
exposures and the
fragrances and the caffeine addiction it
can't handle the immune system can't
handle that so many people are drowning
themselves with coffee and espresso
drinks and they're just beating the crap
out of their immune system so immune
system is just under attack all the time
and So eventually what that leads us to
is a sickness no matter what
but everyone is going to get a symptom
no matter what you see somebody out
there right now they're on social like
yeah I'm doing this and do and that I'm
Into Fitness I'm into this you're going
to have a symptom you're going to have a
symptom it's going to come later maybe
but you're going to be pushed over the
edge too many exposures your immune
system is going to finally kick down and
you're going to be in the immune system
pit just like everybody else so keeping
our immune system strong is critical
having immune system power is
critical having it strong and you'll
hear things out there like you don't
want your immune system too strong oh
you don't really like okay whose immune
system is too strong somebody tell me
whose immune system is so strong you
know I mean even like the best
influencers out there talking about
health and everything they're dealing
with immune system problems that's how
they got into it anyway they got into
the health industry in general because
they got problems and they're seeing
their naturopath and their herbalist and
their acupuncturist and their MD and
their do and they're seeing everybody
because they got all these problems
because everybody's immune system is
challenged that's the day and age we're
in we're in the age of the quickening
right here this is the quickening where
[ __ ] just speeds up and speeds up and
speeds up stuff is happening real fast
out there and sickness and disease is
climbing at an all-time high and it's
staying climbing and climbing and
climbing
2030 so many people are going to be sick
2035 it's going to be unbelievable on
how many people are going to be sick
everybody's going to be sick and
everybody's going to be on social
talking about their
sicknesses that's what's going to happen
it's going to dominate social
entirely to a point where all articles
out there all the media is going to be
talking about sickness everybody's going
to be talking about sickness stories
this is just what it's going to be by 20
2030 nothing but sickness sickness
sickness
everywhere and that's the world we live
in that's the world we're going to be
living and and that's how crazy it
really is when you really think about it
right I mean did you ever expect that
did you ever expect
that yeah you're not alone so let's talk
about the immune system a little bit and
why it's so important to support it not
just support it rebuild
it rebuild it critical really is writing
for truth on IG says do you take the
total immune blend every day even when
not sick I do I take it every single day
even when not sick I take it every day
okay but you can take it every day right
do what your doctor wants to do but I
tell my family you can take it every day
but you can take a smaller dosage if
you're not sick every single day then
when you get sick or you're struggling
with something you can increase the the
dosage to what your whatever doctor
leaves or however what's in it a thyme
blend of thyme and Mullen and a little
touch of zinc it's this perfect
combination right here and what people
don't realize it's the quality of the
time on top of it it's the quality of
the Mullen that you don't get in other
places it doesn't happen it just doesn't
I know I know the quality I know what
they do I know how they do it and it's
unbelievable able it's about making sure
that alcohol wasn't used that alcohol is
not involved at any level making sure
all these different things matter that
this is really clean but the real thing
not everybody saying good quality this
is good quality everybody's allowed to
say that did you know that you're
allowed to say everything's good quality
did you know that anybody who just opens
up a door hangs a shingle and sells
something they're allowed to say our
quality is great nothing beats our
quality there is a difference huge
difference that's important to know it
really is on IG Roxy says where can I
buy it that's vimergy V is invictor i m
is in Mary
eerg vimergy.com
link check out the link in the uh
description so yeah Details
Matter Details Matter I agree I see that
right there okay so let's go into it a
little
bit all right couple of things to know
one
is why are immune systems so chopped up
why are they so beat up and that's
something that nobody really talks about
they're just like this is immune
supportive immune supportive everybody's
immune system is just beaten to a pulp
basically and that's why everybody's so
sick it's struggling immune system you
got to remember that if there's anything
someone's dealing with instantly the
immune system is under siege Under Siege
if someone's got panic attacks and they
got the Titan chest and they got that
vagus nerve I talk about that vag nerves
the
inflammation and they're dealing with
all kinds of anxiety and panic and all
these other things immune system
everything is like that thyroid
condition at all thyroid anybody
hypothyroid hyperthyroid any kind of
thyroid problems at all anything grave
whatever it is nodules in the thyroid
whatever it is immune system was
challenged the thyroids immune system
was challenged the liver's immune system
was challenged and then weakened and
then kicked down a notch so people walk
around with weak immune systems that's
what they do all day long and then the
thyroid disorders creep up and then the
panic and the aches and pains creep up
and then the vertigo and the tentis and
the Les and numbness and the body aches
and pains and the trigeminal neuralgia
all creep up because their immune system
is suffering their immune system is
struggling so very important to know so
let's talk about like stomach flu I want
to go into that a little bit stomach
flu okay so the reason why I would take
like something every single day or I
tell family to take something every
single day like I tell my family take a
little bit of this take a little bit of
the
every single day right little bit of the
golden seal every single day this is
what I tell my family to do all the time
and a little bit of B12 and I want to
talk about why B12 is critical cuz when
we catch something like the neuro virus
or white lung yeah which is really
hurting a lot of people I mean they get
scar tissue in the lung that lasts
forever I mean that's just unfair like
why do they put bugs out there like this
so that we get injuries in our lungs and
then for lifetime we actually have scar
tissue in our lungs like does that make
any sense so I tell my friends and
family it's critical to get B12 in you
after especially after you've been hit
with something because you need that
extra B12 to power up the nerves so
important that alone okay and so what
I'm telling my family right now with all
these these hard times of people getting
sick cuz it's it's really sad when you
see somebody really struggling they get
what feels like a cold to start with
then it then it lingers then it runs
into a fever and up and down and then
after that when they're better they're
not better because now their immune
system was dropped and they were
triggered into something else an epine
bar rising up out of nowhere herb
simplex one rising up from nowhere
because that's what's happening to
people people are getting shingles a
month after they get white lung a month
later they have the shingles because
their immune system was so kicked down
to the bottom that the jingles virus
said this is my time to shine and then
it comes up and it just boom it's up
there let's talk about the Norovirus
that's coming around and it's
circulating right now and it's it's
kicking up so right now there's a
stomach bug out there and what people
don't realize is that a stomach bug can
knock your gut balance off for a really
long time really long time but what you
what you'll never see out there is what
happens inside the intestinal tract when
that bug is around so let's go into that
let's let's try to like makeshift a
little bit of an intestinal track
okay so let's do that we'll make shift a
little bit of a a colon here
right all right and then we'll just do a
little intestinal track in the center
here if you guys can see this
okay
so you pick up the stomach flu pick up
the neuro virus you get it in your
mouth just goes in you you breathing in
it's on your tongue now it's heading
down to your gut okay and it's on its
way so that virus is getting there okay
virus goes down the dadum it's it starts
in your stomach right it goes down your
stomach in your dadum it's heading in
there and what that virus is doing is
it's multiplying really fast and it's
feeding off of foods that you eat so
it's multiplying it's exploding so what
a stomach virus does is it proliferates
at a speed no other bug Pro proliferates
no other bug fires up to that degree to
multiplies to that degree spawns to that
degree but the neuro virus
explodes and it feeds off of undigested
proteins it feeds off of gluten that's
in the system from something you ate a
week ago yeah a week ago it feeds off of
any egg residue egg material any kind of
egg material in your gut it feeds off of
that and then it feeds off of any dairy
products and then it feeds off of other
things it'll feed off of soy
potentially it'll feed off of virtually
anything right so what it does is it
feeds and it explodes it
produces itself rapidly like rapidly and
it's highly toxic so what the Norovirus
is is it's a bug that when it produces
the bug then goes to the intestinal
lining walls and it starts to make
divots it starts to basically try to
poke holes in your intestinal tract and
your colon but nobody talks about this
they're just like you got a stomach bug
you know that's it wait till it's over
and then take a probiotic
so that's what they'll say some of the
best functional medicine doctors will be
like well you got a stomach flu um go to
the hospital you got a stomach flu and
then make sure you get on our probiotics
at our clinic or or our doctor's office
make sure you get on our probiotics so
that's all they do but what people don't
realize is that
virus is mean really mean so stomach
bugs stomach flu EXP load they multiply
fast real fast thousands upon thousands
of replicas then all those bugs end up
attaching themselves to everything the
stomach lining the dadum lining the
small in top of the small intestinal
track all through and as it's happening
if you have a weakened immune system
it's not slowing it down it's not
stopping it and instead that person is
now diarrhea they got stomach pains
they're really nauseous they got a fever
cranking
up because their immune system isn't
stopping it it's not breaking it down so
their immune cells are not there's not
enough immune cells number one to stop
the neuro virus to that degree and if
someone has a weakened immune system
then they really have very small amounts
of immune cells going into this area
trying to stop the neuro virus so the
neuro virus the stomach flu the stomach
bugs what they do is they attack the
Linings of the small intestinal tract
and this is why people get Pockets later
this is why people get divots
diverticulitis
diverticulosis this is why people end up
with crohn's later on meaning a trigger
to get into Crohn's where other bugs can
actually contribute it's all about not
knocking the immune system down allowing
other problems to happen there's people
who get stomach flu that never have a
normal stomach intestinal track ever
again in their life they don't know how
to recover it they know don't know how
to rebuild it they don't know about Mono
eating from the medical medium book
series they don't know about all these
different things they can do they're
just stuck their intestinal tract is
rocked for a very long time and then if
they're older and they're not younger
and they're older it affects them even
more because they already have
intestinal tract issues on so many
levels so the neuro virus explodes and
then it attaches itself to the Linings
of the intestinal tract and if you're
somebody that has pockets of undigested
protein from a weak liver that I talked
about in the last episode or if you're
somebody that's dealing with anything
like putrified rancid fats that are
caked along your intestinal track old
feal matter that's just stuck there and
plastered against the intestinal Linings
and bad bacteria like strep it all Rises
up so the neuro virus and the stomach
flu and the stomach bugs go ripping
through you and then it awakens all the
strep all the staff all the tiny bits of
SEI that you were keeping under control
you know just managing your immune
system was managing all this time and
then what
happens is we get triggered now we have
all kinds of intestinal tract
disturbances years later down the road a
month later so as the virus is ripping
through the gut it's clinging to the
wall of the intestinal tract and it
starts to try to burrow holes inside the
intestinal tract just like white lung is
doing to people when they're getting the
C and they're getting the flu and the C
and the RS V in the white lung right now
and it's going in it's injuring lung
sacks well the stomach flu is
created
manufactured to injure the lining of
your intestinal
tract stomach dadum and so forth it's
there to scar tissue and burrow and
weaken the
lining and wake up other predator
that lie inside of our intestinal tract
like the strep and the seiff and
different varieties of staff and the
hpylori
so as that neuro virus and that stomach
flu is ripping through and exploding and
people are having like explosions of
diarrhea and they're sick and they're
nauseous and they're throwing up or
they're fevered and they're getting the
runs and they're really struggling for a
day or two sometimes a week right now
there's one that's ripping through
that's really messing people up
and when that's happening it wakes up
the strep it wakes up SEI it wakes up
staff it wakes up other bugs like
viruses that could be in the intestinal
tract and then it tries to burrow holes
in the Linings because that's what it
does the bugs go in and they try to
destroy tissue so they're cell
destroyers the reason why we're having
diarrhea and fever and everything else
around it is cuz our body is
reacting and mucus is being produced off
the lining of her intestinal tract
because it's burrowing little holes tiny
little divots in our intestinal tract
and so our intestinal tract is releasing
gobs and gobs of mucus and water and
mucus and it's just streaming out it's
streaming out to try to defend against
the Invader but the Invader causes a lot
of Havoc reaches a lot reaks a lot of
havoc and a probiotic is not going to
fix it after a really bad stomach flu a
fever and also intestinal tract being
invaded like that it takes time to heal
it takes time to eat the right Foods it
takes time to understand what you're
doing and it's critical to keep the
immune system
strong
so I just wanted to show you that right
there and there's other stuff to talk
about cuz we are here talking about the
fun stuff for sure all right then move
this over a little
bit
okay it takes a tremendous amount of
adrenaline to fend off any bug that's
out there right now any kind of flu any
kind of sea any kind of white lung RSV
any kind of neuro virus or stomach virus
it takes
adrenaline heart rate goes
up as you're getting sick your heart
rate goes up that's how it works because
epinephrine is being being released
adrenaline is being released to try to
protect you but adrenaline itself
doesn't help the immune system so what
these bugs do and these viruses do that
get into us when they get into us our
adrenals end up fire alarming it and
releasing all this adrenaline to try to
because that's actually this response
this automics response that's happening
immediately when an Invader enters into
our system but as that's happening our
immune cells are struggling even more
because we have so much adrenaline
pouring into our bloodstream and immune
cells hate adrenaline hate adrenaline it
holds them back it keeps them from
functioning as good as they can function
so our immune cells need
fuel need
fuel and that's why I talk about like I
have my family and my closest friends on
protocols I have them on
supplements it's critical because when
you get sick if you're somewhere and
look no one has no one has it perfect
where well man you know what I could be
wrong about that there's people on
Instagram that they never have to work a
day in their life right they're young
they come for money or something or
they're just extremely wealthy or
whatever it is everything's taken care
of and all they have to do is sleep 12
hours every night they could sleep as
many hours as they want they don't have
to stress out about work they don't have
to they just worry about their
appointments their stress is their
appointments like I'm getting my
lymphatic drainage here I'm getting this
here I'm doing this here I'm going on a
vacation here with my friends here I'm
going to Europe whatever it is that's
their stress right and there are people
like that and they can at least protect
themselves because they're not living
with a lot of real life scenarios
situations they're not trying to work
three jobs to survive they don't have
you know like all these problems in
their life meaning from other family
members or something happening and they
don't you know there's a lot going on in
a lot of people's lives and we can't
help it because there's so many people
that don't have that perfect life life
where they can just relax all day long
and never have to worry about working a
day in their life you know there's a lot
of people that are struggling and they
have to fight to survive and when you do
that right we're always up against a lot
and it's important to keep our immune
system strong and in the eventually
someone who has it really good in their
life and they're young and strong now
still will get symptoms later they'll
still wind up in trouble they'll still
wind up sick I see it all the time but
it usually comes later instead of
early let's see sole purpose on IG says
my fiance was just sick three times in
six weeks flu bug stomach flu bug and
then flu bug again now lots of crazy
symptoms so he's joined me in medical
medum protocols this week now that's
exactly the example I'm so sorry you're
going through that first of all I want
to say that that's awful that's awful
but that's how they set it up you have
to understand that's how they set it up
so that's what they do okay so let's do
a a different little thing on the
Whiteboard okay I don't know why my
whiteboard doesn't really work that
great I really don't
know okay so all
right excuse me for my art Artistry work
okay right can I put a little chimy up
here all
right
okay that is the bug manufacturing plant
that's what that is that's right that's
the bug manufacturing
plant yes
indeed
okay and here are some houses over here
some
roofs okay there's some different houses
everywhere um there's a little village
here lots of different roads you like
this quick art this is really
great right it's a building up here with
some chimney here whatever that's the
village The Village the innocent
people okay there it
is and the manufacturing plant they just
let out all kinds of stuff out their
front
door is what they do they let out lots
of
bugs lots of bugs and they do it
purposely and they time it just right
okay and these bugs end up going to the
village and everybody gets
sick apologize for my my writing
my artistry
skills I did not go to art
school and uh I wish I did I really do
anyway listen so check this out you guys
bugs are layered on top of bugs
purposely so they release them with a
schedule okay so there's a
schedule there it is here got all the
different days of the
month
right here's the first here's the second
here's the third the fourth the fifth
each month they release one flu bug on
the first of whatever day of the month
they want to release it
on when they know it's gotten out there
good enough and it's running its course
they time it and they have schedules and
they release another one on another
month maybe they'll release it on the 3D
okay they layer the manufactured bugs
purposely so it kicks the crap out of
people they want you to be
triggered and injured so you're kept
down and you feed the system that's how
it's done see so you catch the one flu
six weeks ago you catch another flu 3
weeks ago you catch the stomach flu last
week it's layered they put them out like
that and they want everybody in the
village to get sick everybody and they
want older people elderly people to die
correct they want them to die and get
knocked off that's how it's done they
want them sick and they want them gone
that's how the system is set up it's a
kind of a fun little system isn't
[Music]
it they Manu facture the bugs and they
then they stick the bugs in a
containment unit with a bunch of white
mice and they see if the mice all die
they see if the mice live they see if
the mice chalk you know cough and choke
on fleem they see if the mice have
diarrhea all around the mouse
tank and then they kind of say well
we're ready and they eventually let it
out that's the system that's way it's
built lady paath over there in IG just
said I really appreciate how you pointed
out that most of us have so many
stresses bringing down our immune
systems indeed everybody does I am
included in that I am not immune to that
I have stress just like anybody else
plenty of it in fact a lot of it and
that's what happens when you have the
most healing stories on the planet of
people healing you have the most people
with multiple sceris that got out of
wheelchairs in
history the information that's so
Advanced every single you know somebody
who somebody in the influencer world is
stealing and poaching it and using it
because they can't get their own
information and all these people are
healing around the world and it creates
tremendous amount of stress that's how
it works you're not allowed to get
people better in large quantities you're
allowed to get one or two people better
and be like hey I got somebody better
you're not allowed to get millions of
people better hundreds of thousands of
people better that weren't supposed to
get better you're not allowed to do that
not on planet
Earth so my stress is
great chamia says Anthony the flu bug
got around our household but we were
able to stop it in its tracks with
vitamin C shock and zinc shock therapy
plus time water thank you so much for
these tools I'm all pumped up from that
that's actually exciting and I love
hearing that because it's that powerful
that helpful so um let me make some
vitamin C shock therapy let me do
that I'm going to have some now if you
guys don't
mind looking for some utensils here so
I'm going to pop some vitamin C in there
just like that I got some honey over
here too I'm going to pop a little bit
of honey in here and I'm going to get
some water water going some warm water
got that going right let's see I got
some orange juice right here this is
what I've been doing fresh squeezed
orange juice by the way you guys right
that's a luxury that is a luxury
seriously like going out and getting
oranges just really good oranges if you
could find them right squeezing them
making a glass of fresh SED orange juice
is an incredible luxury here okay see
not everything is all B down here okay
anyway I got some water warming up as we
speak there we
go give it a second warming it up right
now so micro C is what I'm using for
this right here do you guys know about
this can I show you this is also a
collagen
Builder and the one thing about medical
medum information is I was the first to
blow the horn on the BS [ __ ]
collagen Market where the collagen
Market was selling all this collagen but
you can't build collagen eating collagen
just like you can't fix your eye eating
an eyeball you can't eat a pig's eyeball
to fix your eyeball you can't eat a
liver to fix your liver it doesn't work
that's not how it works you can't
rebuild collagen in your body you can't
rebuild collagen in your body eating
collagen it's not going to happen so
medical medium information was the first
to call that out that you can't get
better on collagen you can only build
your collagen with collagen Builders
that's how you do
it all right so I got some water heated
up right
here I'm going to add a little bit of
orange juice to this as well this is the
vitamin C shock
therapy water got a little toast see
little bit toastier than I probably
wanted it so let me get some nice
cold orange juice in there fresh
squeezed orange juice look at
that nice can I have a double espresso
please can I have an espresso coffee an
espresso drink can I have a coffee with
two espressos put into the
coffee um you know I'm kidding that you
guys know I'm kidding so this is the
micro SE immune power power okay this sa
is incredible for the skin incredible
for the skin incredible for the immune
system that's an immune Builder
difference huge difference okay so I'm
doing what um you were doing right for
your family you're doing the vitamin C
shock
therapy
incredible I'm going to mix it really
good this has a little bit of the honey
in there it's got the fresh quar juice
it's got the warm water
see an over there and IG says I love
that micro C I have been doing the Skin
Potion and it helps so much my eczema on
my face
incredible I have a lot of people doing
this for the skin right now a lot of
people by the way friends and family and
so
forth see Trace over there in IG I'm
doing the micro C orange juice and MSM
and I've noticed my bruises from
postsurgery
treat in my my um physical therapy
treatments dis appear incredible so much
quicker Game Changer hope I read that
right incredible so that's the micr
that's the total immune okay things at
work is what I care about things that
work it matters it's critical I'm seeing
a lot of stuff being put every day out
there being put out there everybody
wants a pop a supplement out there I
don't blame I don't blame everybody
everybody wants to put a supplement out
there I don't blame them and you guys
know I don't own vimergy this is not my
company I don't have shares in the
company I don't have stock in the
company I don't have a percentage in the
company you guys know that right because
I know BS goes around and stories get go
around I do not own any part of vimergy
on any level people need to know that
it's not my brand it's not my company
very important but it's the only company
I trust at this point to like to to the
degree that I trust I know the people
I've known them for a long time now I
trust them I trust that they won't let
me down and my people down they won't
and they stay literally like straight as
you can be I'm making sure this stuff is
that incredible that's why I support
them that's why I endorse them the Skin
Potion helps with my spots and they
disappearing whoa on on IG that's
incredible okay um so anyway you guys
know about the msm2 that's another thing
for the skin which is incredible skin
and joints and everything so the MSM
that's an amazing one with silica and
that's a whole game Cher all on its own
I mean this this is actually exciting
this cheers me up because I've been
wanting to talk about some of the things
that I'm using my family's using the
medical medium Skin Potion have you
tried it which is the MSM it's the
vitamin C right the micro C and let me
just be clear about this so you guys
know okay if you're interested this
isn't ascorbic acid this isn't the thing
that burns holes in people's
stomachs that that's what I'm talking
about that's a different difference with
vimergy that is the difference right
there because people don't realize that
they go and take the ascorbic acid and
next thing you know they got the runs
they got diarrhea they got stomach upset
it's burning their Linings it's burning
their gut if they're sensitive they had
ulcers in the past and they're taking
all that ascorbic acid it's in there
like sizzling up the ulcers like I I
can't I can't even go even go there like
I will never take an ascorbic acid
straight ascorbic acid vitamin C ever
again in my life I've taken it when
there is nothing else available out
there in the world I've taken it when
there was nothing available I will never
ever ever take a Scorpio ass trate to
Scorpi acid vitamin C ever again ever
and so I'm just I'm just like I know
that I'm blessed to know that this is
out there for me to take personally for
my health and for people to take
personally for their health and I'm
blessed to know that this is actually
here it's just it's incredible this
isn't about like supplementation and
supplements and selling supp this is
about stuff that literally is critical
for life like because of what it is and
what they do it's it's a real Mission
that's the difference with vimergy and
then people just trying to Hawk
supplements grifter H you know selling
and Hawking supplements because they're
just trying to make a buck big
difference I don't own this company I
don't have a percentage a share stock
nothing in this company but I'll tell
you right now I know what they're doing
and it's unbelievable and that's why I
endorse them like flying colors kind of
thing anyway here's the micro shock
therapy can I actually have a little bit
of it if you guys don't mind Julie
Tuesday I read all your comments on
YouTube and you're always helping people
too Julie you're always helping people
as well you're always like letting them
know stuff and everything and I always I
always read them Julie Tuesday 144
vimergy products really helped me get
through some tough times I can feel the
difference there is a difference thank
you for saying that Sage star over there
on YouTube thanks for the honesty and
your Protocols are helping me stop
multiple sclerosis in its tracks dang
right you fight for it you fight for it
okay and that it's critical to fight for
it so many people recovered from Ms so
many people with mm information so
important so important anyway okay I'm
just going to sip this right now I just
want to I can't help it want to have a
little real quick here we're talking
about neov virus we're talking about flu
we're talking about um C RSV white lung
but then we're talking about like what
happens when the scale is tipped so much
you guys you know how I've been talking
about the scale tipping all this time
and and death by a Thousand Cuts for
like years right and now I just saw like
someone just said that someone was on a
podcast like some influencer guy was on
some podcast doctor or something was on
a podcast and talking about scale
tipping Death By A Thousand Cuts I'm
like dude get your own stuff get your
own
stuff but that's what's happening the
scale's Tipping and that's what these
bugs do it knocks them down and their
immune system then struggles their
immune system is already struggling and
now they're sick and it's unfair it's
not right that this happens to people we
shouldn't have to live our lives sick
life is short and as it is life is short
as it is okay we're not living to 500
years old we're not living to 400 years
old right it's another story I want to
talk about on a spiritual talk one day
maybe I'll do that on like the the um IG
broadcast right are you guys actually
signed up to my Ig broadcast are you
guys signed up to that where I send you
the direct message maybe I'll talk about
it there and on my telegram as well so I
want to talk about why this is
interesting why in the Bible people were
living to a thousand years old really
early on living to 900 years old living
to 1100 years old I'm going to talk
about that about how that happened and
what was going on if you guys actually
are interested in that kind of
information I'm not sure but I want to
drop some stuff on that maybe on medical
Med podcast as well at Apple podcast
check out the black tongue episode on
medical me podcast if you haven't
checked that out all right okay all
right just going to sip this real
quick micro C medical medium shock
therapy love it
powerful and delicious you put a little
bit of honey in there and you have a
little bit of that fresh squeezed orange
juice in
there right
incredible all right I'm going to get
the total immune out I want to do a
little total immune shot
mebe 787 on YouTube good to see you all
right you're out and about what's the IG
handle please the IG handle
please medical medium it's medical
medium Marissa spiritual good to see you
too on YouTube I read your comments too
yes aw they are stealing your verbage oh
or they ever information constantly
about Metals too right stuff that isn't
anywhere science or nowhere they just
where did they get it they just came out
of thin air where did it come from I
know it's yeah it's so dark and it's
coming out of them yeah I know I know
it's actually sick and then they're
running ads to the medical medium
Community with the medical medium
information how sick is that pretending
they came up with it or something it's
actually despicable like how can people
live with themselves it's because
they're they're slimy Kimberly says I
have been listening to your new podcast
they are awesome thank you thank you for
listening and I'm going to put out a
stream of them a steady stream of
medical mean podcast at Apple podcast
don't miss them make sure you your
notifications are on make sure you're
always checking in case you don't get
notified yeah I know okay okay so the
total immune is really revolutionary all
on its own okay it's like with me I I
know that people need their immune
system strengthened
but they need them
rebuilt rebuilt not just fortified not
just strengthened not just supported but
rebuilt because that's the kind of
immune system trouble so many people are
in thyroid problems hypo hyper you know
nodules cysts on the thyroid whether
they're tiny or large people that deal
with all kinds of issues under the sun
everything from neurological problems
from skin problems our immune systems
are under attack from everything from
fragrances and anything people who drink
alcohol it's another thing did you know
that it was taboo you guys on another
note can't help it you know that it was
taboo to either to utter the word you
can't do alcohol like it's bad for you
it's not good for you it's not going to
help you even all the vegan
doctors doctors all drink all drink wine
champagne everything right vodka all
drink okay and then suddenly now years
after I've been talking about how bad
alcohol is and I was getting crap for it
that was taboo you weren't allowed to
talk about it on a podcast anywhere you
weren't allowed to about talk about it
on social you mentioned that alcohol was
bad everybody The Gauntlet came down on
you man they chop off your head I'm not
kidding but yet I stayed with it stayed
with it stayed with it talked about
stayed with it was heavy on it said no
you can't do this if you want to heal
you got to get off alcohol it's bad for
you whatever and then now guess what
they're all paring it now like yeah
alcohol is bad for your brain really cuz
science doesn't say that where did you
get that
idea all right look what I like about
total
immune okay
is
um the fact that it works that's just
one right off the the bat Mei over there
on YouTube I noticed that Mayo Clinic
Now talks about non- rashing shingles no
mention of the source um there is a
hijacking of the medical medium non-
rashing shingles information both there
at Mayo PubMed wherever all of all of it
like they've just hijacked medical
medium information with no science and
no studies behind it no studies behind
it and when you look when you look at
whatever they show check this out how
sick is this when they look when you
look at what they show they're talking
about post herpetic pain when the rash
goes
away but they're trying to chalk that up
as it it's non- rashing shingles no they
had the rash it went away and then they
had pain for a year so science of
research did do a couple of papers where
you have pain for a year or more after
shingles but that's not non- rashing
shingles non- rashing shingles is
medical medium information it's having
shingles never a rash ever and having
symptoms right well now they're claiming
they knew that when they didn't no signs
to back it up but mayo and everybody
else is using medical Mee information on
that just it's crazy you know what
there's you know there's good news
though because they're so evil that when
you leave here that evil and you don't
make good with that you don't resolve it
you don't
you don't work on that you don't come
clean about like how many people you
screwed over with chronic illness that
couldn't get back to the source to heal
and it's your fault that so many people
aren't going to heal because you were
evil and you didn't care and you stole
that information to just manipulate
people and then you're on your deathbed
many years down the road you think
you're just in the clear with that you
think you're in the
clear I say my medicinal home on YouTube
propolis shock therapy is in the brain
saver protocol book it helped heal my
canker source and that's the propolis
right there I'll give you a close-up on
the propolis you
guys I mean honestly look if you look if
if you can get one thing one thing okay
you can't you can't lose with total
immune you can't lose with propolis pure
if you can get twoo th things it's like
total immune propolis pure right if you
can get two things that's how critical
that is for our immune systems right
there that's how critical that is all
right you guys we're talking about all
kinds of good stuff flu and everything
else in post flu and post RSV RSV and
white lung and neuro viruses which are
going around and we talked about like
manufacturing they got the manufacturing
plant right there they're growing the
viruses spawning them right out of egg
themselves and then they get released
magically into our environment and it
hits the village right here and then
they calculate it on the calendar of
when they're going to release the next
one and next one because they want to
clobber the crap out of everybody's
immune system and they want elderly
people to die early so that's the
plan and if you don't believe it then
fine it's all make
believe sure we can think that maybe
it's just all make believe and it never
happened no and that's fine whatever you
want to think but yeah it's interesting
isn't it all right so what I'm doing
right here is I am I got my total immune
right there I take shots of it I put it
in the shot glass just like this
okay and I'm going to pop a little bit
of orange juice so I want to talk about
this there's a lot of people that even
though these don't taste bad these taste
good some of some of the vimergy
products taste amazing that people don't
like to use water they can use juice
then so so here I got some fresh
squeezed orange juice and pouring in
there it is and
mhm all
right top 20 things to keep a strong
immune system get plenty of sleep but
what if I can't get plenty of sleep what
if I can't what if I'm working too hard
what if I'm too too stressed out get a
minimum of 8 to 10 hours a night sleep
if you're actually somebody that's
having any kind of problems okay yeah
easy for you you to say let me just
magically sleep 10 straight hours
because I have such an easy life maybe
I'll sleep 12 hours because I have such
an easy life like okay look maybe some
of you guys do sleep 12 hours because
you know you do but I'm just saying that
a lot of people can't get that 12h hour
sleep in I've had 2our nights I've had 4
Hour nights because I had deadlines on
stuff when I did the brain books I was
sleeping like three hours on the average
every single night to get those brain
books to everybody that's was like 3
hours of sleep every night what if you
can't go and just have this magical nice
life where you're sleeping 12 hours a
night what if you can't I know I sure as
hell can't I mean crap three hours a
night of sleep when I was doing the
brain books so yeah so guess what I
cranked up my Subs right I cranked them
up total immune wasn't out at that time
right but other stuff was right cranked
up the gold golden seal I cranked up the
propolis pure I cranked up my B12 and
that's what I used to push through and
to do
that Angela over there okay on X see do
the mm Skin Potion it will help your
hair too Christina Lee says on YouTube
what are your suggestions for night
shift workers I'm a nighttime post
production coordinator for a TV show and
work 6:00 p.m. to 4 a.m. hey you're on
my
schedule that's amazing but am often up
until 5: to 6:00 a.m. how do I need to
supplement my body first and foremost
right always remember that even if
you're not sleeping if you're just
laying there and you're resting your
nerves and your eyes are shut your
immune system is recovering just from
that alone and I want to say this this
is very important for people who can't
sleep or can't get enough sleep they're
working hard everything's off right is
that when you're even laying there
you're laying there and you're calm and
you're shutting your eyes your immune
system is responding and it's
reproducing and it's building back up
even if you're just laying there you
guys keep that in mind even if you're
somebody who's struggling with insomnia
or you have some kind of sleep issue
your immune system is sitting there
building and rebuilding up when when
you're actually just laying there with
your eyes shut relaxing keep that in
mind right there okay what I would do if
I was on your schedule which I am on
your schedule pretty much I'll work 20
hour days whatever and I'm on your
schedule where I'm working all through
the night too I've done that so many
times I crank up my micro c i Crank It
Up that is something I do I crank up the
the micro c i crank up the B12 these are
some of the things that I do and then I
focus on hydration I focus on a little
bit of coconut water I focus on right my
celery juice I if I can if I can get it
done I I focus on that um there's
there's other things too but and I don't
eat really heavy meals that's one thing
right there I don't eat real heavy dense
meals that are fatty I don't eat big
fatty meals when I'm
underslept because that's a recipe right
there for a heart attack right there
you're eating heavily ladened fat yeah
overt fat meals now all the vegans are
doing over fats that's what they're
doing they're all doing over it fats all
the animal protein people they're all
doing over it fats if you're not if
you're working really hard and you're
not sleeping much cranking up over fats
is like asking for a heart attack I mean
so then so I make sure that that's not
happening that's important on its
own
yep great information you guys talk
about rebuilding the immune system a
little bit couple things you can do
right okay I was going to the top of the
list what you'll see out there it's
happening now it's like great ways 10
great ways to rebuild your immune system
sleep a crap ton of hours um stay away
from fried greasy food um and you know
the list goes on right there's a whole a
whole bunch of things out there like
that okay and so
my list is making sure I got enough zinc
making sure I got the micro SE making
sure I'm taking my propolis pure every
single day making sure I am hydrated but
not hydrated with like garbage stuff not
Hydrate with with um you know alkaline
water um you know uh products and stuff
like that on the Shelf where they're
like this is alkaline water and you guys
seen what's happening out out there
right there's some bad stuff that's
happened it's terrible it's terrible and
I've been telling people stay away from
alkaline water crap that's out there
I've been how many how many years have I
told people to stay away from that and
look what just
happened I mean it was just terrifying
which has happened to people out there
right it's like you know like there's a
lot of things that I do to keep the
immune system strong and you know what I
do is I eat every couple of hours so
that my dream aren't flooding so if you
want to keep your immune system strong
you want to build your immune system
back up you make sure you're not
trashing your adrenals get caffeine out
of
there get caffeine out that's critical
by the way there's no science behind
caffeine hurting the immune system but
recently I saw something out there of
somebody like yeah stay away from
caffeine really because there's no
science that says it they science says
caffeine is good for you it's
crazy
so how it is the point is is staying
away from caffeine eating every couple
of hours don't intermittent
fast when you want to rebuild your and
recover your immune system don't do the
intermittent fasting where you're on
coffee all day then you eat a big greasy
fried meal at the end of the night or a
big overt fat meal at the end of the
night I'm intermittent fasting my
stomach staying down I'm not as bloated
at night I could eat what I want yeah
you just trash your renals people who
intermittent fast they seem to improve
improve but do you hear about like
things like 5 years later ask them then
oh yeah um yeah well uh I don't know my
health has been really gone to [ __ ] um
all these different things yeah but you
were on social media talking about how
you're intermitten and fasting four
years ago and how great you were doing
yeah but then I went to carnivore and
then I got really sick on Carnivore and
then I tried this and then I tried that
and I was trying this new program that I
just purchased for $5,000 from this guy
says he's a chiropractor or something
like and then I just did this and did
that and people are just like they're
everywhere and it's like Yeah because it
didn't work intermittent fasting burns
out the adrenals so what I like to do is
I like to eat every couple of hours I'll
have a banana I'll have some oranges
right I'll eat some
cucumbers right I'll drink my celery
juice I'll have a little coconut water
okay I'll have some fresh squeezed you
know fresh squeezed orange juice
okay and then but I'll be eating I'll be
eating I'll have some dates but I'll be
eating every couple of hours I'll have
some greens of some colored greens and
some dates and I'll just eat them
together I'll have some kale and some
dat I'm just saying that this is what I
do and it's to keep the
adrenals strong then I'll have some
steamed potatoes later but it'll keep
the adrenals strong and it'll also stop
the adrenals from releasing and that
lowers the immune system there's so many
things you can do I mean that's what I
do right there keeping myself like
stable so that a I'm not burning the
gasoline in my body which is your
adrenaline I'm not burning it all out
and then I do medical medium recipes
like medical medium soup recipe with
there's so many soup recipes and light
options in the medical medium um books
that are incredible to help protect you
if you're not sleeping as much if your
immune system is low if you got a
support rebuild your immune system Liver
Rescue smoothie rebuilds your liver's
immune system heavy metal detox the
medical me heavy metal detox incredible
for the immune
system so
yeah all these things you guys know the
tools you guys read the
books definitely organic red apples yeah
they're wonderful did you do you
remember the whole green apple thing
remember the fruit was so bad before
medical meme information cracked down on
it and broke its back do you remember
that and when literally every single
acupuncturist naturopath herbalist do
functional medicine doctor MD said stay
away from red apples only eat a green
apple low glycemic just a granny smith
apple is all you're allowed the rest is
just Ain where you're just eating meat
meat meat and you can have a a green
apple how stupid was that the point is
is we broke we broke down the walls of
of fruit fear and yes red apples you're
allowed to have you guys anyway check
these out so let me run through them a
little bit too right that's the propolis
pure that is a gift from God that's what
that is the propolis pure is a gift from
God it truly is I'm going to pour a
little bit out here it's like
this it's the way I like my
propolis I just pour a little bit right
out I'm going to do a little cocktail
right here I'm going to do some total
immune I'm going to pop a little golden
seal in here too as
well let me pop some golden seal in here
nice I'm going to pop a little bit of
B12 in here too there we
go right
there looking good I'm going to pop a
little fresh squeezed orange juice right
in there as
well
okay and there it is you can mix it if
you would like too can mix it in your
little shot glass I've never mixed it in
a shot glass before I'm actually trying
it of course I make myself a
mess there we are that's my little
little immune sister immune system
rebuilding
shot huh
what bartender give me
another too
good can I have some of that orange
juice that's
spiked and I chase it down with a little
bit of orange juice m
so good bartender give me
another Mr Ferguson get Mr Ferguson
downstairs you guys this has been
incredible we covered a lot of stuff we
talked about the intestinal tract we
talked about the the different bugs that
are going around how they're going
around how they release them out there
why they do
it we talked about uh supporting the
immune system in so many different ways
I love you guys listen make sure you
sign up to my newsletter because I'm
going to be doing a book signing in
person and it's going to be in La I
don't have the dates yet but I'm working
on it it's going to be in La I've never
done a book signing in official book
signing ever in all the 10 years and all
these books and everything I've never
done one and I'm going to do one in La I
hope you guys if you're in the area or
if you're heading out there I hope you
come and bring your books just bring
your old books I'll sign up your old
books right there right there in front
of you voila that's what I'm going to do
and um so I'm just letting everybody
know to keep a lookout at Lookout for
that so and make sure you're signed up
to the IG broadcast where you get a DM
message from me because I'm going to
leave like really great stuff
information from Spirit of compassion
I'm going to leave a telegram message
tonight be sure to subscribe to t.
me slmed medium that's my
telegram rosangela aw could we have a
little soul talk please or just some
enduring words of wisdom it's a crazy
time at the moment I'll do that tonight
I will actually leave a telegram and
I'll do some soul talking on the
telegram
tonight I'm
gonna I don't know what time but I'm
going to do it tonight yes wondering
wishing good to see see you on YouTube
yes telegram
message yes telegram message you guys
incredible um so yeah check things out
oh medical mem podcast and apple podcast
black
tongue yep it may not be interesting to
someone until you get one and you got a
black tongue and then you're going to be
interested crispy perspective hey
crispy you leave some serious comments
there's one that you left recently that
I read that was blown away about O A I'm
at the vet emergency right now due to my
dog having been
attacked stomach in kns I'm praying for
you chrisy okay I'm praying for you and
your dog and I'm so sorry stomach is in
knots mine is too um I do have a weak
spot a real serious weak spot and that's
that's animals going through anything
that's just that that's that's my
cryptonite mebe 787 wine was recommended
as a health drink for pregnant women 13
years ago when my wife was pregnant 13
years ago that's it just 13 years ago
check this out too okay wine was
recommended by podcast doctors up until
a few years
ago until they were kind of like getting
scared that we talked about it so much
being that bad and they're like oh crap
the medical meme community and the
medical M information is taking a turn
and pissing everybody off Terry Johnson
over there on YouTube I knocked down
shingles with zinc shock and propis
shock therapy add it to Total immune and
move forward
rapidly yeah
amazing Elaine I would love the
spiritual book please I was I was
delayed on the spiritual book cuz of all
the
lies and crap
and false stories and all that like
stuff that they try to do framing me and
everything else for something I didn't
do and so yeah pretty sick right pretty
demented just slowed everything down and
no I don't have a spiritual book right
now but yeah I would love to do one and
finish one Maria man forini so thankful
for this info and you so thankful for
you too thank you for being here and I
mean that though I actually mean that
that yeah you guys incredible all right
love you guys I will see you next time
let people know where the info is at so
they can
heal yep and give me a thumbs up or a
like or whatever it is on YouTube or
whatever whatever you know platform
you're on that would be
amazing zero VR aw please tell me it is
possible to heal allergies to dogs had a
lot of people heal their dog allergies
I'm going to do a podcast episode um
medical meem podcast at Apple Apple
podcast and it's going to be I'm going
to be talking about animals and stuff at
some point so just listen
out
yep all
right
okay all right you guys oh wait wait
wait so you want to actually heal
allergies to your dog dog allergies yeah
a lot of people a lot of people have
heal healed their dog allergies their
animal allergies the cat allergies a lot
of people have using medical meme
information so many throughout the years
so me keep a light heart always ask your
doctor what's right for you but keep a
light heart but
yeah okay right there EO fruit and
veggies I almost thought it was fruit
and sandwiches no fruit and veggies I've
healed pet allergies right there on
YouTube thank you for actually telling
everybody so you give them the
inspiration cuz that gave me inspiration
it's giving them inspiration Maria
Isabel over there on Facebook thank you
for all your valuable information thank
you for being here
Maria I do appreciate it you guys are
amazing Veronica thank you Anthony thank
you Veronica for being here over there
you
guys truly many
blessings yep and um love you guys I do
guys on Tik Tok I'll see you next
time you guys on YouTube you guys on
Rumble I'll see you guys next time as
well and you guys on IG I will see you
next time take care of yourself