we're talking about thyroid conditions
hyperthyroidism hypothyroidism
hashimoto's thyroiditis even cystic
nodules too we're talking about
neurological symptoms neurological
symptoms everybody's dealing with
neurological symptoms we're going to
cover that thyroid conditions
neurological symptoms
need i say more that's how much is
happening out there and then chronic
fatigue syndrome
cfs chronic fatigue tiredness where
you've got sand bags on your knees and
legs and it feels like you're it takes a
lot to walk walk and it takes a lot to
move right the whole bit or you're just
you're collapsing or you can't function
good or you need naps all day long right
good to see you guys we're live right
now facebook we're live on youtube live
on tick tock good to see you guys on
tick tock live on telegram which is
really awesome too so i'm excited we're
live on rumble which is really awesome
too so i'm excited you guys if you if
you haven't subscribed to any of the
other platforms subscribe to them so
because i do different things on
different platforms and i post different
stuff i got a telegram the private
messages right exclusive messages on
rumble we do some a lot of exclusive
stuff on there good to see you guys
we're talking about supplements dosages
protocols chronic fatigue syndrome yeah
you're not supposed to be tired
no one's supposed to be tired
i've known guys they're never tired
they work
150 hours a week
whatever you know i mean and they're
never tired
they're just not they go to bed at night
they wake up in the morning right until
they get sick someday but there's people
out there that do that we're technically
not supposed to be tired but we're
suffering with fatigue out there
everybody's dealing they need to be
jacked up on caffeine they need to be
jacked up on coffee they got so much
fatigue kenneth says being on a cleanse
and watching you make guac was very
difficult so oh yeah oh my god
yeah yeah this is the crew today with
the guacamole down the center right here
that's on the amazon live platform so
that's where i'm doing all the cooking
it's a medical medium cooking show talk
about all the different stuff i do like
stuff i use the different crackers i
like and stuff like that for family it's
great for holidays all that stuff so i
cover that link is in the description
and in the bio right there so about the
amazon live platform you guys want to
subscribe to that platform
to see me at least i'm making the foods
and doing like cooking tips no one's
ever seen before tips about avocados no
one's ever heard before if you guys
watch that you'll be blown away i made
the grenade i made that i'm just giving
you a rundown i made the famous
guacamole right there medical medium
style i made the cheese
the cheese wheels i made too i made the
cheese wheels right right i made the
grenades right there okay i made the
gravy which is really cool i made that
on amazon live too you'll see how that
that works right there the the avocado
grenade right i made that it's really
cool actually it was really fun but
we're talking about diseases symptoms
conditions here right on this channel
that's what we're talking about
sarah said struggled with neurological
issues after my son's birth
it's healing slowly but feeling so much
better
already with your information amazing
sarah elizabeth so glad you're here and
i'm proud of you okay
because that those neurological symptoms
which we're covering today those
neurological symptoms that we're
covering today with they really hold
people back people struggle you know you
know what it's like so i got two books
in front of me i got supplements and
dosages in front of me we're in medical
medium school right now
anything you pick up here that i
recommend for friends and family ask
your doctor if it's right for you that's
all because we go into protocol we go
into everything go to your doctor say
hey you know is this okay is this book
okay whatever you just go ask your
doctor what's right for you we're
covering protocols dosages supplements
what it means to heal what it takes to
heal like to go further sometimes
because we got to go further with our
chronic fatigue syndrome we got to go
further with our neurological symptoms
and what's a neurological symptom
migraine anxiety depression
depersonalization ocd bipolar
um
tingles numbness ticks spasms ringing in
the ears dizziness vertigo that's all
neurological not just some restless leg
syndrome neurological people walk around
all day long with neurological symptoms
and fatigue
that walk around with the fatigue
and they walk around with the thyroid
problems you know everybody's getting
diagnosed with the thyroid condition
everybody's getting diagnosed with the
thyroid problem everybody's
getting diagnosed with the thyroid issue
anybody who knows about medical medium
information we mean business it's about
having the knowledge having the
protocols having the supplements and
dosages you know and you guys holidays
are coming along if you know friend
family member you know the books are on
sale on amazon right now amazon.com us
right here's the books
cleanse the heel medical medium jammed
packed with life-saving medical
information they're medical textbooks
let's go to five page 532
in chronic fatigue syndrome so page 532
heading there now
so
one thing that's important to know is
that how does someone heal
when we don't know what's wrong with us
to begin with like why are we struggling
why are we suffering what's wrong with
me
you get sick and it's like what's wrong
with me oh got a thyroid diagnosis yeah
but why
why is my thyroid suddenly
failing
why is my thyroid suddenly getting bad
like why is my
my thyroid suddenly falling apart like
how come like what's happening why do i
have a thyroid problem why do i have
neurological symptoms conditions why do
i have any of this so right now let's go
into neurological neurological tightness
in the chest trembling hands there any
every people that's just trembling all
the time and sometimes it's worse if
they don't get sleep it's really worse
right doesn't mean they got a
parkinson's diagnosis or anything like
that they're just trembling
you know they get they get trembly easy
they get trembling when they don't sleep
good enough they get trembly when
um they get trembling when they're also
they get nervous like they get jarred
like if they get uprooted about
something there's trembling more it's
like it's like they tremble more you
know and it's and it's trembling in
different areas it could be in the legs
it could be in different parts right on
telegram you guys know so many so many
people tremble with the trembles and
stuff right so the trembles the restless
legs the restlessness the weakness of
the limbs where you feel like you don't
have that strength
you just don't have that strength right
we're like god i got the like i don't
know what it is but i feel like i don't
have that strength you can have weakness
of the limbs and have a ton of muscle
and still be like not able to
i've seen guys get sick
with lots of muscle and they finally get
sick with chronic fatigue syndrome and
neurological symptoms
and now they're like they they don't
have the strength like they just it just
doesn't work
and twitch's spasms i said right that's
another one too you get twitches you get
the spasms you get the muscle weakness i
covered aches and pains aches and pains
that are unexplainable
are nerves hurting
why are your nerves hurting
why
are your nerves hurting you guys on
tick-tock why
right michelle says it's viral
what you're right why are your nerves
hurting aches and pains why should
somebody have aches and pains i could
see if you have degenerative discs you
have pain because your nerves are
hurting your degenerative discs right
your vertebrae your nerves spinal nerves
right and
but it's always neurological if you have
aches and pains
pain
that's unexplainable that's mysterious
is neurological
it's nerves it's medical medium
information you're hearing it's not like
i went on google blah blah blah
i mean medical mean information all
these 35 years out there on the scene
and now finally people are picking
nuggets up and they're like whoa and
they take it pass it around
it's mm-info about all this stuff
they're the neurological symptoms let's
go into true cause
neurological because everybody's dealing
with these neurological symptoms
right
if physical injury hasn't occurred
neurological symptoms are caused by one
or more of the over 60 varieties of
epstein-barr virus one or more of the
over 30 varieties of shingles
right
there it is
you got mystery aches and pains
right
it's a little bug
you got mystery
restless legs burning skin
jaw pain
unexplainable you guys on tick tock
right
medical medium books just seeing the
doctors have these books all around the
globe
mds write the full words to these books
incredible end these incredible doctors
medical doctors by the way with
prestigious amazing practices helping
people worldwide right
and
they learn
that the viruses like the shingles and
the epstein bar and the hh
hhv-6 and simplex herpes one cause pain
you get the neck pain
you got the neck pain your low-grade
viral
right you got the jaw pain
you got the simplex one low grade viral
and it's mysterious it's like why does
my jaw hurt why does my ear hurt here
why is it hurt here
that's the pain that people are in you
see
so all this info you know is important
all this information i've seen bars that
low-grade virus that crops up when you
get the flu
you get the flu
and all of a sudden now you've got
long-haul flu
and you got the epstein-barr reactivated
this medical medium information
now all of a sudden you've got the
long-haul plague
that's medical medium information it's
published first probably first about
reactivated epstein-barr by medical
medium okay so if you guys want to know
where you are you're in a place that has
advanced information that science is
taking right now from the medical medium
books that one specifically
on that so
we're talking about supplements if you
guys just arrived on tick tock telegram
youtube right
we're talking about supplements and
dosages rumble we're talking about
supplement and dosages how to heal
take the information to your doctor ask
your doctor what's right i'm just going
to talk about what i do for my friends
and family
that's that's what i'm that's what i'm
talking about so we're in here we're
talking about neurological symptoms i
talked about the viral issue right there
that's important neurotoxins it says
right here in the book in neurological
symptoms neurotoxins are released from
pathogens viruses
they release neurotoxins neurotoxins
cause that extra pain the trembling
hands to the tingles and numbness right
the aches and pains the dizziness all of
that the vagus nerves get all you know
wrangled up everything gets all wrangled
up and you end up sick if you guys don't
have the book christmas coming up you
got holidays inexpensive gift right
there
i'm just gonna say straight out dr fun
medical doctor
md good to see you
this is an incredible medical textbook
right 16.99 on amazon 51 off this has
not jacked up in price
just letting you know
it's not it's still keeping at that low
incredible price right now so make sure
you get it when you get a chance or get
it free at the library if you can find
it read the library but i got two
incredible books in front of me right
now here's the medical medium book
historic life-saving book
so many people in the last six and a
half years got their lives back from
this book i still go every day i'm like
whoa so we're neurological symptoms if a
virus likes a food it likes to eat if a
virus likes eggs which they do
they'll feed off the eggs and create a
neurotoxin make you sick so let's talk
about this
dosages for a condition
let's go there
dosages
so if you've got neurological symptoms
and you got the book in front of you
right and i tell friends and family this
is what you do and this is how you do
you ask your doctor what's right for you
take the book to your doctor you'll see
a whole bunch of different supplements
over here and dosages
and guess what
thousands and thousands of people around
the world
thousands hundreds of thousands
right and now millions actually with
this book okay
have taken the dosages and supplements
from this book applied them
and they've helped them the stories are
out there their experiences are out
there and that's what's incredible about
this okay
you need to read the supplement chapter
before you go into these symptoms and
conditions
you need to read the supplement chapter
yes incredible book ella says amazing so
glad you like it
now gave my thyroid healing book to a
family friend who's facing removal
surgery clp great idea great idea
incredible right renata says welcome to
the medical medium community juan so
you're welcome somebody's fantastic
thank you renata it's really nice to see
you so
here we are let's get the anatomy out
let's take a good look right here
okay
yeah so you guys are doing great so
belinda says love this book i have them
all great information
amazing
so
here we are
we're dealing with
a situation where someone's walking
around they got tinkles and numbness
they got aches and pains they got all
kinds of mystery symptoms maybe they got
dizziness maybe they got vertigo maybe
they got any they could have anything
going on that's neurological so why is
it happening people get the epstein-barr
virus it sits inside their liver
it feeds off of all kinds of toxins and
poisons like metals and all kinds of
petrochemicals and everything else that
get inside pharmaceuticals old
pharmaceuticals and that are sit inside
people's liver and then the virus
goes to the bathroom the virus
eliminates
it goes to bathroom
when the virus goes to bathroom
it's releasing poisons and toxins those
poisons and toxins float around the body
and inflamed nerves someone's walking
around with knee pain that's
unexplainable back pain that's
unexplainable jaw pain that's
unexplainable neck pain head pain
dizziness ringing in the ears all kinds
of different conditions what's happening
is those neurotoxins are floating around
the body
and inflaming nerves
so keep that in mind so neurological
symptoms are all those neurotoxins
floating around the body produced by
viruses
inflaming the nerves
so keep that in mind pamela says order
the book amazing i'm so glad i can't
wait for you to read it your mind's
going to get blown
okay
so the whole thing about neurological
symptoms is you have to be able to kill
viruses you have to be able to kill the
bugs creating them and getting the
poisons and toxins out or at least
killing the bugs so let's talk about
supplements and dosages and why that's
important okay so i'm going to put
him back over here
so we're in the subs and dosages where
neurological symptoms you'll see cat's
claw in there
neurological lyme
anybody can get diagnosed with all you
need is a couple of symptoms and a lyme
doctor and you'll get your neurological
lyme diagnosis somebody who got a
chronic fatigue syndrome diagnosis the
same symptoms that somebody with
neurological lyme diagnosis has can
still get that diagnosis that's how it
works you walk it depends on what doctor
you're walking into if you go to a
multiple sclerosis specialist you're
going to get an ms diagnosis if you go
into a neurological lyme doctor and lyme
doctor uh you know expert you're going
to get the lyme diagnosis if you walk
into a lupus doctor who specializes in
lupus you're going to walk out with a
lupus diagnosis if you walk in with you
know an r.a doctor rheumatoid arthritis
doctor and you walk in you're going to
walk out with
a diagnosis of r.a
you're going to whatever you walk in
you're going to walk out most of the
time wherever you walk in you're going
to walk out with that diagnosis
that's just important that's just just
to know and tic tac you just bought the
book incredible you won't be
disappointed with that book
angelica says i've been on celery juice
and heavy metal detox for almost two
years and my tingling and my left leg is
gone incredible angelica that that's
incredible
so important to know i healed uh lemon
balm love says i healed my neurological
symptoms with mm amazing darcy lee says
aw my tingles and numbness are pretty
much gone thanks to you in the protocol
and cleanse the heel i'm freaking happy
i love the freaking that's cool cause
that means you're happy love love love
love you back
that's cleansed the heel right there you
guys are talking about cleanse the heel
the power has it's helping so many i'm
honored you're here seriously i mean
hearing that you're better and feeling
better is just so incredible it's so
incredible and i love that cat's claw is
an anti-viral
it's an
anti-pathogen okay it's an anti-bug
supplement right that's vimergy by the
way that's the one that i recommend i'm
not sponsored by vimergy and i do not
own the company that's important to know
some people be like he loves vimergy why
well i love energy because a i know them
just like and and
they're good people but i know
all the stuff most supplement company
and product out there supplement
different things out there companies i
know all the people because i try to get
relationships with all the companies out
there in hopes
that they upped the quality
in hopes that they up the quality and
vimrji went to that standard the highest
standard that i've ever seen and that's
why i recommend them all the time a lot
of the supplement companies i know okay
when they go to that level
the members you went to i will be
recommending them every single day
you'll see their stuff here so that's
important enough and
and so yeah but i'm not sponsored these
incredible incredible products so that's
the cat's claw right there so what it
says in here for neurological symptoms
and ask your doctor what's right for you
but this is what i would do if i was
sick it says two dropper fulls twice a
day so i'm gonna put some cat's claw in
here two dropper fulls of cat squad
right there
says twice a day
so keep in mind and i like what i like
to do is i like to become friends with
supplement company owners out there
because i have this dream of
will you do the right thing and make the
stuff the best so and then the
friendships blow up like i'm now like
not friends with a few companies because
i asked them over and over again to
increase their quality and they said no
we're not and so i'm like okay well
and then they get mad and i'm like whoa
okay you don't want to be friends just
because i'm i'm hounding you to increase
your quality
it's just it's annoying right
anyway so we got that the cat's gone
right there
so now golden seal
golden seal is antibacterial it's
antiviral
i love it goldenseal is an important one
right there so when someone's dealing
with neurological symptoms chronic
fatigue is a neurological symptom all on
its own so that's the golden seal right
there it says one drop or full twice a
day
is what it says so that's one dropper
full and if you look if you want to do
instead of twice a day and this is what
i do like for friends and stuff i'll be
like look if you got to do two in one
shot and you do you do your you know you
do it once a day then that's what you do
right zinc is critical
for healing neurological symptoms zinc
is critical for healing
neurological conditions symptoms viral
issues pathogen issues zinc is critical
you guys on tick-tock it's so important
it really is and you guys aren't rubble
it's so important so what it says in
here it says zinc it says one drop or
full twice a day
of zinc now you might be like well i'll
just go get zinc somewhere yeah you
could do that but you'll probably get a
zinc that has citric acid in it you'll
probably get a zinc that has chemicals
in it i talk about this in the book
this is important to know okay when
you're in this book you read that
chapter and you'll see how to protect
yourself with the crap that's out there
i can't even tell you how important that
is you guys i can't even tell you
courtney may good to see you
um i read your comments on youtube you
guys if you like the video thumbs up or
whatever or like the video whatever if
you hate the video or not having a good
time still give me a thumbs up give me a
thumbs up
all right so we got the zinc right there
so that's important it's critical when
it comes down to the immune system
if you're sick
something went wrong with the immune
system
if you're sick with something
something went wrong with your immune
system if you're sick
if you got neurological symptoms
something
somewhere along the way in your life
went wrong with your immune system
if you're sick with two symptoms three
symptoms five symptoms 10 symptoms
50 symptoms
something went wrong with your immune
system
okay
that's why knowing protocols knowing
dosages
knowing what to do
is critical
that's why when you look in here and it
says neurological symptoms that's where
i am if you just came on here tightness
in the chest trembling hands twitches
and spasms muscle weakness tingles and
numbness restless legs restlessness
weakness of the limbs muscle spasms
aches and pains you want to know the
dosages and the supplements
melanie shortell says cured me of my
adhd with the heavy metal detox
and can't thank you enough
i can't thank you enough for doing
the heavy metal detox
trusting
in what others have done to get their
lives back so i can be like that's one
more person that got their life back
one more person
one more one more one more
it it's critical that you get your life
back i feel if you're not living the way
you want to live and you're struggling
like you are
i feel that it it's really really got to
be hard for you and and i'm just sad
about it if you're suffering and
struggling cheryl says for one year i've
been juicing 32 ounces of celery juice
and having
and having heavy metal detox smoothie i
also keep it
i also keep it fat free until at least
two o'clock p.m very smart
i also take a few vimergy supplements
like the vimergy supplements here if you
said that you are speaking right now
about
healed my allergies and some strep
conditions as well thank you
however my hair is so thin and lost so
much i'm devastated
the hair comes back for so many people
the whole thing millions of women are
losing their hair
i talk to doctors who focus on the keto
diet all their patients are losing their
hair
i talked to doctors on their vegan diets
doctors are focused on vegan diets and
they contact me and they said why why
what's with the hair thinning and all
their women are losing hair and their
pain their women patients are losing
their hair talk to paleo diet people
doctors that love the old paleo diet
they're all losing their hair animal
protein diets plant-based diets they're
losing their hair the reason why
if you had caffeine in your life
there's a ticking time bomb that happens
later and the hair comes out for women
because women aren't supposed to lose
their hair women are never supposed to
lose a hair
and so if you're under stress and the
adrenals are overloaded from stress
right and you've got the caffeine
running and you got vinegar's another
one that doesn't help right
high fat diet all those years doesn't
help sluggish liver all these things add
up
all these things have intermittent
fasting the wrong way i've seen hair
fall out for people for that if someone
has a difficult experience a
relationship experience they have a
trying time with a relationship they
have a hardship the adrenals then lose
that that hormone they need because
that's i talk about the medical medium
books that your adrenal has to have all
set of hormones there's a specific
hormone to keep hair and follicles alive
okay so and basically what happens is
all these factors play a role the
caffeine is a big one and then the hair
comes out later
so what i would do is just keep on
healing keep on doing all heal all the
all the critical stuff right
and then focus on maybe take take the
hair hair protocol doctor to you to the
hair protocol to your doctor here
and then and then work on that and guess
what on medical medium i've seen so many
women that lost their hair get their
hair back on medical medium where they
came to medical medium
with all their hair missing alopecia
thinning hair all of it and they got
their hair back
and so there's always hope so just just
know that there always is all right so
we're on neurological symptoms let's do
licorice root licorice fruit is critical
for neurological symptoms right
that's an important one
is licorice root so and i don't see a
licorice root right here so but but let
me see if i can grab one right here too
licorice fruit is critical when it comes
down to
neurological symptoms i got a licorice
root right here that's the vimergy
licorice root gonna put that in here
that's important
so
is that a joke copper is the most reason
if you lose hair
too little copper
that's not why people lose hair it's not
copper well so the copper
copper will give you a lot of other
problems if you have too much copper but
little copper you might have been
reading somebody else's comment
having less copper is nothing to do with
hair loss that's a great way to give
somebody copper poisoning because
imagine how many women are going to be
dowsing copper
copper supplements and making themselves
real sick and then they're gonna have
raging eczema raging psoriasis
depression from copper
more neurological symptoms from copper
like lots of copper supplements and
copper whatever devices and utensils and
all that yes stay away from the copper
jewelry stay away from the copper that
that right there is a nightmare for
people that will not help somebody get
better the trends out there are so
painful it's like if you're like if
you're like into creating a copper
product you better believe you're gonna
say when everybody somebody comes to you
and be like what's so good about your
copper mug what's so good about your
copper jewelry it helps you with all
kinds of conditions what's wrong with
you oh i got hair loss i got fatigue oh
copper will help you because i'm selling
copper bracelets so that'll help you oh
i got you know it's like that it's like
that everywhere you turn it's like that
do you know it doesn't matter it's like
everywhere you turn if someone's like
selling if there's a dealer selling
alkaline ionizer water machines it's
like oh yeah oh wow alkaline ionizer
water to help you with everything what's
wrong with you oh it'll help you with
that meanwhile it'll make you sicker it
will make you sicker it's like oh no
copper will help up it'll make you sick
sicker oh full minerals no it'll make
you sicker so it's what people don't
realize
is that whatever trend is happening that
somebody's banking on or standing behind
someone's actually with trend they'll
say it's good for everything wrong with
you because everybody's so sick in the
world now everybody's so sick that if
someone just stumbles across something
like oh i'm starting a tomato company
where we take the tomato seeds and we
crush them and we put it in a capsule
and um uh so yeah i just got an investor
to invest 500 000 in my company so let's
see if we can sell it uh what's wrong
with you got fatigue yes try my tomato
seed capsule what's wrong with you you
got something wrong with you try my try
my whatever
try my pine needle uh brew uh that's how
it works
and that's not how people heal let's go
into thyroid right now we're heading in
there now um thyroid conditions let's
sit there real quick first
okay 546 uh in this book so we're in
thyroid conditions and cleanse the heel
right now you guys we're talking about
protocol supplements
what to do dosages on protocols we're
talking about all of that
and here we are so thyroid conditions
true cause of thyroid conditions you
have to realize there's over 60
varieties of epstein-barr virus
epstein-barr enters into the thyroid
that's what it does very important to
know okay
epstein-barr
leaves the liver
after you've had mono
and it heads up to the thyroid at some
time in your life this is some of the
most important information you can ever
learn
because
everyone's getting diagnosed with a
thyroid condition and has no idea why so
how are they going to heal their thyroid
condition if they don't know why they
have a thyroid condition
did you ever think about that one right
epstein-barr
sits inside the liver
after you've had mononucleosis when
you're younger
it stays in there and eventually when
your immune system gets kicked down for
some reason like i said immune system
the epstein bar leaves the liver
and it heads up to your thyroid
it enters into the thyroid by burrowing
into the thyroid
and then it lives there where it creates
cysts and nodules
this is medical medium info that science
science is finally taking from me even
though it's not good because they take
it and they just mess it up and
and they don't cite back where the
information they took from comes from
which is the mnm books the medical
textbooks
but you end up with epstein-barr in the
thyroid and then it does damage and you
get your hypothyroid every single person
is going to have a hypothyroid or
hashimoto's or hyperthyroid or graves
disease or system nodules diagnosis in
their day
because of the viral epidemic causing it
so giving you a quick rundown about that
so that's important right there okay
so we're in cleanse the heel if you guys
don't have the book amazon.com
51 off get it so you can protect
yourself or go to the library get it for
free if you need
okay
but it's 51 off we're in thyroid
problems now so what is it saying here
it says
fresh celery juice 32 ounces daily if
that's all you can do and it's celery
juice then you do your celery juice
right
5m thf is in there too so that's the
vimer g5mthf right there
that's the best one out there on the
market vimerges v is in victor i am as
in mary ergy dimmerg.com
right i'm not sponsored
i gotta say it because people are like
what what
cat's claw
cat's claw okay is in in is in thyroid
conditions the cat's claw because it's
about killing the epstein-barr virus
that's in thyroid condition
lemon balm that's another one that's in
thyroid conditions so you got the lemon
mom right there okay it's in the thyroid
condition it says four dropper fulls
twice a day
there's one
two
a drop or full is whatever comes up when
you squeeze the dropper there it is
that's a dropper full
you see you see a half dropper full
right there you see i see you have a
dropper full that's a full dropper full
it's whatever comes up when you squeeze
it you see how i squeezed it it's
whatever comes up
that's a dropper full four dropper holes
let me get another one in here
all right we got that
okay that's important
spirulina you'll hear out there oh
spirulina for thyroid i don't know that
you know some people don't like oh yeah
yeah
that the whole thing
the reason why people don't get better
is they don't know what to do
they don't know what to do
and the medical media books have already
proven themselves
i can sit here and
stand on a soapbox
i can sit here shout it from the
rooftops i can sit here on a mountaintop
and shout it all day long
because the books have worked and turned
people's lives around and fixed the
thyroid i just how many people i see
stories every single day my god you
fixed my hashimoto's oh my god your book
saved me my hashimoto's is gone oh my
god my hypothyroidism is but my doctor
can't believe it hey my cyst on my
thyroid disappeared after doing medical
medium protocols for thyroid oh my god
like it's all the time out there
spirulina is one of the things to use
that's the vibrancy spirulina lysine
when you're dealing with these viruses
that create thyroid problems you need
the lysine to knock down the viral load
viral load
you need the lysine to knock down the
because these viruses that create
thyroid problems are herpetic
really important to know right there
vitamin b12
okay what does it say vitamin b12 one
drop or full twice a day get your
dropper full in there
get very important
so magnesium glycinate
hey well no i'm taking magnesium and how
come my thyroid is not better
well one reason is you're probably
taking magnesium
but you're not taking magnesium
glycinate
so it's not absorbing
absorbing
you're not feeding your cells it's that
magnesium glycinate that does the
difference where it feeds the cell so
it'll say magnesium glycinate on here
one capsule twice a day is what it says
microc so it has vitamin c is what it's
recommending in here right
vitamin c
um six capsules twice a day
so in order to knock down viral loads
you've got to have your immune system
being fed with that antioxidant that
vitamin c
that's the immune building antioxidant
that vitamin c
really important
so
you gotta have the vitamin c if you have
look you look
if you get overwhelmed do one thing
one thing ask your doctor do one thing
i'll take a little b12 it says here in
the book you could read the chapter and
you could read like how you can navigate
do one thing
do two things
but know you're on the right right track
know that you're on the right track
that's the whole thing
that you know you're heading on the
right direction
kim says does this mean only rich people
can be healthy because that's a lot of
wonderful products that cost a lot of
money well kim
i can give you a couple of pieces of
information that'll really be helpful
okay one is
i don't charge for
big programs where you have to pay five
thousand dollars to come in
okay i don't subscription charge on my
website millions of people hit my
website millions around the world
the medical medium website is so filled
with free information and millions upon
millions are not giving me a penny
and they're accessing the information
and they're healing themselves
keep that in mind
you don't have to be rich to get the
book out of the library
get the book out of the library
and you can start where you can and kim
i talk about it inside the book
you can start
with a cleanse
you can start there's people that heal
just from the cleanses
without supplementation
every day
so you don't have to be rich
for medical medium information
it's all free
it's all free and it depends maybe
somebody has a really difficult
difficulty they got 60 symptoms they're
struggling and they might need some
supplements someday but they might
get to that point of just the cleanses
and some celery juice or or just
cleanses and then boom they're moving
forward moving forward and then
eventually the friend loans them a
little bit of money a couple dollars for
b12 and then they just next thing you
know it they're moving moving moving and
all the information is free it's free
i'm here right now using my time
right using my time
and my energy
for free
is what it is
and that's what i do and just so you
know
if you get the book
it doesn't even pay for the book the
book is 51 off it costs more to print it
i'm here for free and i don't own the
supplement company
i can start a medical medium supplement
company tomorrow
and make a make a bunch of money about
that but i don't
i'm here for free
and um and i love you for being here kim
and everybody else
so let's go into we're into thyroid
conditions i'm talking about dosages and
supplements i just saw glutathione in
there it's of energy glutathione
look you can start with three
supplements three supplements is all you
just start with that the quality matters
too you go pick up something crappy you
just waste it money and it doesn't work
you go to pick up a zinc that has citric
acid in it natural flavors and alcohol
in it and everything else and whoa you
just you know you get in trouble
dawn says i started with only one at a
time whoa dawn in
now i have lots
and i i cut out so many other things
that cost a whole lot more than the
supplements cost so don you you
navigated you navigated your life you
were like i'm going to make choices i'm
going to make choices i'm going to work
on healing i'm going to navigate through
this
i'm blown away i'm blown away and i'm
proud of you too you guys we're live
right now if anybody wants to know
we're live on rumble tick tock to
youtube facebook telegram telegram my
favorite the pre the prevention realm
says i healed so much with just lemon
water celery juice and lowered fat
because you read the books to learn
about that exactly
incredible you're healing so much
you don't have to be rich
um
see dr fon md says only rich people can
be treated for neurological issues and
mri costs a thousand dollars or more
yeah i mean there you go
that's really just really true
so we're gonna go into chronic fatigue
syndrome we'll head there real fast
right
you guys
i don't know what to say i can't tell
you i put countless hours into the books
i make sure you have the information so
you can heal and make sure you get free
everything kimberly says it's just it's
just three sups
then what three do you recommend it's in
here you've got to read the chapter
kimberly just got to read the chapter go
to the library if you want
get the book the amazon's got it for
sale right now 51 off you know if
someone wants a christmas present for
somebody if they want a holiday gift for
somebody it's an inexpensive gift and it
can save a life
and it has saved lives so that's a
really cool gift you know
um you know somebody might be like well
now i really wanted that book and
somebody would be like well and then
they get sick and they need the book
they're like i wish i got it for a
present tanya says good health equates
to great wealth baby steps and small
changes lead to bigger steps and bigger
changes whoa powerful information we can
do it the books are like encyclopedias
perfect for health references
incredible they're not throwaway books
the one thing about medical medium i had
a doctor tell me like about a month ago
i had a meeting with a doctor who wanted
to pick my brain right they asked me he
basically said you know what i you know
what what i love about your books i said
what they're not throw away books
because i bought dr bulldozer's book and
i bought dr jimson's book and then i
bought dr john's book and i bought dr
book and they were all throwaway books i
read them and i threw them away
but when i read yours
and this is a big md when i read your
books
i couldn't throw them away
he says i'd like to throw away all the
doctor's books because he's a big big
big md because there's so many problems
with what they're doing in those books
that he just throws him away after he
reads them he said i couldn't throw your
book away aw
i said if you really wanted you could he
says i couldn't it was it was too good
and it was too it was pertinent it
didn't contradict itself it was really
chris's says banana mono cleanse well
banana monoclines in the book helped me
with my adhd so much i never had to
think about what to eat
and it gave my brain so much more space
to think about other things and it
healed my neurotransmitters incredible
as it's amazing chronic fatigue syndrome
so i'm in it right now on page 532
cfs that's when the nerves get inflamed
from the viral infections and it shows
you here it's chaga mushroom and i don't
have any chocolate mushroom right here
chocolate mushroom
right
it's a vimerji chaga mushroom right
there
so chaga mushroom that's in here for cfs
okay
that's one
barley grass cheese powder that's here
for cfs
amazing tells you the dosage
lemon balm licorice root
right that's in here
you got the vitamin c you got the zinc
you got the mthf you got the ashwagandha
that's in there for cfs ashwagandha okay
tells the dosage
really incredible really incredible
information so you guys in this episode
here that you're
that i'm honored to have you here we
talked about the viral issue we talked
about the nerves getting inflamed and
let's cover that for a couple seconds
real quick here
when your vagus nerve gets inflamed
everything starts to become a problem
everything starts to go wrong titan is
in the chest you don't feel good fatigue
when your vagus nerves coming out of
your brain stem get inflamed by
low-grade viral infections everything
gets miserable gets really miserable bad
you get the tingles and numbness you get
the itchy nerves you get all kinds of
problems
your vagus nerve the tightness of the
chest you get the tightness of the
throat you get the fatigue you can even
i mean you can get all kinds of issues
and so what i like
in the dizziness and the vertigo and all
this so what i like is making sure i
know my supplement supplements my
dosages making sure i know my right
cleanses making sure i can even start
out small i can straight out a little
bit of time and i know i'm getting to
where i need to go and i know i have the
most advanced information there is in
health
if it makes anybody feel better that's
like sitting on the fence medical medium
books are the number one selling books
in health six and a half years running
now
just think about that and there's a gold
emblem on the book
other health book el health books do not
have that
right there they can't
because the health books out there with
all the little trends and all that that
are out there you guys see they've only
sold 5 000 books
and they hire a company to do it
and they just to make the new york times
less they only sell 10 000 books
there's millions of copies sold around
the world through grass movement
grassroots movement
people use bad supplement quality bad
qual quality of supplements they don't
use the right stuff they're getting
poisoned with
everything under the sun
if it makes anybody feel better there's
a reason why this exploded around the
world medical medium information
so yeah
so bottom line you guys
just know that i care about you i
believe in you i'm going to go live
again tick-tock i'm turning you back on
telegram turning you back on
all right and i'm going to ig
and uh i love you guys greatly and if
you guys get a chance
disaster disaster you guys get a chance
check out the amazon live platform
that's where i'm doing the medical
medium cooking show subscribe because
you'll get blown away i'm showing tips
about fruits vegetables herb spices wild
foods leafy greens tips no one's ever
heard i did avocado today i did avocado
like no one's ever seen the link is in
the bio link is in the description i did
avocado like nobody's ever seen i'll
even show you right here real quick just
one thing see right here right here
i did the avocado grenade wait till you
see how this is made looks like a nice
avocado right there right you guys okay
on on
pilgrim you open up the top and you got
that fresh salsa sitting in the center
you scoop it out and you enjoy the rest
of the avocado in there i actually made
that today
amazon is where i'm doing amazon live
that's where i'm doing the food stuff
here i'm doing the health i'm doing the
medical i'm doing the disease symptom
conditions link is in the description in
the bio and i'm also doing everything
else the trend stuff meaning busting
trends and myths everything here right
talking about sabotage in the world all
of that is on these channels but the
amazon live
is about the tips you've never heard
before
with the cooking i love you guys
i'll see you guys soon go to ig going to
turn telegram back on and tick tock