HD incredible comprehensive information
all through the brain saver books I just
want to read a little to you real quick
here's what ADHD isn't genetic it's not
genetic and it's not gut related neither
of those popular explanations addresses
the true underlying causes of ADHD so in
here I talk about how the midline canal
right there so there it is the midline
canal you guys if you take a look
right here
this section here gets filled up with
particles of toxic heavy metals they
actually fill into the midline canal
right here then as you get older the
brain pushes together
and seals up the midline canal right
there then the metals get trapped in
that Canal making it harder for them to
be removed unless you have the right
things to use the right information the
right protocols so ADHD is a compilation
of mercury and aluminum so I'm going to
go into the book a little bit right here
so I'm reading out a brain saver I'm
excited about this actually so what
really causes ADHD is Mercury and
aluminum settling in the brain's
cerebral midline Canal which divides the
brain's left hemisphere and right
hemisphere
along with some additional metal so
here's the other part that's interesting
so ADHD isn't just the midline canal and
the metals settling into there it's also
metal sprinkled about throughout the
brain in different areas so it's kind of
like that Christmas light Christmas tree
effect going throughout the brain Plus
midline Canal with the metals
and that's important to know it's the
same causes autism as well same exact
cause the difference though is just like
anybody's differences with ADHD or
Autism depends on how much metal how
much is settled in the midline canal how
much is also sprinkled about in the left
and right hemispheres
when these Metals take up resonance in
the midline canal they block internal
Communications within the brain as a
result the brain must adapt so what
happens is Communications inside the
brain is blocked from the metals you've
got electricity going through the brain
right here everybody has a certain
amount of electrical current going
through some run hotter some run cooler
some intense is really intensified
depending on what's Happening
emotionally what's going on in our lives
but either way we have this electrical
grid running through the brain and then
the midline canal being filled with
Mercury and aluminum and mercury and
aluminum being sprinkled about within
the brain
Communications get interfered with
so when these Metals take up resonance
inside the midline canal there has to be
adapting we need that ability because
internal Communications within the brain
get messed up so let's read a little bit
more this is why you often find a child
with ADHD behaving in one manner
when you're asking them to behave in
another the evolving domestic chemicals
children are up against and adults are
another problem on its own so let's go
into that
so not only do we get the Mercury and
aluminum inside the brain and that
interferes with communication because
electrical grid is hitting them so let's
hit that area too talk about that so as
electricity is traveling through the
brain
it's hitting these Mercury and aluminum
deposits when it does the actual
electrical current ricochets or gets
derailed into adjacent tissue throughout
the brain this makes communication
difficult or focused and concentration
or so many other different symptoms
along with it
when it comes down to an aluminum is
more present than mercury in many ways
for some people and then Mercury is more
present than aluminum from some other
people you guys I'm reading out a brain
saver we're just talking about ADHD now
in this book here
brain saver protocols now remember I
don't know if you guys know this is
because I was talking about this the
other day
that's one big book right there okay and
it had to be broken into two huge books
right because it was too big to publish
this is brain saver protocols so let's
go into this section here brain server
protocols and ADHD is right here in one
of the protocols now that's just one
part of this book 300 symptoms
conditions in here and then there's the
brain shot therapies you guys when you
apply the brain shot therapies it's a
new medical medium tool that's in these
books you will be so impressed at the
instant relief of the brain shot
therapies which is a therapeutic tool
it's a medical medium tool inside the
brain saver books but hey when you have
them in your hand and you check that out
you'll be like whoa so let's go into
this a little bit longer now too we'll
we'll take another look
so I'm in symptoms and conditions right
here inside inside insect brain saver
symptoms and conditions that's where I
am so right before ADHD it says
addiction that's one right there then
there's ALS then there's anxiousness
then there's Alzheimer's anorexia
anxiety there's autism there's Bell's
Palsy there's brain fog there's bipolar
disorder
there's balance and dizziness issues
there's brain inflammation it goes on
and on 300 different symptoms and
conditions and seven heavy metal detox
cleanses inside these books seven heavy
metal detox cleanses inside these inside
these books which is really incredible
so back to ADHD so what you'll hear
often out there is it's genetic and what
people don't realize is that toxic heavy
metals are passed down from generation
to generation to generation that's how
it's done so in the womb in utero we
take metals on that's what happens is as
a baby we actually absorb Metals inside
the brain from the family line going
back further and further and further 500
years 700 years a thousand years
generation after generation after
generation toxic heavy metals are passed
along the way and then we pick up new
toxic heavy metals and then we as adults
pass it on to the next Generation so
what you'll see out there now and you'll
find that a lot more children are
getting ADHD a lot of adults too and
it's worsening out there because more
Metals including domestic metals and
inherited metals are getting into our
children and adults and it's being
passed on Generation generation also
gathered here every single day as these
Metals get into the brain it interferes
with communication the electrical grid
and some people have it worse than
others that's why there's the scale is
so huge that's why the scale for autism
the scale for ADHD is so big because
there's so many different variables
where are the metals what kind of metals
how many of them are they deposited are
they just sprinkled about how much metal
is in the midline canal all of this
changes everything to behavior to the
symptom condition Focus concentration to
understanding information to being able
to communicate and talk all of it
changes to the how hyperactive if how
not like all of it matters and changes
as far as the metals and what kind of
metals and where they're located and how
deep they are inside the brain tissue
especially if there's a large amount in
the midline canal going across within
the brain so
you guys this is this one little piece
of brain Saver in the brain saver of
books and hey books are going to be
delivered soon so lock down one when you
can and I'll see you guys in the next
video