so I'm on here right now because I want
to show you a couple tips one when
there's smoke in the air because of the
LA fires right now things are really bad
for a lot of people I mean it's
devastating I'm sure you guys have seen
it out there people losing their homes
people losing their Farms their
businesses their family's homes their
apartment buildings they're losing their
places to live massive
I mean there's all kinds of things
people are evacuating all around in LA
and trying to get out there so anyway I
just wanted to come on here just uh for
a couple of tips number one um I think
one of the big things is because the air
is so dry so so
dry that the Ash and the air it just
cuts through it just gets into the lungs
really easily and I think that's really
hard for a lot of people so one of the
things that you can do is you can like
an n95 mask it's going to help a little
bit I mean it's obviously not going to
protect you with flames and heavy heavy
smoke but it can actually block some of
the ashes it can block some of the thick
smoke some of the toxins that are in the
smoke like the chemicals and things that
are burning in furniture and
carpets and wall boards and treated wood
all that and plaster all that stuff
that's burning that's really toxic from
houses and homes so um you know there's
a couple of uh tricks I want to show
people while we're here you guys coming
on right here this is great but I want
to First all first of all I want to just
say that if you are if you were coming
to the Cafe Gratitude popup dinners the
medical medium Cafe Gratitude pop-up
dinners January 15th January 16th we are
postponing those dinners so check your
email because there's going to be
notices going out to you if you did
purchase a ticket for that popup dinner
on the 15th or the 16th we're postponing
it just you know for for a lot of
reasons one is just for protective
Health measures and everything else it's
really Smoky and so forth out there but
at the same time Cafe Gratitude is
they're open and they have medical
medium dishes there so if you're
somebody you know and you need to grab
some food that's a place to grab some
really healthy food which is really
great you can grab a medical medium dish
in there if you're somebody that's doing
medical medium tools and medical medium
Foods so that's what's amazing about the
maafe gratitude that they they're there
and they have medical medium food on
hand so if you're traveling through or
if you're relocating in the area you can
run in and you can get food there um you
know dishes there which is really
incredible so but if you happen to have
a ticket it's next week was supposed to
be next week on the 15th and the 16th if
you did have a ticket and you were
coming to LA to be there for the meet
and greet with me I'm not going to be
there so we're postponing it and we'll
have dates pretty soon just not yet and
you'll get a refund in a whole bit and
then we will send out some notices and
such such so that you can actually get
the tickets again and all that um so
it's going to be great but right now
there's a lot of Devastation happening
you guys know I want to go I want to
cover a couple of points first is
because the air is so dry
because um you well here's the problem
too with the smoke this the smoke
inhalation that people are dealing with
right now even if you're like miles away
from it you live miles away from it but
it's in the air because it's a lot of
stuff there's there's fire retardant in
the air that they're dropping down it's
a dust like a dust particle like almost
like an aerosol that's floating around
people are going to be breathing that in
so if you're exposed and you're out of
your house and so forth one thing you
can do is you take a towel like this and
I've said this before with other fires
over the years but you take a towel okay
and you moisten it so this is really
important right here you moisten it
right here I'm squeezing out the water
okay just like that all right and you
breathe through the towel a moist towel
that's important you can you can
actually make it as thin as you want you
can double it up depending on how it it
feels
but you could do this too you can hold
it just like this and you can put it
over your face and you can breathe
through it so what happens is the water
is what catches a lot of the toxins a
lot of that dust a lot of the ashes all
the stuff that's coming off of people's
wallboards all the paint That's burning
on their
houses um all the carpets like I said
the furniture all that stuff and all the
different chemicals the household
cleaners they're all burning up in
people's houses all the aerosol cans all
the spray bottles of cleaners and so
forth all the oil containers in people's
garages you know gasoline in people's
garages and and and all that so all the
stuff is in the air plus what they're
dropping on the fires like the fiery T
and everything they're dropping
that all on everybody and you know and
it's really tough when that that hair is
really really tough if you're dealing
with it now if you're in it I feel so
bad for you but um so one of the things
if you're moving around you get a couple
of towels like that you keep them moist
and damp if you're traveling through it
you grab it you put it over your face
like this and you breathe through it and
you'll see the difference what happens
is that that air is so dry because that
air is so dry it's how it kind of gets
you it's not just the oxygen loss in the
air we're already somewhere around 19%
oxygen as it is out there give give or
take on what day the atmosphere and
everything else on this planet and
pollution and all that but oxygen is
going to probably go down to
15% 14% in certain areas somewhere
around there and it isn't just the
oxygen loss it's going to be the
particles it's all going to be the
particles and what this does is it grabs
the particles moist towels grab the
particles and you can do it we could if
you're in your house you don't have air
cleaners it's coming into the house a
lot you might want to do this
periodically and then you change it out
you rinse it out you change the water
out too you do fresh water and you dump
that water out you'll notice when you do
it for a while the water starts to get
kind of
skunky and the water starts to get kind
of um gets kind of murky and that murky
is how much is floating in the air how
much of that Ash how much of those
particles are floating in the air and it
gets trapped in the towel so you know
and then when things come down or you
get an air cleaner and you're able to
you know suck some of that up in the air
you know you're better off but and you
don't have to have it real wet can just
be
damp um a lot of air escapes this isn't
like a mask a lot of air escapes through
a towel through a shirt okay it's not
like uh a really good mask respirator on
there and everything thing filters on
there it's not like that and even that
it Escapes in it's the moisture Factor
that's missing in the air it's the
moisture factor that allows it to really
travel and get into the lungs and into
the bloodstream so I'm just letting
people know and maybe this doesn't even
matter for you and you don't need to
worry about this or think about this
you're nowhere near any of this
stuff but if you are this is a great
technique it's a very stable technique I
mean you don't want to go into a fire
with it and expect it to help you it's
not like that but it helps you if you're
in your home you're dealing with some
smoke that's coming through you're not
leaving you can't go you you know you're
just you're staying in that home you're
staying in that apartment air is bad
outside the whole bit you can do this or
you got to go you got to go get food you
got to get out of the house smoking in
there and it's you know and what happens
if you put your shirt or you wear one of
those those masks that people wore those
black masks and so forth those cloth
masks and everything that people wore
during the whole sea thing the
dryness just doesn't stop it so those
masks just don't stop it I saw like one
news guy earlier today on social and the
news guy had one of those masks right
it's like the cloth one the one that
people wore during sea and still wear it
now a lot of people do and the guy was
out there and you see the air and the
smoke and the ashes blowing around I'm
like that's not stopping anything
because there's no moisture in it
there's no moisture in it it's just not
there so what what it really needed to
do was periodically you know take a
towel and just hold it over like this
and there might be another way to do
that too but hold it over like this and
have it stuck on your face put it right
to your face and leave an air opening
like a little like a gap in there so you
got like you know some Ro in there and
you breathe and like I said that cotton
that fabric with the moisture grabs on
to it and if you feel like the air is
really bad the Smoke's really bad you
can double it up so you can do this then
you know instead of having it on its
thinnest like this that's its thinnest
you know could be like a washcloth
whatever right washcloth this is just a
hand towel like a kitchen towel you can
have it at its thinnest if for some
reason it's really bad then you double
it up make this makes a huge difference
now you double it up like that okay now
it's double got right two layers if it's
really really bad you need to do four
layers that's four layers right there
boom got your hands like this put it
over your
face and you breathe and that moisture
and those four layers acts like really
strong filter and then all those ashes a
lot of the toxins the chemicals the
smoke all of that boom it gets caught in
there so you're not getting so much into
your lungs so if you can you need to
move move around about you know and get
someplace or get food or go here go
there because it's it's going to be
there for a while the Smoke's going to
be there for a while it's not just going
away tomorrow and it's just not it's
it's actually just as bad if not getting
worse tonight until tomorrow for sure
and they don't have any you know none of
its contained from you know from when
you look into it um if you're somebody
that's lost your
home you know my heart pours out to you
truly because it's just devastating
everything about it so um but once again
like I said you know you can do
something like this it's a great tip
great tip now there's this packet I
don't know if you've had this before
it's a medical medium tool book right
here okay environmental disaster air
quality tools all right including some
air cleaners that are the best ones so
the best air cleaners other tools too
supplementation you know for after the
fact as well you get some plays you're
able or things start coming down got to
build your immune system back up you
know after getting everything because
when it goes into the lungs and it goes
into the bloodstream what happens with
chronic illness when people have chronic
illness and they're struggling it could
be a trigger all those toxins all those
poisons floating around Metals so the
hmds is in this packet right here and
you guys already do the
hmds a lot of you guys do anyway a lot
of the people in the medical mem
Community do the
hmds and so the reason why the hmds is
really good because you're capturing
metals that are going into the lungs and
into the bloodstream and quickly into
the
liver and you're capturing those metals
because that's what it is you know all
these homes are burning all these
buildings are burning churches are built
burning um uh buildings are burning all
the office buildings are burning and so
you're thinking about like what is in
that smoke and it's a tremendous amount
of
metals that's what's in there treaded
wood carpets wallboard metal it's just
everywhere including metal that's
burning including steel
aluminum that's in the air all of it so
it's a big deal
Shelly Mart says do you have pamphlet
yeah link is in the bio link is in the
description here it is right here Shelly
Mart says do you have pamphlet
downloadable yes this is a downloadable
right here I mean you know download it
take a look link is in the bio link is
in the description there's a lot of
different Tools in here including the
best air cleaners for the
situation which are really helpful you
know so take a look when you get a
chance download it I mean it can't hurt
to download this and just get a reminder
of some things if you're already doing
some things like hmds you already know
about this trick right here with the
towel that you know fine but there's a
lot of other um Tools in here too so
give it a shot so here it is right here
environmental disaster air quality tools
download right
there really really
helpful
so um
and you would think when you think about
the towel trick like how can that help
how can that help it
helps it helps greatly if you have
experience with
fires um at all in your life in some way
some shape some form maybe smoke from a
wildfire out there in the past or you
know some type of forest fire or some
other
situation maybe a neighbor Burns you
know a fire pit every day or you know a
garbage pit a lot of neighbors they just
burn garbage in different places they're
not even burning wood they're burning
like treated wood and garbage and all
kinds of scraps of things and house
trash and everything and you're dealing
with something like that but you can't
do anything about it this helps more
than people know more than people know
and so what happens you'll notice if you
use it a couple times and even if it's
like a half an hour to you're dealing
with something where you have to open
the doors in the house open the windows
for some reason you open the doors to
let a pet out or something like that and
then the smoke just Barrels in and you
shut the door and you don't have a good
air cleaner or air cleaning
system and um and now you're just
feeling like it's just getting to you
and it makes your chest heavy and if
you're somebody with chronic illness
it's really hard really really hard it
can be a trigger I talk about smoke as
being a trigger in the medical books so
I have over the years talked about that
it is a trigger it's nothing to fear but
it is a trigger and so protecting your
immune system taking care of
yourself um all of that counts all of
that's important that's why this is not
just for you know not just for the
problem in the Moment Like good air
cleaners and then the hand towel the
moist hand towel it's also
supplementation building up your immune
system because that's what gets knocked
down so when we're breathing in all that
smoke that Rogue smoke that's just
coming from all these different things
burning out there it's trying on the
immune system it's heavy on the immune
system it's difficult on the immune
system so it's important to Boom jack up
that immune system make it stronger get
it in a better place very important very
important so keep that in mind all right
all of that counts also everyone is
already fighting guess what the
flu and the new bugs coming so they name
flues different things like you
know like respiratory different
respiratory names and so forth and they
name flu differently all the time but in
the end they're really just bad
flu and they like to change the names
cuz they like to make it look like it's
not a flu they do that too where is why
they do that by the way if you want to
really know is because it's getting out
there finally I've talked about it for
years and I've even talked about it
medical medium books and stuff it's flu
don't just exist they're not out there
because they happen just to be out there
they're let out of the gate every single
year twice a year they let let a new one
out they like to rename them they rename
them because it makes it look like
they're not letting them out you know
there's that whole game that's played
too when it comes down to bugs but right
now with everybody that's dealing with
flu and they're dealing with respiratory
bugs andc they're dealing with that too
it's important to keep your immune
system strong especially with smoke and
this Smoke's this smoke is going to
travel all around the country different
wind currents are going to take it the
jet stream stream is going to take it
it's going to be just floating around
everywhere including all the fire fire
retardant so it's important to have
options here here you got the seven top
supplements that are critical make sure
you download this make sure you the
links in the bio links in the
description it's really handy and good
to have it just is um Le lemon honey
ginger water great for the immune system
cucumber juice because you want
hydration on a different level to get
poisons and toxins out of the
bloodstream so straight cucumber juice
is a great great option there um let's
see what else so many other things too
heavy metal detox smoothie grab the
metals cuz the metals are in the
air heavily in the air so a lot of
people are going to be dealing with
burning and melting aluminum vaporizing
in the air so that's that's really
tricky all on its own
um extractor smoothie that's an option
right there another
tool
Jason see looking
there Jason please DM the medical medium
account
um if you can okay on Instagram so Jason
DM the medical medium account on
Instagram see brain shot therapies are
really good
toxic heavy metal exposure brain shot
therapy that's another really important
one with this kind of smoke with what's
happening out there that's in this
pamphlet too this is
downloadable it's a downloadable just
letting you know there it is links in
the bio link is in the
description what do you have to
lose very
important there is a Chemtrails
exposure very important too here's what
happens right got all the smoke out
there
okay homes houses mansions are
burning from small houses to mansions to
schools everything's just burning up
right now so what happens is then all of
a
sudden higher powers on the planet take
advantage of these situations and they
end up
directing Sea Trail planes in the
direction and the dropping that too salt
in the
wound that's how it's
done but that's that's the process so
not only is this happening you got all
the smoke and all these toxins in the
air but then all of a sudden it's like
yep send the Sea Trail planes send them
on
over dropping out that too it's not like
they
stop it's not like they stop there isn't
some like magic wand to wave and be like
okay well we already have this problem
here now with all these fires and all
this bad
smoke children with asthma are
struggling people are suffering from it
but the so why don't you just stop the
sea trails in this area nope doesn't
work like that but that's how evil works
it's how Darkness works it's like you
got all the smoke and all the stuff
happening and no higher power on the
planet goes all right let's dial down
all the Sea Trail
planes they have enough trouble so let's
get rid of those 1,400 planes that are
going to fly over just in the next
couple of days and drop chemicals out of
them let's just I'm not talking about
fire retardants coming out of
helicopters I'm talking about planes
with sea Trails so let's just stop that
but they don't so those are still
dumping they're just higher above all
that smoke those are dumping their crap
and then you got the evildoers on the
planet that releasing the next bug
respiratory bug which they already have
it's already on its
way next few months people are going to
be coughing their guts out so it's
important to protect the immune system
let's just be straightforward on that
really
important so nobody's stopping the next
bug they're releasing nobody's stopping
the sea Trails just because their smoke
they still keep all that in
all that's happening and the smoke and
the
blaze yeah plus other stuff too and
that's how it's done so you want to
protect yourself so in this pamphlet you
got the Sea Trail exposure shot it is
valuable it is worth
it very worth it really
powerful got the pesticide herbicide and
fungicide um exposure shot there nothing
better than these shot shots for this
kind of stuff different healing foods to
focus on while the smoke is happening
because here's what here's here's how it
works okay unless you're just you're
just trying to survive and you're eating
whatever you have to eat nothing wrong
with that if you're trying to survive
and you're just you're in a bad place
and you're figuring how to survive in
that smoke and everything and you're
eating what you just need to eat totally
respect that totally understand okay of
course but there are some powerful Foods
you can eat to help get rid of toxins
faster that you're inhaling inhalence
that you're getting in your lungs so
that's
important and then we got the towel
right here if you have to go outside
when air quality is poor such as walking
to your car or grocery store or
traveling to your workspace this simple
tip can help traff and reduce inhalation
of smoke and some of the toxins in the
dust and smoke in the air and that's it
place a CLE clean cloth under the faucet
or in a bowl right here of water so the
entire cloth is wet ring excess water
out like I did of the cloth so it is
damp but not dripping with water keep
that in mind damp but not dripping with
water use both hands to pick up the damp
clo cloth leaving some space between
your hands so you can place it over your
nose and mouth and breathe through the
damp cloth and like I said if you're
you're trying to go somewhere you're
going to the grocery store you're
traveling to a
workplace if you're in your house and
the house is filling up but you got
nowhere to go and you just have to live
with it that's what you're telling
yourself because of a
situation you don't have an option or
opportunity really to go anywhere the
house is Smokey inside you can totally
do this it is a
Savor and then air filtration
recommendations in here too so that's
just some of the things right there in
the environmental disaster air quality
tools guess how much this
cost it's free costs
nothing you don't have to get onto a
membership on my
website or social media Pages or
anything you don't have to pay a monthly
fee I put this together with my own
money my own time my team's time and
here it is Julie you if the link of this
pamphlet is in the
bio or in the description destion you're
on Facebook in the
description so you can get it you know
and it's crazy you know crazy everything
is for free with the medical medium
stuff just it's that's important to know
too because nothing's free out there in
the health realm now I saw somebody
trying to trying to take Jabs at like
certain stuff of mine you know that
comes from Spirit of compassion like the
hmds and stuff like that the hmd heavy
metal detox and so forth and then
they're like yeah instead of doing that
you should you should pay on my you know
my website my monthly fee was like 40
bucks or something a month for all my
information you know this guy's
information or something it's like yeah
you're charging people you're ripping
people off with your $40 a month on your
website for regurgitated
information how about making it for free
for people give them that opportunity to
decide what they want to do say of
making them pay and then it makes them
feel like they have no choice cuz they
paid or something the whole thing is
like demented anyway that's for free the
pamphlet was put together for you guys
pass it along tell somebody else here it
is and guess how much this costs right
here I don't know do you have a
washcloth already because that's
free ring it out put it over your
face so it's a really big help it's a
really big help if that's you know if
that's what you need to do
do okay but yeah like it's it's
really it's a demonic World in so many
ways it really is because how did those
fires
start it's a whole another discussion
and like I said no one's cutting off the
sea
Trails over the fires nobody's cutting
those off they just let those pour out
of jets and planes whatever and um I
know one stopping the next bug they let
out of the gate they manufacture and let
out of the gate so yeah it's a difficult
world and if you're somebody with
chronic illness you got to protect your
immune system or at least start maybe
something simple do celery
juice do some celery juice that's it
don't add anything in it straight celery
juice start with 2 oz if you need to
work yourself up to 8 ounces work
yourself up to 16 oz if you really like
it feels good doing it work yourself up
to 32 bounces once a day and build up
your immune system clean up your liver
pull that stuff
out pull all that toxin all that
crap pull it out of the body at least
capture it while it's going in and flush
out the liver do some lemon water too
that's another thing
right you know Spirit of
compassion you know what's incredible
about Spirit of compassion is lemon
water was just like lemonade it was
refreshing put it in water add a little
sugar add a little honey
right that's what you do but to flush
the liver Spirit of compassion was like
well no you use this tool to flush the
liver you use this tool to flush the
bloodstream first thing in the morning
that's what I love about medical meme
information
it's really amazing so cut a lemon in
half
squeeze it so what I would do if I was
in all that smoke and it was out there
and I had a live in it for a couple
weeks or a couple days or a month and
it's in the air
periodically I would be doing you know
lemon water every single morning staying
hydrated but you don't have to stay
crazy hydrated you don't have to be like
drinking tons of water you don't have to
do
that yeah you don't have to go and do
that that's not doesn't mean that's
going to be helpful
but stay hydrated in the sense where
instead of a cup of coffee only in the
morning you're doing 16 o 32 o of lemon
water where it's a glass of water and
you squeeze a half a lemon in there and
that's what you do and you get that
liver flush you get that body flush you
flush those toxins out especially if
you're breathing in all that
metal that's the people don't understand
is outdoor Furniture is
melting all getting vaporized in the
air all the different Metals getting
vaporized in the air it's it's
crazy um I have information coming soon
okay and there's a question right there
from Cynthia why does God and His angels
allow this evil
here I have information about that very
thing that very question coming really
soon it's all part of the spiritual
information that my publisher will be
releasing and it hits that question
directly but get ready you might not
like the
answers you might think the answers are
great you might might not like them it's
intense stuff those kinds of questions
are never answered down here for a
reason I really believe that but Spirit
of compassion has answered them and have
answered has answered that
question and it is a brain Exploder it
is a mind
blower and I have written down all of s
so's information about that
question in a
book and we are trying to release it as
quick as
possible um my publisher is working
really hard so yeah and that answer to
that question you will know like I said
it's not going to be for faint
ears faint
eyes when you read answers to those
kinds of questions because that question
along with another hundred of really
unbelievable intense questions that
people have been trying to get answers
for for centuries are going to be
answered for the first
time
and that's the difference when you
actually hear a voice and can get the
information
um I think at this point here I think um
I've been promising to actually release
spiritual information from Spirit and
I'm uh going to pull through with that
promise so
but yeah it's going to be really intense
really intense okay
so you're ready cloudy says you're ready
all right you guys just wanted to show
you these things remember environmental
disaster air quality tools right
here once again so sorry for anybody
dealing with any kind of smoke or loss
of property loss of buildings loss of
houses and homes breaks my heart truly
if you're in the Los Angeles area
anywhere around there just know my heart
pours out to you check this out even if
you're not up against anything like that
okay and my heart pours out to anyone
who's been injured in any way I have had
a smoke inhalation problem years ago
so um I had some L damage Spirit of
compassion helped me heal and it was
lung damage because of breathing in
smoke from a fire and so my lungs were
damaged from that smoke from a fire and
so it took a year to recover such you
know serious extreme damage but because
of spirit of compassion I was able to do
so so I know what it's like
anyway good seeing you
guys prayers go out to anyone dealing
with anything including chronic illness
even if it's not related to any of this
you know my heart pours out to you you
know I'm proud of you for all you're
doing okay keep up the good work just
know that I
care know that Spirit of compassion
cares
greatly truly you
guys anyway lots of love