People are not being punished for the
crime of dumping these toxic chemicals
onto children, onto people. No one's
knocking on their door telling them to
stop because there is no door. There is
no door to knock on. There's no way to
find them. There is nobody to hold
accountable. One of the problems with
this is they're seen as a free radical.
And so it's really a matter of time
before one of these spaceships,
one of these alien crafts, one of these
extraterrestrials
says enough is enough and starts to
eradicate the chemtrail planes and
starts to eradicate the geoengineering
planes because aliens are using the same
airspace. They're flying through it and
they don't want to see that. There's
going to come a time where there's going
to be a rogue alien that's going to say,
"Time to put the foot down. Time to stop
whatever this is. This isn't helping
human beings down there. It's not
helping us as we're flying through it.
It's dangerous. It's traffic that's in
our way. An alien craft that's traveling
at an extremely high warp speed can
accidentally run into one of these
chemtrail planes. So, I wouldn't doubt
at all that some of these chemtrail
planes or a lot of them start either
disappearing or going down because of
extraterrestrials acting as vigilantes.
[Music]