people always ask me aw when are you
gonna do the alien podcast when are you
going to talk about aliens more and the
reason why I haven't is because
something happened to me years ago only
a small amount of people know my family
some friends that's about it I never
released it publicly what happened to me
I never talked about it out there in the
world I never wrote about it in the
books
but I am doing
the alien podcast I'm releasing it soon
and I'm gonna tell everybody the story
about what happened in my life
years ago
all I can say is
I hope you get a chance to listen to it
and
it gets me every time I even get kind of
choked up talking about it so anyway
it's not going to be a medical you know
illness chronic illness podcast episode
I'm not going to be talking about the
human body or anything like that just
alien stuff so check it out when you can