I'm sure you've heard about the
paranormal triangles, the Alaska
triangle and the Bermuda Triangle and
many more. Now, not all the triangles
that people are talking about out there
are legit. People are looking for
triangles. They're interested. They want
many triangles out there, and there are
many, but not every triangle people say
is a triangle is a mysterious paranormal
triangle. And one of the things is
paranormal triangles aren't just
triangle. They're circles. They've been
identified and estimated as
triangles. They've been noted as
triangles, documented as triangles, but
in reality, not all of them are
triangles. They're actually circles.
They're areas that are actually
circular. And in these paranormal
triangles, which are actually circular,
at least most of them are, there's a lot
of UFO sightings. There's a lot of
sightings of light beams, of light
circles, of crafts, of
spaceships, also
disappearances, missing ships, missing
planes over the last 100 years. So,
where do chemtrails and geoengineering
trails fall into this? Where do these
play a role?