okay
telegram
facebook youtube tick tock we're live
right now we're talking about
plant-based versus animal base and we're
gonna talk about the difference between
plant-based medical medium style
animal protein
medical medium style
because you could be on an animal
protein diet a clean one or you can be
on this animal protein diet or this keto
animal protein diet if you're like oh
i'm doing medical medium on the anal
protein i'm keeping it clean whatever
i'm keeping it nice and good and no
you could be plant-based or vegan
and be like well i went medical medium
i'm vegan now it's like
dude
you can go vegan out there in the vegan
world
and get sick
that's what you can do i've watched it
for years and years and years for
30 years out there because
it's not just medical medium is vegan
because vegans nutritional yeast vegans
all kinds of stuff vegan is soy sauce
with msg vegan is uh high fat vegan is
tons of nuts and seeds and nut butters
vegan is oils fried in pans vegan is
so it's like i went vegan a medical
medium that i went vegan it's like what
do you mean did you do are you medical
medium plant-based are you just
plant-based or vegan because you could
do that all wrong and not heal you know
i went i cleaned up i got rid of
processed foods and now i'm animal
protein keto animal protein you know
keeping it all good but i'm doing
medical medium sure but are you doing it
right are you doing it wrong
how are you doing it how are you doing
your animal protein are you still doing
eggs
because if you still got eggs in your
animal protein medical medium diet
then we're in trouble if you're still
doing cheese and dairy in your medical
medium animal protein diet then we're in
trouble
so
that's something to consider right there
that's something to understand so we're
talking about plant-based
versus animal base that's what we're
talking about there and you can do them
both wrong and not heal there's plenty
of sick vegan people out there plenty of
sick plant-based people out there plenty
in fact where do they go after they get
sick they run back to animal protein
they start out animal protein early in
their life they get sick then they go
vegan they get a little bit better they
find some vegan doctor they find some
vegan doctor online they're doing this
and then they get sick again
and now they're back on eggs and now
they're back on dairy products right you
guys have you seen that and then they're
back on eggs and dairy and everything
else right i just want to give everybody
before we go into the plant-based versus
animal base which is really an important
topic i can't wait to cover it
um this pretty much the last day for the
sale on the juicer just letting
everybody know i figured i'd do that
because
once the sale is over and then the dms
start coming through and then people are
commenting where do i get a juicer
what's the best juicer and i'm like oh
my god you're going to pay full price oh
my god you're going to pay full price
and which is fine because it's still
inexpensive compared to other juicers
but the point is is that why not save
it's 50 off so
why not um and i talked about why this
juice is so amazing it saves you so much
money that it pays for itself a couple
of months the juicer is already paid for
so it's like you didn't even buy it
basically i call this like a free juicer
in a way because it saves you so much
money when you're juicing and other
juicers don't that it actually pays for
itself in just a month or two it's the
mm 900 hds it's the last day of the sale
okay so megajuicers.com
you guys know i'm working with the mega
on this juicer because it is one one
badass juicer is so amazing
and uh it is my favorite and i'll talk
about that in a little bit of why it's
so incredible and why you save money and
why it matters so and you can use
anything in this machine but it's the
last day i think today's the last day of
the sale or tomorrow morning is the last
day all i know it's coming to the net
it's coming to an end so i'm just
letting everybody know but i've already
saved thousands in food food costs
because the juicer so it's technically
bought me like 20 30 juicers or whatever
it is yeah whatever it is i don't know
how it's so you know it's incredible so
back to plant-based versus animal-based
right
a really important topic hey i'm doing
vegan right now you know and and i'm
doing medical medium i went vegan it's
like
what vegan did you do
are you online mixing it up are you
mixing up with other vegan doctor stuff
are you mixing it up with other vegan
whatever because chances are you're in
trap land and you're stepping in
landmines and stepping in traps
everywhere
you got like i said the nutritional
yeast then you got the chocolate well i
can do vegan i'm still doing chocolate
let me do cacao in there okay blow out
your adrenals and when you get sick
later
that's why you went vegan to begin with
because you're sick you went sick when
you get sick later
you're not going to know that the cacao
powder has to go or you ain't going to
stand a chance the details matter
they so matter you guys this is so
important the details so matter in this
they really do so
hey you know vegan and and you know hey
i did medical medium i was vegan it
didn't work for me what did you do did
you do the customized protocols that you
can customize within the books did you
do that are you doing are you doing like
the nutritional yeast and the caffeine
and the apple cider vinegar hey i'm
doing i'm doing plant-based and i'm
doing medical medium but you're doing
apple cider vinegar you're not doing
medical medium you're not it's okay if
you want to dabble look
there are lots of people that dabble and
they dabble and with different things
and they're using medical medium stuff
they're juicing some celery juice or
their closet drinking celery juice or
whatever they're doing out there or
they're doing some other tools that they
learned from medical medium like zinc or
something else and they're doing things
and then they're dabbling though
and they're doing their apple cider
vinegar because they found out there's
some other vegan blah blah that when we
do apple cider vinegar this looks good
but when they get sick
they'll be back over to animal protein
like a run they'll run scared and
they'll be like i did the vegan thing i
tried medical medium they didn't try
medical medium they were doing somebody
else's vegan stuff and mixing everything
up this is so important is one of the
big mistakes i see constantly it's like
oh wait wait what do i do i go vegan
well first of all you can be animal
protein
and do medical medium
you can
be animal protein and do medical medium
you can be plant-based and vegan and do
medical medium
but are you doing it right
are you doing it in a way that you're
gonna heal
are you gonna do it so you can heal your
eczema don't you want your eczema gone
don't you want your psoriasis gone your
vitiligo gone your acne gone your
dermatitis gone your rosacea gone don't
you want your brain fog gone and your
anxiety and depression do you want your
trigeminal neuralgic on do you want your
hashimoto's gone do you want your
hyperthyroidism god do you want your ra
gone do you want your neurological lime
gone for good
like your neurological lyme gone
like for good
then we we just have to get it a little
bit right at least we've got to get it
right
so it's not just about hey i'm vegan and
i'm i'm doing anthony williams stuff no
are you sure because vegan isn't medical
medium and animal protein isn't medical
medium unless it's medical medium
where you're doing the plant-based
diet
but you're doing maybe the medical
medium mono cleanser doing the 3-6-9
right you're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse
moderation doesn't work
when you're really sick
moderation leads to desperation i told
you guys it leads to desperation the
moderation game takes you to a place
where you end up getting in trouble look
you don't have to be perfect i'm going
to tell you right now
this is important to know right you're
probably thinking well what now i got to
like i got to walk such a straight line
with my foods i got to walk such a
straight line with everything
if you're really chronically ill
the details matter and you do have to
walk that straight line
if you can't get there yet fine but just
know that
if you can't get there yet just know
that though
symptoms can be stubborn and if they're
stubborn with you
and your symptoms are really hanging in
there then we got to walk the straight
line we have to get there
we do
if you want to dabble fine but just know
that's what you're doing and that's okay
i got a friend it's like look i'm
dabbling in your stuff and then when i
get sick i dabble in your stuff again i
do more stuff of your stuff and then
when i'm sicker i do more stuff until
i'm better and then i go back and forth
i'm like why do you do that why don't
you just get better completely put it
behind you know what to do and like well
i'll do it i'll do it it's here's what
it is it's okay if you want to dab well
it's okay
but just know
that's what you're doing you haven't
gone them all the way
you're eating eggs once a month you're
having a little butter here in your
coffee you're having a little butter
here in your food you're having some
gluten
you're having some dairy products right
you guys you're having some cheese
you're eating vegan cheese which is god
awful for the body you're eating vegan
cheese and
and you're eating corn right you're
eating corn
but just know
sure
that's okay
but because addictions are tough like
i'm not shaming anybody i'm not saying
i'm not saying
my way or the highway i'm not
i want you here and i want you learning
i want you juicing celery juice i want
you to have a medical device like this
some day in your life okay and i want
you to be able to juice that celery
juice it's if you're dabbling you're
dabbling
but but i also want you to know that you
can get better
if you know the way
you can get better you guys on tick tock
you can get better
you guys on facebook you guys on youtube
you can get better you guys in telegram
you can get better you can and if you're
not there yet because you can't let go
of the chocolate you can't let go of the
caffeine in the can't let go of the
green tea and the coffee and you can't
let go of the energy drinks
and you can't let go of the apple cider
vinegar and the nutritional yeast and
the eggs and the dairy products and the
gluten in the corn if you can't let go
of
the pork or whatever it is that you're
doing the bacon
i get it
but if you're really sick or you're
struggling we can go all the way when
you're ready
they get us by death by a thousand cuts
just so you guys know a little bit here
and a little bit there and a little bit
here a little apple cider vinegar job
you know
a little bit of msg in the natural
flavors oh
fragrances we're breathing in all the
time because we think it's okay for
small another knife
caffeine in different ways chocolate
stabbed again
fats oh stabbed again
right too many fats the traps are there
the death by a thousand cuts is there
and over time
if we're sick
it gets us and it gets us next thing you
know we got cataracts
cataracts
degenerative eye problems and cataracts
and stuff like that next you know people
got that kind of stuff
next thing you know they got like
retinas detaching
next thing you know they got all kinds
of eye diseases next thing you know they
got severe blurry vision right next
thing you know they got brain fog and
eye floaters and pain in their neck and
pain in their head and
ringing in the ears and vertigo and
dizziness and they got all the vertigo
and dizziness
right
check out the apple cider vinegar
podcast at medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast and check out the coffee
matcha tea chocolate episode at medical
mean podcast apple podcast when you get
a chance death by a thousand cuts is a
real thing
so hey look i'm doing vegan i'm i'm
vegan
i don't need to do medical medium isn't
he just a vegan guy or something and i'm
i got this other vegan situation going
over here and then when you're sick
you'll be scobbling down those eggs
you'll be running
for those eggs you know why vegans don't
rip down eggs first of all they don't
know what they do
unless they know mm info they don't know
that eggs feed all the viruses inside
your body to keep you sick eggs feed all
the bacteria and fungus and yeast and
mold that's inside your body and keeps
you sick so eggs feed
all the stuff inside of us
that keeps us sick
right
and i talked about that over and over
again you guys know i talked about the
books and stuff like that but what
happens with vegans and the plant-based
people they get sick because they're
cranking the high fats they're drowning
their gallbladders and liver out they're
killing their pancreases with the fats
they're told to eat too much fat right
and then they're doing that and then
they're doing the poisons like the msg
and the apple cider vinegar and
everything and they're burning
themselves out
and then their pathogens crank up
and when their pathogens crank up
they're sick as a vegan
and now they're proving the animal
protein world right that veganism is
you know the animal protein
tagline it's like yeah vegans what what
a you know all the vegans are sick all
the plant-based people are sick
meanwhile
all the animal protein people are sick
two
all of them the keto people they get
sick sure if you've never been sick
before and you're some guy that had a
little bit of weight on you and you go
into the gym for the first time in your
life and you're 35 years old and you
start eating keto
you're yeah you're gonna start looking a
little better and feel a little better
because it's it's definitely better than
what you were doing but if you get a
real problem that keto diet will kill
you
you can do animal protein but if you do
it right and you do a medical medium
style you can stand a chance
plant same thing with the plant-based
stuff right
same thing with the plant-based stuff
you can do the plant-based stuff totally
wrong
totally wrong
and get yourself sick
and then you're sucking down those eggs
know why plant-based people don't rip
apart eggs because man they love their
eggs they went plant-based and it's the
one place they feel like if they just
get convinced that
eggs are still really good for them
they'll eat them again right and if they
get sick man they're gonna be back
they're gonna be back on their eggs if
they get sick thumbs up if you like this
video
thumbs up if you hate this video
double thumbs up if you hate me
because a lot of people do
i have not made a lot of friends the
apple cider vinegar people hate me the
alkaline ionizer poisonous water people
hate me and scam people hate me
[Applause]
[Music]
kombucha tea people hate me because
guess what there's caffeine and kombucha
tea plus it turns your blood into acid
i haven't made a lot of friends there
i've made other friends though in my
life right some of the most powerful
people in the world
[Music]
right
people have been helping
helping their families for the last 35
years
people that have flown their private
jets around the world looking for
somebody to help them and they found it
found me at my office i've made some
really powerful amazing friends in the
world and i've made other friends in the
world too they're a beautiful spiritual
wonderful people and just incredible
souls
but i certainly haven't made a lot of
friends in alternative medicine industry
i can tell you that right now
because everywhere i turn someone's
trying to screw somebody over and i i
talk about it and then all of a sudden
i'm now the enemy
ionizer water machine people screwing
everybody over with their scam uh water
machines poisonous water i swear i swear
to god i swear to god that stuff is so
bad for you right
i mean that
same thing you know what the apple cider
vinegar stuff great way to burn out your
stomach lands destroy your digestive
tract and dissolve your teeth
but the apple cider vinegar world's got
a billion dollars investing in it so
yeah i become the enemy caffeine
industry the same thing
but you know what
we're going to talk about the
plant-based versus animal-based protein
fat
talk whatever we're going to cover that
a little bit just want to give you a run
down the sales ending on the juicer just
give you that run down you guys this is
the mm-900 hds
mm-900 hds
what you won't find with this juicer
is the metal gears
scratching against each other please
know that
okay there's people out there that say
oh i got a cold pressed juicer and the
metal gears are are grinding against
each other you don't know it but the
masticating gears are grinding against
each other metal particles are in
everybody's juice
another thing you won't find with this
is
[Music]
[Applause]
another thing and metal is not easy to
get out of your body that metal is not
easy it's not like that's easy to get
out sits inside of you when you're
getting all those metal parts in your
juicers
the other thing is how come that's not
wet and sloppy how come that's dry
how come
look at that
nice and dry that's because you're
saving money saving money
save another 20 this week
save another 30 this week right there
less celery
incredible you can't get that with other
juicers it's not going to happen
it's the only juicer the mmm 900 hds is
the megajuicers.com
just letting you guys know the sales
ending it's 50 off you get the celery
juice book right now too you want it
so
[Applause]
this is a herbal extraction just know
that i've told you guys that before
have you had your celery juice today i
want to know if anybody's had their
celery juice today
at all have you
just curious
you guys had your celery juice yet today
machine is low noise very quiet you
don't wake up the family easy to clean
it's just ridiculously awesome man it's
ridiculously awesome
i'm letting everybody know about this
juicer when it's on sale because i feel
bad when
everybody's asking me what do i do what
do i do
[Music]
people complain about celery costing
money while this saves you the money and
pays for itself so this juicer pays for
itself
that's what's incredible it pays for
itself so it'll it'll be paid for
shortly after you buy it it'll be paid
for how incredible is that
how incredible is that 64 ounces celery
juice today
katie whoa
nice well you're doing it oh my god
you're not messing around you are not
messing around amazing
incredible
that's incredible
so
i'm so glad you guys are doing your
celery juice you did it you just had it
jen jen coffin you just had it anna yes
you did
junior
everybody having it on tick tock amazing
[Music]
amazing
so
somebody asked on tick tock where can i
buy it at megajuicers.com
it's the mm-900 hds
that's you know there's others there's
other juicers there but it's not going
to do this
so i'm letting you know so if you get
the wrong juicer so make sure you ask
other people too that know about the
mm-900 hds
that's the dry pulp right there it's
just in my fingers
okay that's dry
i'm just showing you the bottom of the
container on tik-tok you see this you
guys on telegram you see this
this is not a camera trick
that's dry
can you believe that
i mean i'm serious
it blows my mind every time
that's dry pulp
everything's squeezed out of it that's a
dry pulp container
what i mean when i look at it i'm like
this is like for real
like in fact it's so dry it's so dry
it's actually like
it's kind of like freaking me out a
little bit because it doesn't make any
sense but it does make sense it's
designed to squeeze basically every last
drop out of your celery and then you
save because you now you can buy you
know you buy less celery and then that's
20 you just saved and then it adds up
and then the juicers paid for and then
boom like how insane is that it's just
crazy this is
crazy
karen says can the celery juice be
frozen if not how many days can you
store it in the fridge look
24 hours in the fridge is not the end of
the world
sometimes i've gone gone as far as 48
hours and then consumed it okay so if
you had to do 48 hours in the fridge and
consuming it's still better than
anything else you can get out there
okay
if you have to freeze it because you
need it a week later or something like
that freeze it
don't add any water to it don't add any
any ice to it don't add any lemon to it
don't add anything to it you guys so
important
so important but did you see that i'm
still actually like
it's so dry it's coming out like dust
and the bottom's dry it's just
the amount you save is ridiculous and
it's incredible
and that's that's what's amazing right
there on its own
i love it
it's it's it's it's my favorite you know
it's so incredible another thing too to
know that you want to strain it so i'm
showing everybody right now that you
want to strain your celery juice so keep
in mind that you always want to strain
it this is an herbal extraction like tea
okay when you have herbal tea you're
extracting herbal medicine from that tea
so if you have your chamomile tea just
say
or your peppermint tea or if you're
having your licorice tea chamomile tea
whatever tea you're having right and
because a lot of people drink chamomile
tea that's why i'm using that one and
you
do your tea bag your chamomile tea bag
in there you don't cut open the tea bag
and get all those you get those gritty
pieces of
fiber because the it was extracted you
did the hot water extraction in your
herbal tea you see
so
that's the same thing this is not a
vegetable
so important for you guys to know that
this is not a vegetable it's not a
veggie it's not
and when you hear a dietitian out there
or hear you if you hear even a
plant-based so-called expert or a vegan
expert call it a vegetable it's like
whoa
whoa you just don't know you just don't
know when you hear that
it's like they don't get it
that's an herbal extraction this is
herbal medicine it's partly why it heals
people to the degree it does it's really
so healing right
so
why is celery juice healing us why is it
healing millions of people around the
world
why is it doing that dr fine good to see
you incredible
do you eat the shells of the nuts
that's really funny if you're sensitive
because you got a lot of pathogens and
you don't know it like you got the h
pylori in your gut and you got the e
coli and the c diff and you got the
streptococcus and you don't know this
but you're filled with yeast mold
unproductive fungus and pathogens and
everything inside your body and your
liver inside your intestinal tract and
you do celery juice
you might be a little sensitive so you
start with a smaller amount when you
first start you don't have to throw out
16 to 32 ounces you can start with four
ounces and build yourself up start with
eight ounces right maybe you can go into
it right away at 16 ounces
and you can do that
celery juice is a complete electrolyte
that's why it holds power you guys so
let's cover that for a second this is
important right
this is really important
your brain
needs electrolytes
critical
trace mineral salts and electrolytes but
it doesn't need salt
like salt you're throwing on like sea
salt on your food or rock salt or
it doesn't need some that kind of salt
it needs
trace minerals
that are attached to the sodium in
celery it's an entirely different salt
it's not the same
it's not the same as sea salt or the
same as as like a rock salt or anything
okay this is packed with trace minerals
sodium cluster salt so that's basically
you've got a little solar system with
trace minerals around it
inside of here
and it goes to the brain and it
recharges your neurotransmitters
and your neurons your neurotransmitters
and neurons is really important to know
it's a complete electrolyte so let's
cover that for a second every time you
eat check this out
if you guys got a second
i know you're busy
if you eat something
you're trying to collect an electrolyte
from it parts of electrolytes so when
you have a banana or you have a nut or
you have avocado or you have a little
piece of chicken whatever you eat
what you're doing is you're trying to
collect electrolytes from everything
you're eating did you guys know that
you're trying to collect electrolytes
from everything you're eating
but guess what dr sherry green good to
see you they're not complete
electrolytes
it's not complete you're trying to
piecemeal your electrolytes with
everything you're eating so when you
have your salad you're trying to piece
together electrolytes when you have your
animal protein you're trying to piece
together some if you're plant-based and
you're having your nut butter as an
avocado you're trying to piece together
electrolytes
but guess what
why is celery juice reversing disease
healing people changing their lives
turning their lives around like no
tomorrow
one of the reasons is it's a complete
electrolyte there's nothing else on the
planet that's a complete electrolyte
news flash
there's nothing else on the planet
that's a complete
electrolyte
and that's what's incredible about that
it's just one big huge reason
all right
if you guys just got on i was telling
everybody that's 50 off it's like the
sales ending it's ending soon i just i
just blew my mind again by talking about
the pulp and how dry the container is
right
celery juice kills pathogens viruses and
bacteria
all the bad stuff inside of us it starts
to kill it so as you drink your celery
juice
it's starting to kill
those bugs inside of us so everybody's
running around you've got hashimoto's
well guess what you've got epsine bar in
your thyroid you got eczema psoriasis
you got epsin bar in your liver okay you
got acne you got streptococcus in your
lymphatic system and your liver and
other places see that's how it works
so these little bugs are why everybody's
sick you've got neurological lime you've
got both strep and you've got lots of
bugs like shingles
epstein-barr
you get fever blisters any of you guys
could ever get a fever blister simplex
one
that simplex not friendly likes to hide
all in the nerves the trigeminal nerves
loves to hide in there
loves to hide in the brain stem
sometimes and then it creates all these
migraines in people creates all these
other things trigeminal neuralgia you're
hurting here well guess what celery
juice
kills off
that simplex which is your trigeminal
neuralgia think about that how
incredible is that you guys
it's one of the medical medium tools but
it's a great start
and it's a great finish
that's incredible talk a little bit
about the uh plant-based
animal protein thing
okay
so the animal protein people are
infamous for ripping apart plant-based
diet people
back in the older day you guys it was so
rough every time spirit of compassion
wanted to get somebody on the plant base
right the proper plant-based foods so
they can heal
they'd be up against the whole thing of
like angry family members angry doctors
saying you're starving yourself eating
fruits and herbs and wild foods and
vegetables and leafy greens and it was
never easy for the plant-based you know
someone going plant-based right now it's
more accepted the whole bit but still
the animal protein movement still says
some of the same talking points
you're eating rabbit food you're
starving your children
you're hurting your children by not
giving them enough protein you're
protein deficient yourself like they say
all kinds of terrible talking points
right and then the plant-based vegan
people you know attack the protein
people and the animal protein people and
say you're killing animals
you're heartless you're cruel
right and so they're two diet belief
systems
medical medium information this is so
important details matter
okay is about why you're sick it's not
about picking a side of a diet belief
system
if you pick a side of a diet belief
you just
screwed a whole bunch of people
where they won't heal
doctors do it all the time
you screw over a whole bunch of people
and they don't heal if you pick a diet
belief system
practitioners and nutritionists
totally do it all the time
once you pick one side
you're not you're gonna not get a lot of
people better
that's how it works if you go one side
it's not good now you can be on one side
you can be plant-based and you stay
plant-based you can be animal protein
stay animal protein if you want
i always tell plant-based people stay
plant-based if you're plant-based you
better believe it stay plant-based
learn how to do it right so you don't
get in trouble and if you're animal
protein stay animal protein but learn
how to do it right so you did get in
trouble mm info was never on one side of
the aisle or another
and that's why so many people got their
lives back because they brought in
medical medium tools while they were
animal protein they were doing it right
while they were plant-based and doing it
right and they brought in the medical
medium tools
you guys hear that on tick-tock telegram
it's the only healing community
that doesn't pick sides we got animal
protein people here and we got plant
people here
that's right and always did
the other communities
it's like political or something it's
either your plant-based
or it's the animal protein community the
keto community animal keto and then the
plant-based keto
right just just plant-based diet eating
tons of fats
people just do it no matter what you
don't have to name keto or not
they're just doing it
and on that note of keto anyway on a
separate note if you guys want a detail
that matters no one's keto
because
the minute they went off the carnival
keto was just the carnivore diet back
years ago decades ago
because the only way to go into ketosis
is just be on meat only
no one's on meat only unless they do the
carnivore diet the carnivore diet should
get a new name it should be called the
keto diet unless the carnivore diet
throws in sugar which they did now and
they've thrown in honey so they're not
keto either
they used to be keto but nobody's keto
it's another way you know something's
wrong with the system when they can't
even get their facts right
so when you're doing keto you're totally
like screwed over in the whole of the
whole thing and i'll say it i say that a
lot because when you're duped and
tricked
and the walls pulled over your eyes
right
and you've been bamboozled
that's what it is
and basically been through though dupe
shrimp bamboozle
all of that will pull over your eyes
that's what that is
so here you are thinking you're keto but
you're not you can't go into ketosis
because avocado has sugar in it
avocado was never in the keto diet the
keto diet killed people because there
was no sugar in it
the keto diet killed people back in the
day did you guys know that
they died when they
actually only did it they did it like
where it's ketosis where you only do
little pieces of meat all day
six months eight months later a year
later they would go into some kind of
kidney failure
and die
but see keto diet lets in berries now
when they lay in avocados there's sugar
in those so you can't go into ketosis
get it right people not you guys the
keto people the so-called experts nuts
have sugar in them that's why they're
sweet so many nuts are sweet
cheese has sugar in it so what they did
was they let cheese and nuts and avocado
and green juices that have sugar in them
they're letting all these sugar
like avenues in
all these foods that have sugar in them
so it's not keto
like how can you plan on healing
when they don't even have it right know
what they're even talking about now
you're somebody who might be like well i
got better on keto okay fine but when
you get real sick
you'll see where up you've got duped
that's how it's done out there
and you can dabble in medical medium
totally cool i want you to do that if
you want to do that i want you to know
you can go in and out of mm but call it
like it is
i'm dabbling in mm
i'm plant-based but i'm not medical
medium plant-based i'm animal protein
but i'm not medical medium animal
protein i'm dabbling you know call it
like it is it's okay it's all right
don't say i did medical medium for three
years but you didn't because you did all
this acv and all this kombucha tea and
all this nutritional yeast and all this
vegan cheese and all this corn
and then just and all this caffeine and
all this chocolate and then you said
you've been doing medical medium for
three years and then you write a post
saying i did medical medium for three
years and i'm still not better
and
all that does is hurt people
me i'll be fine
but guess what somebody on mattress
island
just got tricked
because that person wasn't doing mm but
the person on mattress island that came
across medical medium that needs a way
out because she's been on with mattress
island suffering she's 24 years old or
28 years old and
can't get a start in her life or his
life and they're on mattress island or
on couch island and they read somewhere
someone said i did medical medium for
three years and i didn't get better yeah
i'd love to be a fly on the wall
and that's the whole thing
it's important to know love to be a fly
on the wall
using celery juice is one of medical
medium tools
it's one of them and it's an incredible
place to start it's one powerful tool
and if you're dabbling it's fine if you
just do celery juice i said this for
years
if you can just do celery juice
that
that would be great
if you can just do the heavy metal detox
smoothie that would be great if you
could just get rid of the gluten
and the dairy that would be great if you
can get rid of the eggs that would be
great just if it's one step at a time
i'm there with you guys on that i am
but keep it straight when someone's
talking about medical medium
like yeah i dabbled
i dabbled maybe i could have done a
little bit more maybe i didn't read his
books thoroughly you know i get it his
books are medical textbooks
it's a legendary book at this point now
millions of copies have been around the
world because people healed there's no
marketing
campaign for it there's no marketing
companies i don't have a publicist
okay
i don't have like
all that i don't have an agent i don't
do that kind of stuff i believe in just
organic
people healing and telling another
person that's what i believe in
and it's
the best-selling book in the world
basically in health
and that's what's incredible and it's
because people are getting their lives
back read the book when you get a chance
the torah says what if what if all we
can get is conventional celery
non-organic then get it get conventional
celery get it
that's not a bad thing get it wash it
and wash out the stalks okay
take your fingers and get that water
going put a little tiny bit of natural
dish soap and soap up the water soap up
the bowl i would get my bowl out right
now and show you but my balls filled
with all kinds of stuff you guys i was
making a whole bunch of stuff earlier
but
just and then clean clean
out this with your fingers and get it
good yeah there's going to be residue
but guess what meaning inside the cellar
but guess what there's pesticide residue
in every single conventional
produce and here's the funny thing
there's there's
there's conventional
pesticide
residue in every single organic
fruit and vegetable
because all the organic fields were once
conventional
and then seven years past five years
passed they started the farm they got
the okay to be organic
and the earth is loaded with pesticides
it's okay
because the celery juice outweighs that
the celery juice will drive out and
neutralize more pesticide out of your
body and pull it out of your body even
when it's conventional celery juice
don't do hpp high pressure
pasteurization i'm going to give you a
really powerful tip right here do not
buy
celery juice in the bottle at the
grocery store health food store
that says it's fresh and raw but it
wasn't freshly made
it's got a date on it that lasts for
quite a while because it's hpp
total
high pressure pasteurization destroys
the celery juice
so you're just getting ripped off
i want mentioned earlier don't add
anything to your celery juice no ice no
lemon no water no no anything else drink
it straight
drink it straight
you know many people i've seen on vegan
diets have come to me for help even like
you know
high profile people celebrities whatever
throughout the years
they're like they heard about vegans so
hey let me go do vegan
and they're still sick with something
and then i said well what about celery
juice oh no i haven't heard of that okay
let's get you on celery juice 32 ounces
every single morning and it was like
miracles happening
miracles happening even with bad vegan
and bad plant-based diets i say bad
because they're riddled in high fat
apple cider vinegar vinegars in general
they're soy cheese vegan cheeses canola
oil
corn vegan restaurant crap all of it you
guys vegan cookies everything i get it
i know everybody wants to have a field
day they want to have fun all of that
stuff
they do
but
the vegan diet the plant-based diet
doesn't mean we're doing it right and
we're gonna get better or we're not
gonna get sick it doesn't mean that
and the animal protein diet is the same
way
same way
okay we're up against so many problems
with their health more than ever before
in our history
mosquito sprays being dumped on us right
now
definitely everywhere just planes at
night dump it all night every everywhere
that's what happens they don't even
forewarn people they don't tell anybody
and
chemtrails coming out of the sky right
toxic heavy metal exposure all the time
right old pharmaceuticals and our system
all this stuff we're up against so much
and
so much stress too when you add it all
up we need some serious fighting tools
and i i'm not kidding about the medical
device thing where i don't want to be in
the hospital
in a hospital bed you know nurse
nurse
and
i'm thirsty can you bring me a cup dixie
cup of water
out of the sink
basically because in the hospital that's
what you get
i just i like these medical devices
right here
i can't contain myself right i have to
fool around once in a while
death by a thousand years
death by a thousand cuts is a real deal
health of fliz
right silly ashley kevin good to see you
it's
truly
real
about what we're up against right so we
get hit on all sides
everywhere so what are we doing about it
what are we doing are you doing your
lemon water right
16 32 ounces of lemon water first thing
in the morning
boom are you knocking down the celery
juice 16 to 32 ounces celery juice
right after that 15 to 30 minutes later
are you guys doing that
whoa
are you doing maybe
maybe after that nice big salad some
leafy greens some spinach some cilantro
throw a whole bunch of bananas in there
if you want some papaya on top of a nice
salad later on have some steamed
potatoes
man you can go real far
i'm not saying we can't have any avocado
and i'm not saying we can't have any
nut butters or something like that i
can't not saying we can't have any olive
oil that's not it
but we literally
fat ourselves to death as a vegan a
plant-based person or an animal protein
person
we just we we tank the fat the vegan
cheeses the soy products all fat the nut
butters the nuts we take it we take it
we take it and we're eating it all two
minutes too much avocado i'm gonna make
a guacamole though i am gonna do that
just not today but i'm gonna i think
next time i come back or something i'll
make my
famous personal guacamole that i like
i've had you know for years and years
and years if i've ever do some guacamole
right and listen it depends on and i'll
show you guys how to make it depends on
where somebody's health is at
somebody be like oh he's anti-healthy
fat he doesn't know anything there's so
many experts out there that know that
that's good for you that's not what i
said
i said that if you're sick and you're
chronically ill and you can't move the
needle we got to pull the fats out
someday even it's a little bit at a time
let's get them out
depends on where somebody's health is
someone can have pathogens that can have
two three different kinds of
epstein-barr cytomegal cytomegalovirus
hpv
they could have that they can have a
whole bunch of things going on in their
system
and
pathogens toxins metals everybody has a
different brew
right and fats are in every food every
single food has a trace of fat in it a
lemon does
every single trace of food has a trace
talk about overt fats radical fats
anyway if you're plant-based or animal
protein
keep in your keep keep in the back your
mind
are you doing it
in a way
that's gonna secure
that you can get better you're doing in
a way that you
can avoid getting sick or sicker are you
doing your animal protein diet or your
plant-based diet in a way
that's right for your body
are you doing
it in a way
that can reverse your condition and get
you to a place of healing and move the
needle and move you forward you guys i
just want to let you know
last day or it's tomorrow morning i
don't know what it is but it's coming to
the end on the sale this is the mm-900
hds i showed you guys if you just got on
here it's ridiculous
ridiculous
dry container that's not a magic trick
it's dry
that's the pull
that means you're saving money and it
adds up and the juicer pays for itself
within literally a little time because
if you need half the celery or
you know a lot less celery
and
more anything you juice whoa are you
saving money it adds up juicer pays for
itself and then you got more money for
food especially with food costs going up
it's incredible are you guys i'm heading
off to ig i'm going to turn telegram
back on i'm going to turn tick tock back
on you guys
i'm heading back to ig
tick tock telegram
let's hope we're not censored
i love you guys i'll see you soon about
like 10 minutes give me 10 minutes
awesome