Angels demons and spiritual tools it's
going to be mind-blowing when people
actually hear the information from above
Spirit of compassion answered a lot of
questions about afterlife after death
it's a big deal Angels Fallen Angels
something called Falling Angels that's a
big deal all on its own the information
about the soul even some stuff about
ghosts how does that even work but
really just powerful information it's an
incredible audio book original audio
that's being released it's going to be
out March 18th I hope people get a
chance to actually hear it it's a big
deal tremendous amounts of
information about angels and demons but
you got to be ready for it you got to be
ready for it because the information is
mindblowing Awakening it answers a lot
of questions all around that people have
like what is a demon what is an angel is
an Angel Real so many people don't even
believe in angels so many people don't
believe in so many different things but
that's the project and it's a spiritual
one but you got to be ready for it the
information is a lot to take in a lot to
digest and it comes from above basically
what I did was I just I asked a lot of
questions and a lot of questions and the
information came through and just like
you know medical medium fashion it's a
lot of information and doesn't just make
sense it is unbelievable B