foreign
Grill yeah big day today
exactly yeah we got we got a bunch of
customers in here right now
[Music]
yep yep yep I got you I got you I'm
getting telepathic messages from grogu
right here a famous customer yep whoa ow
ow ow
bro come on ow
oh when Grover wants uh his wild
blueberry juice he sends a telepathic
message
to my psychic mind and he hurts my brain
really bad until I give him what he
wants yes
how okay okay it's coming right up
oh man it's coming right up can you hold
it in here do would you like it right
here for now okay okay that's fine
yep a grocery's friend ow again roku's
friend is giving me telepathic
yep telepathic message is saying grogu's
friend wants while blueberry juice now
okay oh okay good good good good okay
all set yeah okay anyway ew's Bar and
Grill how can I help you onion rings
what else
french fries what else buffalo chicken
wings well the baby chicks aren't here
so we can give you actually real buffalo
chicken wings yep okay all right we
gotta go we're very busy here
you guys this is the medical medium wild
blueberry challenge day two very special
moment actually I'm very excited about
this so if you haven't heard the wild
blueberry juice is on sale 10 right now
which is incredible the wild blueberry
juice it's a wild food we're going to
talk about the spiritual powers and the
antioxidants of the wild blueberry
spiritual powers and the antioxidants of
the wild blueberry which is really
incredible so that's a big moment
because we're going to be covering a lot
of details and information you don't
want to miss that because it's really
cool you won't hear that information
anywhere else may as well hang out with
us while we're doing this so I'm really
excited we're making the warm wild
blueberry Bowl hence
you see the pot on a burner hence you
see Wild Boomers in front of me you see
a blender all kinds of other stuff we're
also going to make the wild blueberry
latte as well so you're making the wild
blueberry latte I got some wild
blueberry juice in me right now and I'm
pumped up it seems to give me energy and
I want to ask you guys if you can post
your experiences from the wild
blueberries you know so many of you guys
have been doing the wild blueberries all
of these years you've been doing the
wild blueberry juice in the last year or
so whatever you've been doing this how
has the wild blueberry juice helped you
guys I know a lot of people people I
know that say it helps them with their
focus it helps them with all kinds of
stuff with their migraines it's helps
them with all kinds of different things
that's what I've heard other people say
I got doctor friends that swear by the
wild blueberries and the wild blueberry
juice how has it helped you in your life
juice and the wild blueberries whether
it was the hmds or whatever so I can
post anything you guys are saying cool
experience is that actually help other
people find their way too to that
information so I'm excited tag got
medical medium hashtag medical meeting
with your experiences that would be
amazing
and you guys were here making the warm
while blueberry bowl and we're making
the wild blueberry latte and I think I
am going to start in a second too in a
little bit as well because we got some
cool stuff to make
at AWS Bar and Grill we are
always aiming to please and I am at your
service if you guys just got on here
this is day two of the medical meanwhile
blueberry challenge which I'm actually
really excited about and we're talking
about the spiritual powers of the wild
blueberry and we're talking about the
also the antioxidants too and I need a
shot myself but you know what I am going
to have a glass of wine is what I'm
going to have because I like
I like
a nice glass of wine right here
fantastic
a glass of wine
if you guys are alcoholics out there
okay if many of you guys are
maybe past your past life alcoholics
maybe you're like our old-time
alcoholics or whatever you are if you
were an alcoholic you might want to have
the wild blueberry juice in a wine glass
to kind of like help and soothe you
that's what I tell a friend who's like
an alcoholic and I said you should go
get off the wine
get off the wine don't be a wino get off
the wine and make sure you get the wild
blueberry juice in your wine glass
now I never drink I was never interested
at all in it plus I had SOC in my ear
telling me not to drink and not to try
it when I was younger so I adhered by
soc's information
and words and so what I do is I put this
in here instead so that's what I like
very very good
so anyway you guys
here we are
okay let's get going let's figure this
out
I'm gonna have a glass of wine did you
guys have your shots yet or what
hmm
very good
it's a dry wine yes indeed
this glass of wine is 92 000 an ounce
yes it's from a thousand years ago
you know people are spending like that
kind of money for wine that's 2 000
years old they find some old wine
somewhere and they're like it's been
just sitting down in the ground
somewhere
and it's like a bunch of a bunch of
people come out of the woodwork that
have millions and billions of dollars
and they're like buying a bottle of it
for you know for literally a million
dollars a bottle five million dollars a
bottle or something it's like dude it's
just grapes fermented
yeah okay so let's talk about what we're
doing today we're talking about the
spiritual power of the wild Bluebird we
talked about the antioxidants too which
is also something that's really exciting
to me and
um you know the thing is is that this is
a food we are so blessed and lucky to
have here on Earth
like this is a resource
that we are blessed like we should be so
grateful to have this resource in our
hands right now okay I talked about
yesterday how wild blueberries the
species isn't just one think about that
right now if you look at a wild
Blueberry Field it's not one plant
species like others out there in the
world it's not one plant species and I'm
saying that over and over again because
this is huge
there are multiple plant species in that
field of wild blueberries but they all
kind of look the same right you just see
a sea of wild blueberries and of course
the berries are a little bit off in
different sizes and everything in the
field but either way
there are different species in that
field this is their survival method
it's a part of how they have survived
for thousands and thousands of years
which is incredible now here's another
thing too now this is part of like the
spiritual power that the wild blueberry
holds because you can't kill it now you
can kill every tree on the planet
and if you do
they won't come back
because you need a seed you need right
you need an acorn you have to reseed
those trees
a tree will not grow when it's been cut
and burned down
it can't come back an oak tree won't
come back a maple tree will not come
back
it has to be the seed to start another
maple tree a seed to start another oak
tree right and that's how it works
but you can burn the wild blueberry down
to the ground and it rises out of the
ashes
Like a Phoenix
it has spiritual Powers it can survive
the unsurvivable
that's the kind of food I want in my
body that's the kind of food people who
have been through hell and back need
inside their body
that's the kind of food people who have
been through chronic illness they've
been through sickness they've been
through strife and struggles they've
been through suffering they've been
through hardships and losses they've
been through mental abuse they've been
through mental you know power Downs what
that means is just being beaten down
mentally and everything else they've
been through hell and back
and the wild blueberry is for the people
who have been down there before right in
that place where you're on your hands
and knees you're praying to God you lost
a lot you struggled you're even if it's
something that's mild to somebody else
but it's really serious to you where
someone gets serious and whatever
because everybody has a different
challenge
and a different problem
and a different struggle and they're all
important
there's no you know like saying well
that's not important that is or that's
they're all important so whatever
anybody's ever been through
it's important to note the wild
blueberries for them if you're having
trouble on Instagram or Facebook go to
medicalmedium.com we are live right now
on medicalmedium.com so if you have any
trouble on there
because I'm seeing you know a whole
bunch of kind of glitches and everything
right now so if you guys are having
trouble go to medicalmedium.com
hopefully if you guys hear me and you go
there
so the wild blueberry is a spiritual
plant all on its own
that's plant medicine right there
it's not toxicity plant medicine where
you think you're doing plant medicine
and it's altering your mind in a toxic
way damaging nerve cells damaging
neurons you know like ayahuasca that's
not plant medicine that's just a toxic
plant right
that's just a toxic
substance right now I'm not I hope I
didn't get anybody upset I'm just trying
to show you the differences right here
okay same thing with plants that have
caffeine in them right
caffeine is toxic to the brain and I
talked about that many times over the
years and talk about that in the brain
saver book so we're going to be reading
on the brain saver books if you guys
have the brain saver books
check it out
I got a micro dosing chapter in here so
if you're somebody that's into that kind
of stuff read the chapter you'll be mind
blown
so I can tell you
anyway the brain saver books amazon.com
us 40 off
26.29 dollars
I just want to let everybody know that
these are incredible Bibles right here
with a tremendous amount of information
there's 12 books in these two books 12
books including 100 recipes and
everything else a recipe book everything
else too so
there's different plants out there for
instance like caffeinated plants
right caffeine is damaging to the
adrenals
so that's not plant medicine that's
plant toxicity
because it could damage the adrenals
people don't realize that
so when people do caffeine whether it's
green tea whether it's matcha tea
whether it's cacao whatever it is
whether it's coffee that's damaging
their adrenals
right so I mean if you're into that just
don't get mad at me don't shoot the
messenger I'm just telling you what
damages and destroys your adrenal glands
right
so what happens is that there's plant
medicine that doesn't damage your
adrenals or your neurons or your brain
it's a spiritual based plant medicine
that does the opposite it's critical for
Focus concentration it's critical to get
the anthocyanins to the brain it's
critical for your spiritual growth so
there's plant medicine
that rises above
anything like toxicity out there
toxicity plant fake plant medicine
so there's plant medicine that super
seeds
other plants out there for us and our
brain and our health
so that's where the wild blueberry
comes in that's how incredible if you
guys want to know if you just came on
here 10 off you guys know I work with
Wyman's I told you guys
fully endorse them because I don't want
this to go away I want to give as much
support I want to tell as many people as
possible I want people to order this
someday so they can get it into their
body and have that inside of them and I
want Wyman's to keep on making this kind
of resource it's unbelievable they take
the berries out of the field they press
them it goes into the bottle and I want
to talk about stick around because I'm
going to talk about organic versus wild
food because people are confused and be
like oh it's not organic but what they
don't understand
and this is important to know
when you have or I'm a pro-organic food
but I'm also aware that organic crops
are sprayed three times a week with
pollinator killers
organic food crops are sprayed three
times a week
with pollinator Killers nicotine
so don't give me that Holier you're
holier than now crap and how this is a
wild food and oh why isn't it organic so
I'm not going to use that I'm all about
organic don't give me that holier than
now about that because what happens
is people don't realize it that our
organic food is also laced
it's laced with nicotine
MSG
and other stuff
and what people realize is they have to
spray the crap out of organic food or
all the aphids come and rip it apart so
they're loaded with copper
copper in the spray
like the toxic copper and organic spray
and nicotine
so here we are so what I'm saying is
that's a wild food that rarely needs to
ever be sprayed because a wild food can
tend to itself and protect itself a wild
food actually protects itself
so what that means is rarely does it
ever get sprayed and Wyman's will not
use a pollinator killer
if they ever do need to spray they won't
use a pollinator killer what does that
mean why here's the difference
this wild food they won't kill their
bees organic crops they kill their bees
important to know right there so they
also test
and they get zero percent zero percent
in their tests of pesticides but guess
what your organic food companies
won't test to make sure you have zero
percent nicotine
and zero percent copper
from their sprays
so every time you see it and I see in
the comments that Holier the now stuff
like oh it's not organic medical medium
doesn't know what he's talking about
so let me just give you the 101 right
now
your organic crops get sprayed with
copper toxic copper and toxic nicotine
and he ends up killing all the bees and
the pollinators and they get sprayed
rapidly because organic crops can't take
care of itself it's too weak this is a
wild food and I eat organic food I'm
just telling you this is a wild food
they rarely ever have to spray anything
and if they do they refuse to use a
pollinator killer and they test it zero
percent pesticide residue and here's the
other thing the organic food companies
they're not testing to make sure you're
not getting nicotine and copper
remember that this is an important piece
of information and it's mind-blowing and
by the way Wyman's juice is coming to
Europe early next year and to other
parts of the world next year or a year
later so pretty cool
anyway that's really mind-blowing
information all on its own and it's
important to know by the way 10 off
right now wymans.com link is in the
description link is in the profile you
guys know I'm working with them because
I need this stuff to stick around in the
world because they need resources like
this because it's magical and spiritual
and powerful and I love knowing that
that's there for the chronically ill and
everything else so
anyway you guys I am going to make two
recipes today out of brain saver books
I'm excited so let's take a look at that
grogu just got clocked with the book
okay don't worry ow
stop stop okay okay okay you know what
rogue's been doing he's been sending me
telepathic pain waves to make sure that
I get punished every like 20 minutes or
10 minutes
but the good news is I have the wild
blueberry juice here to help kind of
repair the mental abuse that grogu's
been giving me which is unbelievable I
mean the mental abuse okay
I know but I still love having you here
by the way all right let's go okay don't
worry I'm moving as fast as I can I am
all right so I'm going to page 532 and I
even have it marked right here 532 I'm
making the warm wild blueberry Bowl
okay there it is right there and by the
way you guys it's incredible it's really
unbelievable this warm while blueberry
Bowl I love it I make it for myself
periodically I'm gonna try to make it
exactly the way the book says today okay
instead of the lazy way I make it once
in a while
I'm gonna make it way better
so and I'm also making this check this
out
I think I need some more wine
I am also making this right here which
is the wild blueberry latte
latte whoa pretty posh
pretty you know epic and Posh right and
so I'm excited about that and I'm gonna
read a little bit inside the book too
which I'm excited all as well so let me
do that
and you guys just got here we're making
a couple of recipes for day two of the
wild blueberry challenge okay I'm
excited about this what you see is wild
blueberries the juice is 10 off which is
incredible right there we're going to
talk about the anthocyanins a little bit
today everything also making two recipes
I am going to have a little glass of
wine of course there's no alcohol in
here because this is straight wild
blueberries hmm
so good
someone said in the YouTube YouTube
comment they were like I never heard you
lip smack before I've never heard you
lip smack after I had the extractor
yesterday and I was like
lip smack that's what I'm doing so good
it's really delicious that's why
all right oh wait
I want to address a comment that was
also mentioned too yesterday okay so the
comment was this aw you're confusing me
you said
that you can have the five ingredients
in your hmds at any time of day so how
is it possible you would ruin your
smoothie if you put in the wrong stuff
so what that was so that was just
misunderstood what I was saying was
don't put things that will ruin your
smoothie or your health don't put in the
chlorella the apple cider vinegar the
charcoal the collagen all these things
that are not good for us don't put
chocolate in there all these things that
should not be in there that do ruin what
it's trying to do for you because you're
adding all those things that actually
complicate the body of the liver put a
burden on you burden on a system and
burden on everything that you're trying
to do
okay here's the comment right here while
blueberry juice has helped stop
migraines and brain fog for B I've heard
that from a lot of people by the way
that comment I've heard how it stops
migraines while blueberry juice I heard
how it shifts people I heard how it's
actually created focus in concentration
in people that's what I've heard
um so Vanya Health incredible
thank you for that comment so you guys
we're doing some fun stuff I want to
read a little bit too Ingy says while
blueberry saved my brain Anton who has
had a stroke needs them daily
so
all I can say right now is incredible it
really has saved a lot of people's
brains I've seen that happen too so
great
all right so I think you meant anyone
yeah okay let's go into here and take a
look
I just need some more wine
[Music]
this is so good I'm gonna buy a wine a
winery in Napa Valley like a snob I am
like an elite snob
okay um let's see page 95 here I am
right here in brain saver
no disrespect for no disrespect to snobs
and no disrespect for elite latest snobs
no disrespect to them at all no
disrespect to trust funders
and just whatever
you know whatever I mean I'm not saying
there's nothing wrong with that
I'm just you know I just like to joke
around a lot okay let's go
we're I'm going to read a little bit of
this just get in the mood right here
so good
I was a trust funder I use the money for
medical school
yes and I bought myself a penthouse as
well
absolutely
okay
let's just move on
this is a section called everybody wants
to heal
it's on page 95 a brain saver
by the way these books just got released
and they're just incredible they blow my
mind constantly honestly you can't even
like there's so much information in
these books but every single paragraph
Just is like mind-blowing it's just
crazy how it is
everybody wants to heal
nobody doesn't want to heal
you'll hear it out there
you just don't want to heal that's why
you're not healing you got a fear of
healing that's why you're not healing
have you ever heard that BS
everybody wants to heal nobody doesn't
want to heal no one wants to be sick or
suffering emotionally
do you want to be sick or suffering
emotionally nobody does
no one is afraid of healing
no one has a fear of healing that's
secretly holding them back from getting
better but yet people are told that
you guys people are told that all the
time you got uh you have a fear of
healing it's internally you just know
you know you just don't know you have a
fear of healing I am a psychotherapist
I'm a psychotherapist and I'm telling my
patient my client you just have a fear
of healing that's why you're sick still
you know you hear that all the time
maybe you guys have heard that before
right
we want to heal we want to live forever
people want to live forever they do they
do we want to live at our healthiest for
as long as we can
there's also a trusting wire within us
that's been taken advantage of by
Industries
trust we have a trusting liar inside of
us
it's a trusting wire inside of the brain
and that trusting wire has been
manipulated and conditioned
for a long time by the industries
the trusting wire is built into the
neurons inside
the emotional centers of the brain and
that trusting wire is a real thing that
gets manipulated and the think tanks out
there in the industries love to actually
control that trusting wire that's inside
people's brains
okay this has created a brainwashing
within us
a mechanism inside us that wants
permission to do harmful things to
ourselves this is interesting right here
we want permission to harm ourselves
because once we get permission to harm
ourselves then we actually feel good
about it
and we can then do that
that's how it works
we want permission to eat as much
chocolate as we've ever wanted to eat
because oh it's good for us that's what
we're told we want permission to do what
we want we want permission to moderately
smoke we want permission
to smoke as much weed as we ever dreamed
we can smoke right I'm not no disrespect
any weed smokers because that's not what
this is about but we want permission
to do whatever we want to do
we do want that permission
to heart do harmful things to ourselves
the desire for health is so strong
inside of us that we'll try to look for
answers about why anything that's
harmful could be good for us
we have this incredible desire
to want to find something
valuable in something that's harming us
it's really incredible
we want validation that hurting
ourselves is actually good for us
this can make it seem as if
self-sabotage is part of our innate
emotional nature that's mind-blowing as
if we want to harm ourselves when we
really don't we don't want to harm
ourselves but we're brainwashed
into thinking we do
we don't self-sabotage because we want
to make ourselves sick
we self-sabotage because we're taught to
self-sabotage
if someone is eating all this fast food
24 7. there's just there's always fast
food fast food it's a form of
self-sabotage to some degree right
but we're not doing it
purposely
right to harm ourselves if somebody
smokes if somebody smokes weed if
someone drinks if so I'll have another
sip right now
if someone drinks
they're not doing it to harm themselves
we self-sabotage because we're taught to
self-sabotage we're conditioned to
self-sabotage we're practically bred to
self-sabotage why am I even reading this
why am I even talking about this when
I'm doing a wild blueberry date you of
the challenge
because your spiritual powers in this
blue color right here that enters the
emotional centers of the brain that
helps to unwind brain washing from the
industries that is used to get us to
self-sabotage ourselves there's a
rewiring that happens when that blue
juice hits the brain our brain is like a
magnet to the blue anthocyanins coming
off these wild blueberries and going to
the brain
foreign
Cults and I call them Colts because
they're the Cults because they all speak
the same thing
that's how Cults work
they all say the same thing
no matter how you slice the pie
all the different Fabrics of alternative
medicine all still support and befriend
the same people the same thing
because it's one big cult
alternative medicine Cults as well as
top feeders and Bottom Feeders of the
health industry are always catering to
the self-sabotage brainwashing
they are they do you'll see it
you'll see every aspect of alternative
medicine doesn't want to insult
a particular group because they all are
basically working for each other and
around each other
trading within each other
working within each other and that's how
it is out there it's just a fact it's
just what it is
alternative medicine Cults as well as
top feeders and Bottom Feeders of the
health industry are always catering to
the self-sabotage brainwashing how how
ready
no you should have all the green tea you
ever wanted because it's good for you
and then the next alternative Colt would
be like yeah green tea is totally fine
the next Alternative Health cult would
be like yeah green tea is fine oh yeah
it's good for you it's got stuff in it
that's good oh a new study came out and
then another alternative Colt be like
green tea is good for you
and they'll all mimic the same thing oh
yeah you can have coffee do Organics uh
you know fair trade do organic coffee
yeah and you can you know it's all the
same thing oh you can do cacao all you
want oh yeah Ayahuasca is all right if
you do it you know once in a while and
you're having a spiritual moment and
you're with the right Shaman you can do
that too so all mimic the same thing and
all the Alternative Health Cults because
they all work together and they all
speak one language and that's when you
know it is one big cult right
I'm talking about this because the wild
blueberry helps us to break from that
it helps us to break away from that so
we have our own mind
the reason why medical medium
information is hated so much out there
because it gives person other person
their own free will back
it gives them their own free thinking
back their own free will it gives them
answers for the first time so they can
make decisions and choices for
themselves that's what it's been all
about for medical medium information it
gives the person freedom because when
you see it out there you're still all
wrapped up out there and all that other
cold stuff it's crazy how it works the
wild blueberry whether somebody knows it
or not when it's integrated into their
health can help them break from that
it's just mind-blowing information in
here
so let's just keep on reading I'm going
to have a little bit of wine real quick
it's not wine it's wild blueberry juice
if you just got here
that's the brain saver book I'm reading
out out there's two brain saver and the
Brain saver protocols
okay
so often using and here's another thing
too
the alternative medicine Cults will
often use their credentials to
manipulate our trust
there's nothing wrong with credentials I
have a lot of friends with credentials
a lot of doctor friends with credentials
right doctors that work for good not for
evil right
but a lot of people in the Cults out
there they use their credentials to
manipulate people and our trust they
create their own social media channels
and give their five tips in 15 minutes
and in those five tips you'll almost
always find at least one recommendation
that provides validation and reassurance
for self-sabotage
how freaking despicable when you think
about it
because every time I see those five tips
or ten tips or whatever it is you can
see in those 510 tips once again the
same language the same stuff to
self-sabotage is there
a big part of the self-sabotage
brainwashing is that we become
programmed to seek validation that doing
a harmful thing in moderation is
perfectly fine
exactly
Leah Collins says aw isn't here to be
liked or sugarcoat the truth he's here
to heal and break the false light in the
medical community and it's so truth so
that's so true in alternative medical
community and conventional
that's what's so crazy about it all
for The Not So Sick there's there these
self-sabotage measures are often a daily
part of everyone's life so here's how it
works what I mean by The Not So Sick you
guys you just got here today's day two
of the wild blueberry challenge I'm
making a couple of recipes we're having
some fun but I'm also talking about the
spiritual powers
any antioxidants of the wild blueberry
but I'm talking about it in association
with the emotional center of the brain
and how the wild blueberries
have the power to rise out of the ashes
allowing us to have the power to rise
out of mind control
because that's what's Happening Here on
planet Earth in the Alternative Health
movement is people are under mind
control
they're told their fish oil is fine
they're told their krill oil is fine
which it isn't you guys it's loaded with
Mercury but they don't realize it
they're told a lot of things I talk all
about it in the brain books but yeah
it's just unbelievable really The Not So
Sick what The Not So Sick is is look I
have respect for The Not So Sick the not
so sick of people that have symptoms but
it hasn't
impeded their life in such a way where
it robs the quality of their life where
they are in severe severe trouble
The Not So Sick are people that have a
couple of different symptoms and they
run around to different functional
doctors and regular doctors and they
just look for things to kind of keep
them floating and they float along
because they're not so sick and then
eventually the scale tips and they go
down the drain right
the not so sick
for The Not So Sick these self-sabotage
measures are often a daily part of
everybody's life get ready for this
coffee that's a daily part of
everybody's life who's not so sick
they could just still do coffee vinegar
that's another thing in their daily life
that's a self-sabotage
weapon right there is vinegar ages you
fast dissolves your teeth breaks your
immune system down breaks your nervous
system down
wine that's one right there
as long as you have a couple of glasses
on the weekend everything should be fine
yeah moderation
for that for The Not So Sick somebody
that just has like a thyroid problem
that they're managing or something
or they got some hot flashes or
something and they're just you know they
go to their doctors and they're like
whoa I whatever they can still drink
their wine on the weekends right they're
not so sick
so pizza that's another one The Not So
Sick can eat pizza all the time they
could have it on Friday nights they
could have it on Saturday night fried
and greasy food they can engage in that
too whether it's alternative fried and
greasy food whether it's vegan fried or
greasy food whether it's vegan pizza
they can still partake in it because
they're not so sick if we hear these are
not good for us we look for someone else
to say it is good for you in moderation
as long as it's vegan your pizza should
be fine in moderation because you're not
so sick yet so you can handle it as long
as you've got your wine once on the
weekend hey fine you can handle it
you're not so sick yet
we don't want to face the reality of
what we're really doing we don't want to
pay the consequences of osteopenia
coming from vinegar liver conditions
coming from alcohol adrenal problems
coming from caffeine like I was talking
about you guys so we'll never accept
that these are the true causes of these
conditions it's as if in Industry
conditioning has placed a robot inside
us that wants validation to slowly
destroy ourselves even though that's the
last thing we really want we want
validation for the industry
to keep on feeding us these things so we
can destroy ourselves we want validation
to destroy ourselves even though that's
not what we really want we've been
brainwashed to think that's what we want
we want to be healthy and strong and
live forever right I see that all the
time we want to be healthy and strong
and live forever under certain
conditions
some of these conditions are I'm going
to have my dark chocolate and coffee and
vinegar and wine and champagne and salt
I don't know what all this business is
about in this book
hmm I do perfectly fine in my wine
you can't stop me
I'm on page 95 you guys you can't stop
me you can't tell me I can't
and I'm about to go to page 96.
because I'll go and find someone who's a
health authority who says it's fine and
even good for me to eat all that plus
raw aged cheese and grass-fed butter and
green tea and matcha and Kombucha tea
and eggs and I'll run with that
we're taught to self-sabotage by the
industry
all those things are bad for us and if
you're not so sick you can play in that
game and keep on self-sabotaging and
keep on being taught to self-sabotage
but you're never free
you're
part of what they want
the industry and why am I saying this
again because the wild blueberry gets
into the consciousness of Consciousness
it gets into the soul it gets into the
physical brain and it starts to rewire
us the wild blueberry has the ability to
rewire us and to shed that brainwashing
it is the anti-brainwashing food
that will give me the comfy warm fuzzy
feeling inside that I've been validated
for doing these things that are actually
helping destroy my body
I'll even convince myself that my body
loves it my body loves chocolate so much
I crave it my body must love chocolate
my body loves vinegar I love it on
everything my body loves eggs I crave
them they're so good for me
my body likes all these things
and my body's fine with it and my body
needs it this brainwashing and
conditioning
becomes woven into the emotional centers
of our brain it also gets directed
mostly to women kind on purpose and
here's how it works
the systems in the industries brainwash
women kind
so that women kind believes they need
all these things that are actually
helping to destroy their body and if
they're not so sick they can keep on
partaking in it and the minute they get
too sick too sick no one's there to tell
them how to get out of it except medical
medium information which is that alone
is just crazy because why haven't the
other alternative
parts of the industries in the health
industry figured all this out yet yeah
they'll poach a little tidbit for
medical medium here and there and you'll
see somebody squeak it out once in a
while but the alternative industry
make sure it allows the not so sick
people to keep on staying brainwashed
and partake in all the products and
guess what and on top of that the
alternative industry sells it all to
them
sells women kind all the chocolate in
the dark chocolate sells women kind all
the matcha tea sells women kind all the
Kombucha Tea which is really turns the
blood into straight acid I've been
saying that for 30 years sells all this
stuff to women kind
so women kind can slowly decline
yet the emotional centers of our brain
can only be pushed so far when you're
sick or suffering enough physically
mentally or emotionally a survival
mechanism kicks into that happen to you
guys
who have been real sick
did that ever happen to you guys where
where literally something overrode the
brainwashing and you said find medical
meme information or an angel put medical
meme information in front of you or
something something happened and you
guys felt it right when you're sick or
suffering enough emotionally physically
or anything mentally a survival
mechanism kicks in did it kick in on you
guys that survival mechanism did it hit
a survival mechanism in your brain's
emotional centers that has been inside
of us since the beginning of time a
survival mechanism beginning a time now
check this out get ready for this
these wild blueberries have been here
since the beginning of time
tens of thousands hundreds of thousands
millions of years ago the wild blueberry
has been here
and there's been a mechanism built
inside of us since the beginning of time
that gets tripped up and we're finally
done I'm done
with the brainwashing
I need answers
I need to heal I've suffered enough
that survival mechanism says no
I hear it's not good for me
no I hear a glass of wine on the
weekends is not good for me I'm
suffering enough as it is no I hear
tinctures herbal tinctures from other
companies with alcohol in them are not
good for me I had enough
no I heard
that that's not good for me I heard I'm
not supposed to be swallowing clays it's
not good for me I heard from medical
medium
no I'm not supposed to be caffeinating
my adrenals to death and burning my
brain cells out
no I had enough it's time to heal
I'm going to align my physical body to
that understanding finally I'm in too
much pain I've been through hell and
back I've suffered enough I'm too unwell
to mess around now I can't play games
anymore something Clicks in
it's a survival mechanism that started
at the beginning of time with the wild
blueberry
where you once learned it's not good for
you something Clicks in where you once
learn it's not good you know it's time
to stay away from that caffeine in the
vinegar and the salt all the salt and
the chocolate you know it's time
something rewires in your emotional
centers of your brain that says I can't
destroy myself anymore
I can't search for validation to support
something that's harming me from the
Cults out there
from the vinegar cult and the chocolate
Colts out there and the all that the
cacao Cults and everything all the Cults
and Ayahuasca Colts and all the smoking
cults and the alcohol cults
right and all of it and above something
inside of you says I'm not going to
partake in the cult anymore that's out
there I don't want to destroy myself
anymore I've been through hell and back
I've suffered enough I've been sick I
can't take it anymore
I've been pushed around too much
I've been toyed with too much
I'm not in the business of destroying
myself anymore because I want to live I
want to heal I'm not afraid to heal I've
never been I've never been afraid to
heal and it's time
why am I saying all this
on blueberry day
whoop pardon me on wild blueberry day
because a blueberry can't do anything
for us like a wild blueberry can
this is a wild food
it has lived for thousands upon
thousands of years
it wasn't
grafted into some kind of thing and then
plant it to be cultivated it is wild
and it Harbors information
what happens in us when that wire gets
tripped and we're done with the Colts
and we're we're totally awake and we
really truly became awake
this enough is enough strength inside of
everyone it starts to kick in it's the
moment when you put your foot down it's
the moment when you truly find yourself
when you're working with and aligned
with your body that's what the wild
blueberry is about it's about aligning
with our body it's about taking the
subconscious's Consciousness and the
soul and the physical brain and making
it become one so it's not fragmented
not even the snakiest salesman on social
media videos or the sneakiest
chiropractor doctor or nutritionist
on The snakiest infomercials can give
you the validation anymore to go into
the robotic mode of I'm going to destroy
myself with a smile on my face
and be happy thinking about it
because my body deserves and needs what
I'm putting in it
that old brainwashing that manipulated
your trusty wire and sent a message to
your brain's emotional centers to
override Common Sense and Sensibility
about what your body really needs that
brainwashing won't work anymore
even if everyone around you has been
brainwashed and they challenge you as
you start trying to eat healthy get
healthy get better you know how to stand
firm have you guys been challenged
you're doing the medical medium
information and you're getting your
lives back and you're working so hard on
your your life and you're doing that
information have you guys been
challenged
challenge my people around you all of it
has that happened to you
you're doing the right things now you
got the information you're saving your
life you're getting rid of your symptoms
and you're being challenged at the same
time
when that time comes that's when you're
Reborn
it's The Rebirth of finally moving out
of that mental and emotional pain moving
out of that in between and turning your
life around
and that reminds me
of the wild blueberry
it's Reborn
it comes out of the ashes you can't kill
it
and then it's there for us
and it's that spiritual power it holds
that blue color is an anthocyan and it's
different than any other anthocyanin and
it goes to the brain and it heads into
the emotional center of the brain and it
rewires us
let's make some blueberry while while
blueberry recipes
[Music]
all right you guys you need anything
hold on sorry
yeah
yeah ew's bar grill is going okay today
I heard there was a new person here yeah
yeah they're here they're sitting down
over there yep
what yeah we wanted
four glasses of wine
with wild blueberry wine
yeah no alcohol
really incredible you guys okay all
right
you guys I'm gonna need that right now
sorry about this
wait oh oh grogu stop grow goo
hold on you guys
um we're in halftime right now bro who
just sent a pain wave to my head
he's been tormenting me
see he uses his telepathic skills
he uses the force
and he just sends it right to my because
I'm psychic right my brain and he sends
it right to my psychic brain
and boy does he heard it really bad
really really bad
ah
Kroger you're gonna kill me I swear
foreign
[Music]
wild blueberry Bowl turning it up
I'm gonna put some shots over here you
guys I need a little bit of room
you guys okay
all right
this is an incredible recipe
it's right out of this book right here
the protocols book
two things to know one thing is
amazon.com us 40 off right now an
incredible book Incredible books right
here don't miss out your minds will be
blown I was reading out of the brain
saver book
incredible recipes in the brain saver
book as well so don't miss out seriously
you guys it's absolutely incredible
these books anyway and 10 off on the
Wyman's wild blueberry juice you guys
know I work with them because I want the
stuff to stay around I'm telling
everybody I can
this is incredible if you haven't signed
up to the challenge this is day two sign
up go to medicalbeam.com download your
PDF with your groceries your free pdf
it's all free get your grocery store
shopping list okay
and the details are there the details
about the challenge incredible you guys
I'm warming up this right here we're
going to go in here and get some recipes
out right now let's do it
what a day
quite amazing
all right let's take a look
warm wild blueberry Bowl right there
that's what we're making let's get
started right now
this is getting hot I have my little
griddle on
I got my ingredient list here four cups
of wild blueberries are going in there
so let's do that now and get a little
measuring cup
so I have my little measuring cup so
we're going to do four cups
so let's do that you know grogu your
your
um
your little vessel that you're in tends
to move around because it's floating
right with the force
all right so let's get some wild
blueberries in here now
so we want four cups in this recipe are
you guys doing this with me because
that'd be amazing there's two cups right
there
let's go with four cups
now what I love about the wild blueberry
and we're gonna still talk about the
anthocyanins a little bit more as well
and we're going to talk about
antioxidants too not all antioxidants
are the same not all people are the same
not all water is the same
that's something to know
and certainly not all antioxidants are
the same
now this is a wild food
it's entirely different than a
cultivated Berry
let's go with four cups we got it in
there
right
half cup
of pure maple syrup
and I'm about to get that right now
I got some maple syrup right here
amazing
let's go with a half cup a half a cup
here let's do that nice
okay
it's a little bit of maple syrup
incredible
got a little bit of that in there
nice
all right one and a half tablespoons of
arrowroot powder We're not gonna do that
yet we're just gonna warm this up and
get it going
I'm gonna put the lid on okay you guys
and then we're gonna make some
additional are you guys have you done
this recipe the warm wild blueberry Bowl
it's really an incredible recipe
it's amazing
you guys
um have you tried wild blueberries have
you tried the wild blueberry juice have
you had an experience with it what did
you feel a lot of people feel like their
mental Clarity is better a lot of people
feel like they're focusing concentration
is better a lot of people feel like it
gets rid of a headache a lot of people
experience this migraine relief they
experience so much it's what their
experiences are and what I hear out
there all right so I've heard this over
and over again I've talked to doctor
friends and they say their patients love
it all of it please share your story on
a real an insta story whatever or you
know a post
um share it tag at Medical medium
medical medium so I can share it too
what was your experience with wild
blueberries did you have it in the hmds
all these years did you have an
experience with it along the way do you
love your wild blueberries that's
another thing all on its own
so that's important too so I'm just
making sure that I have that heating up
now
there we go
now the warm wild blueberry Bowl
is a special one
I really love it
I'm going to take this lid and move it
you know my favorite thing is it's not
just this wild blueberry challenge
like one of my favorite things is
starting to like cook and do stuff you
know like this because this is what I
love right so I want to do more lives in
the future where I'm making some of the
recipes out of these books which I'm
excited about too so I'm looking forward
to that
now
when it comes down to anthocyanins
you're looking at amphocyanins with a
real rich rich blue color that purple
blue color okay now
anthocyanins for different parts of the
body like they go in different places in
the body and what I love about the wild
blueberry anthocyanins
is this information I got from SOC is
because of that rich color that deep
deep blue color the anthocyanins are not
designed to just go like
in one specific like they're not
designed to just go everywhere they're
designed to head to the Noggin that's
where they head
okay because that blue color that
anthocyanin is geared for metaphysical
and physical that's the whole point so
when you see that deep blue color what
you're seeing is metaphysical and that's
what you have to think
so I am going to get some arrowroot
powder
and uh one and a half tablespoons of
water
and get that in here I will try not to
spill it on the book
there's one tablespoon I'm going to do a
half now
perfect
[Music]
okay
very interesting so I'm going to mix
this up
so this is the warm while the blueberry
Bowl
now I notice people will say like I
don't have wild blueberries
so I'm gonna use
regular blueberry
if you can't find a wild blueberry don't
use a regular blueberry a cultivated
regular blueberry won't cut it if you're
looking for something Madison more
medicinal and you can't find the wild
blueberry
then go with blackberries
it's not going to do the same thing
right it's not going to do the same
thing but it's a step above your
cultivated blueberry
because a lot of people they'll just run
to the store they don't really know
anything about the wild liver they don't
know anything about what's going on and
they're uncertain like incredible let me
just go get some blueberries it's not
the same thing so that's important to
know
okay
now I'm going to add this in
so what you see here is the arrowroot
starch
okay
I added a little bit of water to it
and then it's going in now
wonderful
and now I'm going to Stir It
I don't know how easy you can see this
but
there you are hey look at that
fantastic
let that get a little hotter
I don't want to call I put them in they
were already chilled the blueberries the
wild blueberries were already some of
them were frozen still I'm gonna cook it
for about one more minute
yep
because you want your you want it to be
a warm wild blueberry Bowl you don't
want it to be a cold wild Livery Bowl
because that will happen especially if
you take them out of the freezer
you want to make sure they're warm and
nice and comfy and warm and fuzzy
which is incredible
and I'm going to get them ready now to
serve if you guys don't mind
and then next we're going to be making
the wild blueberry latte
grogu
every time grogu gets Disturbed grogu
sends me a telepathic message
okay
I'm trying to use here's the thing I'm
trying to use the wild blueberry to help
with the brain the emotional centers of
the brain
and grogu is sitting there sending
telepathic messages to the emotional
centers the brain to cause pain but
that's the great thing right I have
something to battle that that's right
kuroku all right getting ready to serve
you guys
looking for my serving Bowl now
okay
here we go
this is one of my favorites
have you guys made this before
or is this your first time
I'm curious
I know that the books just got out there
and they haven't been out there long so
you might not have like discovered this
yet or anything
but there you go
that's amazing
that's the warm while blueberry Bowl
right there
you guys don't mind right
thank you
hmm
it's insane it's so good
it is so good
it's amazing
seriously you guys
this is the way to eat it
destroy you guys um that concludes uh
see you later bye
just kidding kidding I'm here
all right put it out
it's just so good all right let's get
making the next thing
let's get going on
[Music]
all right
we're making the second recipe right now
I'm gonna bring this over here
do you guys mind
foreign
I can't get enough of wild blueberries
I'm even gonna have this
I Can't Get Enough
maybe I might take a shot glass from
baby grogu
h
you guys are 10 off right now
wymans.com links in the description it's
incredible
and if you're worried about that organic
Thing versus wild food thing just watch
this whole video from the beginning and
and totally get an education about how
it works because it's critical to know
that information
it really is all right let's go so we're
making the wild blueberry latte right
now this sweet and creamy drink is
delicious
okay you can watch the replay at
medicalmedium.com
of this uh wild blueberry challenge day
day two you can watch day one as well by
the way all right three quarters of a
cup of water
[Music]
here we go
thank you very much
what's next
half a cup of unsweetened almond milk or
like coconut milk or unsweetened oat
milk I'm gonna go with coconut milk
next
doing it we're doing it
half a cup of Frozen
while blueberries or I'm gonna use the
juice that's my favorite way of making
it so that's what I'm going to do
I'm gonna have to open up another bottle
I think I'm going through all these
bottles right now
you know what it is everybody wants a
shot
I think it's just me doing too many
shots is what I think it is all right
Darcy Lee says oh my God the wild
blueberry latte to the bomb so freaking
good it's so good it's insanely good and
I am going to be very happy while I'm
partaking
in the consumption of this wild
blueberry latte
all right so let's keep on going there
gonna use a quarter cup wild blueberry
juice
since I already used this it's perfectly
fine and use it again quarter cup here
nice look at that you guys check it out
yeah this is the bomb
this thing is so insane
it's insane
so good all right
one to two tablespoons of honey raw
honey is what I prefer got it right here
one to two tablespoons
let's see
Maybe
one to two tablespoons all right that
should be good
okay
boom
all right
half a teaspoon of cinnamon
come on already
oh my God I'm so excited it's ridiculous
quarter teaspoon of ground cardamom
yes let's get the cardamon open here
okay
there we go
that's why I like doing everything live
because you just don't know what's gonna
happen maybe the cardamon isn't open yet
quarter teaspoon of cardamom
foreign
boom
I'm gonna blend it you guys
all right
don't go crazy on the blending
just try to take it easy
all right we're doing it mine is
happening
after this we're going to pour it in the
pan and we're going to heat it
nice
I would say that's good enough wouldn't
you guys
I'm gonna pour this in the pan it's
probably gonna sizzle
okay
I think I'm gonna strain it you guys I'm
not liking the way it looks I forgot to
strain it
all right
all right I'm going to strain it into
the pan
nice
nice guys sometimes you just have to
improvise
do it right
so I don't want to do it the lazy way
today because I make this for myself all
the time but I do it like the quick and
lazy way
I wouldn't call Lazy whatever I just
like whatever I slap it together
whatever you want to call it
and but I want to do it like to the
letter
all right let's get that in the pan and
let's get that going
woo
let it warm up a little bit
I don't make it all the time all the
time I just make it for guests that come
and then then usually I just slap it
together but like I want to like do it
really nice right now
so I make it when guests are
coming and then when they try it they go
this is unbelievable on the holidays
you guys when if you just got here I saw
somebody just in the comments or like
what's he doing what is this
day two
stage two of The Free Medical medium
wild blueberry day challenge
watch the video the replay at
medicalmedium.com watch it from the
beginning
okay if you're ever having trouble
viewing this on IG or Facebook or
wherever go to medicalmedium.com it's
live on there right now we're streaming
it live and I am updating and adding new
information to medicalmedium.com
enhancing it making it an incredible
website free information everything no
pay walls go there get all the recipes
all the different things you name it and
if you had a chance you guys leave a
review at amazon.com for the brainsaver
books
right here both the books amazon.com
under 40 off okay get it free at the
library if you want you can get these
books free at the library if you don't
want to go and get them at 40 off at
amazon.com Us free the library
you guys if I had a feather for every
time I said free at the library
with these all the medical medium books
I'd be flying away
medical medium podcast check it out the
light infusion meditation that is in
these books and I did that right there
on the medical game podcast and I have a
new podcast episode coming out next week
which is going to be awesome really
awesome too
all right we're just getting this ready
this is the wild blueberry latte
amazing how you guys doing did you have
your shots
foreign
all right
now the thing is is that
if you
are wondering like why do I love the
wild blueberries so much
there's so many reasons it's hard to
keep them all in all like count it
because there's that many reasons
because you're looking at extremely high
antioxidants
what does that mean when you have
extremely high antioxidants
helping the body to stop oxidizing what
happens when the body's oxidizing or
slowly dying or quickly dying
So the faster somebody's oxidative rate
is inside their body the faster they're
dying
so that's really what it comes down to
yes you can have a lot of things
oxidizing you right so I talk about that
in the medical meeting books you can
have a lot of different things that are
oxidizing and breaking down the body
so everybody's different they might have
more oxidation than somebody else
but oxidation is what breaks this down
and it shortens our life one way or
another regardless of what's Happening
inside our bodies you guys I'm going to
make a little announcement right here
light blast make sure you sign up to the
medical meeting newsletter so you can
learn the date and the time
of the light blast because that's going
to be really exciting so sign up within
the next month so you can make sure
you're there it's going to be a limit of
like a limited amount of people though
so get to that newsletter sign up so you
can be there to receive that light blast
when the day comes and we do it but it's
going to be a limited amount of people
allowed
when I do that light blast
so keep that in mind too so sign up when
you get a chance
light blast is it's going to be really
exciting
I'm really looking forward to it all
right this is nice and ready
nice and warm and good
you will get the chance to sign up on
the medical medium newsletter that's no
problem you can go to the medical medium
newsletter and sign up but sign up so
then you can get notified
through email when the light blast is
going to be
important to know
all right you guys so let's get this
ready right here
just letting it heat up a little bit
more
so I like my latte being like hot
Wendy says we'll be there no matter what
awesome
Lisa says I'm signing up incredible
amazing
corny says I want to lay in a field for
the light blast
okay guys
now I'm going to pour this into a
measuring cup is what I'm going to do
next
here's my measuring cup right here
okay
and
I'm going to pour this in
and I'm not going to try to pour this on
top of Roku right here
nice
get another little saucepan on
I'm going to pour this into a cup
so it's not done yet though you guys
that's the wild blueberry latte
in motion it's not done so there we go
now I'm a I'm gonna froth
this up or episode wait a second
I'm going to put it in the pan first
all right
okay just want enough in there
we're doing it we're heating it up right
now
now I don't want to turn this blue what
happens is if we have so much blue juice
around and everything else like that you
don't want to turn it blue so I'm going
to get a new utensil because I've done
this before where I turned
it blew and you just want you don't want
that
okay
it's kind of breaking it up a little bit
hmm
if you guys just came on here I'm making
the wild blueberry
latte
from brain saver
I want to show you what it looks like I
don't think I did that yet I might have
here it is this is what I'm making right
now you guys
the wild blueberry latte
since I'm such a snob
I like my lattes
just heating up the milk
non-dairy this is coconut milk right
here
latte's almost done nice and hot inside
here we're almost there
but we have to we have to froth it so
that's next
it's getting a little bit hotter because
you want that heat to get into it
because when you get the heat into it
you can froth it up better
if it's not really warm enough you can't
give it that froth that you got to do
just about there
and I got this little frothing tool
this is a great holiday treat
because you can it just keeps everything
so good and so good for you so it's an
incredible holiday tree
all right so we're just about there
we're gonna pour back now into
the measuring cup
perfect
now I'm going to click this on
so what I'm doing right now is I'm just
giving it a nice
nice froth here
okay
guys we're almost there we're gonna make
an incredible drink a latte everything
we're using today if you're curious is
on medicalmedium.com check out the
supplement directory and the kitchen
tool directory
since you guys are always asking
all right
I think this has gotten definitely nice
in
frothy
all right
let's go
now what you want to do is you want to
put this gently in here you don't want
to just push it all in there one shot
you just want to kind of have it gently
go in
like this
you don't want to mix the two you don't
want the blue
mixing with the froth the coconut froth
how high you want to bring it to the top
is totally up to you
I'm going to bring it up really high
so that froth is kind of like right up
there whoa
that's insane
that is just insane
I'm really proud of myself right now you
guys
seriously I'm gonna sprinkle a little
bit of cinnamon on top
you don't want to overdo it
darn
it's not what I wanted to do I wanted to
sprinkle it everywhere on top
and not in just one shot like that
that's how it was supposed to be done
right there
you live and learn I'm only human
that is
incredible tasting when you guys try it
you guys are going to be mind blown
and you know what
it's like you're not self-sabotaging
it's you're not like you're not
brainwashed out there to self-sabotage
with all the addictions that we don't
even know we have
we're far from it
this is entirely different
and the wild blueberry has so much to do
with it
because it gets to our brain it rewires
us and it stops us from being a toy
it stops us from being a tool for the
industries
we get free
we break free is what we do day two of
the medical medium wild blueberry
challenge can't believe it
I might take a sip
oh my God
that just puts me in such a happy place
incredible you guys
have you tried the wild blueberries
ten percent off the Wyman's wild one
very juice incredible wymans.com
w-y-m-a-n-s have you tried wild
blueberries whether it's frozen or in
this incredible juice
what was your experience can I get
medical medium hashtag medical medium
whatever your real your posts your
stories are let us know how you feel
what it may have done for you over time
whether it's chmds or whatever
um
so good I can't take it I'm gonna need
more
amazing
what do you guys think
did you have your shots
I'm just gonna be into this right now
boom incredibly guys
amazing for day two we read a little bit
in the brain saver books
I'm having a blast with you guys
I don't even know what to say I'm just
happy
I'll see you tomorrow for day three
catch yesterday's live day one make sure
you sign up so you get your download
your free pdf grocery shopping list free
free free free free Challenge free
everything free education on wild
blueberries free everything all of it
incredible check out medical meme
podcast at Apple podcast when you get a
chance and check out medical medium.com
because of everything I'm doing to the
website so you have an endless amount of
healing information it is not held back
it's there for you
so incredible if you don't have the
brain saver books grab the brain saver
books when you get a chance
can't free at the library or amazon.com
us leave a review two as well it helps
and uh I love you guys dearly it's been
an honor
such a great time and I'm going to
actually have some of this oh where's my
wild blueberry Bowl right there my warm
water blue rainbow Sun Moon love says
thank you for a fun day at Medical
medium University I am full and feeling
good from all the blueberries this
morning amazing
um
so good oh my God
[Music]
medical meme University is free
you don't need fifty thousand dollars
and you'll learn how to heal
what better thing is that
I love you guys