right now live on facebook live on
youtube now on tic tac live on clubhouse
happy to be here heavy metal detox
smoothie medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie
because everybody has toxic heavy metals
in them you got depression you got
anxiety
depersonalization bipolar
motion motions are all over the place
but don't know why i mean just all over
the place
right and it's just more than that
sadness different types of anxiety
different types of sadness
and then if you've got skin conditions
vitiligo
eczema psoriasis you got the toxic heavy
metals good to see you guys coming on
here
um heavy metal detox smoothie is what
i'm making
i'm going to juice some celery too you
guys do in the morning cleanse medical
media morning cleanse
really exciting time because so many
people are doing it good to see you guys
so this book right here is helping to
save so many more people good morning
getting your lives back getting your
health back this book is powerful
seaweed hero good to see you guys we're
live on tick tock facebook youtube
clubhouse just so you guys know when you
come on here
this is on sale on amazon.com u.s 1699
51 off i'm going to cover some of the
other different cleanses the 369
advanced
cleanse a 369 original cleanse
heavy metal detox cleanse so exciting
the anti-bug
cleanse and you guys next month in july
we're going to do the anti cleanse
challenge so i'm really pumped up about
that so you guys want to
keep that on the radar you might want to
grab a copy of the book so that
when we do that anti-bug cleanse
challenge in july that you're prepared
and so amazon has a sale on this book
check it out try to get at the library
for free if you need to too
there's an option doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie talking about why it's so
important anybody dealing with anxiety
and depression this big one right now so
many people
have it so many people are dealing with
it
so i want to make some stuff good to see
you guys coming on tick tock
good to see you so loving these lives on
tick tock incredible incredible
so happy so what can i do for a bloated
stomach that is swollen i look 20 months
pregnant i can't take it please help
so i want you to be your own detective
is one thing i always tell you guys
right
the details matter and this this this
really kind of brings up a whole thing
right here it's like
it's not black or white there's
50 shades of details in between
and when we want to heal or get to that
finish line of healing
we've got to know those details steve
hill's matter that's where it matters
i noticed on the health scene out there
the details don't matter
it's all black or white you're either
vegan or you're animal protein black or
white
vegan or animal protein you know you do
collagen or you don't do collagen black
or white
right it's just it's it's everything's
everything's just black or white out
there
and but yet everything is still under
the whole umbrella of
autoimmune out there your body's
attacking itself it's black or white
you get an autoimmune diagnosis it's
your body it's attacking itself that's
what science research says in
alternative medicine conventional
medicine it's black or white
everything's just black or white so you
just you're trapped in that in in
medical medium land
in medical medium land when you leave
the colt system
when you leave the science research colt
system and you leave the colt system and
all the alternative therapies you leave
like when you leave the cold related
system that's out there and then you
land in medical medium land right where
you got the sensible information things
make sense
details matter it's not black and white
anymore
it's not like you're vegan or you animal
protein and that's it
it's like you vegan okay okay all good
you animal protein okay all good all set
no it doesn't work like that it doesn't
in order to heal
you got to know all these details man
you got to know these details austin
good to see you joe
good to see you right you got some
bloating and you feel like you're 20
months pregnant
and you go out there they're gonna be
shoving all kinds of stuff in you
apple cider vinegar try that for your
bloating try this for your bloating try
this for your bloating and it's
in the details matter like what to stay
away from what to what to take care of
yourself how to take care of yourself
what to do rebuilding hydrochloric acid
is a big part of bloating
okay and cleanse the heal talks about
that so
if you're somebody that's got a question
like hey i'm bloating what do i do
the answers are here that's a great
place to start and it's on sale 16.99
on amazon.com us check it out wyla green
good to see you
so glad you're on here
making the heavy metal detox smoothie
we're covering some good information
too gonna talk about anxiety depression
lorena good to see you too
okay what you see right here is a leafy
green you guys on tick tock can you see
that
and that's a leafy green that's cilantro
details matter
when do you have any help on long covet
if you look at this book right here
there's a whole section on that just so
you know
and long cove it actually stems from
medical medium that's where it's first
published and that's where it originates
from meaning the concept
of long covers actually comes from the
reactivated epstein-barr
that is actually in the medical medium
book right here
new edition though make sure it's the
new edition right there right
so healing
takes more than the whole black or white
thing you're just
not gonna heal if we see everything like
that
you can't it's just not gonna happen you
might be able to manage something for a
little while
you might be able to stay in the game
for a little while if you're not so sick
but if we try to do the whole black or
white thing
it's black and white it's either black
or white we're just gonna get in trouble
because it takes more than that
cilantro's
not an answer details though
matter you guys lots of cilantro
as a leafy green changes
everything simple as that
margaret valentine good to see you
thanks for coming on
and just simple as that you guys if
that's all you take from here if that's
all you take
cilantro eat more of it you just moved
yourself forward
boom you moved yourself forward right
there right there
i'm just saying it matters it matters
that simple detail
okay another detail
bananas are good for you
here's incredible detail they can help
you with gastroparesis they can help you
with intestinal conditions crohn's
colitis
they can help you recover from serious
digestive trouble
digestive problems details ready
don't eat them green but guess what an
alternative medicine out there
they're teaching you how to eat a green
banana now you just peel a green banana
and you throw it in your protein shake
you throw a green banana in there
right green banana powder or whatever
and they just want you doing the green
banana thing
epic disaster epic
disaster on the intestinal tract for
someone who's struggling
the details matter and here's another
detail
so critical you guys check this out just
you guys just pick if this is all you're
taking from today
it's that worth it you don't eat them
over
ripe this is getting there that's
getting there
that's borderline but you'll hear out
there an alternative medicine world
right
you'll hear wait till they really get
nice and you know right there's there's
a whole thought process you got
you don't you want to make sure they're
really brown you don't want them brown
you want them in between right you want
them in between
there's a certain stage is a good time
for to eat a banana
it's important these details matter but
eating green bananas is not a good
good thing it's not a good thing
okay chronic fatigue syndrome uh build
meal
on tick tock chronic fatigue syndrome so
cleanse a heal there's a section in
there now let's just go over
we'll go over chronic fatigue syndrome
for a second this is important so when
you go back
inside this book you'll find cfs is what
you'll find okay
and i'm just cutting through the back of
this book to look for cfs right now
this is an important topic right here
because
so many people have chronic fatigue
syndrome and they're suffering within
it's like where do you go
what do you do and the details matter so
when you come in here and you look for
chronic fatigue syndrome
and you find it in the back of the book
because that's where it is it's in
cleanse the heel
you'll see supplements and dosages you
might be somebody that got a diagnosis
an autoimmune diagnosis maybe you've got
lupus maybe you've got fibro
maybe you've got some other diagnosis of
some type of autoimmune diagnosis just
know you can go in here and find the
autoimmune section
and when you find the autoimmune section
you're right there you've got
answers you've got a direction like if
you go through the back here here's lyme
disease right here
and here's another thing too a lot of
people who get cfs
diagnose diagnosis of chronic fatigue
syndrome
they end up with a lyme diagnosis most
of them end with lyme diagnosis
and then you look here you'll see in
lyme disease section right here
you'll see all the different supplements
all the different dosages
so important so chronic fatigue syndrome
is caused by epstein-barr so when
someone's dealing with
chronic cfs chronic fatigue syndrome and
it's
chronic tiredness right they can't
function it's
neurological fatigue details matter
it's not black and white you're tired
it's cfs
black or white no it's neurological
fatigue
because of the nervous system being
burdened by something
all these details matter you see how it
works you guys
and here it is here the cfs section
right here
so uh mecfs right
it's also called other things too
because they rename it every decade they
never give you an
answer to why anybody has cfs nobody
ever learns
why they're sick with cfs right but they
rename it every 10 years
for no reason okay so
in the chronic fatigue syndrome section
you'll see cat's claw being really
important the reason why is because when
you read this
true cause of chronic fatigue syndrome
any of the over
60 varieties of epstein-barr virus
ready it's not black or white
details matter over 60 varieties of
epsilon bar virus that means
people have different varieties
different varieties different strains so
important right there
ready accompanied by toxic
heavy metals and we're doing the heavy
metal detox movie
so we're going to do the heavy metal
detox moving you guys on tick tock i got
this wrapped up right here so you can
see it over here right
okay toxic heavy metals such as mercury
and aluminum can create this condition
that i call neurological fatigue so if
you hear that term out there it
originates from medical medium
information now doctors are using it
they call it neurological fatigue
there's no scientific study with that it
comes from medical medium
which is far more pronounced in limiting
than simply being tired that's
neurological fatigue
here's another thing details matter my
god
a high fat high protein diet accelerates
the condition if you're dealing with cfs
any kind of chronic fatigue syndrome
no matter what diagnosis you have
whether it's lyme disease or something
else
seaweed hero says my dad had his best
friend
pass away two months ago from lung
cancer
then his sister passed away last month
now his dog
could die this week it's been a rough
year for my my
dear old dad i'm so sorry seaweed here
it breaks my heart
you know it breaks my heart seriously
and thank you for being
uh such an incredible person too you're
always giving a song lyrics all the time
everybody's always into the song lyrics
you always put down for everybody all
the inspirational song lyrics
they got depth and meaning and you're
just such a me
such a meaningful human being really
truly
so when it comes down to
having that chronic fatigue syndrome now
it's about well it's about epstein-barr
virus
it's about toxic heavy metals so what do
we do you got to kill the virus
that's details matter you got to kill
the virus all of this
counts so now you're dealing with a
virus
so you got autoimmune we're dealing with
a virus you guys
you guys if you want to know this
powerful information i mean it's in this
book
it's on sale john sale 51
off amazon.com us i mean incredible
jackie jackie saunders says i was
bloated
and looked 20 months pregnant took
18 months to clear details do matter
it takes time and commitment keep your
faith it's so important
thank you for being here jackie it's so
awesome it's so awesome
so we got to get rid of the toxic heavy
metals you guys
we gotta kill the bugs that are in us if
we got a problem
right and here's that detail that i read
here and the true causes
of cfs it says a high fat high protein
diet
accelerates the condition
so wow so it's those little details so
we have to figure out
what's in your book medical medium
that's different than cleanse the heel
it's a lot honestly both books just so
incredible both books okay
they're two completely different books
this book's
got so many different cleanses in here
right supplements and dosages to over
200 symptoms and conditions the other
book
has a cleanse a powerful cleanse it's
brought people's lives back
to the other book though has meditations
in there
that's one thing right there powerful
powerful meditations to heal the soul
it has the story of how it how i started
out
you know with medical medium the gift
and hearing spirit of compassion
and it goes into depth about adrenal
fatigue hypothyroidism hyperthyroidism
chronic fatigue syndrome and
fibromyalgia so that's that's what's
incredible about medical medium book one
also medical medium book one covers long
covet
too so the whole long covet and that's
where it originates from
so if you hear about reactivated
epstein-barr being behind lancovet
that's what this
is it comes from here it doesn't come
from a podcast doctor
it doesn't come from a study it comes
from this book published here first and
then they take the information from here
a lot of people in the health movement
they take the books
take the info out of it or they take it
from the live they watch the lives it
also covers menopause
pm pms lupus ebv
chronic fatigue syndrome like i said and
there's just some of the stuff that
that book's packed ptsd depression
whole chapter on depression funds to
heal
it's a whole other level of incredible
incredible information
so so we're talking about cfs a little
bit so many people are dealing with it
right now
and it also comes with the whole thing
work exactly the
aftermath of the plague people are up
against clency heal is a
trouble shooter that's a trouble shooter
book right there
and you guys should check it out right
there so says cat's claw right here
in the cfs cask law
is anti-viral so giving you guys a
little lesson that's
so critical so imperative and valuable
it's invaluable right so you got the
cat's claw right there right also it
says barley grass juice powder
but we're making the medical medium
heavy metal detail smoothie
and then you got the spirulina it says
in here it says the barley grass juice
powder in here too
so that's in here
um it goes glutathione right there and
that's another one the stuff that i use
you guys because i'm always asked that
and i got to kind of
catch it ahead of time on that because i
know i'm going to be asked
because it always happens i get dm's
non-stop about it so it's of emergency v
isn't victor i
am as in mary e-r-g-y bemidji.com that's
the
supplements that i actually use i'm not
sponsored on tick tock health with liz
book is better than gold hey liz i'm
honored
thank you uh means the world okay
and i really appreciate it i really do
so all these little things matter
they truly do when it comes down to
getting chronic fatigue syndrome better
here's a critical tip maybe you're
somebody with
neurological line maybe you're somebody
with lupus by bro
r.a maybe there's just somebody with an
autoimmune diagnosis i'm not even
talking about the moment but it's under
autoimmune
which the book covers but here's a
critical detail
don't get bled to death don't lose your
immune system
you go to the doctors talk about
getting half vials of blood taken
protect yourself because they remove
your immune system
and then all the conditions get worse on
everybody a month later
somebody's worse millions of people are
worse with their chronic autoimmune and
chronic conditions they got a podcast
episode medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast it's called blood droplet
leading and vampirism
and it's the system the medical system
is drawing too much blood out of
everybody
you can ask for half files quarter vials
you can ask for smaller
amounts and then go in again at another
time and not
lose your immune system which then you
get in trouble because here's how it
works
this details cell lifesaver lifesaver
you get too much blood taken you lose
your immune system
and the virus that's giving you sickness
the whole reason why you're in the
doctor's office to begin with
getting your blood taken even though the
doctor doesn't know you're viral
the whole reason why you're in there
sick is because
of the virus and when your immune system
gets removed constantly
through removing your white cow by
getting too much blood
your viruses get stronger and you're
sicker
and sicker and sicker this is why so
many people lyme disease have lost their
lives
many have died from getting 20 vials of
blood
15 vials of blood 10 vials of blood
every two weeks 30 40 vials of blood
okay and because the neurological lyme
was a virus
right which you can learn about in the
medical medium books
okay and
you can listen to the love blood draw um
episode on all the details
and then we get in trouble darcy lee
that podcast is amazing
thanks medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
my job is to protect you guys
that's my job i wake up in the morning
and it's to protect you guys we're
talking about anxiety depression too
that's a big one the personalization
bipolar anything emotional to we're
talking about
we're doing the heavy metal detox movie
because we got to get metals out
check out this detail okay the metals
end up in the brain
they dampen the electrical impulse field
neurons weaken and we get severely
depressed severely depressed and
getting metals out is critical
it's critical so important let's work on
a heavy metal defect smoothie we're
going to juice some celery too
so here we are let's get this over here
there's a heavy metal detox cleanse and
cleanse the heel
okay first part of
cleanse the heel check it out heavy
metal detox cleanse so
all this counts i mean your health
matters right
just it does protecting your health
matters
my job is to be that health protector
nancy says told a friend about your
books
she got it from the library and texted
me yesterday all right
and said it is fascinating she also
wanted to know which juicer i'm using
and i told her it's the omega
the omega juicer yep mm-900 hds
that's what i'm gonna use to juice in a
little bit too yeah can you do oat milk
in the heavy metal detox smoothie nope
can't do a milk in a heavy metal detox
smoothie gotta have it fat free
has to be fat free let's get some wild
blueberries so let's talk about what
goes in here
right there got some wild blueberries in
there
did it right there right two cups wild
blueberries
right i'm not against you getting a
blood test
that's not it go to your doctor learn
how to protect yourself i'm not saying
don't get a blood test
just got to do it right that detail
matters greatly okay and listen to the
podcast medical mean podcast at apple
podcast the blood draw episode truly
listen to it you really should
let's put two bananas in here
let's do two bananas banana banana this
is free powerful information
i get it i get it everybody tells me the
same thing over and over again
everybody you know people people try to
reach me
uh professionals in the world of
marketing you're the big medical medium
why do you give everything away from for
free no one appreciates it
if it's for free that's what they say no
one appreciates it you have to charge
for it and then they appreciate it
that's what all the
spiritual gurus do they charge for
everything programs and retreats and
meditations
then they appreciated everybody you know
what don't don't insult my people
they appreciate it the medical medium
community appreciates everything for
free
valuable information like this you just
don't insult them
by saying that they do appreciate it
they're not the other people out there
in the world that need that for some
reason
this pamela says are cilantro and
parsley
equal for cleansing ability they're not
but partially
if you got to use it use it okay i'm
okay with that
parsley's healing healing on on its own
parsley is really powerfully healing
it's a great
medical medium tool we'll talk about
that another time too
healthy list says appreciate it so much
just i
you know what i know that's i totally
know in the sense where you get it you
get why it's free
and and you do appreciate it and and i
appreciate you like you can't even
believe
it's not a substitute for cilantro
parsley
it's not a substitute it's not
but you can use it and it's helpful it
is helpful right
it is one of the things that i wanted to
talk to you guys about have you taken
pharmaceuticals before are you stuck
taking pharmaceuticals now
right you're taking antibiotics in your
time have you taken any kind of
pharmaceutical in your time
this is an important piece of
information if you're wondering why
should i do the heavy metal detox
smoothie
why should i do it if you've been doing
pharmaceuticals
if it's something that's been in your
life
where you have to do the pharmaceuticals
for anxiety depression
you got to use them for high blood
pressure you got to use them for
cholesterol whatever it is that's
happened in your life you got to use
thyroid medications
whatever happened in your life that is
warranted
having to use pharmaceuticals you have
to realize
inside pharmaceuticals are toxic heavy
metals
that's what's inside pharmaceuticals
lots of toxic heavy metals aluminum is a
big one in pharmaceuticals
lots of aluminum in pharmaceuticals look
at a fluoride treatment
in the dentist office that's a
pharmaceutical based fluoride treatment
that's what those are
pharmaceutical all that fluoride right
all that aluminum byproduct
pills drugs of all kinds all have metals
every single drug cold medicine
every single pharmaceutical
has a toxic heavy metal in it it doesn't
mean stop taking your pharmaceuticals it
means
hey maybe we can do the heavy metal
detox smoothie anya says can you take
heavy metal detox when you're pregnant
there's nothing in a heavy metal detox
smoothie can't use while pregnant i tell
doctors that all the time so doctors ask
me that all the time
there's nothing in there cilantro
a little seaweed bananas
wild blueberries spirulina barley
rashi's powder
it's all just gentle but what happens is
when you work it together
it just it cleans out metals holds on to
it
takes it out of the body you ask your
doctor what's right for you what i would
do is
tell your doctor you want to do the
heavy metal detox movie so if you're
pregnant ask your doctor can i take the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie
see what your doctor says listen to your
doctor if your doctor wants you on the
heavy metal detox smoothie
then do it if your doctor doesn't want
you on the heavy metal detox smoothie
then don't do
it anyway one thing that happens is that
in the book just so you know this
explains it in detail for the pregnancy
stuff like what do's and don'ts and
stuff like that so honestly
amazon.com us 16.99 take advantage of
the 51
off deal take advantage or go to the
library for free but take advantage
either way
it's here it's a medical textbook you
won't be disappointed with that book
you won't you guys why get the metals
out
why get the metals out because we've
taken all the pharmaceuticals
the cold medicines the antibiotics the
birth control
right how many how many women are on
okay we've all taken the pharmaceuticals
that's a big place where the toxic heavy
metals come from
right there because i know what happens
sometimes i talk about get the metals
out get the metals out everybody's eyes
glaze over like what
there's no metals i don't see any metals
there's i'm not eating any metals the
hell is he talking about
there's no i can't see metals the doctor
doesn't see metals inside of me
no one sees any metals what do you mean
what what's going on that's where the
smoke and mirrors the tricks are right
there
and the details matter so where are your
toxic heavy metals coming from like
where are they coming from anyway
did you ever breathe in a little bit of
this
so breathing a little bit a little bit
of this clones perfumes
did you ever breathe in some filled with
metals
filled with metals like cranked
cranked aluminum cans do you ever
breathe in any kind of insecticide or
anything
like that do you ever have any dental
work done
you have any dental work done anything
at all in the dental work field
boom insect killer how many people are
like killed the spider in the house kill
the
kill the spider in the house air
fresheners scented
candles that's where the metals are too
you're breathing in some scented candles
boom
you just breathe in lots of metals the
pharmaceuticals are a big one
all pharmaceuticals the metals are
relentless
do you ever buy a new shirt a new
piece of clothing they're laced with
fungicides
and you know what's really annoying now
you buy a new piece of
clothing right you guys a new piece of
clothing
and you know what happens brand new
piece of clothing
it's not only laced with a fungicide but
it's laced with air freshener from the
factories or where they're making the
stuff or where they're boxing the stuff
so
there's there's air fresheners in
everything now they're contaminating all
the clothes
you gotta wash them yeah you just gotta
wash them
i talk about the whole thing with
scented candles fungicides perfumes
clones and cleanse the heel
critical place to read about it to you
guys
so why do they put so on tick tock why
do they put
metals in there
why do they do a lot of things to ruin
the lives of millions and millions of
people
why why does science research turn their
back
on children with conditions that are so
debilitating when
they don't even study them why do they
do a lot of things why are homeless
homeless or why are homeless starving
when we're throwing away billions of
tons of food from every single grocery
store that's actually good to eat
and we throw it away each week and it's
a law you are not allowed to
be a grocery store and take two tons of
food that you're about to throw out that
have back dates on them and everything
you're not allowed to take it to the
homeless and save all these lives
why are children in tent city and you
can't feed them
because you have to go through some
demented system to feed them
right how come how come sunscreen
is so toxic and scented scented
and toxic like you don't have to have
toxic scented sunscreen but they do it
anyway right
like why do these things that why are
chemtrails being dumped on us
like in the chemtrail episode did you
guys ever listen to that chemtrail
episode
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
the uncensored version
have you listened to that why are they
killing all our birds
what you know thousands of birds fall
out of the sky and just die in streets
or fields all around the world
and die in mountains where you don't
even see them as they're flying because
they run into a chemtrail
and they die and they fall they fall
down to the ground thousands of birds
millions of birds we're not gonna have
birds down the road
why are they doing that i'll tell you
what darkness and
evil darkness and evil that's it and
there's a war of darkness and light
there's a war out there of darkness and
light there's evil
on the planet and that's what they do
they put terrible things in
pharmaceuticals they put terrible things
in
our water systems they put terrible
things it's just there's dark
evil right and light
right okay so
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie
we're talking about the medical media
morning cleanse too i hope you guys are
still doing it continue it make it a
part of your life so you can heal
okay you guys gotta fight for the
fragrance thing you gotta fight for
knocking it out someday
i mean you buy clothes complain when it
comes with fragrances on it right
packages come load of fragrances
complain
when you know you're you're going into
your dentist office and they got the
plug-ins and they're just stoking
everybody out complain right
it's like because what they did the
chemical companies
they don't think you're ever going to
complain the chemical companies
produce all this stuff for fragrances
just so you know
to kill us to kill us
you better believe it the stuff isn't
even even
isn't even like safe they just make a
chemical and they put it out that
that that next month they just make a
deadly chemical put it out the next
month
pop it in something like a centi candle
or something else
and then the byproduct of all those
chemicals goes into the planes
to go up in the sky and be dumped on you
so they can get rid of it because you're
not allowed to dump it in the water
system anymore
complain to others about the perfumes
colognes because just poisoning your
kids
poisoning your pets that's just what
they do
poison your family friends they may not
know it
but teach them fun fun
fun cilantro i just put in there
incredible detail if you do more
cilantro
you get more healing done it's a leafy
green highly
mineralized but also takes out toxic
heavy metals
it's got some cilantro in there
got two bananas in there too and let's
do some orange
cilantro is an herb but you can use it
as a leafy green that's medical medium
information you could eat it as a leafy
green when i was first
many years ago as as a child practically
when i was first teaching people about
all this stuff
i'd be like cilantro is a leafy green
and they're like what iceberg lettuce
look you didn't hear me cilantro is
leafy green iceberg
lettuce there was an iceberg lettuce
zombie problem in the health movement
every single you you guys don't even
know like the plant-based doctors that
are out there now that seem to be on
everything like meaning like to be hip
on everything
it seems and all that they were in
iceberg lettuce just just 12 years ago
10 years ago
years ago it was like they didn't even
know about a leafy real green right
and then when i blew up the kale thing
when i exploded the kale thing
because that's medical medium that
started the whole kale movement which
turned into
chips turning to kill everything right
that was me lecturing about kale
teaching about kale that was
talking to tens of thousands of people
about kale so when i
when i started the whole kale movement
of getting that out there
it got into the system where all of a
sudden then the vegan doctors and other
people were like okay
kale okay kale kale right before that
they're just like
well iceberg lettuce iceberg lettuce
iceberg lettuce it was like it was
unbelievable
um jesse knows a lot of products out
there that say they're they're natural
fragrances they're they're chemical
based they're chemical toxic
chemicals michelle l good to see you on
tick-tock great to see you
um such a pillar in the community you're
always helping people out it's
incredible what you do
really all right got some cilantro there
we got the bananas we've got the
wow blueberries throwing orange in there
let's squeeze it in
nice orange right here i love the smell
of oranges
mandy can we use dates in heavy metal
detox you can
you can okay it's the only dried fruit
i'd say would be okay
right but try to keep the dried fruits
out because dates aren't really fresh
dear appleman good to see you i went to
the kale festival once
you think they thanked anthony william
the kale festival
i think they thanked anthony william for
breaking his behind
on getting that whole kale thing out
there it's like just like we got the
celery juice thing out there
you think they think aw for the kale
you know no of course not
oh man there's some good people in the
world thank god that there's a lot of
bad people in the world
that there is there is i know there's a
big thing in the spiritual movement no
one's bad everybody's great hitler was a
good person are you kidding me
that's psycho that's so psycho that
whole that spiritual
that spiritual brainwashing that's going
on with that one there's no bad people
in the world and hitler was actually a
good guy he just was misdirected or
misguided are you kidding me
my god oh my god it was genocide there's
no bad people in the world meanwhile we
wiped out the native americans they
barely exist on the planet
they live in squalor and then we throw
them a bone once in a while and try to
publicize it like we've taken care of
the native americans when we've on
them for
for centuries we just destroyed the
native american culture
no one even talks about it
i mean look what happens even when all
the rights come up
everybody's fighting for rights for
diversity still they just don't no one
wants to even
like recognize the native americans it's
like oh no those are those crazy native
americans over there
jumping around right there yeah no we
don't we don't focus on those at all
meanwhile we've genocided them to death
it's just unbelievable
well i got to put the spirit lean in
here in the barley grass juice powder
you tell me if the world is like got it
all right
or something anyway the point i'm saying
is
it's come kind of reason why i talk
about stuff like that is it comes down
to this
if we don't have control over a lot
around us but we got control into what
got into us and if it got into us in a
way because
of not good stuff out there okay
i just put some spirit leaving here so
what it's about is empowerment
you can dump some chemtrails but guess
what that stuff that's being dumped on
me i'm going to get out of my
body you can't rule
my life that's what real empowerment is
real empowerment is is knowing what's
going on but being able to do something
about it
because i can make the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie
i could protect myself from a chemtrail
i don't know what you're doing over
there
but i'm gonna make sure i'm empowered
and i can actually take care of myself
so when toxic heavy metals get into us
through all these different ways that i
was talking about right because the
reason why we went down that
place of yeah yeah
the reason why we went down to that
place right
of fragrances and metals being in
fluoride treatments
metals coming out of the sky right and
saying a chemtrail
metals in all kinds of different avenues
that were exposed to
metals and pharmaceuticals right the
pharmaceuticals and metals
it's like metals don't have to be in
pharmaceuticals for some reason
somebody thinks it's a good idea who's
not looking out for everybody's best
interest right
so the reason why i'm talking about all
that is because hey
we could do something about it you're
not gonna take you're not gonna
and you're not gonna disempower me
because i'm gonna get the medals out
and i'm gonna get cleaned up and that's
the key
right there anyway spirulina is
is really an incredible weapon against
all of this toxicity
i love it for for being a weapon against
radiation exposure
i love it being a weapon against the
fragrances and the air fresheners
and all of that okay so that's what i
love these tools so i just put in a
teaspoon in there right there that's the
vimergy spirulina visa vs victor i
m e r g y dot com it's the best one out
there
by far hands down there's no better one
than that
so i'm going to put in the barley grass
juice powder that's what i'm doing now
now what you're going to find out there
is corella
everybody's going to be like corella
that's what you use right everybody's
going to be
well corella doesn't work these details
are critical and i talk about that and
cleanse the heels so
get a copy when you can right 51 off at
amazon
but get a copy when you can learn about
why corella's not the way to go
that means books talk about that these
are capsules i'm just opening the
capsules
putting in the smoothie because i ran
out of the powder
i got to order the powder right
so i'm putting some capsules in there
all right so we got that
this is one critical detail right here
so if you want to get metals out it's
got to be a spirulina
a high quality one is best but it's got
to be a spirulina
corella will not get the metals out and
this is
where the whole thing happens again
where
the details do matter because people
don't realize that
so important right another detail is i
don't use the
pacific spirulina anymore so any
spirulina that's derived
grown on you know on the west in the
west
any pacific okay the ocean's got too
dirty in the last few years so i stopped
quite a ways back it just got too dirty
it's got even dirtier than ever before
it's at a point now where i just can't
even trust anything like that
so so this is the best one is november
just letting you know
all these things count we got the orange
in there we got the wild blueberries
let's grind this up
oh put a little dulce in there yep
atlantic dolce
important let's give it a little
having fun with the blender
what question mark spirulina yes
okay we're good
we are blended up nicely
indeed we are medical medium heavy metal
detox smoothie
so what i like about the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie it's one of
the
it's like a prayer answered
for anxiety depression
there are people that were in such a
deep dark space with their depression
they didn't want to be depressed they
didn't want to be sad
they didn't want depression right but
they had
such a systemic deep depression inside
of them
the kind that people only understand who
have been there who who have been in
that zone of depression
not a depression where something tragic
happens
and you're you're trying to move past it
and it could take years and you're
you're just you're emotionally injured
through it you know
the depression where and you can have
both you can have a depression from
toxic heavy metals
and that depression too of course right
but with the kind of depression where
people are depressed they don't want to
be
depressed and they're just curled up in
their bed they can't move forward their
life they feel like they can't get they
can't
push through they're just living with
the depression every minute
it's like it's like a cloud over their
eyes
they can't see even though they're
looking even though they can see but
they feel like they can't see anything
they're just they're just living with
that depression to such an extent
and it's a cover depression in here okay
and cleanse the heel i cover it in the
other book too medical meme new edition
but this is the medical media morning
cleanse that we've been doing heavy
metal detox cleanse
so important heavy metal detox smoothie
has freed so many people you guys
of that clinical deep dark depression
and that that means everything for
someone who's going through that
and when it comes down to to anxiety it
does that too so what's
happening with the depression and the
anxiety let's cover that real quick
let's do that i'm excited about this
so actually we'll cover it this way here
so when it comes down to depression
toxic heavy metals they get into the
brain
that alone can create depression because
your neurotransmitters are being
affected and your neurons are being
saturated by toxic heavy metals aluminum
mercury
lead cadmium copper copper is a big one
for everybody
and people get copper in their brain and
it causes this problem so it's important
and when the brain gets saturated with
metals
okay and it's not detectable by
equipment technology today it's not
detectable by medical you know tests
the doctor can't detect it here's the
problem with toxic heavy metals they go
deep in organs and then there's not
enough
of that toxic heavy metal going through
the bloodstream for the doctor to
identify unless it's a fresh exposure
and then they can identify it if they
look right
but a deep exposure is something where
the metals go deep inside the brain
deep inside the liver deep inside their
body
okay so when it comes down to depression
and anxiety metals play a huge role
because they
oxidize they start to break down so the
metals start to break down and oxidize
and when a metal breaks down and
oxidizes it travels
so instead of being say here
right left hemisphere somewhere closer
to the frontal lobe instead of being
there
that the metal starts to travel because
it oxidized and it
out gassed and it what it did was it
exploded
metals tend to rust and explode
i hate when that happens that's why
we're
live okay the head of my dummy just hit
the floor
all right so when those metals lean
those metals
they oxidize and they rust they travel
it's byproduct caused by it so let's go
into that a little bit like why are they
doing that in people like why
are metals here we go you guys why are
metals
oxidizing why are they moving why are
they running off
ashley kevin i know it's funny right why
are they
why do they do that because of acids
and oxidative fats so we're told to eat
fats eat fats eat fats and what you're
noticing is medical medium warning
cleanse
medium heavy metal detox smoothie
doesn't have any fat in it
so there's no almonds there's no almond
butter there's no peanut butter
in that smoothie there's no cacao
in that smoothie so the heavy metal
detox
smoothie doesn't have the fat in it
because it's all that high fat diet
everybody's up against
24 7 that's oxidating
the metals and making them hard to even
remove
or clean out so the medical meeting
warning cleanse
is a great way to do some metal removal
that's what it is to remove your metals
in the morning and when you do the heavy
metal detox smoothie
you're one smoothie past your depression
you're one smoothie past your anxiety
you're one smoothie past your bipolar
your depersonalization your sadness
that's unexplainable
your memory loss
your brain fog how many guys have dealt
with brain fog
how many of you guys out there have
dealt with the brain fog just curious
as i know so many of you have dealt with
the brain fog big time
big time i know so many of you guys have
right ptsd ptsd can
completely worsen when the metals are
there
i talk about that in the medical mean
books ptsd can worsen
the experiences that create ptsd can
worsen if metals
are adjacent to the problem in the brain
very important to know you know so you
want the metals out
right the brain fog is a big one for
people so brain fog yeah you had it oh
my god yes you too
oh whoa you two on tick tock wow
brain fog and ptsd here whoa on tick
tock
whoa yeah lots of brain fog yes you too
so you guys a lot of you guys have dealt
with the brain fog then well
a big part of the brain fog is toxic
heavy metals that's a part of the brain
fog it's not the complete picture
some brain fog cases can be all toxic
heavy metals but some can be low grade
viral
issues with the metals and that's why
you need to cleanse the heel book to
actually learn
it's so important to know so important
enough
the brain fog is a big one for a lot of
people totally
i totally get it so let's move that over
you guys we're live right now facebook
we're live on
youtube where else we're live on
clubhouse live on tick tock right
okay compassionate goddess sarah i was
fired from a job before because of brain
fog
before i found you sarah just know that
i i really feel for you on that one
that's awful
to like to be fired for a job you know
and you're probably
a brilliant unbelievable amazing worker
person
highly intelligent and everything and
the brain fog can just it just
people just don't understand they don't
thank you for being here i'm so glad
you're getting better
so glad the heavy metal detox smoothie
is best
before you start doing fats it's best in
the morning
that's the best time to actually use it
just so you know
does the heavy metal detox have to be
done in the morning it is best then but
you can do it at other times in a day if
you really want to
you can you can break the rules a little
bit if you have to
there's room for it medical medium
information is about the details and all
the details matter if you want to go all
the way but for best results if you want
to go all the way but it doesn't mean
you're not going to get some results if
you do the heavy metal detox smoothie
some other time or
if it was after fats at a certain meal
or whatever it is it's it's okay
if you have to bend the rules russell
i was also fired for general performance
issues aka brain fog oh my god
oh my god really you know it's just
it's it's so hard it's so hard okay
it's just so hard i mean honestly
it breaks my heart seriously because i
know how much goes into all of that it's
not so simple
if you went through a lot with that all
of it the brain fog and everything
[Music]
people don't know what it's like to have
brain fog unless they've been in
somebody's shoes with brain fog
people don't know what it's like they
don't know
you you gotta experience it man you
gotta experience it
i'll tell you experience it
then you know what's up it's really
really hard on people that brain
toxic heavy metals play a role in that
brain fog
they play well sometimes they play the
complete role
in that brain fog okay sometimes they
they play the complete role
right medical medium info
is about getting results getting people
better
and it's not all talk i notice in the
health movement
that's what people are always saying out
there now
but it's all talk
because in order to help someone heal
and get them better
you to protect them you got to give them
the info to protect them
you got to teach them about the blood
draw
you got to teach them about these things
that no one knows about in the industry
unless they get it here so many details
when you really learn the information
it's packed
chock full of nuts
[Music]
thanks you guys for coming on i see more
people coming on too chris good to see
you today
inside the medical medium cleanse the
heel book you guys is the mono eating
cleanse
that's inside the cleansing build book
so i'll talk about that a little bit the
369 original
369 simplified 369 advanced
really powerful cleanses inside that
booklet to heal
i hope you guys get the book take
advantage of the sale
hi anthony thanks for all these lives
you're welcome
you're welcome i want you guys to have
access
to the information i want you guys to be
able to heal take it
all the way all the way
amy tang says is the mono eating cleanse
safe for breastfeeding
if i was breastfeeding i would be doing
the moderating cleanse yes
ask your doctor with you know ask your
doctor what he thinks
what's right for you but i have a family
member
who's breastfeeding right now right
and um i made sure she was on the mono
eating cleanse because she's got
digestive trouble
anita says thank you for all your
knowledge thank you for being here
[Applause]
[Music]
it's not about a lack of calories the
motto eating cleanse is in a diet
a lack of calories like crunching your
calories down
[Music]
that's not what it is so
yeah it's not like you're starving your
baby or your body
of being able to build breast milk
that's not it you make sure you get the
calories in
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah if you want to be plant-based and
do that mono-eating cleanse
and be plant-based yeah you should do it
you should do it
[Music]
problem is in the plant-based movement
so much misinformation out there
[Applause]
and i noticed all through the years of
the plant-based movement no one
in the plant-based movement
[Music]
people that were elevated in their
position in the plant-based movement
knew why anybody was sick i mean okay
let's talk about fast foods and
processed foods but they still don't
know why anybody's sick
a plant-based movement as far as it ever
got for information was
if you eat junk food you're gonna get
heart disease
so the plant-based movement was all
about if you eat junk food and processed
foods
that if you eat all that fast food you
know i mean the plant-based movement was
all about fast food right
don't eat all the fast food and kill
yourself with all the junk fast food and
animal
products and animal grease that was as
far as the plant-based movement ever got
they didn't know why 20-year-olds were
on mattress island
not able to talk or walk they didn't
know why 25 year olds
would lose their jobs and careers or
they would they would get out of college
and get a job and then all of a sudden
have to go home and lay in bed
they didn't know why college girls and
college boys would kind of have to come
back
from school and stay at home with their
parents and live there for the next 10
years sick
they didn't know that the plant-based
movement just knew about fast food
greasy food
that's what they knew about so now
they're learning more
through medical medium through osmosis
which is medical medium information
getting all
out there plus i've taught a lot of the
plant-based doctors throughout the years
about the low-fat and other stuff so
that they've taken that information
further right
but because you know medical medium gets
its information from above
they always like to try to find some
kind of study that has nothing to do
with the information at all
but just has one word in there that's
similar and be like oh it came from that
no it came from medical medium because
there is no study on that
so anyway let's get a strainer and do
this
and then you can't get then all these
other people are misled and can't get
back to where the real information is
that they can heal that's the only
reason why i care about it
i never got into this as a child to be
known or anything
that's that's not the game that's the
bad game
i got into this to save lives right
and i was forced into it to save lives
and then i i then i had to make sure i
got comfortable with that
when i was really young i talked about
that in medical medium books right
that's your celery juice right here
but you got to be really in it to
protect people and make sure that you
really do get them better
i was working on people tens of
thousands of people for so many decades
and then i was working on all kinds of
professionals that were trying to make a
name for themselves in the plant-based
movement so they would talk to me
get all this information right about
heavy metals or about something
and then they would go out there and try
to make a name for themselves
so they could sell a product and become
famous right and
i sat back in my office while people
traveled around the world to come see me
in my office because i was known as the
bizarre symptoms guy
and that's how everybody got to know me
is i had an answer
when there were no answers and
you know it should be really about the
person suffering struggling
and knowing where the details come from
so they can heal all the way not take
tidbits to make yourself look big so you
can do some documentary somewhere
or some podcast and then not show people
the way and be like you know what
i'll never forget this one this one case
okay you guys
uh this young woman who was
23 years old right she lost her job
she she couldn't function she had severe
fatigue
she had the eye floaters tingles and
numbness she had the electrical shocks
right happening in her head where
electrical shocks would almost knock her
over
she had the jerks and the twitches and
the spasms she had the back pain neck
pain
she had the burning skin burning mouth
burning tongue right all that stuff
right and she went to every single
doctor every practitioner and she
finally found this
chiropractor this chiropractor
in l.a right she found him and the
chiropractor said
i'm using my intuitive ability and i
think you have epstein-barr
epstein barr and she was like oh my god
i got an answer for the first time
that epstein-barr is a virus
so what do i need to do and the
chiropractor kept on saying
i'm not sure try maybe this and you got
epstein-barr and she was like oh my god
i have an answer i have an answer
maybe i can function for the first time
in my life
right and every time she asked him for
more information
he said this chiropractor said i'm not
getting any i'm not getting
any intuitively i'm not getting anyone
anyway
this person this this woman
got into the lottery system and medical
medium when i was still seeing people
this is many years ago she got into the
lottery system
she was chosen in the lottery system and
she got an appointment with me
and she told me the story and i said
it's a chiropractor in a way is this
person's name this
and she goes yeah i go well that's a
client of mine
the chiropractor in l.a wanted to seem
like a big wig
knowing a part of the information
but not telling her where the
information came from and how she needed
to find medical medium to get all of it
she she was obviously an angel
got her to the direction of medical
media because the minute she got her
appointment with me and this is before i
publish books that
everybody can get a chance to heal he's
just you know and then she got an
appointment with me
she was able to heal and get all the
information and she couldn't
understand why this chiropractor would
hold back
and do this to her and so she contacted
the chiropractor and said
i'm talking to anthony william he's
giving me all the information about why
epstein-barr causes this why didn't you
tell me that's where you
that you actually knew him that you
actually saw him as a
as a as a client and he was just
he was it was ego thing right and
that's the problem that's just one out
of just i mean
that's just one example and it's sad to
me
so when the podcast doctor says yeah
there's metals that cause psoriasis but
won't link it back to the only source
that ever said that which is medical
medium how's anybody gonna get rid of
psoriasis but yet on the podcast they'll
look like a superstar people like what
what what
anyway we just made the heavy metal
detox smoothie i didn't do the lemon
water let's make that real quick
let's do a little recap okay so we'll
make the lemon water i'm going to do
lime water
almost lost that lime that thing went
flying forward whoa almost hit the
almost hit the screen so we're going to
do a little line right here
just a little lime water 16 to 32 ounces
of lime water you should be doing you
guys the medical medium morning cleanse
right every morning
flush out the liver of poisons and
toxins learn about it this
is on sale 1699 51 off at amazon.com us
take advantage of it
learn how to do the medical media
morning cleanse 16 to 32 ounces of lemon
lime water right there okay
there we go all right 16 to 32 ounces of
celery juice
right there okay right
heavy metal detox smoothie right there
okay
those options that's a real
powerhouse of a medical medium morning
cleanse
because it's medical medium morning
with a heavy metal detox
smoothie that's incredible right there
that's a window into getting to the
finish line
that's the window into getting to the
finish line man that's it
there's other options in the book that
go further okay you can get into the 369
advanced you can get into the 369
simplified
original you can get to the anti-bug
cleanse you can get into the mono eating
cleanses for digestive problems you can
get into the heavy metal detox cleanse
yep said anti-bug and you can get into
all the cleanses
and then you can get into the true
causes of the conditions
learn how to do supplementation right
like
learn how when you learn how to do it
dosages and supplements in here you are
getting the winning tickets
the winning tickets that's the bimmer
gb12 v isn't victor i
am ergy dot com it's the best stuff out
there
i'm not sponsored but the best stuff
there is
and that matters because you get a bad
b12
you're not getting to the finish line
this is what people
would come to me for there'd be a
waiting list
in the millions there'd be people like
waiting like waiting to talk to me as
the decades went by
and i could only talk to so many people
daily right and it turned out to be over
200 000 people
250 000 individuals one-on-one since
being young
all the way to when i pub published the
first medical meeting book
and in that process that was a fraction
of how many people were trying to reach
me
and if people knew years later i'd be
sitting here saying
here it is and they do know because they
do have the books
here it is and here's the dosages and
supplements
of what to do and how to do it what kind
knowing that well
this is the one to take not the bad one
like all these things matter
just so great it's great it's great it's
great
it really is you guys i'm going to ig
instagram gonna have some fun we're
gonna do some stuff health with liz i'm
turning the tick tock back
on right in a little bit because i'm
going to instagram in a little bit i'm
going to turn tick tock back on
and i'm turning clubhouse back on you
guys so i'm going to be on ig
yeah seeing you guys you guys are still
throwing some comments out
appreciate you guys very much i can't
wait
so yeah can you please talk about poor
eye contact
poor eye contact um in the sense if it's
poor eye contact in the sense where
it's exhausting to make eye contact
that's that's that kind of thing that's
this the
weakened central nervous system i've
helped out people through that and talk
to doctors about it
if it's if it's a an issue where it's
hard to make eye contact because
it's a struggle or you feel like you
can't
it's all in the nervous system it's all
about recovering that nervous system
learning how to do that one day at a
time
can chip away you can start a little bit
at a time you could start with some
celery juice if you really want
okay and you can start wherever you need
to start
all right and um but heavy metal detox
smoothie amazing with
for kids with autism adhd by the way
critical for that right medical media
mommy talked about that
with her child and and how the heavy
metal detox movie
helped with making eye contact for you
especially with children with autism
so important i mean really really this
is
invaluable information i love you guys
going to ig
heading off to instagram turning tick
tock back on i hope you guys will be
there
i'm really looking forward to it i love
you guys much okay
and i'll see you then