the episode
is released
the anxiety episode is released
they say it's all in your head
for years and years and years when
people suffered and struggled from
anxiety they've been told it's all in
their head
and we know that's not true
of course but that's what people are
told and in the end even now they're
told it's all in their head really you
got anxiety um
whoa uh really are you just you know you
got emotional problems is there just
something wrong with you why do you have
anxiety i mean the amount of stuff that
people go through the amount of hardship
they go through with this whole anxiety
thing is unbelievable i talk about all
the different symptoms so medical medium
podcasts at apple podcast
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
you don't want to miss
this anxiety episode it's like a
docu-series
style that's what it is podcast it's a
docu-series style it's not a throwaway
you don't want to miss this packed with
information honestly the link is in the
description
there's no way i can deliver
all the information that is in that
podcast episode there's no way i could
see i couldn't sit here for hours and
deliver
all that information
line for line in the anxiety episode at
medical meeting podcast apple podcast
line for line you guys is jammed packed
with information
jam packed david witchin hey man i'm
glad you're here um
everybody's coming on glad you guys are
here this is great i'm seeing familiar
faces
it's incredible link is in the
description right there you don't want
to miss this episode i'm just
being straight out about this you guys i
know
i delivered the uh the uh i mean an
incredible caffeine episode i know i
delivered the brain fog episode the b12
episode and these are amazing the apple
cider vinegar episode but i'm just
telling you right now the anxiety
episode that is like it's like no other
um that i've done
the whole bit you don't want to miss
this so you know they say it's all in
your head that's and that's the subtitle
of this episode it's a docu-series style
episode it's packed with information so
you can heal i'm going to talk about
some symptoms of anxiety that's what
we're going to do here for a little bit
we're going to cover that um kathy owen
says
hello anxiety is real yes it is and i'm
so sorry if you've gone through it
you'll listen to the podcast amazing
kathy you've got to check it out you can
hear the uncensored version at apple
podcast so medical medium podcast at
apple podcast that's the uncensored
version that's the one
that you want to hear okay that's the
platform you want to hear that is right
there i'm kathryn elizabeth good to see
you i'm glad you're here hi anthony
another mind-blowing episode neurons
having to take a different path in the
brain
that's what i talk about in the episode
that's one thing that's one thing in the
episode so much information so many
tools that you can apply
i mean
really and
i mean it's such an amazing amazing
episode that you guys have to listen to
you know and look to help anxiety i have
those meditations so listen to the
meditations too the brain meditation
the moon meditation by the way full moon
coming up our way full moons coming up
our way the moon meditation you guys
have to do the moon meditation during
the full moon for sure so medical media
podcast at apple podcast the link is in
the description you can hear the moon
meditation which will help with anxiety
freeze the bird meditation which will
help with anxiety too
and i'm glad you guys are on right now
um so you don't want to miss this
episode because it's packed with
information i talk about the tightness
in the chest okay
that you know the numbness and the arms
tightness in the chest then the the
whole feeling can't breathe the anxiety
the feeling of you can't sit still all
the different symptoms um coupled with
if you've been struggling with a symptom
or condition and then having anxiety how
people don't understand that and how
that works um
so i'm so glad you guys are on tonight
so glad and darlene says hi anthony
thanks for all your podcasts this
episode
is
mind-blowing it's mind-blowing so i hope
you guys catch this dr fonz here
medical doctor amazing amazing doctor
he's here uh
also it's it's incredible to have you
here so glad it's honored to have you
here you're a great man of medicine a
great man of wisdom and medicine it's so
great that you're here you know
you guys that this episode the link is
in the link is in description so you
know
this episode was one of these episodes
where i was like well how much
information can i deliver how much can i
do in here and i would i was like okay
let's just do
as much as we possibly can as much line
for line wow so much in there so much in
there
so it's so great to have you guys on
here right now so um
find out like we could do with this link
is in the description medical medium
podcast at apple podcast you don't want
to miss this one i see everybody's here
it's great familiar faces everywhere
it's so great that everybody's here um
so many it's free so that's the other
thing so people say well
you know um he's just pushing his
podcast what is he what is he selling
like uh are you kidding
uh medical medium information uh has
been free
since day one since day one going back
going back going back that's all i do
it's like free everything and this
podcast is a docu-series
podcast that's what it is really so you
gotta realize that the production and
everything in it it's not the same these
aren't throwaways like okay i'm gonna
start a podcast let me get a couple of
people let me get some guests on and you
kind of just shoot the crap and that
whole thing coffee talk coffee talk the
next next oh hey you come on what do you
got go next round next month's cattle
call cattle call and you know that's
great there's nothing wrong with that
but this
is these are answers this is life
changing this is about getting your life
back this is about rising out of the
ashes this is about healing this is
about saving lives and that's what
matters i mean no matter what
that's what matters robin s said
wonderful podcast i still have more
anxiety than i realize but but it isn't
debilitating anymore thank you and soc
for all your hard work incredible um so
glad you're here you know so if you've
been through emotional hardships
emotional hardships emotional struggles
emotional trials emotional difficult
times
i talk about what happens is a heating
up of the brain occurs
so a certain part of the brain the whole
brain gets heated up but a certain part
of the brain the emotional center of the
brain
gets heated up so anxiety is a physical
thing it's actually a physical physical
thing that's going on trisha marie's
here so good to see you
anxiety is a physical problem and that's
what people don't understand out there
like shake it off man like you got
anxiety no big deal like why don't you
go run on a treadmill and you'll be all
set and why don't you kind of you know
whatever it's not like that doesn't work
like that ashley's here at ashley
applesauce
incredible glad you're here tonight you
know today so it's like the bottom line
you guys is um
jamie says once i listen to your latest
podcast i can't even wait until the next
one well
i'm so glad that you know you guys are
listening to it it's this is a
life-changing
episode
and
i put so many tools in there and talk
about what they do and i talk about
triggers that's the other thing whoa
you guys i covered triggers like no
other in this i mean seriously
i
i trigger i i cover the triggers in ways
that people never even heard because
there's so many of them and they talk
about what's going on with them if you
have anxiety you could be getting
triggered with something in your
environment something you're eating you
could be getting triggered so i talk
about those those triggers so important
and so important for for healing so
that's one thing right there so when the
heating of the brain occurs in the
emotional center so that's what happens
so when you get bad news
when you get bad news what is it is it a
breakup is it somebody's backstabbing
you some betrayal happened somebody let
you down emotional trust maybe it's a
really hard loss
a really
horrifying horrific loss and i have a
friend that i talked to just recently
who had a terrible loss a couple years
ago
just got awful and
and he was telling me that when it
happened
this loss happened
he got knocked off of his feet he hit
the ground and i told him what happened
was when you got delivered that news
when that news came in
the brain
went into extreme heat in the emotional
center just extreme heat in there just
went in the
like boom like a heatball
lightning going on in there and that
lightning
cauterizes
some tissue because he got anxiety after
his bad news that happened he never had
anxiety in his life and then after that
bad news when he had that terrible loss
all of a sudden now anxiety started to
creep up it started to creep up a little
bit at a time a little bit at a time
more and more and more and more
and as it was creeping up and getting
worse and worse i told him what was
happening so aries alien says um
aries says i love your catchy poems
intro and
poetic in the podcast
uh they're so powerful thanks for
informing me about anxiety i can finally
leave the house again oh my god that's
incredible aries i'm so proud of you and
i'm so glad you heard the podcast it
means the world that you're hearing that
and you're getting any kind of help and
any kind of information and that matters
he showed us here yes i love the part
where you covered triggers and what
happens to our soul that was so
incredibly validating we're live right
now if you guys just came on here this
is live streaming
so there's no confusion okay so this is
straight up
i'm live right now right betty said what
is the name of your of this podcast
medical medium podcast
at apple podcast that's the platform
right there that's uncensored for the
medical medium podcast link is in the
description
check it out
check it out so
my friend got this really horrific loss
in his life that happened a couple years
ago and it hit the emotional center of
the brain and it just exploded with heat
and no one realizes that's what happens
the electricity that fires up and then
your adrenal surge and you're in fight
and flight like how how what can i do
what can i do how can i stop this what
can i what can happen here and
and when that happens it just gets
hotter and it burns hot and then you get
these calluses i talk about in the
emotional center of the brain like
a physical injury
and that physical injury that occurs in
brain tissue and neurons needs to heal
over time and i talk all about it it's
really a powerful episode that's just
one thing i talk about the different
triggers i talk about that and i talk
about the symptoms like the tightness in
the chest and the panic attacks and the
different varieties of anxiety and what
it feels like and i cover all those as
well so i mean honestly
you guys even if you don't have anxiety
it's a fun episode too because it's
packed with information and that's just
it's always good to learn it's always
good to have this information trisha
marie said you're a
poetic so empowering i you know what
it's funny is
that there's messages in all that
information
too there's messages in the poems and
and the inspirational uh
inspirational it's living words from
above and the inspirational words that
are there so you guys and i know so many
of you are dealing with anxiety right
now and i'm like okay wait a minute
anxiety is a big deal right now because
i'm always dealing with people having to
have that trying to help them and
make sure they have the information they
need but
right now in the time where we are right
now it's just people are so anxiety
ridden it's like elevated to a point
that's in just unbelievable so really
this episode is so important
lexi hannah says your brain meditation
really helps me oh fantastic i hope you
keep on doing it and keep on doing it
because it's so helpful
um
and
really that the brain meditation is a
great one the moon meditation the moon's
coming out soon so check out the moon
meditation link is in the description
medical media podcast at apple podcast
and the reason why i say that so many
times because someone said someone said
to me like why do you say that it's like
uh because then everybody they don't
know where to go because then another
person be like well i don't know where
to go where do i listen to it so i'm
trying to help as many people as i can
you guys are so patient you're like ah
there he goes
says it again you already know where to
go you already know where to go i know
link is in the description
um so thanks to you guys for being so
patient with that
but
if you guys can tell other people if you
can post about it or send the message
out about this episode that would be
incredible and about the meditations
just spread the message share the
message if you can
uh so great and it's going to help so
many people and you know we're a
grassroots movement there's no big pr
marketing big big marketing firms the
medical medium
whatever it's nothing like that
and
it's all about healing with the
information like the book right there
you'll see behind me the medical medium
cleanse the heel if you don't have that
book you might want to get it um it's on
sale at amazon 51 off so you might want
to get that right there i mean so and
that's an incredible gift for the
holidays and stuff to help people heal
so and you know i have a friend that
just got it too and they're like well
i'm getting this book for a family
member for uh for the holidays
um catherine elizabeth says when you
describe being on the toilet toilet bowl
and having a panic attack i said oh my
god he's talking to me catherine
it's it's
that is
where
that's where everybody goes i mean where
so many people go yeah it's i've seen
that it's like well a lot of people go
in their car a lot of people go this
they go into the kitchen
but but yeah it's like sometimes just
you go into the bathroom and you're like
oh my god am i dying and the panic
attacks oh it's so hard it's so hard
joanne says wendy when do you speak of
healing anxiety it's in the podcast
episode it's that's where it is so
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
the link is in the description don't
miss out
um
and you'll understand all about anxiety
what causes it
what symptoms or what okay one thing
you'll learn do you have a mild form of
anxiety do you have a moderate form of
anxiety do you have a severe
form of anxiety like which one do you
have you'll learn that in this episode
too
um
yeah just ebn flow says i love all the
meditations and use them all amazing the
podcasts are fabulous can't wait to see
your topics because i know they will get
down to the bottom of these things so we
can take charge of our own health you
guys that's what i want it's like i want
you to be able to take charge of your
own health take control over your own
health get better get stronger
know what's wrong and
it's not enough just to know you have
anxiety it's not enough we need to know
what tools you use we need to know what
we're doing i mean it's not enough just
to know it's not enough to have a
diagnosis of anxiety like you have
anxiety like that's what you have you
have anxiety well okay great well
why
uh you're going through some emotional
stress uh okay well sure but wait a
minute someone else is going through
emotional stress how come they don't
have it because there's real physical
reasons this is a serious thing i mean
it's debilitating for so many people um
claudia says i had severe anxiety to the
point where i couldn't walk i had
numbness in my arms oh my god i couldn't
breathe also chest pains couldn't drive
people can't drive when they have
anxiety and so many other symptoms so i
started changing the foods and started
juicing celery juice and it worked
celery juice and i'll tell you why
it's a complete electrolyte it goes to
the emotional center of the brain when
you drink your celery juice and you know
what's funny you guys i don't have a
celery juice right now with me i have
fresh squeezed orange juice
right that's what i have so
and that's what's really funny there
right there um but i wish i had a celery
just right on me right now but anyway
those electrolytes the sodium cluster
salts that are in celery juice only go
straight to the emotional center of the
brain and start booting it up start
giving the neurotransmitter boosts all
of this you know the whole bit
um marcelo how you doing i've been
suffering from chronic anxiety attacks
for months how did you get that
information
well how do i get the information 30
over 30 years of helping out doctors
with their troubleshooting with patients
that's what i did my whole life okay i
was the guy that was known to be like
the bizarre symptoms guy where people
came from all around the world to search
me out seek me out and off this is long
before the internet was born too and to
find me and find information so they can
find the answers that's what it is it
comes from a source that i was gifted
with as a child but really it's not my
gift i'm just a messenger to give you
guys the information it's the gift is
for you so you have this information so
you can heal
and that's what it's all about so the
information is all unique the medical
medium information it has been um
for all these years and you know what's
funny is to see you know it just it gets
out there and then
people don't cite it back and they don't
know how much in the health movement
really is medical medium stuff going all
the way back for 30 years and then a few
years go by and no one realizes it and
they take another little piece doesn't
get cited back and then it's just it's
amazing how it works but then people
don't know where the all the source of
information is for the toxic heavy
metals the mercury the aluminum in the
brain and body and the viruses and
epstein-barr virus all these different
things that i talk about um
anyway
you guys link is in the description
and when this says aw your anxiety
podcast is so cool put it on the ship
put it on the shelf so helpful for
sufferers that's so awesome so glad
you're listening to that thank you for
being here
another incredible person and you know i
just you guys like i want to make sure
you have
what it takes to heal and this one's
packed don't get
fooled this episode line for line when
you listen to it you got to listen to it
again you're going to miss so much and
they miss so much you can listen to this
episode over and over again and you'll
learn and learn and learn it's
it's created that way so that it's so
packed
that you it's just it's it's really
amazing so i want you guys to know this
um please share
leave a review if you can at apple
podcast so that's the place to listen to
it that can be podcasted apple podcast
joanne says i am healing my 80 year old
mom of anxiety whoa i started with your
cleanse to heal protocol cleanse the
heal back here that's that's incredible
um comprehensive medical book right
there you guys you can have it in your
hands and it would be so helpful i
started with your cleansing heal
protocol amazing results people should
know to follow your cleanse to start
your body hears heals your mind you guys
are you know you guys are incredible
joanne thank you for that seriously um
look it's like this i tell you guys all
the time okay i'm live by the way if you
just got on here we're live streaming um
regina my anxiety is in high all the
time that sometimes i feel paralyzed
whoa
the thing is that that is as i talk
about that i talk about that in the
episode where you can just be paralyzed
on the floor
on the floor you know there's this
little part in the episode by the way
it's a little part in the episode one
little tiny piece compared to what's in
there and it's a it's a it's a guy
talking to his friend
and his friends like
oh i got anxiety but i just hop on the
treadmill and just run it off and it's
gone
and meanwhile his friend is telling his
friend like what do you mean you're
curled up in a ball on the floor shaking
you know it's like it's people don't
realize how
serious this stuff is
i mean really don't
moon's coming out moon's coming out
moon's coming out moon's coming out moon
meditation
link is in profile link the link is in
the description the moon meditation
really important now apple podcast is
the platform uncensored medical medium
and just letting you know in case you're
you're interested to actually hear that
that episode the whole bit anxiety
episode and you guys it's important to
know like
is it mild is it a moderate version what
kind do you have i talk all about that
in there
uh braun jones says funny this comes up
when i just was talking about it i never
believed it was a real thing until i
began suffering it myself oh my god
after my accident whoa it's hard to
accept that i have this it is the worst
thing i've experienced comes on so quick
oh that's so
first of all it's just unbelievable i
came after the accident you know i talk
about that i talk about how trauma
emotional trauma
accidents
losses all these things and then what
happens is the center of the emotional
part of the brain okay emotional center
of the brain it starts to heat up it
starts to burn up like lightning bolts
going through there because we're
electricity in here it's all electricity
running through our brain and those
lightning bolts heat up in there and
when they do you're just burning that
tissue because we have no choice that's
how it is
and and then we get the anxiety later on
cynthia says i'm also doing your heavy
metal detox day five now uh feeling the
heel
i love your moon meditation moon
meditation
moon big moon coming right the moon
so you guys anyway
i covered so much in this episode i just
had to tell you guys i had to
this is an exciting one for me uh
because
honestly i put so much in this one and i
i do that with all the episodes if you
listen the episodes you hear it but i
mean i i like i think i like even
pushed it to like
even to a point where i was like oh my
god can i even do any more
um but listen you guys know where to
find it link is in the description thank
you for coming on tonight
um this has been amazing ann says my
anxiety is paralyzing every day i
haven't left the house in almost a week
and a half
no one understands
and you must have heard the episode
right no one people don't understand i
say it in the episode i see it in there
how people don't understand they don't
get it
i mean really really it's that it's that
difficult so difficult lorraine l is
here too tonight um i just saw our
comment go up
um you know you guys are really
incredible incredible
that you're here and everything
alexandra alexandra says what's the
title of the book so the books behind me
it says medical medium cleanse to heal
it's the most comprehensive
medical textbook there is
supplements in there as far as how to
take them how to use some dosages over
200 symptoms and conditions
uh
so many cleanses in there different
cleanses to help heal it's a recipe book
you guys too that's a recipe book people
are like when you're coming out with
your recipe book
that's a recipe book that has more
recipes than recipe books it's almost
100 recipes 75 recipes in there i mean
what more can you do
regina what's the name of the podcast
medical medium podcast
at apple podcast so medical and then
medium podcast
at apple podcast
you don't want to miss it you're but i
i'm just giving you a forewarning
there's some really powerful episodes
there and there's the brain meditation
the moon meditation freeze a bird
meditation try those
um
i mean it's a guided meditation i'm
walking you through
rebecca says you're an incredible human
completely changed my life it seemed
like i was healthy to everyone but with
heel to cleanse 150 days straight celery
juice
um heavy metals
shake cutting out the troublemaker foods
you got cleanse to heal that's what it
is i now i now feel incredible after
nearly a decade so cleansing heal is
bringing your life back
it's bringing your life back if you guys
don't have that book
guys should grab it you guys should grab
it i mean if you don't want to get it on
i mean it's 51 off at amazon.com us if
you don't want to get that we go to the
library whatever get it for free there
hazel hi anthony when will you do an
episode on uh on eye thyroid disease
and thank you for loving us and caring
for us i do love you guys i do care
about you guys that's what it's all
about and you guys know i mean i've
talked about this in lots of some of my
lives i've done
what i've said everything's for free
um i don't have subscription charges on
my website i don't withhold information
from you guys
like
it's always for free and stuff too yeah
i care at the whole point bobby loves to
thrift hey i'm glad you're here uh today
my hands usually crack this time of year
since celery juicing the last six weeks
my fingers hands are not cracking or
bleeding from washing my hands so much
my skin is so hydrated and i'm over 50.
incredible that's amazing the celery
juice is that powerful um you're you're
at the home of the celery juice movement
it's the it's here
um susan renee vemma g.coms b12 and
lemon balm has helped me and take the
edge off it's the best best b12 my
opinion the best lemon balm is vimergy
um
right on 100 so what i use that is by
far the best so if you guys you know if
you want the best b12 if you want the
best lemon balm for anxiety and
everything else or whatever anything
you're going through it's what i take
it's their lemon balm it's been rg visa
victor i am as the mary e r g y
best company out there i always share
you guys share with companies i love out
there is the lyman's wild blueberries is
what i use there's other companies i
used to
eachota says uh oh comment went up so so
much information you guys um and you
guys remember i'm not sponsored either
not sponsored
so something that's really important to
know
so
look you guys this is is it oh carolyn
says is the new book about anxiety
carolyn
um
it's a podcast episode it's a
docu-series style podcast podcast
episode it's medical medium podcast at
apple podcast see
that's why i say it because somebody
nuke pops on and they don't know they
don't know where it is and i want you to
know
so if you guys can tell everybody to
please tell everybody um you don't want
to take time out of your day or anything
but if you got a minute and you can tell
somebody else and share it please share
the medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast um
help them learn how to use it and get
that information for free
mary says uh i'm glad i came across this
anthony i'm going to check it out thank
you incredible well you guys i love you
and i'm going to let you go and just
thank you for being here hope you listen
to the podcast episode and just know i
care about you and may the angels be by
your bedside tonight help you heal
and do some healing tonight as you're
sleeping
god bless you