live on facebook live on youtube gonna
make the apple
salad got some apples right here got
some greens which is critical
leafy greens and i got a lot of
different things here got some bananas
in the back so i'm gonna talk about mono
eating in a little while i also have
some potatoes here they're steamed
i don't know if you guys can see those
on there on the radar there but i'll
show you in a little bit
which i'm going to talk about too
there's a lot going on here got my
celery juice
of course i got my wild blueberry juice
which is an incredible tool
but either way here's what we're doing
we are talking about
how to figure out a way a direction for
so many people to heal so
before you jump to conclusions or
anything what that means is
people are like hey i got this what do i
do it's like i got this problem i got
eczema
i got fatigue you know i got heart
palpitations where do i go what do i do
and i want to be helpful i want to be
able to help everybody
know what direction to take
simply simple healing good to see you
see margaret good to see you too
um some of you guys coming on uh hi from
bulgaria neil yeah great
awesome bulgaria incredible incredible
good good to have you here truly truly
and so i'm going to talk about like
what to do a path with supplementation
um how to figure out what's wrong with
you all these things
matter and i want you to be able to have
the most direction possible so making
the apple salad
then i'm also going to be talking about
look how to use
medical medium tools medical medium
information
it's very important stephanie says love
spending my nights with you aw
i'm here i'm excited i'm i'm honored
you're here live we're live on facebook
live on youtube just letting you guys
know
and um this is great it's a great night
so
i'm gonna make this apple salad while
we're doing stuff
um but we're really gonna cover so much
so let's start let's start heading into
that now
so i'm gonna take the book one medical
medium new edition which you can get
free at the library you can also get at
bookstores local bookstores get at
amazon.com
the key is knowing what's
wrong right knowing your true cause
that's critical just so you know knowing
you're true
be yep be a detect catherine says yes to
be a detective for our health
knowing yeah it's right exactly knowing
what's wrong what's the true cause of
what's going on
okay and just so you know if there's
anybody new here this isn't about
trying to you know pawn off a book onto
you can get it free at the library
okay if you want to buy it you can buy
it too this is about saving lives
this is about using medical medium tools
which has already saved millions of
lives around the world
okay and so this is about like
how can i help you in the best capacity
right now through
a youtube and a facebook live right
because you know it's critical to read
the books and to learn learn learn
but how can i help you through
this short this short you know
meal preparation informational
educational
show for the moment so that that's the
key right there all right so good to see
you guys coming on i'm excited
um anyway so let's get into it a little
bit before i make the apple salad if you
guys are just coming on here
making the apple salad that is on the
back here
on page 348 there it is right there the
apple salad
which is exciting right you guys like
apples
very healing food but it's gonna be
about
and and look and you can use this as a
snack the salad can be used as a snack
it can be used as a meal if done if done
right you've got to just make sure you
put a few more apples in there
it can make it really good good to see
you guys coming on just reading the
comments too
so because i want to be helpful and
everything
so i'm excited uh suzanna tucker i've
been able to help heal
my low back pain and scoliosis with your
teachings aw and soc
amazing truly amazing so you're look you
know you've learned
how to use the information how to use
the books
um glad to see you here june seeing
everybody coming on here
incredible quinn good to see you great
great
all right you guys i'm gonna make the
meal but before that let's cut into this
a little bit i just showed you what i'm
going to make in a little bit too
smoky mountain paradise nice to see you
guys
incredible incredible i'm honored you're
here
all right so supplement section
on page 57 of this book so i want to get
to there right now
right so when someone has autoimmune
because that's what's going to happen
you're going to everybody maybe you
maybe your friend maybe your family
member can be diagnosed with autoimmune
okay you may not be told it's autoimmune
right away
but you you'll be given a diagnosis
because that's what happens and here's
the direction
of medical research and science right
now okay
the direction is for everybody
to get a diagnosis that ends up falling
in the category of autoimmune
so that's the direction like that's
their goal and
their goal is to make sure that
everybody is in the direction of
the of autoimmune their goal is to be in
that direction
because it takes the blame off of
medical research and science
that's what the autoimmune tag is about
so
you can get a name you can get a brand
new name for your illness
this year coming on and the year after
this year and the year after this year
next few years there's going to be a lot
of new diagnoses coming on
a lot of new names developing
because a lot of people are going to
have a lot of new
neurological problems big
time i don't know if you guys know what
i'm talking about
i don't know if any of you guys know
michelle i just saw you come on each
other good to see you
um yep it's all autoimmune all the time
you chota it's your fault
it's your fault right your body's fault
okay
and uh margaret says yeah oats have more
fat they do they do they have a little
bit more it's true
so what happens is they need to funnel
the medical industry needs the funnel
your aches and pains your tingles and
numbness your burning skin
your pain in your ear your neck your
back pain in your teeth
your pain in your feet your your um
every
you know everything everything there is
um your you know your all
your body's symptoms are gonna get
funneled into autoimmune that's where
they're gonna get funneled into so i'm
just letting you know
and and
most all of these diseases and symptoms
are going to
end up being neurological okay
that's what they are and so there's
going to be coming like
so many people already dealing with
neurological symptoms right they're
already dealing with it be open-hearted
good
good to check out those greens right be
open-hearted check it out right
cilantro parsley um
romaine lettuce yup so
coming up okay we've already everybody's
already out there dealing with symptoms
right
250 million americans alone
in the u.s have symptoms that are
neurological 250
million have neurological symptoms right
even if they're mild to really mild just
headaches
okay maybe some tingles once in a while
but they got them right they got them
but
coming pretty soon in these next few
years
is going to be neurological symptoms and
an epic proportion
never seen before in our history all
right that's what's coming
and so um
and i you know and i've got to be
careful to what degree and what i say
about this so i won't go into
those details but they're coming
anyway so medical medium information is
going to be needed more than ever before
in history it already
is and it's being used but man what's
coming it's going to be
really on a level no one's ever seen
but all these symptoms that people are
going to be getting
are all going to be lumped into
autoimmune they're going to be packaged
up they'll come up with new names but
they're going to be packaged up to
autoimmune right so what the medical
industry is going to do is they're going
to funnel all of that to autoimmune
and send it all the way into the
autoimmune basket
autoimmune autoimmune it's just going to
go all the way in there and the reason
why is it protects
medical research and science because
it's put on you so now it's all your
fault
it's all your body's fault and and we we
we can easily get sucked into that one
i'm sick
i got some fatigue i can't explain it i
got brain fog
i got flashing lights in my eyes i can't
see i'm
dizzy all the time i'm in i can't find
my balance
i'm not feeling good it is my fault it
is because my doctor says
i got autoimmune and so if i got
autoimmune that means that my body is
attacking itself
so that's where it goes so um
anyway and the reason why it goes into
autoimmune like i said is to protect the
medical industry that's one of the big
reasons and autoimmune means cause
unknown
that's what it means so they say well
it's your body turning against itself
it's your body's immune system attacking
your glands
and your organs but still
cause unknown they don't know why
your immune system is attacking your
organs but your
immune system isn't attacking its organs
that's just the theory that's just their
theory their excuse if that's what it
might be
that's what it must be because here at
medical research and science we know
everything and when medical research
decides knows everything then
you're the one that's got the problem
it's your body's faulty and that's how
it works
anyway um and i want to talk about
neurological symptoms a little bit so i
got the brain
in there too so
when medical medium books are
fairly easy to use you just have to
spend a little energy
and get familiar with them right so
that's medical medium new edition i also
have cleanse the heel right here too
on page 57 it says supplements for
autoimmune disorders
and diseases okay later stage
epstein-barr because
medical median books has revealed the
truth about
autoimmune diseases being viral so
that's epstein-barr
so it says including lupus and r.a
rheumatoid arthritis right
um and if you look here it says if you
have a condition
that is not listed in this chapter and
yet your symptoms match up to
epstein-barr so it's about learning
about your
symptoms because the symptoms match up
to epstein-barr
the tingles the numbness right
unexplained aches and pains
even plantar fasciitis that sepstein bar
you know
all these different things jaw pain head
head pain
cranial nerve pain too it's what
shingles but you can also have
epstein-barr and still be sick still
have migraines
so all these symptoms
right so um
and so i want to read a little bit so
you're welcome to
customize your supplement protocol
between this list
and the previous list right for early
upsteen bar so what you're doing is
you're saying
what's wrong with me why am i sick
i need to know the true cause that's the
key
i need to be my own detective and i need
a guide
i need information and so
when you come in here you can lock down
what your symptoms are
learn about what's causing your symptoms
realizing okay that many symptoms are
caused by epstein-barr once you get into
the book
and that's really important to know um
so
if you're struggling with lupus and
it's and it's skin related aspects are
bothering you more you can turn to
eczema and psoriasis
or lupus style rashes okay or
and so all this is important too so i'm
gonna go into it a little bit more too
on some other aspects of it
um but you guys good to see you coming
on if you just came on i see a lot more
people coming on
i got the leafy greens here got the
apples i'm making
an apple salad that's in this book on
page 348
showed you guys earlier um so that's
another thing too so there it is
i'm going to show you the recipe okay
so that's what we're working on in a
little bit
medical medium tools are not just fruits
and vegetables
they're leafy greens they're wild foods
they're herbs yes fruits and vegetables
too
and medical medium protocols are
supplements
minerals all these things matter to
healing
it makes a big difference it's details
matter and then it's how to apply these
tools
okay so every every way you can and it's
good so if you look at autoimmune
disease if you guys are dealing with
autoimmune
and you look at the supplementation
you'll see fresh celery juice
which i've been drinking a little bit of
it now right mine's kind of settling
so there it is fresh celery juice it
says
work up to 32 ounces twice a day if
possible
if not work up to 32 ounces every
morning so if you got autoimmune
the book is clearly stating
32 ounces of celery juice
working up to that so that right there
is an example then you can see the
supplementation
in here too so i'm going to read
page 271 so i'm going to go there
to supplement protocols so i'm glad you
guys are coming on um
reading comments too and i'm gonna help
out in any way i can
so this is critical guide to supplement
protocols critical information when it
comes down to supplement protocols okay
before you leap into the supplement
protocols
make sure you read this chapter so
that's a big part
of you and you can take this to your
doctor that's the whole point you can
take the book to your doctor take
this supplement section to your doctor
okay if you're wondering about whether
supplementation is right for you know
that the supplements recommended in this
book
are are an optional step that's how
medical medium information works right
you can start with celery juice you can
start with
taking out the no foods taking out the
troublemaker foods
okay and each step you take
you can move forward to your healing
process
if you feel like you're not going as far
as you need to go
it's endless in here it's endless to
take you
all the way to that healing zone
and that's what's so important you know
i noticed that the people that
heal are the people that learn how
to read the books right learn how to
take those next steps
so it's there my doctor is like a closed
book i saw that right there
um all right it's interesting comment
so if you prefer to focus on foods
you can focus on foods by removing the
troublemaker foods okay
you're more than welcome to do the 28
day cleanse or any of the medical media
cleanses i can cleanse the heel
right you don't have to play in
supplement land yet
if you don't want to and that's what's
incredible about medical medium
information you can start with just
avoiding some of the foods medical
medium information is about avoiding the
apple cider vinegar the milk cheese eggs
butter okay so letty i see you're saying
tinnitus question mark question mark
question mark so
i'm gonna take the book let's go look
so so i'm in the book now
okay and what you'll learn is tinnitus
when you go
into the book you'll learn in the
epstein-barr chapter that tinnitus
is caused by epstein-barr that's that's
that right there is a critical
piece of information so you'll learn
that
the labyrinth of the inner ear gets
inflamed
by the virus so now you already know
what's wrong soletti you know what's
happening with your ringing buzzing
popping vibrating
humming and you know so what happens
though is that when we go and look for
help
out there no one knew what to cause
tinnitus
unless it's like damage to the ear
itself from an
injury physical injury or a decibel
injury
like you know you're in rock concerts
your whole life and you're up on the
front row
right and then the you know that gets
damaged that way
but or maybe you're around large you
know
loud machinery in your life you work in
a factory and you got like extreme large
machinery and you never use the ear
muffs
but
[Laughter]
but anyway the labyrinth of the inner
ear gets inflamed and i talk about that
in the book so now you know what's going
on
and you know it's epstein-barr that's
advanced medical information
that was never out there until the books
but
once you know it's about going into the
books and finding
those supplements that's one option
knowing what foods to remove that's
another option too
so that's what's incredible so i'll give
you a quick rundown on this right here
so you can start by doing the cleanse
inside the book
you can also remove troublemaker foods
like the milk
cheese eggs butter corn soy
you can go further look out for the msg
the natural flavors
the nutritional yeast the apple cider
vinegar
be cautious on how much caffeine you can
go even further and further right
but the whole goal is you can take it as
far as you need to go
to do that healing all of this matters
i'm in the new edition if anybody wants
to know right here it's the medical meme
new edition
okay you guys are just coming on okay
the supplement protocols in this book
are for people looking for something
more
so some people hey i've been doing your
celery juice
anthony william for like a year now and
i'm feeling so much better thanks
it cleared up my gout right
it cleared up my gout my skin got better
and then somebody else
it's like i've been doing their celery
juice and i'm just not getting to where
i need to go i mean i improved
but i can go so much further but i don't
know how or what or where
and then that's the next level it's
about going that
next level so it's important and then
that's the supplement protocols in this
book are for people looking for
something more
looking for options because their
situations are perplexing to them
right if you know anybody right if
that's you
then delve into the treasure trove of
options in the form of specialized
supplement lists for individual symptoms
and conditions in this book so you
can delve into that specialization
that's in here
okay it's important to know that our
deficiencies are a big part of why we're
sick so
deficiencies a big part of why we're
sick
zinc for example is practically
non-existent
in our food today so zinc
is non-existent in our food today
animal proteins all of it alike
all right some in secrets behind chronic
mystery illness and how to finally heal
and then do addition critical
information for people that need to heal
need to move forward so zinc
is a deficiency everybody has so the
reason why
people don't move forward in many
situations is because they're zinc
deficient
so this is an example right here
a zinc deficiency lowers the immune
system
so we're always in need of it so a zinc
deficiency
lowers our immune system
so then we become more susceptible
austin good to see you tonight
all right um just so important
we also have a lot of toxic heavy metals
in us and
spirulina spirulina is critical for
removing
the toxic heavy metals so you guys see
where it's going
you see where you got different options
you can start with hey i'll start with a
little celery juice
let me remove a few foods that's fine
too right
what kind of foods well he talks about
in here let's remove some foods
okay so that's right there and then it's
like well i want to move along quicker i
want to get this further along i want to
make this happen so let's
get into some of the supplements he's
saying everybody's got zinc deficiencies
so i'm showing you guys how this works
everybody's got zinc deficiencies so and
that's why it's important
so that's a zinc right there so that's
the vimergy zinc right
and that's the one i use for my friends
and family and
there's a supplement directory at
medicalmedium.com so you know the safest
stuff
more effective stuff without the alcohol
and the natural flavors and the msg and
everything else that goes wrong
and so the point is is like just the
zinc deficiency alone can move
someone forward so if someone's got the
tinnitus they got the vertigo
they got the burning skin they got the
aches and pains they got the fatigue
they get their autoimmune diagnosis if
someone has that autoimmune diagnosis
whatever it is you can look up your your
diagnosis to see if it's listed under
autoimmune right you can look that up
out there
but if you have an autoimmune condition
you'll see zinc inside the book right
here and then you'll see
dosages okay and a zinc deficiency
is a big one for people that's a huge
one it's a
zinc up to two dropper fulls twice a day
so someone with autoimmune it gives you
the dosages right here
up to two dropper fulls twice a day
of zinc so i'm giving you guys a window
into how to heal take take all this to
your doctor if your doctor
you know supports it your doctor
supports if he doesn't just do what your
doctor says
but the bottom line is i'm giving you
options
and the zinc deficiency is one of those
problems that everybody is living with
so when anybody gets a new condition
they get a new problem that zinc
deficiency is going to get in their way
big time now
you can just start it you could be
someone and you start out with just a
couple of tiny drops where it's
literally just a drop and not the dosage
that's in the book
ask your doctor what's right for you but
that's you know so when i tell
doctors or friends and family hey this
is how you use the book i'm giving you
guys that window now
um i was in a conference this morning
phone's ringing you guys
hello yeah
uh
uh-huh hold on you guys this call
this is actually a real phone call right
now this is i have it hooked up right
now
this is a real one okay um
what did your doctor say your doctor
said that
you don't have you don't have a zinc
deficiency how would he know
how would your doctor know that he
doesn't he does
he doesn't doesn't really know does your
doctor know that
that you have epstein-barr he doesn't
believe it he doesn't think so
okay so he doesn't think you have
epstein-barr all right
so what does he think your tingles and
numbness and your fatigue is
and you're ringing in the ears and your
dizziness
and your brain fog what does he think it
is he thinks
he thinks it's your telomeres okay
so what's he saying it's genetic oh okay
so he thinks it's your genes
all right so he thinks he thinks it's
your genes
okay um what did your last doctor say
didn't you have a
didn't you have a better doctor before
that oh he said it was parasites in your
gut
what did he do he gave you a whole bunch
of gut health
probiotics did it help it didn't
all right he said that you had parasites
okay well did it did it fix it what did
he do
all right it didn't fix it what did your
last doctor do though didn't you have a
pretty good doctor before that
that doctor got you on a keto diet
really
it kind of helped a little bit because
he got you off of oh got you off of
those processed foods
okay all right well that's good at least
he got you off some processed foods
right what did he say your problem was
he said that your body was attacking
itself
so you had like an autoimmune and your
body was attacking itself all right
what did your doctor say before that so
you had a doctor before that he said
he said that you you it was idiopathic
all your symptoms just they weren't
really real because you couldn't find
anything wrong
that's your fourth doctor really
well all right well look all i know is
if you take a look at the book you'll
find so much information to get better
you really will you guys
um so anyway
the information is here so when you look
into autoimmune you'll see the different
supplementation
how it works zinc is one of those key
things to get people better that's the
vimergy zinc by the way i'm not
sponsored
remember gv is in victor i am as mary e
rgy
um i see some people have been through
that you've been through that right
that's just the tip of the iceberg i
mean i can't i would be here all day to
tell you how many doctors and what they
say and how
as you go along um yeah
so it's critical to read the supplement
section to how you use the supplements
and if you look down the line for
autoimmune you'll see the different
supplements you'll see lemon balm in
here
and the dosages so that's important too
so chapter 21 is where you read about
the supplements and i'm going to go
there
back there right now
yeah so uh
and we're gonna make the apple salad in
a couple minutes to you guys
all right so here we go um so as i said
before you can start with the celery
juice that's one option right there you
can take away the no foods you can take
away the foods that are troublemaker
foods
okay so i'm in here
critical critical tips all right so
where to start
once you've found your symptom or
condition okay
remember that once you've found your
symptom or condition in the books
and you learn about what is wrong like
why
am i dealing with the symptom or
condition all right
you don't need to take every supplement
listed in here
for it if you're sensitive you can try
one supplement a day
if not you can put them all together as
your daily regimen
as a middle ground you can choose a
couple to start with and then take it
from there
celery juice is always a good place to
begin beyond that vitamin b12 is another
place
so that's the b12 right there that's the
beemer's eb12 can ask your doctor what's
right for you
perfectly fine you can take this to your
doctor see if your doctor agrees with it
or not
i want you guys to do whatever you feel
like you know you need to do
i recommend family and friends like
that's the b12 so that's an example
zinc is another another one too so a
good place to start is the zinc
the b12 the vitamin c
so vitamin c is the the microc is the
one i use right there so that's the one
i use
you guys can use what you want to use
but there's reason why
i like the better stuff because the
details matter because you
you move forward so much better okay
and lemon balm so it's it's that's a
place to start
when you're when you're dealing with a
problem it's like you got the b12 you
got the vitamin c you got the lemon balm
you got the zinc that's a great place to
start okay
bring in those then if you're ready to
move forward and your list contains
spirulina curcumin cat's claw or lysine
those are the next ones in so there's
the spirulina right
and then there's the cat's claw right
and then there's the lysine
right here okay and and you can bring
those in next
and add those in later on if you're not
experiencing what you want from these
supplements
you can add a few more from your list
and you can always take smaller amounts
than the listed dosages if you're
sensitive
right you also have the option to enter
mixed supplements from the different
lists in the book any supplement from
this book
is an option to use
so um sun moon you got a question
it's do we take the supplements with
food or without food
okay the book sun sun moon good question
sun moon love that's a really cool
handle
it's an awesome handle um yeah you can
you can you got to read the book right
and you'll find it in there
so the answer will be in there okay um
you don't have to take supplements with
food
or without food okay you can go either
or
and that's important to know because
here's how it works it's like
people will people will take supplements
with
no food at all so they'll just take the
supplements and no food
and when people just take the
okay they don't have enough glucose in
their bloodstream so
glucose is really important so eating
some time before supplements or eating
sometime after supplements is always a
good idea that's what i that's what i've
always told doctors to tell their
patients
you can do what your doctor wants you to
do in the whole bid and whatever feels
good
but i like having some kind of glucose
present
with supplements for myself when i take
them so when i take supplements and this
is for everybody here
too i'll take my supplements with like
uh my shot glass of wild blueberry juice
i'll take my supplements with because
there's a glucose in there
i'll take my supplements with some
coconut water i'll take my supplements
i'll have an
apple after i've had my supplements i'll
have the medical medium smoothie of
course the smoothies that i do all the
time for myself
lemon water with honey in it is a great
one too
like that's a great one but i like
having a little glucose a really good
question but you can you can do it you
can do it without food and you can do it
with food i like having a little bit of
glucose that's what i like
definitely if you're sensitive food is
actually always a great way to go
so as i was saying like a great place to
start is some of the basic supplements
that are really important
and i've seen in so many situations
people dealing with symptoms
where they just use a handful of medical
medium tools
and they'll use the troublemaker foods
they'll get out
they're like okay aw i got rid of the
milk cheese the butter the pork i went a
little further i got rid of the corn
i got rid of the you know of that right
there so they move that out
i got rid of the gluten so they move
that out of the way and then
it's like what do i need to do now let
me bring in some celery juice
and then they bring in some celery juice
okay and then now they're there now
they're making a couple of medical
medium recipes now they're doing the
healing broth
and they're like okay i'm getting better
i'm getting better i'm getting better
but i'm not where i want to be yet but
i'm getting better so i know
i'm on the way what do i need to do now
well let me look in these supplements
let me look at the protocols let me look
at the different
the supplementations of where to start
and
let's go in there and so that's what's
really great so
if you're dealing with more than one
symptom or condition at the same time
and want
one clear place to begin pick the health
struggle that looms
largest in your life that's so important
right here
isn't this great you guys were doing
this for free we're not you those guys
don't have to spend ten thousand dollars
for big program and sign up
this is you know i want to just be here
right now in your own backyard
and i want to do this with you right now
give you this info
um so pick this pick the symptom
that looms over you the most
pick the symptom that's the most pain in
the butt the biggest
problem in your life you can pick that
symptom
so that's important to know for example
if you're plagued by chronic fatigue
syndrome
and that feels most pressing you can
focus on the supplements for chronic
fatigue syndrome
at the end of chapter three the
epstein-barr the chronic fatigue
syndrome right over time you may find
that working on
one issue takes care of another
how about that right so you're working
on your cfs
and all of a sudden or your lupus or
you're working on your lupus your ms
your cfs your or your symptom or your
vertigo your tonight's whatever you're
working under your thyroiditis
what your thyroid problems whatever
you're working on and all of a sudden
right all of a sudden other symptoms are
going away
other symptoms are going away the whole
bunch of different symptoms are going
away
okay and that's it that's what's amazing
um
and you can switch it off a little bit
and focus on different supplements on
different pages
if you're sensitive you can use just a
little bit at a time you can do like a
little bit of b12
i recommend that to family and friends
that are friends that are sensitive
but the book explains that to you and
everything let's make a let's make a
dish right here by the way medical
medium new edition talks about pandemic
talks about the plague that's going
around
ebv talks about ebv in depth okay really
important too
and long-term symptoms because of
epstein-barr
and because of the plague triggering off
long-term symptoms and i remember when
plague first started i was the first one
out there
explaining how that is going to trigger
a lot of people's problems um jeff
johnson i have been deep into medical
media protocols i am now
out of a wheelchair walking
again from severe nerve pain and feet
psoriasis is slowly healing too thank
you mmm just
incredible incredible so proud of you
out of a wheelchair
doing the medical medium protocols
that's incredible that that means
everything
means everything let's start making some
food right here you guys
um you guys are interested this these
are the supplements that i use
because what happens is someone will
take a b12 that's got preservatives in
it they'll take
a zinc that has a preservative in it you
can go to medicalbean.com to my
directory that's the vimergy stuff i'm
not sponsored by those guys
but i am working with wyman's on their
wild blueberry juice
uh which i'm really proud to say because
i want that stuff to stick around it's
an incredible tool that i
never thought could even imagine that
could be out there it's really hard to
create that stuff
um really difficult
so anyway um and i actually need a shot
right now
which would be nice guys i want to
answer some questions if i can there's
just so much to cover
so i'm just having a shot of this as we
speak
didn't have my shot today
and so what i'm recommending friends and
family to do a shot
every single day is what i recommend so
so good i just love getting in touch
with it too
it's the power that has i love it how it
gives me kind of a rush because it
starts going through my body
it's ten thousand tens of thousands of
years
of information stored in those plants
that have grown in the coldest and
harshest places on the planet
incredible um debbie says i removed all
no foods doing celery juice and heavy
metal detox smoothie every day
taking six of the vimergy supplements
skin getting better and toes all better
whoa skin's getting better and toes are
all better
incredible still bloated a lot though
not sure what to
add talk about mono eating a little bit
his head there for the moment
so first of all always keep in mind no
matter what whoever
like whoever's out there like that's
listening right now that maybe your
comments are
aren't coming through because so many
comments or however it works or i don't
see your comment right
for all you guys out there okay
keep in mind that there's a lot of
pitfalls out there okay
so as you're trying to heal this is
important information this is really
critical
as you're trying to heal and you're
working on it
right you're doing your medical medium
information
you got to look out for snags right and
this is for anybody okay new medical
treatments
question them always be cautious you
know and
that's something that could be a snag
for
people coming up
right there's that's a huge
pothole huge pothole and
someone may not realize how much of a
pothole that is
that's number one number two like blood
draws
really critical to know that's why i
that's why
you know i talk about um medical media
podcast at apple podcast the blood drop
look letting vampirism episode
too much blood taken because when we're
sick
we get too much blood taken all the time
and we don't know how to ask our doctor
to pre you know protect yourself to
have him protect you or her protect you
we don't know how to do that and i talk
about that in the episode
the blood draws can send people back so
bad it's ridiculous
corey says where can we buy the
blueberry juice um
like shop s-h-o-p dot
wyman's w-y-m-a-n-s dot com
that's where it is and they got a sale
on a case of it
so the whole bit i'm working with these
guys because i'm hoping this this stuff
stays here because it's incredible
um and then and with the supplements
it's been rg.com you guys know
v is victor i m e r g dot com so i'm
gonna go into the mono eating talk in
just a couple minutes but i'm just
saying so some of the potholes right
the blood draws it's getting your blood
drawn and
people go backwards and they go
backwards and they go backwards because
they're losing their immune system as
all that blood's being taken and they
don't know how to protect themselves you
guys i know many of you guys that know
this stuff
and how it works and i talked about and
i'll just give you the quick rundown i
talk about the only need
i only need that much
for like a gamma of tests i mean that
much
they only need that much like boom you
wouldn't believe
how much they can get out of there but
they take all of our bond they they
basically do over time
and they just chalk it up to like you
just create your
new blood it'll be good for you create
new blood right
fresh blood you know get your fresh
blood going like you know the whole bit
and it's a major scam
and they take too much they take too
much and that sets everybody back that's
fighting for their lives so when you're
fighting to heal they're sucking the
life out of you without realizing it's
the system itself it's broken i talk
about that medical media podcast at
apple podcast okay the blood draw
podcast
i just want you guys to have every
opportunity to heal just every wherever
i can so let's go into mono eating for a
couple of minutes before i make the
recipe
heading there now right
um i'm in the motto eating chapter right
here
and let's read a little bit mono eating
can be an incredible technique for
recovery
from certain health issues it has
several applications most notably for
gut healing and food
allergies mono eating saved my own life
when i was a child suffering from food
poisoning hey that's me
okay so exactly so motto eating saved my
own life
you guys because from food poisoning
because food poisoning kills a lot of
people
it just just really really takes a lot
of people down just letting you know i'm
going to cleanse the heel now
a little bit uh the mono-eating
so go into that too a little bit
figuring out what to eat figure out what
to eat when you're challenged with a
digestive
system problem can feel impossible and
this really helps clear that
field that playing field so you can
learn right so gastroparesis
undiagnosed gut problems if you're in
that like
what's going to happen here's the gut
health world the gut health world is
going to be like
all-encompassing right every single
functional medicine doctor
every single doctor you guys go to every
single doctor everybody goes to it's all
going to be about gut health take these
probiotics
let's do some stool samples let's look
for parasites let's
look for this let's look for that so
it's all going to be about gut health
from here on out right
but it doesn't mean that's the answer or
it doesn't mean
the remedies are going to be the answers
because
they've been focused on gut health
anyway alternative medicine's been
focused on gut health going back now
decades with the whole candida
farce so we're kind of still stuck in
that gut health world which is gut
health gut health gut health and that's
the problem
and it's got health um and so yeah and
guess what our guts become
a mess absolutely a hundred percent and
there's no doubt
we get bacteria in our gut we get
inflammation in our gut because of
bacteria and viruses in our gut we get
all kinds of problems in our gut medical
medium information's always been about
that right
but how do we really fix it so you're
not doing harsh
gut cleansers and gut tonics
and gut powders and
probiotic you know probiotics and
everything else and not still
moving forward to where you need to go
like how do we address that
so the mono eating cleanse is a great
way to do it for gastroparesis
undiagnosed gut problems even diagnose
gut problems crohn's colitis
um elevated histamines in people's
systems
food sensitivities food allergies all of
that ibs
right celiac and and
digest the bloating pain gastritis
okay yep yep that one so all of them
and this is a way a technique to work on
how to heal and it talks about how to do
that and i'll give you a quick run down
like when it comes down to bananas right
one thing you'll be told in alternate
medicine
is you know stay away from bananas too
much sugar and that's an
epic disaster because i've seen bananas
take
people from the worst conditions
physically with all kinds of different
diagnoses including gut problems
i've seen bananas and leafy greens like
bananas and romaine lettuce
bananas and green leaf lettuce bananas
and red leaf lettuce right
butter leaf lettuce i've seen that take
someone to the finish line of their
healing
where and i talk about that in the mono
eating section of the book
and in the moderating section the book
it'll be like okay you're drinking your
32 ounces of celery juice
right okay you're doing your bananas and
your lettuce
so and you're doing a mono version of
that there's also a potato version too
where in the mono eating cleanse there's
also potatoes we're doing steamed
potatoes
and greens it's important
yeah uh hello i'm here
okay well here's what happens right
um okay so i hear
spirit of compassion right
from above since i was age four okay
and some people might find that
difficult to understand and some people
totally they're chill with it they're
fine with it right
and um but that information has helped
millions heal around the world
um it's hard for a lot of people because
they don't have they're not having that
same
conversation with spirit of compassion
so they're feeling like where do i go
what do i do
so then they'll go to a doctor then to
another doctor then to another doctor
then to another doctor right
right you did that you did that you've
been to a lot of doctors
i totally get it you went to a
nutritionist too and a dietitian
okay and you got a health coach awesome
all the support is great
it's great there's nothing wrong with
all that support it's awesome
but i know at the same time you're
worried about like
because you can't hear soc spirit of
compassion
how are you gonna be able right i got it
how are you going to be able to like get
the information you need
so you you feel like you're stuck going
to your next doctor
and your next specialist and your next
specialist
okay i get it all right i understand i
want you to know that
the books are spirit of compassion the
answers
are there you just have to
systematically take your time and go
through it or
or yeah let the angels guide you a
little bit
you open the book you find a spot and
you open it to that page for a reason
because you're getting guided yourself
that's an option too
but what i would do is focus on your
biggest problems right
and then look into the book find your
biggest
problem and start a little bit at a time
and have a little faith and confidence
because the information's there and you
can find your way
you just have to look into it and see it
and see it
really glad you called
so anyway you guys um i was talking
about mono eating and how helpful that
is
so i'm giving like i'm giving you guys
like really
powerful information here um
and this is why it's important about the
details
everybody's they're just lost out there
they'll
be doing something that's partially good
for them but then they'll be
mixing it up with something that's bad
for them they'll talk about getting
metals out of them
but they'll be using corella to get the
metals out which doesn't get the metals
out
they'll try to get their gut health
better and then they'll get rid of
gluten
but they'll be using apple cider vinegar
which destroys your gut
see see where it goes this is just
little examples okay
right and fixing things takes
the details all the details matter
it all matters so it's all about the
details so important to know and
what a lot of people do is they'll get
stuck with something
that's going around and they won't know
that it's not a good thing so they'll
have the natural flavors they'll have
the msg they'll be doing chocolate
they'll be doing their nutritional yeast
they'll be doing too many things
and they add up and when they add up it
stops you from healing so the good
things you're doing
are battling the bad things you're doing
see
so it's like good versus bad good versus
evil it's
constantly good versus evil in the diet
good versus evil even in the supplement
world right
and that's what everybody gets up
against and it makes it even harder and
harder to work with as far as for your
healing let's talk about the recipe
guys i hope i'm giving you some good
information tonight meaning like
streamlining
some tidbits so you guys have have that
under your belt
let's start making a salad i'm going to
use some of this romaine lettuce this is
romaine lettuce which is
i like romaine lettuce now you can chop
it up as fine as you want you can chop
it up as
is is little pieces i like chopping up
in littler pieces for this
so this is the apple salad
so i'm going to get a little bit more in
here
move this aside for a second
a little bit more right we got that
going in there let's do
a little bit of cilantro in this salad
you guys don't mind look i'm using this
as a leafy green
i'm not using that much right and
putting it on top of a piece of fish
actually what people do
with fish is they'll put this much
that's your cilantro cilantro in a
guacamole people use that much
cilantro and guacamole right they use
that much that's all they'll use
look at that right or on a piece of fish
they'll chop up that much if you're
lucky and put it on top of a piece of
salmon right
we're using a leafy green medical medium
tulle
and i don't care what anybody says you
guys no one used
leafy greens until they learn the
medical medium information out there and
if you learned about leafy greens
through some other source it came it was
osmosis through another source that
learned it from medical medium
35 years of teaching people about leafy
greens people just used iceberg lettuce
in the health realm vegan realm
iceberg lettuce vegan realm it was
iceberg lettuce
yeah that was it you know the vegan
realm was it was gluten bread
it was bread with gluten in it and
iceberg lettuce
i mean that's what it was and then when
someone got sick it was some wheatgrass
juice
that was it i mean it was literally just
down to that little batch of things the
medical medium information
blew the roof off of all of it for all
these years
i have a whole episode on apple cider
vinegar in the podcast
indeed i do linda thank you for that i'm
going to put some
cilantro in the salad that's a leafy
green
that's using it like that that's how
we get better it's these details there's
so many of them the medical medium
information
okay so many it would blow your mind if
you knew
what i've done in the last 35 years who
i've helped who i've talked to who i
spoke to in the health realm
who i've guided and how that information
has crossed
all lines all around the world
and you know how you might be like ah
how can that be true oh really
how can i how come i'm the only one
that's figured out how to save lives is
it because i'm a genius or something
because i'm not a genius figured out
about the blood draw problem
that's knocking people back left and
right how come i'm the only one when the
plague just came out recently
to talk about the after effects before
anybody uttered a word about it like
how come i'm the only one that said
no you use the lemon water to flush your
liver
flush your liver it's not because i'm a
genius that's
spirit of compassion right but either
way
you know all these tools right but
and then they get out there and they get
passed around
and people just forget you know it's
like oh
i mean there's premier medical clinics
using medical medium information right
now
no science behind it it's just coming
from medical media
elizabeth hey truth i see so many people
now using a bunch of cilantro in their
smoothies yeah but they're not saying
medical medium right liz
they're not saying medical medium but it
comes from medical medium information
it only only comes from medical medium
information
but then it gets it gets passed around
right and here's the thing
when medical medium tools get out there
people use them and it's protecting them
against all the bad stuff they're doing
so there's there's this thing happening
where they're getting some of the
medical medium tools whatever they are
and then they're they're battling the
bad stuff they're doing that's out there
right
and you know this is how it works okay
so let's go in just a little bit of
making
so i got cilantro in here i got some
parsley you got a decent amount of
parsley
and it's so good when you use a lot of
parsley right so i'm going to just chop
up that a little bit more
okay now let's get
let's get some apples going
got some apples here i'm going to slice
them thin you guys
this can be a meal keep that in mind i'm
doing thin slices of apple
some thin slices of apple here right
just some thin slices and i'm gonna
cut the slices in half so i'm stacking
them see what i'm doing
this is fun right now totally fun
i'm gonna put the slices in here this
can be a snack
this can be a meal you can eat this all
day and you can make a huge batch i've
done that before where i've made a huge
batch of this right
and wow all right get some apple slices
in here and you can do a lot more
um i'm just actually kind of making that
pretty quick right there i'm going to
cut an onion
onion's going to get me onion is going
to get me
i know a lot of you guys got tricks like
put the onion in the fridge
run the onion run the onion under water
put it in the fridge right but i'm
always like no i just want to get it
done
i don't want to play onion games
okay so i got the onion right here thin
slice of onion
i like for this it's nice and thin put a
little onion on here too
you can make this big use a lot of apple
okay put a little red onion on here like
this
right got some got your apple slices on
there too
okay um
and raisins a few raisins on here right
put a few raisins these raisins are kind
of stuck together
you guys know how raisins work so i'm
just going to put a few in here i'll mix
them up in a little while
too when i'm eating it a few raisins on
here it looks beautiful though
so good for you right all right you got
different dressing options you got a one
not
one dressing option is maple syrup one
and a half
um one and a half teaspoon tablespoons
of maple syrup i love maple syrup i
don't know about you guys
but i love it i'm gonna put a little
maple syrup on here
so good for you
okay that's one dressing this is the
dressing i'm using on mine though
right you got different dressing options
you'll see in the book and
um two tablespoons of lemon juice let me
get my strainer over here
my strainer's got a little bit of celery
pulp in there
there we go
let's get some lemon going
there you go
one and a half i mean sorry two
tablespoons of lemon juice can go in
here but you can do a lot less
you can do a lot less you can do
everybody's different they'll be like
hey i only feel like using a half a
lemon right now only feeling
i feel like using a whole lemon i'm
using a whole lemon so i'm getting up to
that tablespoon easy
see more than that that was actually a
real juicy lemon
okay so here's what you're getting out
of this
so you're getting glucose from your
apples
but you're getting a blend of the
glucose from your apples
and then you're getting the mineral
salts from your leafy greens
so you got your cilantro you got your
parsley okay you got your your
lettuce okay and when you get your
electrolytes and mineral salts
and your glucose combined all at once
all right
because you got your raisins in there
too for that glucose
this is the basically what this is is
like one of those
healing tools for the brain because it's
glucose mineral salts electrolytes
and you do this on a regular basis
you do this once a week and you're
moving forward that's like
you know it's like how many healing
tools that's a healing tool right there
okay have it as a snack
you got your wild blueberry juice right
that's a healing tool right i mean
that's what i
that you know like like all these
healing tools you got the right
supplementation right
so you got your you know you know how to
use your lemon balm you know how to use
your zinc you know how to use your b12
when i was younger
okay and i'm talking years ago right
um and i was helping out families
families would be like you have to come
into the nursing home
come into the nursing home aw and you
know help
my grandfather you know help my
grandmother help my great grandfather in
the nursing home
i know they got more in them i know i
just need you to tap into what that is
i'd take some b12 with me i'd go into
the nursing home
okay this is 30 years ago all right
go into the nursing home right and i'd
be
administering the b12 with the family
right there
right and you'd see after two days
all of a sudden you'd see someone that's
85 years old
and really sick you see them like spark
up and start coming back to life
i've seen this with young people with
all kinds of autoimmune where diagnosis
autoimmune but really low-grade viral
infections and high-grade viral
infections right
and they're really sick they could
barely function
there's fatigue they're bed-ridden
bed-ridden people in their 30s
people in their 20s people in their 40s
right and i've done the same thing when
i was younger
it's be like bring the b12 in and when
it's the right kind of b12 what you see
happen is like a miracle all of a sudden
now
you've got someone that's moving forward
like all the details matter
they just do um anyway guys
i'm heading off to ig and tick tock and
i love you guys
dearly um i'm gonna have a little bit of
this
probably a little later and you guys
know the different options
um but here remember i'm going to ig
right now
going to tic toc right now come with me
if you can and after that
i'm going to 369 cleanse on instagram
on ig and tik tok again it's gonna be a
long night we got a lot to cover
who knows what i'm gonna do later uh i
don't know what kind of moon i'm in
all i know is it's gonna be fun