critical medium live streaming it apple
cider vinegar
is it friend is it faux episode 11
the teeth dissolver that's the episode
episode 11 the teeth is over
apple cider vinegar so look you guys
i mean the amount of the amount of crap
that i got for putting out that episode
is definitely pretty intense because
what people like to do
is they like to hi everybody they like
to
judge before they hear something right
so instead of listening to everything i
said about apple cider vinegar the good
things and the bad
they're just like oh apple cider vinegar
i've been using that for 30 years
i've been great meanwhile they got all
these health problems you know it's like
it's like i've been using apple cider
vinegar for 10 years
and you know and i love it meanwhile
they got all these issues they got skin
issues they got this issue they got that
issue they got this issue
anyway they've seen a dentist a hundred
times anyway the whole point is
in the apple cider vinegar show it's
really intense lots of information it's
packed with information
hey you guys great to hear from you glad
we're all here
um so i want to talk about that a little
bit why
apple cider vinegar is the teeth
dissolver number one but also
why apple cider vinegar in general may
not be the best
thing to use and i talk about why in
this episode so
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
if you just got on here just so you
know the link is in the description so
you can actually hear the episode
because when you hear it then you'll
know what's going on have you guys heard
the episode
um incredible i'm glad everybody's here
coming on so much to talk about
and cover you guys heard about the so
alexandra said it was great explain so
much
right you know the information that's
there it's important to know
because you need to have a choice if
you're dealing with a health problem
maybe you have a minor health problem
maybe you've got some bloating maybe got
some skin issues
maybe you don't feel good and you're
tired maybe you got some you know
brain fog maybe you got some
neurological symptoms or or whatever's
going on in your life for example
psoriasis and all these things
taking apple cider vinegar internally
taking internally is not going to help
i know this gets people ruffled oh man
just yeah the pitchforks the torches
you know the stones the rotten tomatoes
everything's being thrown at me about it
but you know what it's like this what do
i do
it's like do i protect people who are
actually
dealing with struggles health struggles
and not feeling good and are sick
do i try to protect them or do i just
care about myself and just be like i
don't want no trouble i ain't gonna say
nothing
i don't want any crap i'm not gonna say
nothing i'm not gonna tell anybody
anything but you know what
it's like we gotta just we can't do that
we gotta
we gotta we gotta look out for people so
i don't care i just have to look out for
you guys so
i talk about how acetic acid
does a few things that we don't like
that we don't want in somebody's body
one thing is is it blows out the gastric
glands you got these stomach glands
they're in your stomach
those stomach glands make or break
all kinds of different health conditions
when you lose all your hcl
because these stomach lands get tired
and tired in your stomach and they got
tired and they get tired
what happens is then we do all this
apple cider vinegar
it's because we're trying to get rid of
acid reflux we're trying to get rid of
bloating we're trying to make our skin
better
apple cider vinegar can get you better
it can fix anything
oh what's wrong with you oh apple cider
vinegar you got gout
apple cider vinegar you got eczema
psoriasis take
two tablespoons of apple cider vinegar
that will fix everything
you got you got and you know what it
doesn't work that way
it's not what happens it's not how it
works
it's it's you know it's not it's not a
problem
solver it's a problem maker
for a lot of people along the way as
time goes on
and i'm gonna explain why like why does
it help somebody with acid reflux
why does it help somebody with acid
reflux but
somebody else it gives them really bad
acid reflux like
they drink it they're like oh my god
they're throwing up or they drink it and
they're like stomach gets bloated
bloated bloated bloated bloated
like dear lord what just happened or
they drink it they're like i feel sick
and nauseous and i'm dizzy
you know and there's a reason why
someone can drink it and feel that way
and then another person
can drink it and be like hey i think my
acid reflux is improving whoa
i think i'm getting a little slimmer
around the waistline whoa
so i'm going to talk about the
differences cindy don
hey thank you i listened to this episode
this morning i wasn't aware of a lot of
this and i have so many symptoms
and had no clue how many things vinegar
is
in yeah you know i talked to people over
the years and i'm like stay away from
vinegar
if you're gonna do a vinegar do apple
cider vinegar okay
if you're not gonna get rid of your
vinegar i've had people say
i'm not getting rid of my vinegar i'm
not going i'm not i'm keeping my vinegar
i'll be like can you do apple cider
vinegar
it's the best one i've been saying it's
the best one
for 35 plus years like it's the best one
but guess what there's all kinds of
pitfalls even with that
so check it out i'm going to go a little
bit further and someone's got a question
can you use a straw and i'm going to
talk about that straw
so it's the medical medium podcast at
apple podcast that's the uncensored
version the uncensored platform so if
you want to hear
the medical medium podcast at other
platforms it's going to be censored
missing little pieces
i know every now and then somebody be
like what do you mean well you'll be
missing pieces and so forth you won't be
able to hear the whole thing
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast
and you'll hear the apple cider vinegar
episode
and you'll also hear other episodes like
the neurological symptom episode the
brain fog episode
right the meditations the moon
meditation the brain meditation
wait do you hear those guided
meditations and what they do and how
they can help heal you you know
free is a bird meditation where you go
on a trip flying and you free your soul
check those out when you can so um look
you know you guys valerie says hi from
seattle i love that you share info when
you're looking out for me
you know i'm honored i want to look out
for you guys so i want to talk about
can you drink can you drink
apple cider vinegar or whether diluting
water or straight
can you do it with a straw first of all
you're going to hit the back molars no
matter what you stick a straw in your
mouth and you suck that stuff
up it's going to get somewhere it's
going to get on the back molars there's
no question it's going to get there
so that's number one you guys so
important to know number two is
unless you jam that straw so far down
your throat
and you actually try to suck that stuff
up from your glass through a straw with
a straw halfway down your throat
you're really not going to keep it away
from your teeth but that's not the
problem
it's not about it touching your teeth so
much
it's about it being in the body acetic
acid has a chemical reaction so it's not
just
when it touches something like teeth
it's not that it's the chemical reaction
that happens
inside the body trace mineral calcium we
rely on
to keep our bones strong so they stay
strong throughout the years
trace mineral calcium is how we keep our
bones strong
our teeth strong and what happens when
you put that acetic acid
i know a lot of people say what's acetic
acid what is that
well it's vinegar and a lot of people
say you know
how can i do this let me use a straw
that's not it when you dump the acetic
acid in your body
a chemical reaction happens throughout
your entire body
and then it starts to leach that's when
it could leech
calcium it can take your trace mineral
calcium away
so that that trace mineral calcium isn't
going into bones isn't going into place
it's like
okay you know vinegar use for decades
will lead you into
problems with your bones and teeth and
apple cider vinegar yeah it's from
apples and i talked about in the episode
why it's good but you gotta listen
to the episode to know why apple cider
vinegar i say
is good but why you still have to worry
about the uncensored
platform is the medical medium podcast
at apple podcast the link is in the
description
make sure you hear this it's so
important um
and i'm live right now you guys live
streaming just so you know we're live
right now i always go on live that's
what i like to do
so um jennifer says listening to it a
second time now
thank you for listening to it the second
time because then i know that you're
actually
like getting every you're getting all
the details you're getting all the info
wow i've been taking so much of it this
makes so much sense i'm off it thank you
i'm happier off of it now you got to
know something i have nothing to gain
to get you off of apple cider vinegar
like what motive can i have
um get off apple cider vinegar that's
going to help me a lot over here
anthony william let me tell you what
happens when i tell you to get off apple
cider vinegar anthony william gets a lot
of crap so the only thing i have to gain
by getting you off your apple cider
vinegar is a whole
bunch of noise and crap and so
i don't like making my life more
difficult than it already is with all
the stuff i'm up against for putting out
truth
all the time constantly and it it goes
against the trends that are actually
backed by money
you guys know how it works but i have
nothing to gain by trying to actually
say
say hey stop doing your two tablespoons
apple cider vinegar every morning
stop doing this i have nothing what can
i gain besides a smack in the head
which i get anyway from all this stuff
like why do i want that anyway
bottom line okay let's go into what it
does your gastric glands this is
critical michelle l says people are
detailed oriented
laugh out loud um so people aren't
detailed oriented laughable laugh out
loud that i messed that up just now
uh read that wrong so listen you guys
your little stomach glands produce
hcl that's how you keep your bloating
down
that's how you keep pathogens down like
bad bacteria
that's how you break down and digest
food
properly okay it's that hydrochloric
acid that your
your stomach glands produce and
when you drop in acetic acid like boom
i got apple cider vinegar in here two
tablespoons
it's mixed in water i'm gonna have some
now
oh god so acidic ah my mouth is
puckering
mmm ah my stomach feels sick now
and this is just straight water but the
point is is when you put that apple
cider vinegar in
what it does okay is the minute it goes
into the stomach
your stomach the lining of your stomach
sees it as a poison
so it starts to release mucus so it
starts to produce mucus to battle the
acetic acid while
it's sitting inside your stomach it
starts to battle it
and then it's one thing the next thing
is your
gastric glands have to over produce now
hcl
to try to neutralize this acetic acid
because now there's an
acid competition going on okay so your
gastric glands are trying to literally
neutralize the stuff it's
pouring out the hcl what happens is you
can
play that game if you got strong stomach
lands
you can play that game for years until
that game
bites you in the butt and then you lose
all your hcl and then you're just in bad
shape altogether
lena says linda says i think it has
burned my esophagus
i drank it regularly and now i'm
wondering what's wrong with my voice
it listen i mean you can heal that you
can heal things
you can work on healing but yes it's
that aggressive that acetic acid is that
aggressive
loreno hey hi anthony acv is causing a
variety of responses which is good
uh sorry is causing a variety of
responses which is good
people are talking and questioning so
the episode really is helping out there
amazing ruffled feathers
yeah i like that term ruffled feathers
haha yes
that terms better than getting a lot of
crap
that's really good so anyway look you
guys
um patina says patina says i i feel so
amazing with your medi with your
meditations you know
the meditations are really healing for
the soul
the moon meditation really powerful you
guys check them out
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
that's the official platform
best place to listen to it without a
doubt it's uncensored it won't be
disturbed
listen to it there so important the link
is in the description
and it's free it's free like
huh you know i'm not even saying not
even saying hey can you get the cleanse
the heel book to help you guys heal and
move your lives forward faster not even
talking about the cleanse the heel book
these days which you can get free at the
library too
but i want you guys to hear these
episodes because then i know
you can help protect yourself you can
help heal
um alexandra says brain fog episode was
gold
it's one of my favorite episodes the
brain fog episode the medita
the meditations are helping me heal at
another level
sharing it everywhere thank you for
sharing it everywhere thank you
thank you you're helping others you know
it's about people healing a link is in
the description
so i'll talk about apple cider vinegar a
little bit more so
look i get it people they get attached
to something they don't want to lose
their
vinegar okay people love their vinegar
they love it in their food
they love it you know so it's not too
far of a stretch for somebody to say hey
apple cider vinegar is going to help you
try this try a tablespoon of it every
day it's going to get rid of your
disease it's going to get rid of your
symptoms and conditions it's going to
get rid of whatever
and you know i know people are like
they're they're desperate to try to heal
things and
it's it's an easy it sounds like an easy
quick fix you know and they're just like
okay let me try this
and then you know hear more out there
you know pro at acv
let me try it let me try it but really
what's happening
you blow out your gastric glands this is
just some stuff right
you get the acetic acid you lose your
calcium you wear down your teeth you end
up in a dentist chair
and you know what's going to happen when
you end up in a dentist chair you know
it's like
happens to the plant-based people they
always end up in dentist chairs but it's
like no one talks about
a little bit of vinegar here throughout
their life nobody talks about other
things it's just it's crazy
leslie says that love love your
straightforward shooting of information
your sarcasm and your podcast makes me
laugh
and hearing your voice is like hearing a
message straight from a father thank you
i try my best i know i'm more annoying
here
i know because a family member said you
know it's funny because on your youtubes
you seem really annoying and then you
see really annoying sometimes
because you're you know you want to get
your information out to help people heal
but on the podcast
seems like it's a whole nother thing so
you guys got to hear the podcast it's a
whole nother thing
that's funny it's because you know i
want you guys to heal
and i want to kind of i want to make
sure that i inspire you the best i can
and i know some people they're like all
right
i get it you want me to do something to
heal and that could be annoying i get it
i just want to look out for you guys i
mean
what else is what else is what else is
there to do you think about if you're
suffering with a symptom or condition
let's work on it and heal so medical
medium podcast at apple podcast is
uncensored
that's where you hear it apple cider
vinegar teeth dissolver episode
you don't want to miss it um i have
straight water in here today i don't
even have tea in here
i was kidding about the acv in here
you guys should try the meditations the
moon meditation
freeze the bird meditation i'll talk
about the moon meditation for a moment
too okay
it's using the moon's magnetic pole
not gravitational pull really magnetic
pole pearl says
the uh meditations are powerful are
amazing
everybody says amazing so the magnetic
pull using that when you connect to that
you're doing the moon meditation
it can help you relieve emotional pain
help you relieve
old soul wounds so you have to try it
amy says this is a good question what
about baking soda
totally not for it doing the whole
baking soda thing getting it all in your
intestinal tract
bad idea i'm sorry i haven't even said
enough about that
i should probably talk about that some
sometime too it's terrible
terrible uh shen i only sleep after i
hear your meditations thank you soc and
aw
um share the meditations with other
people leave a review at apple podcast
if you can
if you can you know if you guys have got
a minute if you can it'll be great to
get other people there
uh sydney says i've been having a lot of
brain fog and anxiety attacks that
follows from
that so i definitely have to check out
that video yeah
you got to check it out you gotta chase
an audio not a video which it's an audio
it's a podcast
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
the link is in the description
if you have an android or you have some
other kind of device
just go to medicalmedium.com you'll see
the menu podcast in the menu
then you can listen so that's fine rita
says which of your books would you
recommend to help
with psoriatic arthritis you're looking
at it right there
psoriatic throat arthritis is in there
cleanse the heel it's got over symptom
200 symptoms in condition
75 recipes guys that book is on sale
right now at amazon.com us
for 16.99 51 off um
see leah says i love your meditations i
do them every night before i go to
sleep it calms me and i sleep like a
baby
also coffee podcast was so touching so
sad i cried so much
the coffee the coffee matcha tea
chocolate podcast i just listened to it
yesterday and
last night and it just it blew me away
again
and it is sad you know i talked about
the whole farming situation with it i
talked about other things
yeah it's unbelievable really cindy says
yes the brain fog
on point feels so great to have someone
that understands and also gives us
solutions that aren't
medications forever grateful thank you
for being on here i'm grateful for you
grateful for what you're doing for your
health and for yourself
grateful for sharing the episodes with
other people so they can heal
being a beacon of light to help others
heal i mean that's what
matters that's what matters um so
important to know say guys you know the
apple cider vinegar
saga that i've seen develop over time
and just and just grow and grow and grow
has been something that's really
disheartening to some degree because i'm
like okay great well
no one's gonna who has time whose energy
when you're sick who's time
energy reserves resources when you're
sick
you're not feeling good you're
struggling who has all that time and
energy
to just all to throw away to something
that may not
help you in the end or doesn't help you
in the end you know
i will say this if you're gonna do
vinegar and
that's just the bottom line and i can't
stop you
and i can't okay do the apple cider
vinegar for sure if you're gonna do
vinegar
do it i would do it sparingly and i
would only do it in your dishes that you
like
if you're not gonna give up vinegar but
i
i would let it go if you can and other
vinegars too
like you know i talk about what apple
cider vinegar really does that's good
topically i could talk about putting it
in a foot bath one option there talk
about others too so you might want to
check it out in the episode
apple cider vinegar teeth dissolver
episode
metaqueen podcast at apple podcast um
irena says i love your poems at the end
of every episode
do they come from spirit or you write
them yourself
they come from spirit of compassion is
where they come from
and you know spirit compassion has a way
of delivering information
so that we can relate and so that's
what's incredible the messages from
above
in the poems and check you know check it
out when you get a chance
you know it's at the end of each episode
most of the episodes anyway
and uh it's you know it's funny the
podcast
is a lot of work but it's so worth it
when the episode is done
when it's done and i'm uploading it i'm
like
going to help more people heal gonna
help more people get better
so it's really great because that's what
it that's what it's about
it's about neurological symptoms are you
guys dealing with ringing in the ears
tinnitus aches and pains jaw pain
neck pain dizziness feeling of being on
a boat
right vertigo you know any kind of ticks
and spasms buzzing humming popping in
the ears
vibrations in the body burning gums
burning mouth
trigeminal neuralgia migraines anxiety
and panic
mandy says where do i find your podcast
for anxiety
okay so neurological symptoms is the one
you want
for that so what you do is you go
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
it's link is in the description look for
it look for the brain fog episode
look for neurological symptom episode
both of those
are neurological it's all neurological
anxiety
is your nervous system and what happens
is the neurological symptoms
i talk about the vagus nerve and phrenic
nerves
those are the anxiety nerves phrenic
vagus nerve that's the anxiety nerves
okay so important we're live right now
by the way you guys if you just came on
here
um i like doing it live i like doing
these videos live you know what i mean
and
if i say something that's whatever is
whatever it's live
it's just we do the best we can you know
um stumble on a word or two whatever
so the bottom line is neurological
symptoms great one
upgrade episode brain fog episode did
you check out the air fresheners
episode air freshener sent to candles
because why do i have to like
say it again because someone told me the
other day and said
hey i just plugged in a whole bunch of
air fresheners because
my cat is smelling up the house or
something or i think it was the cattery
they said
was one of their pets they said so i put
in all these plug-in air fresheners
they're like what
get the plug-in air fresheners out of
the house toss them out
scented candles toss them out use the
natural candles you know that no
none of that scented you know chemical
scented stuff because
you'll you'll have a problem that i talk
about in the episode you have to listen
to the air freshener or sent the candle
cologne perfume episode
at medical meeting podcast apple podcast
you got to see that right there
um nancy says what is it that you are
selling
and what is it all about with love
please tell me i got
i just got in well i'm not selling and
selling anything it's a free resource
there's not even commercials in this
resource it's a podcast
it's the podcast episode which i'm
talking about is apple cider vinegar
podcast episode
so i want you to listen to it i would
like you to listen to it
anne's medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast link is in the description
thank you for coming on um and yeah i'm
not selling anything and you can get
the cleanse the heel book to help heal
that free at the library if you want you
know i mean i don't know like that's
really great
you can also get it on sale on amazon
but the bottom line is i'm not selling
the podcast it's a free resource so you
can heal
it's a great question there's no
infomercials there's no commercials
you'll see that on podcasts you go on a
podcast and you're like why is there a
commercial now
why are there infomercials why are there
advertisements left and right
you don't get that with my stuff not now
anyway and i'm trying to keep it that
way
for sure valerie says i needed to hear
the neurological one
so much me if that's so much you then
you've got a lot of the symptoms then i
feel really bad so i'm sorry you're
struggling with that i've learned so
much about my health from you and can't
thank you enough
valerie i know you can heal you keep up
all the hard work do you have the
cleanse the heel book
um you know so you can get all kinds of
information the neurological episode is
really powerful at least
you know what i told a a doctor friend
the other day that contacted me and said
i listen to your neurological episode i
love it
um you know and these tools are great
and this doctor friend of mine is
applying those
tools for their patients with
neurological symptoms so at least you
know the tools are in there in that
episode
so it's great it's great um so
anyway apple cider vinegar the teeth
dissolver episode
it's out check it out link is in the
description
all right subscribe to medical media
podcast at apple podcast
put a review in there if you really like
that would really help spread the
message
share if you can share the share the
podcast episodes
um donna says love your podcast i got
three of your books
looking to get healing incredible i'm so
proud of you
blown away truly blown away you guys are
amazing
proud of all of you you're doing so good
um just one last note
meditations bring them in your life
i guide you through it i do all the work
in the meditations the moon meditation
the brain meditation although the brain
meditation
it's it's pretty intense so i'm just
letting you know it's pretty intense the
brain meditation the moon meditation
and then the freeze the bird meditation
um all three of them
nancy says would you send me the link to
your episodes i suffer
a lot with arthritis oh my god arthritis
is terrible so the link is in the
description
that's where it is and you can listen to
the episodes and i hope you do
hope you tell somebody else about it as
well
so susie said so many air fresheners out
there yeah there's
smells everywhere it's like intoxicates
us from every angle
breaks down our immune system all of it
so it's pretty intense
um nesmus says brain meditation is great
i'm honored you're doing the brain
meditation i'm honored you're using it
to heal because you can still use it you
can still
keep on using it the anesthetist thank
you aw soc
it's kind every time you think soc soc
appreciates it believe me
joseph shingles can be reversed see
cleanse to heal joseph thanks thanks
for telling everybody that it's so
important people know that
it is oh yeah uh rosanna says i look
tired oh
yeah tired to the bone without a doubt
working hard just got a book
in because you guys got another book
that will be coming out eventually
been working day and night on the book
day and night on the podcasts episodes
day and night on other stuff i'm working
on i'm probably getting four hours of
sleep at night
consecutively for weeks now i worked a
22-hour day the other day
22-hour day and i
am tired but you know what
you know it's life life just got to make
sure i get this work done
make sure you guys heal in everything um
so look you guys proud of all of you
just know i stand with you um right
alongside your healing with you guys try
the guided meditations
i want to be able to heal just with
everything that you
everything you have in your body is
there it's just about giving our bodies
what it needs
it's about giving our ourselves what it
needs
giving our soul what it needs and the
whole combination
so we can just get better and better and
better and better i love you guys take
care