spinach soup that's right medical medium
spinach soup it's a powerful tool it's
not just spinach soup it is a game Cher
it can take someone from here to there
with their healing it can and I'll tell
you why for a lot of reasons we're going
to make it and I'm going to make it I
got the spinach here I got the celery
here I got the tomatoes here got a
little basil got some oranges I'm really
pumped up about this and we're talking
about low sodium low sodium sodium
crisis or somebody with low sodium
somebody not able to retain sodium or
somebody that's actually maybe doing it
wrong and they don't know it but they
need to do different things to keep
their sodium up to par um hey let's go
into that right now too so and I have
some tea right here Lem bomb
tea nice good to see you guys coming on
here we're going to be talking about a
lot about sodium how much sodium are you
on are you doing sodium are you adding
sodium to all your stuff so what you
hear in the health movement
is you'll hear and you've been hearing
this probably for years I mean it's
going on I think 20 years maybe 30 years
as you'll hear out there take salt and
put it in some water give yourself some
salt water you know take a pinch of salt
or a bunch of salt and throw it in take
a teaspoon of salt or more and throw it
in your water you have to have salt in
there do the rock salt do the sea salt
do the high quality salt and so that's
been a big one in the health movement
it's ridiculous it's actually not even
correct for somebody what they need and
it it's one of those snake oil things
that are out there and it's just being
passed around there's no science to it
there's no real science to it it's just
one of those things where it was a good
idea hey put salt in your water that
will keep you stable and so forth but
really it doesn't it dehydrates you
further doesn't allow the water that
you're drinking to work for you and it's
not the right kind of salt so let's talk
about different salts as we're doing
this right now and you guys if you just
came on here I'm making the healing
spinach soup the medical medium spinach
soup
I'm really excited about it it's a
powerful healing tool I mean if you use
the spinach soup correctly meaning you
make it and you consume it you make it
right and you consume it on a regular
basis what it can do for you how it can
just change fibromyalgia ra you know
eczema psoriasis chronic fatigue
syndrome Lyme disease like what it can
do for you is a miracle multiple
sclerosis you can literally live on that
spinach soup every single day
and clear up problems like neurological
problems aches and pains tingles and
numbness stiffness of the neck um knee
problems inflammation all through the
body I mean how it can help is just a
miracle so we're going to go into that
but we're talking about sodium and
interesting spinach has a lot of sodium
in it spinach does but there's a
difference between that and throwing
sodium in water so let's talk about the
two different sodiums out there so
there's commercialized sodium out there
that kind that's thrown in junk food
processed food fried greasy food out
there it's the commercialized salt it's
also the salt that you see in the
grocery stores that's not like Himalayan
rock salt it's not like sea salt or
something like that or a really high
quality sea salt instead it's the
commercialized junk salt it's what I
have called All These Years road salt
it's in all the food it's in all the
restaurants restaurants don't buy 50 $60
bags of salt like a $60 bag of black
salt a $60 bag of you know rock salt
people don't do that in restaurants and
restaurants out there worldwide it's
just salt it comes in a 50 lb Satchel 50
lb bag and that's what goes and it's you
know it's all about how you can make
that meal as cheap as possible for the
bottom line that's what restaurants do
out there I mean that is the reality
that's life out there on planet Earth so
what happens is people get road salt
they get
commercialized Den nutrient ised salt
that's what they do and it's all about
you know getting that in all the food to
make people like it and make them crave
it that's the key and then there's
hidden salts hidden
msgs yeast extracts which are msgs and
you'll notice yeast extracted is in
everything these days now I mean it's
gone from here to here like it used to
be just in one item here one item there
in the past now it's in everything
organic foods packaged Foods soups
sauces you see yeast extract everywhere
what that is is MSG toxic MSG and it's
thrown in everything toxic MSG with
added road salt commercialized sodium
other different
chemicals thrown in tagged and named as
yeast extract thrown in everything out
there that you see now you'll see it in
sauces and soups like I said you'll see
it in packaged Foods canned stuff you'll
just see yeast extract everywhere out
there so you got to look out for that
the yeast extract is not good but it's
another form of bad sodium another form
of bad sodium really important to know
so I'm trying to cruise through this
information cuz I got a lot of
information and I'm trying to like I'm
trying to spill it out the best I could
for you guys so let's hit it so you got
the commercialized rock salt I mean not
rock salt commercialized road salt you
have that called it that for years it
doesn't have the nutrients it doesn't
have the profile in it and then you have
other salts bleached salt yeah they
actually have
bleached sodium if you can imagine not
only just commercialized it but they
bleach bleached it that's a whole
another game too now that's not as
popular anymore but back in the 60s and'
7s salts were bleached so we've learned
to acclimate and learn to like salt even
if we don't realize it we've learned to
like it we become addicted so we're a
society today that is addicted to Salt
now a lot of coffee shops put salt in
the water in the machines so it becomes
coffee Salt Water coffee they don't
advertise it you don't know it nobody
knows it but sodium is in a lot of
coffees out there it's in a lot of
coffee shops it's in a lot of um coffee
chains not in everyone not in everywhere
so you might know somebody be like they
don't put sodium in their coffee there
you go medical medium but let me tell
you a lot of them do and there's a
reason for that they want it salt they
want their coffee salty and then when
you add your sugar and your milks or
whatever you add your soy whatever it is
that's people like in their coffee you
add that in and then that plus the
sodium that's additionally added you
have yourself a coffee that becomes
really addictive and so you keep on
going to that coffee chain to that
coffee place and you can do that you
know for a lifetime I mean you can go to
the same coffee chain for a lifetime
because of it and people say I like that
coffee so it's the sodium in that you
know in that coffee you're drinking
that's really kind of makes it really
kick in for a double addiction so not
only do you have the caffeine addiction
right there but you have the sodium and
the caffeine combined surprise surprise
surprise nobody knew that
ha but yes it's true so it's sodium
thrown in everybody's coffee that they
buy at the coffee chains uh-huh so
there's that one so let's go into the M
MSG a little bit too okay yeast extract
is being thrown in
everything because it's another cheat
way of getting sodium in there so you
actually have a burst of flavor you can
look at the package the package of the
food the package of the can okay and
you'll see a certain amount of sodium
but yet it tastes so good it tastes so
salty why why why a lot of times yeast
extract is thrown in there but they
don't add it they don't meaning they
don't add that Sal salt level they don't
put it to the ingredient list you see
how it works 300 mg 300 mg of sodium one
gram of Mill one gram of sodium two gram
of sodium but yeast extract really
potent form of sodium takes it to now Bo
off the charts so there's a lot of
packaged food and a lot of canned food
and stuff even healthy stuff I'm talking
about like organic or healthy stuff or
all natural whatever you want to call it
organic this that non GMO and you're
like oh these these chips are really
good this is really oh this is my
favorite chip right here yeah oh let me
look at the sodium honey we better look
at the sodium are you getting too much
sodium in you and it's like yeah it says
300 milligrams that's about pretty much
the level I see another whatever you
know and then but it tastes so good
because the yeast extract is a whole
another level of sodium that they are
cheating people and people don't
understand this and that's the thing you
know like um these are hidden things
that no one's talking about instead
they're talking about other things
medical medium brought to town over the
years talking about the fragrances now
they're talking about the citric acid
now CU a medical medium they're talking
about right they're talking about so
many different things they're talking
about the natural flavors now
but yeast extract that's a whole another
one so I want to get that out there
because people need to look out because
it's rocket it it's taken off and I want
people to look out for their health and
their well-being and that yeast extract
is is toxic it's toxic not just because
of the MSG which is one reason why it's
toxic I mean they're actually selling
MSG more than ever before now people are
sprinkling that stuff looks like white
asbest they're just sprinkling that
stuff on everything you know MSG people
are buying MSG MSG is good for you now
it's like absurd it's insane but that's
what I mean how do you heal chronic
illness when so much is happening out
there like this so so let's get into it
a little bit more in the sod world the
yeast extract is a hidden sodium right
there you got to look out MSG natural
flavor hidden sodium in a lot of
situations natural and organic flavoring
right sodium it's another level of it
MSG another level of it and then it
doesn't have to go on the package so you
don't see it on the package instead but
it's in there and you taste it and you
become like a sodium demon like it takes
over you that's like a literally an
addiction and you know people have to
deal with that I'm going to have a
little sip of Lem mom tea and then I'm
going to continue if you guys are okay
damn so addictive right Kim
exactly all
right let's
go talk about sodium deficiencies in
people like they end up going to a
hospital and they get their blood tested
they're sodium levels are down and first
of all there's a couple things to
understand a lot of people go to thep
hospital it's not because of a sodium
deficiency but they don't know why the
person's really struggling they don't
know why the person ended up there with
a fainting spell or whatever it is they
don't know why the person ends up um
they're not sure what's going on the
person goes to the hospital not sure
they having a heart attack they having a
stroke what's wrong with them did they
faint are they dehydrated right all
these things that have to be checked out
all the boxes have to be checked when
people go to the hospital
so what happens to a lot of people that
get food poisoning or they get sick
their sodium level strong drop their
sodium levels drop and depending on what
time of day and what time of night and
so forth depending on what kind of
stress they're under how hydrated they
are depending on how much water they
consumed if they're consuming too much
water your sodium could drop if they're
consuming too much water and they're not
consuming enough like coconut water
they're not having spinach soup they're
not having enough celery juice maybe
they're only doing 8 O 16 ounces of
celery juice but it's not enough for
what they might need but a lot of people
out there just in the conventional world
alone end up at the hospital with low
sodium and a lot of people end up in the
hospital because they've had a stomach
flu stomach bug or a flu or they don't
feel good or covid or something and they
they end up in the oh I said the word
we'll see what happens they end up in
the hospital and they do all these tests
they're like what's wrong with these
people and they find that their sodium
might be low in that
moment and um so they instantly go well
okay we got to hook you up with a salt
bag you got to get an IV bag got to get
IV and you get the you know the the the
salt bag is what they do they hook you
up they bring your sodium levels up
they're like okay we're we're good we
brought your sodium levels up but people
don't realize that one thing is sodium
levels that the conventional medical
model lives
on is sodium levels that are determined
from high salt diet for decades for
decades in the last 60 70 80 years they
been
determining that salt level that number
that they believe a normal human being
should sustain or
hold that number is too high to begin
with in the conventional model this is a
mistake made now you have to realize
they' come up with a lot of different
numbers throughout the decades one
number back in the late
40s mid to late 40s was B12 so they were
able to determine hey we can look at B12
in people and said the 1950s and 1960s
came along and it was all about B12 but
they determine somebody's number but
they don't realize in a B12 situation
how life has changed the amount of
stress people are under the amount of
pollution people are under the amount of
um radiation people experience would
don't even realize it and you and here's
a side note right here don't mean to go
off a beaten path but you got to be
really careful when you're hiking on
trails and you're in in mountainous re M
mountainous regions and stuff like
that you got to be careful that you know
there's a lot of testing that is
occurred out there in different places
in different lands and there's a lot of
radioactive areas and you got to be
careful because people walk right into
radioactive areas and then you know 6
months later 2 months later their nails
are falling off their hands and they're
having all kinds of different problems
but that's another note I want to talk
about because it's happening more often
than people know all right so you guys
coming on here I'm making spinach soup
mhm we're talking about a lot of
information right here here we're
talking about sodium are you on enough
sodium are you sodium deficient what is
going on in your life quick announcement
too just so you know Cafe Gratitude
medical medium collaboration the menu is
launching October 15th so October 15th
in LA Cafe Gratitude has medical medium
meals on the menu unbelievable it's
actually really exciting
too if you were able to get a ticket for
the 21st 22nd 23rd 24th of October where
I'm going to be there at Cafe Gratitude
for a meet and greet and we're all going
to sit down and eat if you happen to get
that ticket in you're coming I can't
wait to see you I'm excited congrats on
getting that ticket because it was hard
a lot of people wanted those tickets so
if you were able to somehow beat
thousands of people into getting that
ticket and you're going to be there it's
going to be be fun I'm happy for you I'm
excited I'm going to be there I'm going
to say
hi another
announcement Gia Gia Health conference
so it's the Gia and heel Health
conference I'm excited about this the
Gaia and heel Health conference all
right November 9th I am pumped up about
this I'm going to be speaking right
there check out my website you can see
the details and the information you can
sign up to the live stream you can be
there live I'm going to be there so it's
going to be in Colorado you know when
you get a chance I haven't been to
Colorado in a while I'm actually excited
about it I want to go to Colorado I'm
going to travel around Colorado for a
little bit and explore
Colorado it's going to be really cool
just letting you
know there are limited tickets so um
make sure you grab one if you can
limited ticket at the Gaia heel
conference November 9th so I just want
to let everybody know are you going to
be there are you buying a ticket I'm
going to be there as a speaker I hope
you guys
come it's going to be exciting it's I've
I've never done anything for Gaia so
this is exciting I'm I'm pumped up about
it you guys I want to give Gia my
support in any way I can I'm going to be
there I'm pumped up Jackie over there ad
dubs the nature podcast is my faith
nature is saving me mentally always I
have so many friends in my
backyard I love nature love nature it's
incredible Christina
K hey a who attacked your podcast
aha yep uh somebody attacked my podcast
the
Spotify podcast medical medium on
Spotify and it is completely gone it is
wiped out I'm going to talk about that
for a minute somewh over there in IG do
you know that the medical medium podcast
content on Spotify is no longer
available yep I do know about it so do
you guys remember a podcast episode I
just put out pretty Rec recently do you
guys remember the podcast that I put out
it's about
damaging and problematic
supplements right one thing that has
happened with medical medium for quite
some time is I get attacked severely by
Massive money-making Industries now I
know a whole bunch of people are out
there they're on social and they're on X
and everything and they're trying to
solve all these different injustices and
health and everything else and I get it
and there's a lot of different problems
out there right but they're
overlooking like other big problems that
are causing serious serious problems
with people they're overlooking that
medical medium doesn't do that right I
already broke all the information out on
all the fragrances I already broke all
the information out on that original
information of when you go through the
airports and your luggage goes through
that you have to throw your luggage out
after a certain amount of time so you
don't have your baby or child just you
know you know standing next to that
luggage how it's loaded with radiation
I've already done so many things right
the blood draw I talked about the blood
draw crisis I've I've put out things
that are actually brain bending
mindbending because it's just it's
incredible information to educate people
so they can heal information from s so
right or how what I've never known of so
much of it but what happened was I put
out the podcast just like other podcasts
that I put out and I I obviously pissed
people off and I put out the problematic
and damaging supplement podcast and you
got to think about it there's a lot of
money behind colostrum a lot of money it
is an evil
evil
industry um evil for a lot of reasons
and there there's a ton of influencers
selling claustrum there is so much going
on with claustrum Millions hundreds of
hundreds of millions of dollars are
being made off of colostrum and um I
gave colostrum a real ass whipping is
what I did and um and also charcoal
activated charcoal Millions hundreds of
millions of dollars into that activated
charcoal industry a lot of people
selling it a lot of influencers pushing
it I gave charcoal an ass
whipping and then then you know and then
other things too also I did and ACV you
know the ACV chewy gummies and all that
I hit that one pretty hard and people
that work in these
these apps and in these companies you
know they get they might have somebody
invested in it and so forth that they
might be invested in it and then
boom there it goes gone you know the
podcast is gone so for
now and uh and I'm working on it so it's
all
good Denise says I thought gummy
colostrum okay
um terrible absolutely terrible so many
people are duped I mean the Wolves
pulled over their eyes on that one you
want to get sick and sicker someday take
colostrum you will get sicker and sicker
it's it's uh really bad stuff I have
a podcast coming out pretty soon talking
about some different stuff and you'll
you'll learn about it it's really
scary yeah it says Apple podcast is that
secure right Apple podcast
also um got upset because of that
episode so you know and so there's all
kinds of triggers being pulled right now
so bullets are flying I'm missing a lot
of episodes right now on Apple because
what happens is that medical medium for
years has been exposing like the real
evil right the real evil and
so because of that I'm always attacked
and just always all kinds of things like
that and you guys know this I mean I I
haven't talked too much about it over
the years but I took a little bit about
it
right like for instance this whole
sodium thing this will get me a bunch of
crap too just so you know you don't know
it but the whole throw salt and water
thing is like a demon in the health
movement just see now every trainer
tells every single client throw salt in
water every single bodybuilder throws
salt in water every single health coach
throw salt and water every s single
naturopath chiropractor throws salt in
water that's a demon in the industry all
on its own like the crap I'm going to
get for the talking about how that's BS
to throw salt in water how it's
problematic and there's and all kinds of
things about it so but this is how it
works I mean you know and you get
original unique information from medical
medium all these years when nobody was
doing anything if you even go back five
six seven years
ago right8 years ago 9 years ago and I
was publishing information that was
mind-blowing people didn't didn't even
know on any level so much of it's been
poach and stolen but the point is is
like what was everybody doing all they
had was some eat better books out there
it was like paleo books that was it just
you know some eat better books was about
it nobody knew anything about what
caused illness sickness symptoms
conditions true causes nobody uttered
heavy metals it was just um it was
ridiculous so so a lot of years I I put
up with a lot throughout the years you
guys have no idea how many times I've
been a
attacked and jabbed at and stabbed in
the back and everything else because
you're not supposed to do that you have
to behave and you have to just you have
to act like a Roman you have to be a
Roman you have to behave you can't look
out for the chronically ill God forbid
you do something that's really for the
chronically ill like really looking out
for them stopping them from from
saturating their intestinal tract and
colon with with uh colostrum and
charcoal stopping them from destroying
their teeth and bones with ACV like the
industries became monsters billion
dollar in Industries so all it takes is
me putting something out there and they
still they still fear a little old me
it's ridiculous all right let's go into
sodium a little bit more and I'm going
to be making a spinach soup in a couple
minutes too which you see is this
beautiful pile of spinach right here
which I'm excited about I'm going to I'm
going to like show you tricks on like
making a really good spinach soup and it
it has to do too with good oranges and
good tomatoes but if you can't get good
oranges and good tomatoes we can do
something else but we can still make
that spinach soup and get it to taste
great in the whole
bit all right so let's hit a little bit
more in the sodium front there's all
these hidden sodiums and then there's
also techniques like putting sodium in
water and drinking that in that fashion
all the time it's not a great idea for a
lot of reasons um you're salty when you
put in water and you do it that way you
salt your organs you can actually get a
liver shut down or a case of
pancreatitis if you salt your water too
heavy just so you know you can put your
liver in a catastrophic situation if you
throw salt in your water yeah because
what happens is it's a Mainline to
putting salt into your liver it's
different if you made a tomato sauce and
Grandma threw some salt in it there's a
big difference and still that's not the
best thing in the world because
everybody's so salted out but the point
is when you salt water and you're
somebody with chronic illness and you're
just listening to some trainer out there
whatever it is and you see them online
you see them on social you see them on
YouTube and you see people everybody I
wasn't doing great until I put sodium
till I put salt in a glass of water
every single day and by the way go to to
my website and you can buy my little
sodium packs at the same time whatever
it is the point is you can put your
liver into
catastropic shut down you can go into
liver
failure if you overs salt water and you
don't have a meal around it you don't
have food to try to uptake that sodium
so you're somebody and you're working
out you didn't eat anything that day
you're intermittent fasting or something
you're doing anything like that and
you're sitting there and you're just
throwing salt in water because somebody
told you it's a great idea and you're
training in the gym whatever it is and
you're running on your treadmill I don't
know taking a walk and you're just doing
that you're damaging your liver that's
what you're doing it's crazy all right
so yeah all right and I see somebody see
somebody popping up some certain
influencer names and stuff like that
through there and I just saw one that
has stolen all my liver information in
the just the last 3 4 years they they
read Liver Rescue one that you you know
think is a great person with a lot of
Integrity I just saw that and that
person I won't say their name that
person hijacked half of Liver Rescue and
then they were teaching it on their
YouTube channel and everything else it's
sickening and I just saw that person
like hey yeah this person yeah that
person took Liver Rescue information
it's stuff I got to live with but
whatever okay let's go back a little bit
more into the
sodium aspect of things it's key it's
key to have sodium come from places
where other trace minerals are attached
okay so that means if you use a good
sodium like sea salt right it's going to
have other trace minerals if it's a high
quality sea salt it's if it wasn't
stripped it's going to have some trace
minerals if you use a good rock salt or
something like black salt it's going to
have those trace minerals there right
it's going to help but you still can't
abuse that and throw that in water and
that's what you're doing you're just you
know throwing that water and sending it
down you still can go into liver shock
and shut your liver down for half a day
and if somebody's really sick you can
shut it down even longer and in
eventually into liver failure if you
don't know what you're doing and then
nobody knows what happened to you you go
to the hospital nobody knows what
happened to you so that happens to
people every day because of salt thrown
in water okay so let's keep that in mind
so even when you use these good salts
like a good Himalayan rock salt like a
good sea salt or a good black salt even
if you use that you got to be careful
and use them sparingly I'm not totally
against those salts I'm not you can use
a little bit even on medical medium
dishes but you got to be easy on the
sodium too you can't use a lot of that
you blow out your pallets you'll blow
out your your taste buds and you'll get
you'll acclimate to an addiction level
of
acclamation and you'll you'll then
you'll be like addicted to sodium and
you won't be able to live without it
when you're cooking or making your food
or making your raw dishes you won't be
able to live without it and what's going
to happen is you're going to lose your
taste to food you're going to lose your
taste to other things and you won't be
able to acclimate to those other things
you need like parsley being heavy on
parsley people are adverse to parsley
they don't want to be they don't want to
put lot of parsley in their food they
can't handle it so in including like a
lowfat dish or meal they don't want a
lot of parsley do you ever see anybody
put a head of parsley on a piece of
salmon or a fish do you ever see that no
they won't it's like a Sprinkle of
parsley on dishes whether it's fish
whether it's meat whether it's something
else whether it's a steak whether it's
whatever the sprinkle of parsley right
somebody makes an egg omelette how much
parsley is going in an egg omelette
probably none really it's probably just
a few like red pepper are put in there
and a couple of other things right
onions right in your in your egg
omelette the point is leafy greens are
not eaten enough and leafy herb greens
are not eaten enough they're not in
people's diets they're not there and we
need those because those contain sodium
but the right kind of
sodium and we also need those because we
need to acclimate to their flavors just
like cilantro how many of you guys now
have gotten a lot of metals out of your
system you've also acclimate it to the
flavor of cilantro you can only do so
much and now you can do a lot of it you
can only do a little bit now you can do
a lot of it right the cilantro it's this
is important to know and what happens is
that if you overs salt everything and
you're killing everything with salt
you're never going to acclimate the
foods that will be very important to you
when you consume them on the right
levels and the amount of you know of the
amounts you need and that calls for
spinach too if you're overs salting
everything you're never going to enjoy a
piece of spittage really truly enjoy it
because that's where the sodium should
come from same thing with celery as
well so when we're overs salting our
food with the good salt because that's
what you're thinking too some of you
guys because I know some of you guys are
like I use the best salt you know I use
I use the you know the best Himalayan
salt I use the black salt I use the you
know the the good sea salt from way up
North I understand those are the ones to
use but if you overdo it you're never
going to acclimate properly to the foods
that your body and your organs need and
want you're never going to be able to
acclimate to that spinach to that celery
to those herbs to Lemon you're not going
to be able to really acclimate in the
places you need to do so which are
critical for healing and here goes the
next the next level the sodium in celery
is not the same sodium that they're
putting in all the food it's also not
the same sodium as the rock salt and the
good SE salt and the black salt is
either it's they have a subgroup of
sodium in celery I've talked about that
sodium cluster salts okay it's not only
a macro macro sodium is in celery which
is the best sodium the best one not only
a macro but a micro sodium in celery so
the celery has a micro and macro sodium
in it very important to know there's a
reason for that right this is medicinal
sodium this is a different kind right
spinach spinach leaves spinach the plant
the stems have also sodium in there as
well now the sodium in spinach is bound
so what the difference is it's bound to
other minerals they won't
separate they won't separate
so what happens is when you take a rock
salt Himalayan rock salt when you take a
sea salt and you take black
salt black Salt's a little different I
like it I like it better in many ways if
you take the Himalayan salt and the sea
salt and you throw it in water the trace
minerals don't stay bound they
separate and they lose their viscosity
so this is important to know when you
have sodium coming out of spinach it's
why it's one of the reasons it's so
healing when you have sodium out of
spinach in your diet in your bloodstream
it stays bonded to certain trace
minerals which makes that sodium last
longer in your system and not a flash in
the pan and then boom it's in your organ
and that's it so here's the key right
here big one right here when you're do
sodium in the water like a good salt
that I talked about rock salt sea salt
okay it's a flash in the pan in your
bloodstream it's like treating something
with medications
conventionally that's what it is it's
like treating something conventionally
with
medications
right keep that in mind it's not the
Deep rooted Long Haul of fixing things
and healing things it's the conventional
model mindset you put salt in there it's
in your bloodstream and gone it's a
shining star and then it burns
out understand that this is a big
one so people are getting salt hits and
that's what happens with yeast extract
and natural flavoring those are msgs
those are salts salt
hits so you're getting these quick you
know these quick highs like salt drug
highs you guys see what I'm saying so
what happens is when your trainer's like
yeah you just put salt in water that's
what you need to do get the good salt
you know make sure it's the rock salt or
whatever Himalayan and you do that and
you're getting a quick hit so you're
getting what's called like a salt High
it only sits in your bloodstream for a
certain amount of time gets discarded or
a hunk of it gets buried and
crystallizes so what's happening to a
lot of people's brains is they're
getting crystallizations from salt
deposits in their brains namely MSG is
one of them or
MSG bound to other
salts so what happens is
that sodium can build up over time
Harbor a nice safe haven in your brain
or brain stem and become crystallized as
the years go on and you can literally
have these salt deposits in your brain
that MRIs will be able to detect as
years go on and you're getting older and
older and they're just going to say Mrs
Smith you have Alzheimer's really you
got Metals salt deposits scar tissue and
all kinds of other things growing in
there so you want to minimize whatever
can grow in your head Dr Fawn right
there blood tests change dayto day just
because it's low in serum doesn't mean
it's an accurate reading correct of
what's in the cell even if you use
Spectra cell or other nutritional
analysis I agree that's actually really
good that's really good thank you Dr
Fawn MD amazing doctor and that's
actually um amazing information thank
you for bringing that to our
attention which takes me to another area
I want to go really quick which is is
okay the reading the salt reading in
your blood work in your blood test okay
salt reading should be lower than it is
is what it should be they have it on the
modern world's salt level the modern era
salt level they have it in the 1950s
spectrum of where sodium should be with
everybody had the salt shaker and every
single meal was salted heavily with not
Himalayan rock salt not pink rock
salt not black salt not sea salt
everybody's Shaker had the road salt in
it the
1950s is the stat they use for how much
sodium should be in your bloodstream
that's what they determin should be your
sodium level it was in in a day in an
age of every single meal had a salt
shaker at the table and every man salted
the crap out of their food didn't matter
what it was this is what happened okay
doctors weren't like watch your sodium
Mr Smith watch your sodium Mrs Smith no
they weren't it was like that so it was
everybody was salting the heck out of
their food that's what they were doing
that was the 1950s and it was the road
salt and that's the measurement they're
throwing on you today there it is they
never adjusted it they never did the
science to actually really determine
what's good what's bad and so what
happens is if you threw up one night you
got a little food poisoning maybe you
got like you know the neuro virus maybe
you got the stomach flu something hits
you you've been throwing up for a couple
days you can't really hold food down you
go to the hospital they're going to say
it's your
sodium they're going to say it's your
sodium your sodium is low you're in
you're in a sodium crisis this what it
is say you're somebody with a
neurological problem where you have a
weak neurological system and you're
having a flare up or you're have you're
you're partially dehydrated you don't
have enough glucose to your nervous
system and you end up in the hospital
that night because your husband brought
you in and you're going into the
hospital again because you can't really
feel your arms well that it's not a
stroke you been down this road you had
every test they think it's multiple
sceris they don't know what it is you're
back in the hospital they're going to
say ma'am your sodium's low and that's
why you're dealing with this your
sodium's low and that's what they're
going to tell you that's how it rolls so
keep that in
mind if you're if especially if you're
not able to get what you need in in you
it's another thing your sodium is low
back in the 1950s the TV dinners were
born the TV dinners were so high in salt
it was off the charts everybody was
saturated in salt in the 1950s that's
the test they use still to this day and
that's what's going on there all right
how do you how do you actually sustain
sodium so you're not having to rely on
water and salt water and
salt you have to bring enough sodium
into your diet that naturally occurs in
plants and herbs that is the key right
here okay
so in this glass right here I have lemon
balm not particularly high in
sodium I have honey in here
too and I have
water okay this is not a salty Brew in
my
hand all right if I eat a celery stick
and drink some tea I'm bringing those
sodium cluster salts into the mix into
the bloodstream and it could sustain and
sit in my blood for quite a while a lot
longer than any kind of salt hit so if
you
take Himalayan rock salt or a sea salt
and you throw it in
here okay and mix it up it's only going
to give you a quick hit that quick hit
will be in your bloodstream for a very
short time any excess will either be
urinated out or will go into your liver
or in another organ eventually for
storage it may never come back
out keep that in
mind when you're doing something like
healing tools like the medical medum
spinach soup something changes it's also
addicting so it makes you feel good for
a minute and then makes you feel like
you need more salt is really highly
addictive so that's another thing too
and like I said your acclamation drops
for things that you need salt from and
it raises from for chips and stuff like
that okay so let's hit
that why are you addicted to chips how
many of you guys I want to ask you this
question right here can you be honest I
know you guys will because it's a
medical medium
Community
um so tell me this are you guys eating
chips are you guys are chips getting in
your way are you eating the really
what's called clean chips or healthier
chips what kind of chips are you
consuming give me a rundown on that if
you guys want
how many bags of chips have you had in a
month I've been so Julie says I've been
addicted to chips congrats for being
honest and telling me that's amazing
crispy yeah chips
addict Hey listen by the way I'm not
judging anybody on this chip thing you
need to know that like I'm totally I
totally understand like you need to know
that I understand I'm not judging you on
any level this is important I'm not
crispy you're doing chip
very addicted to Salty snacks says Kim
Miller me me me me me no I see you no oh
my
God okay so clean chips you crave clean
chips right so they're all better chips
everybody you guys are doing a lot of
chips right okay I see a couple of names
of some Brands right okay I see another
brand name of chips whoa you guys are
all doing that chip no wonder why it's
sold for $1.2
billion no wonder why it's sold for $1.2
billion you guys are eating all that
company's chips
amazing all right
so all right so here's what happened so
you're not doing your spinach soup
you're doing chips that's what's going
on all right all right all right there's
no shaming here and there's no judgment
I understand life is hard and I
understand getting a nice bag of what
seems to be a healthier chip salty and
crunchy completely understand
okay
yeah yeah I mean it it it's a higher
quality right a higher quality sea salt
is usually added to like better stuff
out there you'll see sea salt you'll
hear that so I want I want everybody to
know it's okay to use a little bit of
salt if you want to use a little bit of
salt it's okay to use a little bit of a
high quality himalay uh rock salt or a
sea salt okay so like the meals the
medical medium meals at Cafe Gratitude
on October 15th they're easy on the salt
and they use a really high quality sea
salt okay but remember it's not thrown
in water and just thrown in water plus
they're easy on it so I like a little
bit of that here and there okay and I
like that but what happens is that
restaurants put a ton of salt in stuff I
mean they just put grams and grams and
grams of salt in stuff and those crunchy
chips Yep they're they're going to be
salty and they're going to have that
edge so here's the key what has you
coming back for those chips so you stay
addicted is the salt the salt content
keep that in mind along with stuff like
yeast extract in a lot of those
different chips along with natural
flavors in a lot of those different
chips all different forms of sodium
thrown in there okay and MSG and so
forth so that keeps you going it's this
addiction to Salt that's a big part of
what it is so you're going to want to go
and get those chips cuz you want that
salt if you don't have salt on those
chips you will not be eating them I
promise you this if they were
saltless you would have three chips a
week at best and you'd be looking for
salt from something else to to dip the
chip in something
salty so you got to understand it is the
salt that you're addicted to
and that salt over time with on that
level builds up in our organs and so
forth but it also knocks your ability
away your natural ability to gravitate
and consume things like the spinach
right here it takes
away your natural like pallet and your
body's natural connection to something
like spinach instead you're going to
hear something out there spinach is bad
for you Ates aoic acid that's not true
that's not true and this is a raw
spinach soup there's a big difference
spinach is one of those things that if
you cook
spinach some tannins can come out okay
and that could be that that could be you
know one thing too it happens when you
cook spinach a little tannin will come
out it'll make it taste weird even
slightly
bitter when it's raw it is perfect
absolutely perfect perect some are over
there let's see I've been addicted to
chips for my whole life recently I
started having spinach soup and I don't
desire chips as much is that a
coincidence you're getting the right
amount of salt from the spinach soup
into your bloodstream and into your body
and then you're intuitively connecting
to all of that psychically intuitively
all that you're connecting to that that
whole thing and then it's making it so
you're like I don't want those chips as
much I don't want to eat those chips as
much this inredible that is incredible
okay so here's how the industries work
salt something and you will be a buyer
and consumer for a
lifetime make the chip somewhat a better
healthier chip so-called better
healthier chip and salt the crap out of
it and you will eat even more of them
because in your mind they are a
healthier chip so then you feel safer
and better to actually consume that chip
and you're going to be addicted to that
chip because of the amount of salt on
that chip and you are going to be a
buyer of that chip for the rest of your
life what that sodium is going to do
over time it's going to build up in your
organs and your liver and your brain and
create problems another thing it's going
to do it's going to stop you from making
the connection you need to make to a
medical medium healing tool or a a
healing herb or healing green it's going
to prevent you from acclimating to
something that could save your life and
return your health back and you'll be
addicted to this other stuff that the
salt's in you'll be prevent it'll be
preventing you from actually learning
how to consume the right kind of salt
which is what you see in my hand and
you'll actually you'll you'll pay for it
one way or another as
time goes
on
M God you guys are so addicted to
chips totally understand not making fun
of anybody here baby in over there it's
like the more I put salt on my meals the
more I have cravings for chips or
something yes that's another thing too
that's how you eat more chips so the
thing is with chips eat chips to your
sick eat chips to your sick
the salt makes you want to eat the whole
bag eat the crap out of them and then
the next day eat another whole bag the
next night another whole bag it makes
you want more and more of it because of
the
salt
yep all right rund down on sodium
problems like I said I talked about
before the conventional model for the
blood test is wrong it was gauged on the
1950s when everybody body was using road
salt and it was done that way and
everybody had a salt diet okay we still
have salt diets now better salts like I
said are happening yes chips have oil
too but try to eat those chips with just
oil with no salt and you will not be
happy you will be a miserable miserable
consumer
customer if you just have the chip with
the oil on it a healthier chip with
healthier oil on it maybe avocado oil
whatever it is and you don't have the
salt in there you will not waste your
money on those chips anymore that will
be
that all
right how come people have low sodium in
many
situations they have low
sodium because they're not getting any
of the correct vital real sodium they
need to be getting from celery G juices
from lemons yes lemons from spinach yes
spinach even a cilantro has a little bit
in there they're not getting it from
Tomatoes tomatoes have a little bit of
natural occurring sodium in it which is
incredible
tomatoes so these are things that are
critical for people for their healing
that's the kind of
sodium that resets everything oh man I
hate that word reset I hate that word
everybody uses that word every time they
think they got a new idea a new plan in
health a new whatever it's like a reset
a reset everybody want to sell sell us a
new program reset reset meanwhile not
really it's not really it's not really a
reset not a real
reset but good you know good marketing
all right you guys let's start baking
some spinach soup so much more to talk
about sodium so the way you sustain
sodium in your in your
system
okay is by getting sodium that's bonded
and attached to other
minerals it stays in the bloodstream
longer and when it enters an organ it
doesn't get dumped as trash meaning and
piled in some corner you got to
understand that sodium won't hold a bond
when it's in sea salt like I said it
won't hold the bond when it's in say
Himalayan rock salt of some kind or pink
salt it won't hold a bond long enough
inside the body it's a quick fix meaning
it's a quick hit is what it is it's a
quick hit it won't hold the bond and
when it won't hold the bond then it gets
stored in the liver somewhere as a
deposit of garbage stored in the brain
as a deposit of garbage just like guess
what MSG same thing
stores and becomes garbage trash trash
salt even if it was a great salt what
I'm saying is if you throw it in water
that happens if you use a little bit of
the pink salt and a really high quality
sea salt in your food I'm okay with that
or should I say Spirit of compassion is
okay with
that because that's where I got that
piece of information
from got to get got to give Spirit
credit
sometimes ASO over there on YouTube
spinach soup makes it so easy to get
tons of greens exactly which is what
we're going to do right now which I'm
excited I have mine plugged in right
here my machine I'm pumped up about
this see I've cared myself and many
clients from potato chip addictions
using spinach soup and leafy greens they
reduce salty crunchy Cravings
boom
boom amazing seriously really is all
right this is how you hold your sodium
it's bonded doesn't get thrown out like
trash or stored in an organ like trash
okay especially when you put like on
like okay for instance when you put like
a sea salt a high quality sea salt on
food that's not garbage garbage food you
put it on food like this or food like
you know like a medical medium potato
salad or something and you put it on
that kind of food it's different you can
get away with it you can use it that's
why at Cafe Gratitude we're using some
we we're staying easy on it which is
incredible but we're using some it works
but you don't want to be putting it in
throwing it in your water like your
trainer's telling you and you're
guzzling it down and you think you're
doing your body good your your Skin's
going to turn to crap down the road
you're going to dehydrate your Derma
it's going to be it's going to be a
quick hit in your bloodstream then gone
it's going to store in your brain and
liver that's a different
story and then when you do things like
this the spinach you're bonding that
sodium to minerals they stay in your
bloodstream and they regulate they
regulate that's what I needed to say
this whole time
sodium from the celery sodium from the
spinach regulat so what I'm going to do
is I'm just GNA to just knock this down
a little bit I want a lot in here so I
want to show you guys what I
do okay someone might just do that and
that's all they do they put like a cup
in there couple of Cups I'm going to put
more now it's not crushed and chopped
finely and put into like um measuring
cup but what I want to do is I'm putting
a lot in here I'm making a thick one
like kind of like a dip so it isn't
going to be a real liquidy spinach soup
it's going to be like a thick dip okay
and I'm not putting anything else in
here yet so keep that in mind all
right putting some more spinach in here
like this look how much I got going on
in here look at
that half of a big
container and I'm using a food processor
now you can make it your consistency
want with the food processor you can
actually pulse it like I'm doing see
right
there okay so I got a decent amount of
spinach in there and I can get more in
there too I'm not going to put a lot of
celery in here that's why the recipe
doesn't call it calls for like one stick
a half a stick you can do a quarter
stick I'm just going to do um a quarter
of a stick it's extra sodium it's a
different variety of sodium so you're
looking at two different kinds of sodium
right here you're looking at celery
sodium you're looking at spinach
sodium I'm going to put a little bit of
Basil in here not a lot but I'm going to
put you can put more in if you want I'm
going to throw some basil in here to
give it a little bit of a twist into it
there okay all right
tomatoes
so you know two three mediumsized
tomatoes are great you can do a little
less if you really wanted to a little
bit more there's sodium in tomatoes
there is sodium in
tomatoes yes different form of
sodium these all hold a bond and as they
hold a
bond you're going to have a regulation
of sodium in your bloodstream so you're
not you don't become an addict you don't
become a sodium crack addict cuz that's
what happens sometimes it can be hard to
get good taste T ing Tomatoes I want to
head into that field right now okay I
got to tell you guys something you get a
sweeter tomato like an heirloom tomato
spinach soup tastes extraordinary out of
this world if you get a tomato that's
sweet and it's not so acidy the Tomato
the the spinach soup tastes absolutely
incredible okay these aren't really that
acidy they're on the sweeter side this
is a good tomato I'm using right now and
when you use a good tomato boom you can
just live off of this it tastes so damn
good and if you're worried about protein
oh my God my God my God the whole
protein thing protein protein protein
protein you're getting a lot of protein
from your spinach it pains me to say it
because honestly the whole protein scare
and protein fear based crap that's
happening out there is unbelievable and
ridiculous for a billion reasons and
someday we're going to explore all of
them but the point is is you're getting
plenty of that if that's your if that's
your stuff you know that's your thing
okay so I got a um orange right here
another key
if you get a good orange a sweet orange
one that's not that like you know what I
mean like um sharp one that's not as
sharp if you get an orange that's smooth
and it's sweet and you have tomatoes
that are sweet and also smooth not as
bitey you can make this taste so good
now if you if you can't do that and you
got whatever tomato and that tomato
seems really like kind of more unlike
the you know acidic side where it's
acidy even though it's an alkaline fruit
even though if you get one of
those then you might want to put a
little honey in it so I got some honey
right here so I can show you but I'm not
going to need honey in this one I have
great oranges sweet oranges orange
season is in in the US is hitting right
now right so I'm putting a little orange
in here and here's the other thing if
you put more orange in there you got
more of a liquidy spinach soup you can
customize it to your
liking you don't have to have it where
it's it's exactly a certain amount like
I just put two oranges in here basically
okay I'm going to add a little bit more
spinach too now garlic if you're
sensitive where it's too harsh for you
try only putting a little bit I'm
putting a small clove of garlic in here
right
now but one clove of garlic works in the
spinach soup sou okay you really love
garlic you're welcome to put more if you
don't mind that garlic being Hot and Hot
on your palet and everything if you
don't mind that put some more in there
I'm okay with that but I'm doing one
clove of garlic doing a small clove that
was small okay and
then all right I got everything in here
I'm blending It Up This Is A thick
one and guess what I'm doing would you
believe it I'm adding the rest of the
spinach I'm making this a really really
thick spinach soup so good when it's
like that so good look at that right
there you want to put a little more
orange in there you can a little bit
more garlic you can I put basil in there
I got half a celery stick in there you
can put a whole celery stick in there if
you want this is the way I'm making it
right here for myself my favorite way my
tomato are decent they are tasty and
what you're seeing here is different
forms of sodium there's a little bit of
sodium in basil so you got basil spinach
celery tomato sodium in all of those and
guess what there's a little bit of
sodium in
garlic okay there's sodium in
garlic um you can use a little bit of
mango if you don't want want to use a
tomato you can use some mango if you
don't want to use a tomato okay now on
the spinach soup I can do a couple of
different
things let's see let's
see couple different things you can do
with
it what is the best option here for
something that looks kind of cool going
to go with this bowl right here nice
ceramic
Bowl
okay all
right move this
over
okay right
there that's
wonderful I could take a spoon I could
um scoop the rest out I might do
[Music]
that get some of this
out I could have even made this
thicker could have done that definitely
this is a healing tool just so you know
it can move the needle this isn't just a
soup this is a healing
tool powerful one so much so this can
get people out of the worst chronic
illness when used properly there's
people out there bedridden throughout
the years that I've known personally and
I got them out of bed by using this tool
right here this spinach soup the medical
medium spinach soup this is not a joke
this is not just a recipe this is a life
saving technique a lifesaving tool you
guys got to know this you care about
people out there you care about somebody
in your family someone you
love make sure you make it for them ask
their doctor what's right for them have
them ask their doctor if it's okay but
this is a
miraculous healing tool right here and
it's these things put together spirit
compassion has taught me going all the
way back many many years decades since I
was
young that it's the combination of
these and the combination of getting
that much raw spinach in you along with
everything which people don't get in
them they don't it's the combination of
all of it put together and the sodium
being all bonded and the different
varieties of
sodium this is next level for people's
healing this can get get people out of
wheelchairs over time this can get
people who can't build any muscle
they've had wasting away diseases
because their nervous systems they can't
function so they they can't use their
muscles this is the kind of tool that
gets people out of hell and brings them
into the Heavenly light of healing it's
this right
here this is a
profound profound tool from above people
don't know this but it is it's a miracle
for
people and I'm not trying to sell
anything I don't own any spinach
companies it's
critical it okay over there on YouTube
it definitely moved the needle for me on
day six of the advanced 369 cleanse
gratitude for being
amazing this trauma with me in my
lifetime or this time it's amazing I got
to tell you guys
something okay like influencers these
days they won't hold anything unless
they're getting paid that's just how it
works
now nobody's paying me for the spinach
soup I just want the chronically eel to
heal that's all that
matters this is a tool that does
it and if you make it right
and like I said you can put honey in so
let me just show you kind of the level
of Honey to use so let me do that okay
say you don't get a really good tomato
say you don't get a really good orange
all right maybe your spinach isn't the
best tasting spinach what you do is you
get your honey and you just put that's
it so a little bit of honey that's all
just like that and then you mix it
up right you mix a little bit of that
honey in there like that that's what you
do incredible over there in IG spinach
soup got me out of the hospital when my
heart stopped three times whoa Patty on
IG
W so good there's a taste there's a
flavor when it's done
right so
good how often do you do you eat the
spinach soup every single day you could
eat it every single
day Caitlyn over
there like you said in the podcast
having spinach soup for 28 days for
dinner and life
changing lifechanging dinner is
lifechanging
incredible yeah
it's a bird over there in IG do you eat
this warm or cold okay everything could
be put in the refrigerator so it becomes
cold I don't heat it up so it's not
heated up it's not cooked this is a raw
spinach soup but you can take your
spinach out put it on the counter you
can let it warm up room temperature you
can put your tomatoes out on the counter
let them warm up you can keep everything
on your counter and let it warm up when
you make it it'll just be room
temperature that's the way I eat it
can I have
it
see can I have it if I suffer from
gout ask your doctor what's right for
you but you better believe it I've had
people I've known in my life and so
forth they're doing spinach soup for
their
gout just don't do your spinach soup
with a big fat steak cuz if you got Gout
and and and I'm not making fun of meat
don't do your spinach soup with a big
pile of beans either and don't do your
spinach soup with a big pile of nuts if
you got Gout you don't want to be eating
a lot of protein if you eat a lot of
dense protein like animal protein which
doesn't mean that's the protein that
works whatever but the point is if
you're doing any kind of protein a high
protein spinach protein much different
it's a different kind of protein but if
you do like a whole bunch of bean
protein where you're just doing a big
pile of beans and you got Gout you might
get in trouble if you do a big pile of
nuts and you got Gout you're going to be
in trouble you you'll get in trouble if
you do a big pile of meat and you got
Gout you're going to be in trouble so
what I'm saying is yes a spinach soup is
great for gout it's great for for
everything and um it just is it's a
liver healing
tool Steph over there on IG spinach soup
helped bring me out of the darkness of
chronic fatigue
okay it's amazing that you said that
because I'm going to tell you right now
okay back in the day back 30 years ago
and even earlier when I was helping
people they're coming to my office every
single day from around the
world all
right I I had so many people on this
Healing medical medium spinach soup tool
from Spirit of compassion and I watched
people who could were being carried in
by their family because chronic fatigue
was so bad I've watched them go from
that condition to months and months
later with the spinach soup being one of
the tools and one of the most important
ones they were using at the time and
I've watched them just come out of that
fatigue so it's what you're saying right
there it's
incredible if you guys don't have the
medical medium
books get a hold of one go to the
library get it for free get the cleanse
to heal if I were you and I don't have
the medical medium books or all of them
get cleanse the heel out of the library
right now get medical medium new edition
book one out of the library right now
get the brain saver out of the library
right now get the books read them take
them into your
heart and learn how to
heal I will post the spinach soup recipe
in the Instagram broadcast channel make
sure you are there are you guys
listening to the medical medium
broadcast CH channel on IG are you guys
listening I've been leaving some
messages
lately angel messages and so forth are
you listening to my telegram messages
how many of you guys are listening to my
telegram messages because I'm leaving a
message every single night sometimes
it's really late but I leave messages
every single night angels and so forth
and all of that just healing messages
from Spirit of
compassion that information is coming
from Spirit of compassion as I'm leaving
it on telegram just so you
know Cindy over there on YouTube I feel
fantastic whenever I feel whenever I eat
the medical medum spinach soup my
digestive system loves it so good for
gastroparesis so good for Digestive
troubles oh my God so
good incredible I saw somebody said they
feel fantastic again Denise I started my
health Journey with you almost 3 and a
half years ago it helped so much I
haven't had it in a while but now that
will make it next
week incredible and you hung in there
for three and a half years even with all
the different attacks I get from all
different
angles from the apps and everything else
the different shutdowns and different
censorship and remember when my T
remember when Tik Tok I don't think you
guys remember but I was heading up to
like a million subscribers on Tik Tok
and my Tik Tok videos were were in the
millions of views we were getting the
wor out about chronic illness and Tik
Tok they got rid of the entire account
and they didn't allow a way to reach
them they did it so they didn't leave
any data behind for me to ever contact
them and when I F found finally found
somebody in there they wouldn't help
when I found somebody through somebody
else and everything and they wouldn't
help and then if I told you the rest of
the story your mind would be blown what
happen happened with that Tik Tok
account with what they did your mind
would be blown they purposely deleted it
and then they waited exactly 6 months to
the day before they changed the a guard
that I was in contact with and when they
changed that Guard the guard said
exactly 6 months to this day we can't
reinstate your account now someone was
actually guarding over the six-month
period so I couldn't get my account back
talking about sick that's
sick think about and I'm thinking about
a lawsuit too for censorship on that on
that one so I'm actually working on that
and I'm preparing for possible other
lawsuits
too and we believe we have enough data
and then some so it's just sometimes you
know you get pushed too far and
you have to pull a trigger tired of
being harassed so anyway you guys
incredible this spinach soup very very
healing make sure you bring it into your
life other tips for sodium levels add
lemon to your water let's hit that real
quick I can't leave you without some
other tips can't can't can't can't can't
okay all right so I was never a big one
for drinking gallons of water a
day you know what I mean like over
through the throughout the decades
throughout the health you know all these
years of the health movement shifting
and changing medical medium bringing
information into the health movement 3/4
of the health movement has been changed
and shaped because of medical medium
information the other quarters the same
old BS but the point is is that in the
health movement it was always drink
water back in the 80s back in the 80s uh
90s drink a lot of water drink a lot of
water and people just drank and drank
and drank no results to all their
conditions and symptoms but drank lots
of water it was never one of those where
you know you should be
drinking you know 30 o of water um every
half an hour I mean you wouldn't believe
the advice I've seen out there people
have you can drown
yourself drown yourself your lungs can
fill up with water your bloodstream can
thin out too much with water so medical
medium information was always about
adding solids to water do you guys get
what that is adding solids to it right
adding lemon this isn't a lemon right
here I can grab one really quick but
adding lemon to your water lemon holds
sodium it holds other solids
calcium the minerals the metals soft
Metals we need magnesium right so lemons
hold these and so what happens is when
you squeeze lemon in water you you just
diverted a chance to
drown doesn't mean you still can't drown
yourself it you know with drinking too
much water but you advert you completely
adverted you you've diverted that
possibility to happen easily so what
happens is with lemon lemon in water it
allows okay th that sodium to get to
where it needs and hold and stay bonded
with other trace minerals to keep
electrolytes high so your water isn't
thinning your bloodstream out
empty
empty so Spirit of
compassion wanted people to be on lemon
water because of flushing the liver of
poisons and
toxins flushing the body of poisons and
toxins one of those ways of doing it is
lemon has detoxification
like detoxifying
minerals that can help push out garbage
junk and pull it out
right if you're somebody who all they
have is distilled water you have to add
some trace minerals into that water you
have to add lemon into that water at
least lemon into that water so if you're
a distilled water person now you're like
You' got rid of all the
solids okay r o reverse o mosis there's
still solids in there keep that in mind
most Ro systems leave some solids in the
water distilled water
distillers they get rid of all the
solids and then you got and then you're
drinking that water if you drink too
much of that distilled water and you're
drinking way too much of it now we're in
a water topic I got to do I got to do
another live on this maybe I'll do a
podcast or something but you're drinking
distilled water you can get in trouble
because there's no solids in that
water okay plus distilled water might
take something from you that's good
because you're using water you need you
you have to have solids in that water
it's critical so lemon this is this is
medical M information just so you guys
know and if someone's poached a tidbit
here and there throughout the years
there's nothing I can do but what either
way but what I'm trying to say is
that that the lemon water added to water
makes it so you have less likely chances
to drown in it you have also
electrolytes staying keeping that water
strong so that you don't collapse those
neurotransmitters so if you're somebody
that's chronically sick and you got
neurotransmitter problems and you got
neur neurological problems and you're
not well your nervous system struggling
and you're just drinking water and water
and water it's not going to be a good
thing you got to have you have to have
water that has something in it solids
like coconut water coconut water has
solids in it so that's a whole point it
has sodium in there it's got different
minerals in there trace minerals that's
what coconut water has naturally
occurring same thing if you something
similar is when you take lemon and you
squeeze it in water you're doing the
same thing you're putting solids back
into that water but with lemon
water you're actually flushing out the
liver you're actually flushing out you
know the body's organs you're flushing
that junk out that's medical medium
information I said a million times that
I'm not the first guy or the first
person on this planet that decided to
cut a lemon and squeeze it in water I
never said that in a million years
because it's not true just frankly it's
not true but medical medium information
that I put out for these decades is that
lemon water first thing in the morning
is a flusher of toxins and poisons from
the liver when the Li gathers it up all
night long and it needs to get pulled
out the lemon water does
that and also bringing all the
electrolytes back into the water that's
also medical Med
information bringing the solids back in
like the calcium and so forth so that's
why lemon water is so important with the
healing process some people over drink
plain water they over drink plain
water and if you over drink it and
you're electrolytes start
dropping including sodium too
electrolyte starts dropping it's one of
the electrolytes potassium gets thrown
off your sodium pottassium your glucose
gets thrown off glucose is part of an
electrolyte it becomes a part of an
electroly Jackie my son drank too much
water with friends one day and he felt
nauseous and felt like throwing up he
learned I think one of the most terrible
things is like water drinking contests
every five years they all forget that
somebody died in the middle of a water
drinking contest every five years and so
there's uh you know
hazing that's a prime example somebody
died like 25 years ago from a hazing
where it was a contest to drink the most
water for a whole bunch of newbies at a
fraternity and um you know some kid
drown right in front of everybody and
you can't save them they're drowning
they're on the floor flapping around and
then they're just they're
drowning and you know this is just it's
like every five years another person
drowns from like a water drinking
contest and I'm like what is going on
here how come nobody remembers and
nobody knows because that's what
Everything Changes in three years and
the same thing with all the influencers
now and the podcast influencers and so
forth the crap they were talking about
three years ago two years ago four years
ago is embarrassing having people do the
worst things and now they change their
tune and grab some good info from like
mm or something and now they're changing
it no one looks back 3 years ago and
says Whoa you were saying that you
really are like a shape shifter you are
a
chameleon and a carpet bagger celery
juice for sodium incredible a lot of
people are not consistent with drinking
enough celery juice they only drink 8
ounces or 6 ounces I'm not sh putting
shade on that drink 2 ounces but their
stress levels are going you know up
their their adrenaline is pumping they
need more more than just 4 ounces a day
and quite frankly a lot of people
there's you know they they stop drinking
celery juice and they remember drinking
it a year ago and they think they still
drink it or something that's something
that happens too people tend to remember
their referencing in their brain a time
when they drank a lot of celery juice or
a time when they ate something really
good but they haven't been doing that
and they're dabbling you know dabbling
and stuff they're dabbers right and
they're
dabblers and they're doing that but they
they don't
remember like yo you haven't drank
celery in a few months you had one glass
of celery juice a month ago you're not
going to keep your sodium levels strong
so you're going to be relying on
addictive behavior you're going to be a
salt
addict a salt crack addict and you're
going to be just doing that so it it's
crazy that's what happens you guys and
then next thing you know it you know and
if they got weak adrenals uh
yeah I know all right you guys there's
so much to talk about I could sit here
all day which I love to do I would love
to do that and I love doing it but weak
adrenals and sodium levels that's a
question that comes up all the time so
weak adrenals and sodium levels right
just because you have weak adrenals
doesn't mean that you're not going to
have any sodium levels but if you're
hitting your body with the quick hit the
wrong sodium it's not going to help your
adrenals keep that in mind right you can
also cook your adrenals and salt you can
pickle them understand that too so
here's here's some bad information
that's out there may as well talk about
this here's some bad
information your adrenals need salts
your adrenals need salt you know
trainers out there now health coaches
out there graduating from whatever
health coach act you know Acme health
coach you know company in corporation
and they're just stamping them out it's
like you need salt for your adrenals
sodium for your adrenals dude you can
pickle your adrenals you can pickle the
out of your
adrenals just for the record you can dry
them up like little
prunes if you overs
salt if you overs salt this is like a
new this is like a new Flash a
bulletin if you overs salt you can
pickle the out of your adrenals and
turn them into little
prunes keep that in mind need salt for
my adrenals need salt for my adrenals
you're killing your adrenals you're
killing your adrenals need salt for my
adrenals you're killing your adrenals
and then it gets worse need more salt
for my adrenals but your adrenals are
being pickled and they're shriveling up
and dying more salt for my
adrenals ma'am your adrenals aren't
doing
good at the doctor's office naturopath
kinesiologist acupuncturist MD whatever
you're at the doctor's office your
adrenals aren't doing good they look
like they're getting worse iridologist
whatever your adrenals are getting worse
every you know it me oh more salt you
need more
salt and you're addicted to the
Salt so you're misreading all the
signs but that's the amount of stupid
crap that happens in the health
field and when you're sick and
chronically ill it's the wild
west you get too sick because of all the
out there to
too it's really bad and that's why
Spotify somebody in Spotify said just
play a little joke on him let's take
down his uh Spotify account especially
when I'm talking about alkaline ionizer
water machines and
colostrum and apple cider vinegar
chewies which is a billion dollar
industry people aren't doing the medical
medium healing tools celery juice
spinach soup coconut water leemon water
Etc they're doing other things like
eating you know eating salty foods doing
other stuff throwing salt in
water and eating keto look you guys
there's things you can do for
healing and the medical M spinach soup
it's one of the most powerful tools that
you can bring in to your lifestyle right
there Tik Tock right there
IG right there YouTube right there
Rumble one of my favorite apps right
there I could have I could have packaged
all this information and charged for it
I could easily package these up and
charge for this I could package this
whole sodium thing up and put it out
there and charge for it you got to pay
$39 to download it and thousands of
people will do that thousands and
thousands of people will do that
doesn't mean someday I won't because
I'll have
to all the bull crap that's happened but
the point is is I try not to do
that
anyway all right you guys check out my
telegrams please you guys seriously in
Rumble and everywhere else on YouTube
check out my telegrams I'm leaving these
exclusive messages on telegram talking
about angels What Spirit of compassion
knows about angels the unknown Angels
I'm talking about Mars period I Al I'm
talking about different things Pride and
Prejudice like what's up with Pride and
Prejudice the 1995 version I'm talking
about that I'm talking about a lot of
different things on there on my telegram
just letting you know okay so make sure
you're there make sure you get to my
telegram Channel make sure you subscribe
please get on there so I can deliver so
I can deliver that information deliver
those exclusive messages for free with
information and make sure make sure you
sign up to Medical medium inside scoop
Instagram broadcast channel
please because I only want you to get
the information so you can heal and move
forward the other night I was on there
leaving a one minute message and I was
talking about taking my supplements and
I was taking my vimergy supplements
right here is the propolis there's the
B12 you know you guys know I endorse
those guys cuz I've never seen stuff out
there like that
ever get ready for Cafe Gratitude launch
medical medium Cafe Gratitude
collaboration October 15th it start they
start putting the dishes on the menu
they launch it there and if you signed
up and got a ticket if you got a ticket
for October 21st 22nd 23rd
24th we're going to be in the restaurant
together I've never done anything like
that we're going to be in the restaurant
together we're going to have a killer
time we're going to eat it's going to be
sick it's going to be a meet and greet
it's going to be on an intimate level
for sure it is going to be amazing
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie is at airwan in the fresh press
juice section make sure you get that
there
too boom I don't know what else to say
get on my newsletter so you know what's
up get on my newsletter annab Beth Lee I
just love the messages oh I love leaving
the messages it's my
favorite I love leaving the messages
Spirit of compassion gets me when I'm
really tired I'm leaving the messages
when I'm super tired which is kind of
funny like I'm exhaustedly tired like
I'm done and I leave the messages on
telegram when I'm so tired and then I
sit there and I listen to Spirit of
compassion and I say whatever I hear and
that's what that's how I leave the
messages on telegram where I'm hearing
Spirit of compassion and I'm leaving
leaving the words and I don't even know
what I'm saying sometimes because I'm so
tired I had no idea I just heard the
word and I said it and I'm like what did
I say don't even
remember
crisy oh yilia
Hoffman you're on fire today W must have
took vimer celery Force love spending
Saturday with you
see what hero are you leaving lyrics on
the YouTube are you guys you guys just
so you know I read all your comments on
YouTube and on Rumble I read all the
comments and I read them I don't just
read them like this like the influencers
do they poke through them I actually
read them and and really take it in and
and look what's going on rise with melum
and we wouldn't mind to pay for this
info at all plus you could protect
yourself a lot
better I know I know I'm at that
point gotta be honest Elaine spinach
soup in a mason jar on the go so good oh
yeah well you know what's really funny I
was going to put this in a mason jar but
then I realized I probably wasn't going
to do it I was going to I was going to
make a mess and it was going to be the
Sweedish Chef all over again in
here Christine Phil over there on
Facebook do you read telegram comments
yes I do every last one of
them I
do I read every single telegram
comment yeah my team helps me with that
they do they do my team helps me with
that and I read every single
comment
yep they help me do it so I can read
them
all so it's really
awesome they have to turn on the apps I
don't know how to operate
them I'm
embarrassed but
whatever my team has to turn on the
apps because knowing me I will
accidentally clip click click on the
live
button and I will be watering my plants
outside not even know
it send me in the comments is what I
usually ask people to do listen hey I
want to tell you
something
um there's something that I really care
about you guys
and um I don't know a greater honor to
both meet you guys like I have many of
you in
person I have
a um
I have a memory process that is unlike
any other I have an ability to remember
which is really cool I don't know how it
was given that gift Spirit of compassion
said it has very much helped in many
ways but I have an um unique ability to
actually
remember when I meet
someone so I want you to know if you
guys were
there um at the meet and greets uh was
the greatest
honor and I take in a lot of information
because of spirit of
compassion in that short time we meet
it's incredible Karen says over there I
love the spinach soup it has been a
lifechanger for me it is so good for you
oh my God it's so good for you but the
Cafe Gratitude medical meeme
collaboration I'm going to tell you guys
that's like that's like your next
level it's in um 9 days in county or
something like that
um yeah cold white
spring good to see you cold white Spring
May good to see
you anyway all right I love you
guys off I
go you guys um by the
way there might be like we we might get
a visit from
like
um we might get a visit from um you know
the fly on the
wall we might get a visit from the fly
on the wall at some point I'm letting
you know I don't know if the pirate is
going to make a visit but dror jobi
might make a
visit Dr Nesbit might make a visit at
some point feel the same way cold white
spring and you know I think um and even
yeah even Samantha
although Samantha changed her
name so yeah might be a Samantha visit
and a Bryce visit Uma there might see be
some
visitations
yep yep there really could be there
could be a year of humor coming up in
2025 there might be a new year of humor
mixed
in although I don't know how much that
really helped me over the years I know a
lot of people were agitated by my humor
I just can't please everybody I don't
know what to do all right you guys would
you guys are cool all
right I will see you I'm going to have
this and I am
pumped
Pumped I'm going to eat that whole Bowl
in