okay
everybody's deficient
we come into this world deficient
babies
are sick
when they come into this world
liver problems
intestinal tract problems
skin conditions
right
that means we come into this world sick
and if you don't come into this world as
a sick baby
you get sick later
newsflash
everybody gets sick
somewhere down the line in their life
they will get
sick is that negative thinking no
it's reality it's truth
is what it is
the traps are set for everybody
they're set
you can step in any moment any time
that's how this world works
traps are set
so we
fall in them
walking along i'm doing rl
and we're in the trap
that's how it works down here
we come in this world efficient
because our parents were deficient
their parents were deficient
and it goes on down the line
we come into this world with toxic heavy
metals
our parents have toxic heavy metals
their parents had toxic heavy metals
their parents had toxic heavy metals we
come into the world deficient fill the
toxic heavy metals filled with poisons
and then
we continue to get poisoned
pharma poisons us
the chemical industry poisons us
we're live right now we're live on
telegram by the way we're live on
facebook we're live on youtube we're
live on tick tock
good to see you guys
i'm happy i'm here right now by the way
i got the juicer out because celery
juice is still one of the most important
medical tonics
you can have in your life
one of the most important medical tonics
you can have in your life this is a
medical device right here
you guys there's a juicer sale right on
for the mm 900 hds i'm mentioning it
because after the last sale a couple of
months ago
everybody said hey i uh where where do i
get a juicer uh and i'm like you missed
the sale
everybody's asking every day the sale
lends and then a hundred people ask
where do i get a juicer i don't have
much money is there any juicers on sale
that are the right one or a good one i'm
like oh my god and you got to wait for
the next sale
but
you guys important conversation i'm
going to make some celery juice why are
you doing celery juice
why are you doing it
because it moves the needle
how come millions of people around the
world are doing celery juice
getting their lives back
because it moves the needle
right it's one of those incredible tools
it's a medical medic it's a medical
medium tool
and we're going to talk about it why
it's helpful why it's helping you now if
you don't do your celery juice anymore
you're missing out
you're missing out it's important to do
especially where we're going
especially where we're going so back to
talking about deficiencies okay and
people being sick
if you didn't come into this world sick
you get sick
everybody gets sick along the way
sure
there's some rarities where they don't
get sick until they're in their 50s or
60s
right
but those are disappearing now we're in
a place where everybody gets sick
and the traps have been set
the human traps are set
so people stay sick get sick have to buy
all kinds of you know pharmaceuticals
medications they gotta be on
[Music]
that's what happens
everybody's gonna have all kinds of
inflammation inside their body they're
gonna have all kinds of blood clots
inside their body they're going to have
all kinds of neurological conditions
going on inside their body
right what's a neurological symptom
migraines head pain neck pain back pain
dizziness vertigo tinnitus tingles and
numbness ticks and spasms brain fog
that's just a few
that's just a few neurological problems
right there
right
and then what about anxiety depression
bipolar ocd how about that neurological
symptoms
guess what
you can talk to anybody right now and
they'll say they got some symptom if
they're honest about it like they want
to talk about it
but coming up in the next year
two years
it's just like symptoms symptoms
symptoms doesn't matter what age you are
and it's happening already so what are
we gonna do about it
what are we gonna do about it
how do you battle the negative with a
positive how do you empower yourself and
battle the darkness
how do you take control over your life
and battle evil
i i ran into somebody the other day
people still think there's no evil out
there
i couldn't believe it i was like are you
kidding
there's no evil out there i i ran into
somebody the other day
right
haven't talked to him in years and
they're like yeah i'm on this whole
thing where there's not there's no one's
bad there's not a bad person out there
i'm like
i'm like what are you kidding yeah
there's no bad people out there there's
no there's you know it's it's the
universal balance it's just there's a
universal balance in the earth is flat
too
there's darkness out there there's evil
out there
you know there's a system set in place
to make sure people stay sick
there's chemicals
all
in the earth's not flat there's
chemicals all in everybody's houses now
just coming in like the trojan horse in
in just the trojan horses bringing in
all the chemicals loading them up
bringing them into the house loading up
bring them into the house
that's right
you order a package now thousand
chemicals warehouses are filling up
their their warehouses their fresheners
and scented candles and chemicals
right
so
there is evil out there chemical
industry creates these toxic soups and
they poison your children that's not
evil
no that's not evil
so the chemical industry drops mosquito
spray on everybody
drops mosquito spray on your children
doesn't kill mosquitoes because they're
always there that's not evil
no
that's not evil
that's just a couple of things i could
go on and on all day
right by the way if you just got on here
you guys the juicer is on sale it's the
mm 900 hds at
megajuicers.com that's where the sale is
take advantage of it's 50 off they
actually give you
a book and
just
making a note
i had no part of it they actually
the company megajuicers.com
that even telling me
went got a whole bunch of celery juice
books
and they're giving a free celery juice
medical medium celery juice book and
this is this is packed with information
about all the ins and outs about the
do's and don'ts about celery juice this
is an important book but that's just a
fraction of what's in here i mean
there's information
on how celery juice kills off pathogens
helps people heal with all kinds of
symptoms and conditions they're giving a
free book
and two glass jars
with and 50 off on the omega
mm-900 hds make sure it's the mm-900 hds
the celery juicer is the best one there
is link is in the description you guys
we come into this world of fishing we
stay deficient here's the problem here's
the problem the boat's filling up with
water it's filling up with water the
boat's filling up with water right
and you're bailing out the water
you're bailing out the water and it's
coming in faster than you can bail out
the water you see how that works you
guys
right
that's what's happening nowadays it
didn't happen so much before you can
come into the world efficient before
and you can get by
you can get by you can get by then you
have your heart attack
you can get by
i got cancer now
you can get by you can get by and then
but now it's not like that it's you're
sick with all kinds of crap and then you
have your heart attack you're sick with
all kinds of crap and then you get
cancer
that's how it works now
in the past deficiencies were you got
your deficiency and you ate what you
wanted and you did what you wanted and
then you just died of a stroke
that was that was the past right
okay
you came into the world you were
deficient you lived your life you went
to school you did your job you got your
work you did your job you got married or
whatever you did in your life or not and
then you're moving through your life and
then you get a heart attack
but here's the new here's the new way
it's getting done now from here on out
here's the new way you come into this
world efficient and then you're sick as
a child
and then the medical treatments and then
this stupidity and all kinds of stuff
and you just get sicker and sicker and
sicker
and then you have a heart attack
but you were miserable for all those
years before your heart attack you're
miserable miserable for all those years
before cancer
before cancer you were miserable all
those years before kidney disease took
you out
you were miserable all those years
before a brain tumor took you out you
were miserable and that's how it's
getting done now
it's not like you live your life you
you're born deficient you don't really
take care of yourself you don't know
what to do no one teaches you you live
your life you go decades down decades
down and then you get your brain tumor
but you had a good life
it's not like that anymore you're sick
with fatigue brain fog
anxiety you've got numbness on your body
tingles on your body you know you're not
you're sick in all kinds of ways you get
your you know you get your appendix out
you got problems left and right and then
you get all these lipomas you get all
this other stuff you're sick you're sick
you're sick
and then you get
whatever's gonna happen
so
what are we gonna do about it
that's what i wanna know so i have
spirit of compassion
right
what are we gonna do
and it's like we do the tools we bring
them into our life
we get medical devices
that will probably someday be outlawed
i wouldn't doubt it
if 15 years from now you're not allowed
to have a juicer in this world
your doctor will have to write a
prescription to see if you're eligible
for a juicer
okay
not to mention 15 years down the road
you might not be able to grow your own
fruit tree in your yard
because
the forces of evil want to take
everything away from everybody
infect them
make them sick and poison them
contaminate them and then take away the
things they need but right now we have
these things we have the medical device
right here now we can do something about
it
right yeah
they're going to take away b12 years
down the road they're going to take away
other things down the road
fix what you need to fix now
work on what you need to fix now
right and hopefully hopefully
hopefully
the light is fighting for us
and we get to keep things like juicers
and
b12 and
gold and seal you don't think they're
gonna take goldenseal away they'll take
goldenseal away
the power the evil powers you know
what's funny just talk to a person
they're like there's no there's no
darkness out there there's no there's no
bad people out there are you kidding are
you kidding
when i hear that i can't believe what
kind of
what kind of
spiritual brainwashing is that what
direction is that
you know
you have to know what's happening around
you in order for you to protect yourself
in order for you to heal
you have to be aware of what's going on
around you
so you can protect yourself your
children your loved ones people you care
about your friends your family
that's mindfulness it's awareness is
mindfulness
awareness is mindfulness that's what it
is
right
and so
i'm here to say
let's talk about one of the most
powerful ways one of the most powerful
tools
to keep your body in check to give your
body back what it needs protect your
body helping to cleanse you in
everything so we got the celery juice
and
every now and then you'll see somebody
say oh i've been doing medical medium
for five years
[Music]
medical medium for five years
it's more like for most people
i found a medical medium five years ago
and i've been messing around in between
i've been cheating
on medical medium information
kind of like when somebody gets into a
relationship i've been with jack
i've been with jack for a long time i've
been with jill for five years
yeah but i've been cheating
[Applause]
i've been dabbling with some other
relationships while i've been with jill
i've been dabbling with other
relationships
i've been doing medical medium for five
years
but i've been cheating
dabbling
i'm still doing you know some crazy gut
powder that
tears my gut apart and then medical
mediums tools have to help fix it
i'm still doing uh
my eggs
i'm still doing my alkaline ionizer
water machine which is the most toxic
water on the planet
so then i have to still do my celery
juice to counterbalance it i don't know
i'm counterbalancing it
i don't know that's what's happening
if i get sicker i just assume it's the
celery juice
medical medium for five years doesn't
mean someone's been doing medical medium
for five years they found medical medium
five years ago
[Music]
i get it it's not easy there's over a
thousand protocols you got to customize
the one that works for you the
information's in the books
i get it
you guys just came on here celery juicer
fifty dollars off
it's the mm-900 hds
um omega juicers.com that's where you go
and get it
right
and they give you a free celery juice
book 50 off on the juicer
two glass
um jars
sale is on right now for this juicer i
know a lot of you guys have the juice
room you love it i love it you know i'm
working with the company
right you guys
because it's the best juicer you know
what you'll find in this juicer
or you know what you won't find in this
juicer you know what you won't find
metal gears
you won't find metal metal metal gears
in here going like this yeah i got a
cold pressed masticating juicer yeah oh
yeah but you got the metal gears
metal on metal
metal gears going like this so you're
juicing for years with those metal gears
and you're just getting all that
stainless steel inside your body
this is a very quiet juicer
[Music]
very quiet
in the mornings juicers are so loud
and this is a really quiet juicer
[Music]
and that metal does more damage to us
right
the metal gears
[Applause]
if anybody has this juicer you guys know
you're saving money already i've saved i
don't know thousands at this point
juicers paid for itself over and over
again i know i tell you guys that
because it's so cool
i can't help it i gotta say it
is the mm-900 hds if you don't know
about this juicer it's on sale 50 off
they give you a celery juice book
we come in this world efficient
and we can't put back what we need fast
enough it's being used up faster than we
could put it back you're in a boat
the water's filling in the boat and you
got a bucket and you're trying to drain
the bottom of the boat
the water's coming in
faster
than you can shovel the water bucket the
water out
we lose what we need inside our bodies
faster and we can put it back in
you want to get better you want to heal
that's one thing we have to know right
there
[Music]
that's one thing we have to know
we have to get the things we need in
faster than what we're using and how
we're losing it right moderation
is not going to work
moderation is not going to fix anything
moderation
is a guarantee
to turn into desperation
[Music]
do you guys hear that
moderation guarantees
desperation
a life of sickness
that's what moderation guarantees
[Music]
[Applause]
it guarantees a life of sickness
and then getting into a desperate
situation
[Music]
and hopefully not a desperate situation
where you're on your hands and knees and
you're praying to god
a lot of people have been there they've
recovered with medical medium
information
it's good to see you guys i'm excited to
be back
i'm excited to be back we're live right
now on tick tock live on facebook live
on youtube i'm excited to be back right
now don't add anything in your celery
juice
i'm gonna i'm i'm gonna run that by you
no ice cubes no water
no ice water no lemon juice
no powders no supplements
don't add anything in it
it's an herbal extraction you're using a
medical device
and it's an herbal extraction
that's what it is so keep that in mind
it's an herbal extraction
now
this is a cold pressed juicer
okay
and it squeezes so much juice out of
anything that you run through it
that the pulp is dry
and that is incredible when the pulp was
dry like that okay
[Music]
moderation
guarantees desperation that's what it
does in the end right
so you know when you run across some
yeah i've been doing medical medium for
five years
they found medical medium five years ago
i know people that found me when i was
in the office why people were filing in
they found me 30 years ago 25 years ago
and they can say i've been doing medical
media for 25 years but in between they
fell off the wagon
they were you know too many steak
dinners
too much chocolate cake
too much gluten too much eggs in between
too much pizza in between too much fat
in between
too many bad supplements in between
because people just they just buy bad
supplements they just buy bad stuff
constantly everything in between yeah
they've been doing medical medium for 30
years
well how are you doing how are you
feeling since you've been doing medical
meeting for 25 years how are you feeling
well
you know i still
i'm battling some things and yeah oh
really medical medium didn't work
medical media must not work i'm not
going to try medical medium that person
did medical media for 25 years no they
found medical medium 25 years ago they
walked in my office and then they got
lost along the way because it's easy to
get lost along the way they weren't
doing 32 ounces of celery juice
they weren't doing their heavy metal
detox smoothie anymore or they may not
even started it
and
they're not doing the recommended
supplements
and they're not even doing the protocols
for their conditions
like how they found medical medium 25
years ago
they're not doing the cleanses
keep that in mind
you guys it's fun to be back they were
dabbling
you know what's interesting though on
another note check this out right
there's millions doing celery juice
around the world right now okay
right
and there's no money being put into
advertising for you to do celery juice
like there's no money out there
saying
get your celery juice and drink it
because it can do this and that for you
right
but there's
billions going into the apple cider
vinegar market kombucha tea market all
these other things that aren't good for
you nutritional yeast market
millions a week in advertising hundreds
of millions of dollars a year in
advertising so that you actually get
brainwashed
you get brainwashed
because that's what's happening right
now there's all this money being dumped
in to all this stuff do you guys know
that did you know when you see a
commercial on tv or something for like
apple cider something or you know some
kind of whatever do you know the
millions and millions of dollars being
put in
by those shareholders being by the but
you know by the ceo of that company by
all
you know executives by everybody in the
company right but the owners of those
companies how much millions and millions
of dollars are going in to teaching you
you better take this apple cider you
better take this kombucha right well
that doesn't exist with celery juice
that's not happening out there so it's
it's the dirty secret
this is the dirty secret and there's an
underground on the planet right now
drinking this every day
on the planet right now people drinking
it all around the world
it's pure i'm not just talking about the
juice
it's pure
it's the light
okay
it's not like something toxic like
vinegar something toxic
right
or nutritional yeast with msg
or something else
millions of dollars hundreds of millions
of dollars are being put into that to
brainwash you that's dirty
that's dirty
that's dark and dirty that's what that
is that's not of the light because a
those things don't fix anybody b
hundreds of millions of dollars are
being put into it to brainwash you while
it's not fixing you
right that's nasty
this is pure
of the light
right when you drink this you can
actually be rest assured that there
isn't hundreds of millions of dollars
trying to brainwash you being spent
every day on television all over the
internet on youtube ads ads to trick you
into trying something
this is because people got better
and they tell another person
that's what this is
so this is of the light right here
and that's the difference
think about that
please talk about the urine therapy
craze yeah it's ridiculous doesn't work
it was around forever it never worked
it's a bad idea
and it doesn't work
yeah
it's it's it's it's actually
it's actually a ridiculous idea
i've watched it for years
people have poured into my office with
all kinds of conditions they tried it
you're in therapy
anybody's sick long enough who hasn't
tried it did it fix them no it didn't
but here's the thing
you might do some urine therapy
right and also get told to do b12 and
also get told to you know medical medium
information get told to do your celery
juice get told to do other things
and that's the stuff that gets you
better get told to eat less fat get told
to eat more berries right
that's the thing that works you're in
therapy doesn't work it doesn't
terrible idea
it's toxic
it's really a bad idea
first of all
your body gets rid of urine
okay
for a reason
we're not supposed to drink it put it in
our ears
put it up our behind
we're not supposed to do that with urine
i know people that are sick they're sick
they're going before they come to me for
help over the years they've been going
all around and they're putting they're
doing urine therapy enemas and they're
making themselves so sick you guys
couldn't even believe it they're putting
urine in their ears
a very high profile person came to me
years ago for help
they were being guided by a health guru
on the health scene
that was somewhat known
and that health guru was telling
this extremely high profile person with
their sickness to do urine therapy
this person was doing it and staying
sick
they were putting urine in their ear
drinking it
putting it up there behind
and they were sick
when they came to me
it was a miracle for them
because that's what they said in their
own words
they got on the celery juice they got in
the heavy metal detox smoothie they knew
what supplements to use they knew how
and why how to use cat's claw they knew
what to do they got themselves a medical
device they brought them
they brought their life back they
started doing the mono cleanse in the
369. they brought their life back and
then they couldn't believe how foolish
they were that they were doing urine
therapy
the details matter
so we're juicing some celery just used a
little bit of celery now you guys the
mm-900 hds is on sale it's 50 off it's a
medical device
okay
strain your celery juice that's what i
did i strained it here it is amazing you
get the celery juice book that's what
they're doing it's omega juicers.com
this is the mm-900 hds
you know when i hear somebody say take
control of your life i'm like i scratch
my head
when i hear somebody like on the circuit
or on the scene
say gotta take control over your life
i'm like okay empty words
what's behind it
gotta empower yourself
gotta take control over your life
okay okay i like where this is going
but how empty are those words what's
behind it
right
make sure you're doing your coffee
enemas make sure you're doing your urine
therapy make sure you're doing your
fecal matter implants make sure you're
doing your vinegars make sure you're
doing your collagen and i'm like
you just disempowered yourself
and now you're teaching other people to
disempower yourself there's millions of
dollars going into coffee enemas right
now as far as to get people brainwashers
millions of dollars going into college
actually
hundreds of millions of billion dollars
goes into collagen to brainwash you guys
right now
vinegar absolutely billion dollars a
year going into brainwashing you guys
right
haven't you had enough
here's how it works
powers that be
the darkness loves to use the
chronically ill
they love to use the chronically ill
they love to
make their life more difficult
that's how it works
and unless you're seasoned will you ever
know
and unless you're sick enough will you
ever know
that's how that's that's just basically
the bottom line
so
you guys
just want to give you a rundown on sale
that's happening right so um let's talk
about the medical device for just a
couple of seconds here okay this is an
herbal extraction
anybody who undermines the power of
celery juice and say well it's just a
vegetable juice doesn't understand they
just don't know okay it's herbal
medicine when you guys bring it into
your body some incredible things happen
please know that this is a big deal so
when you bring
when you bring that herbal medicine in
know what it's doing for you okay
so carol says why not just eat a stalk
of celery a day yeah you can do that
you can have a stalk of celery a day
right
it's it's healthy to do that chop it up
throw it in salads but it's not gonna
fix anything
it's not going to fix anything
a stock of celery
is not going to be able to clean up that
mess that's in here
okay
you got years
of putrification going on in here
you got rotting animal flesh in here
this isn't an anti-animal protein
thing you guys know that by now this
isn't anti-vegan either whatever
it's just about what's in the intestinal
tract
you can have years
of rotting flesh
just sitting on the sides of that colon
and intestinal tract just pocketing all
in there
years of toxins and poisons inside that
liver right there okay
years
of the stomach glands being shot
shot
here's what happens you go into your
doctor's office you go into a functional
medicine doctor's office
um yeah you got you got
microbiome problems you got it's like
you got low hcl is what you have
you can't you got to get your
hydrochloric acid your stomach lands
built back up that's what celery juice
does
you got to get the hydrochloric acid
built back up to par so it can clean
break things down destroy pathogens
but they won't tell you unless they know
medical medium information unless that
doctor or functional doctor knows
medical medium information so you go to
your practitioner doctor
and they'll just
they'll just be like okay you got
microbiome problems here take this this
this and this right
and
whatever else they'll say
but you guys have to understand
they won't say well your stomach lands
have been beat to crap for too many
years they're weak and depleted and we
have to bring them back
once you get that hcl built back up
that's empowerment
okay
his medical medium information is how
you get these things sorted out how you
get these
problems sorted out and
one stock of celery is not going to
clean all that out and fix the stomach
glands and restore them and clean up
your liver one stalk of celery it's not
going to clean up your liver
it's not going to do any of that and for
you guys who are freaking out about
lymphatic systems right
i'm just going to give you the rundown
right here okay
for the people that are freaking out
about the lymphatic system medical
medium doesn't talk lymphatic system he
doesn't talk lymphatic system
that's ridiculous
if you don't
take care of the liver
i've written a book about the liver
right liver rescue if you don't take
care of the liver
then you can never take care of your
lymphatic system
lymphatic system is this the dump yard
for the liver
i don't get it okay do all the massage
on your lymphatic system you want you
can do all that you can do
you can do all the you know anything you
want with your lymphatic system
you can jump on your rebounder you can
do massage okay
lymphatic massage you can do all these
things but unless you fix the liver and
clean it up
you'll just be chasing
your tail
you'll chase your tail
and there's only theories about what
makes the lymphatic system good or bad
or what helps the lymphatic system it's
just theories
theories that develop from people that
don't even know why anybody's sick to
begin with
but that's the tail chasing problem
happens i'm trying to fix my lymphatic
system trying to fix my lymphatic system
what you got to be fixing your liver is
what you got to be fixing or you're just
chasing your tail that's what you feel
like that dog that chases the tail until
you've got to try to stop the dog and
say it's okay you don't have to chase
your tail anymore
that was fun but we got to stop chasing
our tail
your lymphatic system's only as good as
your liver stagnant sluggish livers is
what everybody has
that's how the weight comes on
and the overflow of that toxic liver
goes into the lymphatic system
the overflow of that toxic liver goes
into the lymphatic system i have to say
it twice if i don't because here's what
happens everybody thinks oh the
lymphatic system that's where to go hey
i'm talking to another person about
lymphatic system
yeah i'm taking this new lymphatic
system product right here said i'm doing
uh what who's lymphatic system product
like didn't even know why you're sick
and you're taking just a hush posh stuff
thrown together
like a theory
here's the thing
medical medium information gets people
better because not only
does it make sense
but because there's a real reason
why it works
you can't clean your lymphatic system
unless that liver is cleaned up
your lymphatic system is your dumping
ground
it's your garbage can for the liver
liver gets over filled it gets stagnant
sluggish and it pours all into your
lymphatic system and you can play with
that lymphatic system all you want
but until
you do what you need to do and that's
one of the tools right there can you do
something for it there's a lot of bad
ideas out there
okay
and in order to heal you've got to know
how to weave in and out of them
bypass them it's like driving your car
into a pothole you see or you see
something on the highway like a rubber
tire that popped off a truck
right
you see a top pieces of tire all over
the highway with metal sticking out of
the tire right you're on the highway
okay
what do you do you just you just run
right over that tire
65 miles an hour is that what you do
when you do that you're eventually gonna
pop your tire and go off the road and
crash
and possibly die
so mm info is so we don't have to weave
so we can you know don't have to just
run over those tires
so instead we can be like whoa we got a
tire coming let's get around it whoa
wait a minute i was just sold on a whole
lymphatic drainage program i spent three
thousand dollars on when i could have
purchased a ten dollar medical medium
book and found out that the liver needed
to be cleaned up let me weave around
that tire oh the tire boom boom
and then for a street cred i got to
mention it because it just gets stickier
and stickier and uglier uglier out there
each year after each year
and the ghouls come out
is what they do
pure and of the light there isn't
hundreds of millions of dollars going
into this to get you to drink it every
day on television there isn't anything
nothing just people getting better while
people out there are getting sicker and
sicker and sicker
check out the medical device see mm-900
hds omega juicers.com
it's a medical device
this is an herbal extract tonic
and herbal extract it's not going to
happen by just having a celery stick
sure sure
sure
definitely have celery in your diet
making a little salad right you making a
little salad you chop up some yeah you
guys put this on my salad it's gonna be
great
right
you shouldn't be eating tuna fish
you can pop a few pieces in your tuna
fish salad but you shouldn't be eating
tuna fish right
right
you can definitely have right here you
can have some celery pieces
my dogs love celery pieces
right but i actually give my dog some
celery juice
the celery pieces aren't enough
you guys a couple of notes on
deficiencies
we got to put back in the tank
we got to get we got to get it back in
the tank it's like that boat the water's
filling in you can't shovel it out fast
enough and the boat sinks
and right now the world's getting to a
place
where they're hitting you on all sides
yeah we can just be in denial and
pretend it's not happening and then you
step in and then something happens
and then we're in trouble but they're
hitting this on all sides and that's how
they do it so guess what
this is one of the tools to bring in
get the mineral salts inside the brain
get the vitamin c that comes from this
right here you know get the chemical
compounds that restore
everything get the sodium cluster salts
that restore your stomach lands get the
liver flushed out you get that toxic
stuff flushed out man anything's
possible
anything's possible and most importantly
you kill off pathogens
i've been talking about viruses for 35
plus years actually even when i was
younger right
okay tempo viruses still was blue in the
face a ton of viruses talk about viruses
talk about viruses right
and what are we talking about today now
we're starting to talk about viruses
this right here paul i love you too man
this right here
is a big deal
people in the next five years are going
to need those medical medium tools it's
going to be their only chance
it's going to be their only chance
it is
going to get ugly it's been a lot of
contamination
a lot of contamination recently
people are going to need what works
love you guys
guys i'm heading off to instagram
where
i'm censored
and
they'll probably just kick everybody off
but maybe not maybe today will be good i
haven't been on there in a while so we
might be okay you guys are live on tick
tock right now facebook youtube
we're live on telegram
so i'm heading off to instagram i'm
gonna turn tick tock back on i'm gonna
turn telegram back on i might talk about
some different stuff because i tend to
do that i tend to switch it up too just
naturally happens and now i'm talking
about something else
okay
i love you guys