in their body they're worried about what
they're eating they're worried about
different exposures they're worried
about the quality of what they're
ingesting or putting on their body it's
all about oh this has got coconut oil in
it this has got and everybody is always
concerned about like what bad things
could be in things meanwhile I see it
out there every single day they're
taking supplements
and they're taking supplements that are
filled with crap
and they're getting ripped off
bottom line that's what's happening out
there all day long it's going on out
there and people don't realize it
and there's a whole bunch of people out
there with sensitivities
but they don't realize they're taking
supplements with all kinds of different
additives in there and different
impurities in there and different toxins
in there and they don't realize that's
contributing to their sensitivities
so so many people out there don't know
what's in their supplements they're
blindly taking things that seem like
they're trendy or hot companies in the
moment or fast talkers or people who own
supplement companies that are talking a
good you know Vibe they're talking good
whatever our stuff is the best stuff and
the best quality meanwhile there's crap
and garbage all through it and this is
going to blow your mind when I discuss a
little bit about this you don't want to
miss this episode because if you care
about yourself if you care about your
health you care about your body you're
going to want to know whether you like
me or not whether you're somebody that's
like
well you know what I like the medical
medium guy well I don't like the medical
medium guy because I don't like his
personality or whatever it is you still
should know so you can treat your body
good you still should have the respect
for your body
to actually just learn and to be
educated and understand what's going out
going around in the supplement world so
this is a critical talk today what you
see in front of me are is propolis and
lemon balm
so you see propolis and lemon balm right
there in front of me so that's the
vimergy brand right the vimergy brand
that I endorse and there's good reason
why I endorse these guys
because they don't do what all these
guys are doing right here these are just
a few
and wait till I tell you what these guys
are doing now you don't see the name of
the brand but these are in the store
these are in Whole Foods these are in
Sprouts these are in all the different
you know um health food stores these are
out in La these are out wherever these
are online
but I'm going to talk about what's in
here that will blow your mind that you
don't want going in your body and it's
not just these here I can have hundreds
of supplements in front of me right here
where I actually Mark out the label but
I can tell you what's going on inside of
them what's in there what kind of hidden
ingredients are going on that everybody
is taking because everybody becomes a
sucker everybody gets ripped off and
that's happening out there so yeah this
is a mind-blowing talk right here about
supplementation
and I'm going to talk about the propolis
and the lemon balm right here too by the
way there's a sale at imaging.com check
out the link in the description you have
to get the code though you'll find the
code Link in the description Link in the
profile at vimergy.com you'll see the
code there too if you buy a hundred
dollars worth of supplements at
vemergy.com you get a free four ounce
bottle of lemon balm and when I tell you
what's in the other lemon bombs out
there in the world you'll be like oh my
God okay if you get two hundred dollars
of supplements at vimergy.com you get a
free lemon balm four ounce and a free
propolis four ounce almost four ounces
right there and that's mind-blowing like
over 60 dollars of savings sixty dollars
of free products if you get two hundred
dollars at the imagery of
supplementation
and so this is all important too it's 71
dollars not even sixty it's seventy one
dollars free product so I want to tell
everybody before we go into the hardcore
truth about supplementation what's in
supplements out there the impurities the
additives the toxins all of it this is a
critical talk right here if you care
about what you put in your body if you
care about what you ingest if you care
about what you eat you want to know
what's going on and you want to know
this information you guys blown away at
that sale are you guys like totally
blown away I see a whole bunch of people
really Blown Away you guys 71 dollars a
free product if you buy two hundred
dollars worth of product at vimergy.com
you get a free Pro Bliss and a free
lemon balm almost four ounce bottles
it's sick that deal is absolutely
incredible it's so good so
here we are let's go into it a little
bit so why care about lemon bomb why
care about propolis to begin with
because you're looking at nervous system
think about that nervous system and
you're looking at immune system two
critical aspects of regaining Health
right there this isn't just because oh
lemon bombs interesting lemon bombs fun
propolis is interesting propolis is fun
no it's not that at all this is critical
nervous system
central nervous system right
and immune system two critical aspects
of moving someone forward
so important right there so many people
are sick so many people are struggling
emotionally mentally physically all of
it and two things immune system it's so
important and nervous system
we're going to go deeper on to the
nervous system deeper on to the into the
immune system as well so let's get down
to the nitty-gritty let's get down to
the bad news the bad news
when you go into the store and you're
buying your lemon balm and you go in the
store and you're buying your propolis or
whatever it is you're buying
you have no idea what's in there and
what's going on and what's going wrong
basically
you're just being ripped off or fooled
or taken advantage of and that's what
it's like in the supplement world
that's how it works so let's cut into it
a little bit
I am going to take a look here okay for
a second now this is a propolis right
here
see I got the brand marked off this is a
propolis right here
now
this propolis does not say it has
alcohol in it
it does not say it has alcohol in it
keep that in mind so if you're somebody
that's into propolis this looks like a
great company it looked like a great
brand it's in the store it's out there
you purchase it you don't know
but it has alcohol in it when it says it
doesn't when there isn't alcohol on the
label now I opened this up
and it smells like
I'm at a bar
that's how much alcohol is in this
propolis
it smells like this is a shot of whiskey
that's what it smells like I opened it
up
and it smells like straight grain
alcohol
but you would never know that
there are propolises that say alcohol
free but still have alcohol in it
and that's something to know all on its
own
so there's propolises out there that say
alcohol free but still have alcohol in
it this is a propolis that no one would
ever know has alcohol in it
they would never know because they'd be
like wait this doesn't have all the
ingredient says
is glycerin and water
it's all it says
there's so much alcohol in here
you can get like
Tipsy just breathing that in and that's
how propolises are out there
that's an example
[Music]
here's a propolis right here from a very
well-known company a company that's in
every store a company that's out there
everywhere
okay this is in a tincture bottle if you
go into the health food store if you go
anywhere you go into Whole Foods there's
a whole section and this is a tincture
within that section not saying the brand
and this one says it has alcohol in it
it's a propolis that actually says it
has alcohol so at least you know it has
alcohol in it but here is the amazing
part of this one you'll see this
propolis ready so this says it has
alcohol in it
which you don't want so if you guys are
confused at what I'm saying
the vemergy propolis pure does not have
alcohol in it hidden in it doesn't have
it hidden
right but this is a propolis right here
from a company from a brand that's in
Whole Foods or any other food health
food store everywhere across the land
it has alcohol in this propolis
a lot of it
it's cane sugar alcohol though but it's
cane sugar alcohol and then you'll
notice something about this propolisa
this is important to see
see how dark it is
take a look how dark it is
propolis
should never be dark
now you might think well maybe that's a
good thing you're getting a lot of it or
something or you're getting you know
there's a lot of propolis there's resin
what you're seeing right here
is burnt propolis
that's what you're saying burnt resin
it's useless
so if you went into the health food
store and you wanted to buy propolis and
you just bought a bottle of propolis and
it was dark like this
that's burnt
it's destroyed
that's what you're looking at right
there see this
this is going to be highly educational
episode right here I think it's
important that people know the truth of
what's going on because I think I had it
up to here actually with all the BS out
there to the degree that it is and
people who don't know what they're
talking about but what that is
is burnt propolis now here's another
thing you're looking at with this
propolis now this is a very well-known
brand that people have high respect for
out there get ready for this
guess what else you're seeing you're
seeing impurities
you're seeing impurities from a single
pass extraction
this is going to be mind-blowing
you might want to watch this episode
over again to be honest
this is single pass extraction what that
mean it means is heavy metals
impurities garbage and junk
is all still in there
so you go out there and you buy a
propolis and it looks like a dark
propolis and you're like oh my God that
looks pretty good first of all there's
alcohol even when they say there isn't
alcohol even when this one says there's
no alcohol and you actually open this up
and it is literally an alcohol
like
an alcoholic drink
like if you drink that
you'd be like boom
it hit you like a shot of whiskey
[Music]
so what you're seeing here
is dark propolis dark propolis is burnt
dark propolis is harboring impurities
lots of them metals
beeswax not the healthy stuff all
impurities
is going on in there so it is
filled with a whole bunch of different
stuff and junk that it shouldn't have
it's called single pass extraction
now when you're dealing with vermergy
propolis pure
you're looking at multi extraction
technology
that's the difference right there guess
what I don't care who puts out of
propolis out there I don't care who's
doing what with the propolis
I highly doubt it's going to be
multi-extraction technology
highly highly doubted and that's the
difference right there so that's the
Imaging now propolis here we are okay
all right and you'll take a look at this
golden golden color right here
see if you can see this I know I might
not be as close but
take a look right here
okay it's the golden color you see that
that's from multi extraction technology
it's leaving the bioactives leaving all
the bioactives but separating the
impurities separating the junk and the
garbage that I was talking about that's
in the other propolises this is so
important to know
propolis shouldn't be dark it shouldn't
be dark brown it shouldn't be black
that's single pass extraction that means
it's missing the extraction process is
missing it's letting all the impurities
go by it's letting all the toxins go by
and this right here and the reason why
people say this propolis is like a
miracle for their health a miracle for
them and works like nothing else for so
many things and reasons in their health
this is like a god-given miracle to have
this right now on the planet to have
this type of propolis because it doesn't
exist with the other companies it just
doesn't exist Juliet over there on
YouTube says
the vimorgy propolis cleared 16 ulcers
from my mouth it was the only thing that
worked you're not the only one I I heard
or hear out there say what it does for
ulcers in the mouth
it's unbelievable what it does
and so I'm showing you right here a
god-given miracle in the supplement
realm right here which is the propolis
now if you just got on here you just got
to know that beverage is giving a free
bottle of propolis away and a free
bottle of lemon balm away with 200 order
of emergy.com
so Julie over there in IG says provolas
healed a cold sore in two days
OMG
it's that incredible now take a look at
the difference ready I'm going to keep
on putting more in here so this is the
golden extract right there it's called
multi extraction technology
peace and veggies says propolis pure by
vimorigi has healed my mouth thank you
vimergy and guess what
just think about that think about like
what that is what that even is how
incredible that is
so
all right so I wanted to show you that
there's so much to talk about you guys
so let's get into it a little bit deeper
let's talk about this a little bit more
I'm very excited right now
for a lot of reasons
Renata 144 says over there on YouTube aw
there are people who buy alcohol-based
subs and believe they can burn the
alcohol off of it by cooking it not sure
can you please speak to that to clarify
for the community I talk about that in
medical medium books by the way and yes
you can't get rid of the alcohol by
heating it up doesn't work the residue
of the alcohol is still there the herbs
are still damaged alcohol damages the
herbs so it destroys them very important
to know alcohol and tinctures
annihilates the phytochemical compounds
the things that we need the bioactives
it injures them so even if you're
somebody like well I'll burn off some of
the alcohol somehow by heating it up
basically what that means is you have to
get such a heat to burn off the alcohol
where you have to light it basically on
fire so you have to go super hot
super hot to try to burn the alcohol out
of those alcoholic tinctures if you're
going that hot you've just destroyed
your herbal tincture you just destroyed
the constituents the phytochemical
compounds the bioactives you just
completely annihilated that by being
fooled and tricked by being told you can
burn it off and then you'll be fine
these are the mistakes made out there
but that's the problem and that's why
people don't heal because all of these
checks and balances aren't there people
are in the dark they don't know what's
going on with their products and healing
and things they need or detoxing or
what's not detoxing and what is they
have no idea and all of this including
things like yeah using supplements out
with alcohol can slow down healing and
it even reverse healing so alcohol in
products even can reverse healing so
you're somebody that's trying to heal
you you think you're doing something
good for yourself and you're taking all
these supplements without alcohol
calling them and you're going backwards
because of it that's that's how it works
so
mind-blowing information let's go a
little deeper
so I just showed you a propolis
that's dark
and I showed you why because the
propolis is burnt
that's why not just burnt
but also
it's got all the impurities in there too
now you're looking at the difference
right there
you're seeing right here the propolis
pure
with the multi-extraction technology
what that means is it takes out
impurities
but leaves the bioactives
the other propolis is out there single
pass extraction they let all the garbage
pass through
it hinders the bioactives
so we got that right there critical to
know if you guys just got on there on
here if you buy a hundred dollars
of supplements from vimergy.com and the
link is in description you get a free
almost four ounce bottle of the lemon
balm which is incredible for the nervous
system
if you buy two hundred dollars of
supplements of energy.com
you get a free almost four ounce bottle
of propolis pure
and a free bottle of lemon balm so you
get that immune system Helper and you
get that nervous system helper
71 dollars free product I don't see
other companies doing this out there I
just don't see it especially the quality
here we're talking about Dr Fawn said he
is absolutely plugging the product
because it works my patient used it
topically to heal his rashes when the
prescriptions from the dermatologist
never work thank you Dr fun
so it's important to know something okay
there are ways to do plugs for
supplements and things like that there
are ways to do different stuff but in
this situation here I'm showing you how
incredible and how different the
vermergy products are compared to what's
out there
because I see it all day long I see
people getting propolis out there that's
filled with alcohol
or it's burnt or it's got all the
impurities and it's got all three it's
burnt impurities and has alcohol in it
and it's a shame it's truly a sin it's
really a shame and nobody knows it and
they're just walking around blind
they're ripped off no one's telling them
anything and they're not moving
themselves forward the healing process
now that's just the Stark truth and it's
critical for people to know and yeah I
support vimergy and for these reasons
because that doesn't exist with other
companies so yes I'm gonna plug them and
I'm going to talk about them and I'm
going to share this information it's
critical Dr Sherry green over there on
IG
propolis pure is phenomenal for so many
conditions love it for my patients
so I'm on the propolis pure talk I want
to get into that a little bit it's a
multi- extraction technology to separate
the undesirable compounds critical to
know
that's a big deal all on its own
so it removes it's a removal system of
unwanted purities like toxic heavy
metals and all these other different
things that's what's so great about that
process
these propolises and there's plenty of
them out there I've literally probably
purchased almost every single propolis
that is out there at least every one
that's popular everyone that's on the
Shelf
and I've gone through them all
and they're loaded with junk and garbage
they're either burnt they got the
impurities
or they're just loaded with alcohol and
the thing is is there's alcohol in all
the propolises out there and maybe
there's one that might not have it but
here's the trick the ones that say they
don't have it still have the alcohol in
it hidden ingredients
and alcohol is one of the hidden
ingredients they also hide natural
flavors now they hide preservatives they
hide all that stuff so let's go into
lemon balm a little bit
move these aside right
the not good propolis so moving that
over all right let's hit the lemon balm
so let's go into this a little bit so I
have a lemon balm that's very popular
here it is in my hand
I bet you a bunch of people even
watching this or that are going to watch
this have this lemon balm they don't
know the brand but I'm sure they have it
it's a very popular brand and most
people buy this they just go into the
store and they buy this brand so this is
a lemon balm right here
okay
so this lemon balm is a three to one
a three to one
keep that in mind
that that's its strength it's three to
one okay you'll see this one's dark
but lemon balm
should be dark
it should be keep that in mind but this
is going to blow your mind
lemon balm should be dark
because of the herb itself
so as you can see
I put the dark
Herb in here
but that's three to one
it shouldn't be that dark
and that's scary
gotta think about that for a minute
it shouldn't be that dark
why is it that dark
hidden ingredients
hidden impurities
very important to know
and I'm gonna go into depth about this
on on the lemon balm front okay
so it's memory lemon balm right there
it's supposed to be dark
keep that in mind
and you're probably like well what's he
saying
remember she
lemon balm is ten to one
ten to one
think about that strength difference
so let's go into this
lemon balm is supposed to be dark
and here's that brand
look how dark it is
but it's three to one
it's not supposed to be that dark
it's supposed to be a lot lighter than
beverages ten to one
which is really high potency
if your mind isn't blown
I don't know what to say I don't know
what else I can do
this is a really important piece of
information right here in the supplement
world
and yes I'm the only one talking about
this out there
the only one and I noticed the
supplement companies and the influencers
that work for supplement companies and
all that stuff
they won't go near any of this kind of
talk because their companies are guilty
of so much
they won't go near any of this
very important and it's also why I'm
hated
by competitors out there
they hate how incredible all this is and
how it shows them up so take a look once
again
I'm going to take the popular company
and
it's like this all around
I purchased so many lemon bombs from the
best companies so called out there
so ready here we go
that's the lemon balm from a popular
company and you guys are watching how
dark that is but what is mind-blowing
is that's a three to one ratio which
isn't that strong
then what the hell is in there
that is the question hidden additives
hidden ingredients that are not
disclosed junk and impurities what the
hell is in there
okay
very important to know because this is
the vimorges
that's the vimorges
lemon balm
it's not as dark
but
it's ten to one
stronger
this is three to one
do you see how dark that is and this is
ten to one
look at that
that's less impurities less additives
less junk
whatever's in here
is scary
because a three to one can never be that
dark do you guys know what I'm talking
about
so yeah all the lemon balm tinctures out
there and all the new companies putting
out lemon bombs because they they
because it got trendy because of medical
medium
it's like this and I'm going to show you
another version of lemon balm that's
lighter and it's scary for a whole
nother reason so I can't wait to show
you that
so here we go
so that's the difference right there
okay
next let's go into another aspect of it
so that's a lemon balm right there
all right
here's a lemon balm a different lemon
balm right here
okay
all right
this is a lemon balm that tells you
nothing it doesn't tell you it's a three
to one it doesn't tell you it's in
anything it doesn't tell you
how many milligrams it doesn't tell you
anything this is a lemon balm that
someone will go out and buy because it's
a popular brand it's out there on the
Shelf
and they'll buy it thinking they're
getting themselves better I heard lemon
balms good for medical medium I heard it
does all this and all that he talks
about it in his book let me go to the
store let me buy a lemon balm and then
they buy one take a look at this lemon
balm is supposed to be dark
that's not dark
now that's scary all in its own
what does that mean
that means this company
is doing something who only knows
it's either they have so very little
lemon bomb and someone's being ripped
off so everybody buying this lemon balm
tincture that I won't show you the brand
they're being ripped off look at that
do you see it's supposed to be dark
but yet
unlike this one which is really dark
this isn't supposed to be that dark
because this is just a three to one
so this one here is
spooky this one here is spooky
because lemon balm tincture is supposed
to be dark but this is golden
and on the bottle it doesn't tell you
to what degree of lemon balm is actually
in there so that's anything from
impurities hidden ingredients to very
little lemon balm
someone takes it they don't see a result
and now they're not getting better
someone takes it they don't see any
improvements they don't see anything
happening or changing
and they don't get better
fly on the wall if I only was a fly on
the wall
in everybody's house and saw all the
mistakes all the tricks all the rip-offs
it's just unbelievable
so over there on YouTube
Edie says can you speak to the fact that
bemidji's products
formally contained alcohol in years past
huh beverages products never contained
alcohol and any years passed since the
Inception of that company to this very
day that's false information and that's
how rumors are started purposely
and that's sad because that's what's
happening right now and there is an
attack on Bemidji because of the quality
being so good because it's unbelievable
stuff it's god-given in my opinion from
what I've seen
and it's that incredible and companies
can't keep up with it they can't match
it they can't on any level
and that's why there's so much trouble
out there with rumors and and fals
cities and all of that all right so
let's go into this a little bit deeper
now with some other stuff so I showed
you
the lemon mom with the light color
brand a lot of people have it in their
cupboard I can guarantee so many people
have it
it's light because there's hardly any
lemon balm and there's something else in
here instead which is really sad
here's the dark lemon balm but it's
three to one but it's pitch dark which
means something's wrong here
it's not supposed to be that dark it
means a lot of impurities a lot of junk
and garbage in there and then the
propolises with the alcohol the
propolises that say they're alcohol free
but they're not alcohol free how are
they allowed to do this they just are
and that's how the supplement World
Works anybody can basically put out
almost anything without checks and
balances so that's important to
understand all on its own there is so
much alcohol in these propolises this
one is off the charts you smell it and
you can get drunk that's how insanely
entrenched in alcohol that that
supplement is
it's insane
so I just want to go over a couple of
different cool things here about all of
this because this is important so let me
just remind everybody a hundred dollars
of energy product if you purchase a
hundred dollars of energy product you
get a free almost four ounces of lemon
balm
nervous system
so good and if you purchase two hundred
dollars at vimergy.com link is in
description link is in the profile you
get a free almost four ounce bottle of
propolis pure and lemon balm which is
mind-blowing 71 dollars
right there take advantage of this stuff
when it happens like this take advantage
of those kinds of sales those kinds of
offers that are out there but you got to
use the code go to imagery.com check out
the code that's something I could stand
behind it's a company I can stand behind
because of what they do and their
process so I want to remind people
I'll go deeper into this so propolis
pure contains over 50 percent of the
bioactives
it's critical to know that the
polyphenols over 50 percent active
bioactive polyphenols like quercetin and
other polyphenols important to know
that is part of the multi-extraction
technology to get rid of impurities but
preserve the bile actives very important
to know
and immune system is critical
heartlight says there I'm a clinician
I'm a clinical psychologist
and the Bemidji supplements are critical
for mental health as well amazing over
there on IG
I think what happens is that people
don't realize when they invest into
something that they're using on their
body or inside their body they don't
know really what's going on there
because there was a law passed that
allows companies to not disclose they
don't have to disclose hidden
ingredients a certain percentage of
hidden ingredients in their
supplementation
and no one talks about this
I'm the only one I've seen out there
talking about this the reason why is
because
supplement companies and influencers
that either own supplement companies are
starting their own supplement companies
they're not going to say oh we don't we
don't have hidden you know percentages
and they're not going to say that
because what they do is if you have a
bunch of money you can go start a
supplement company tomorrow if you had a
bunch of money you can go and say okay I
will go to this manufacturing place they
will put it together for me I want this
this
you know and they put it together and
they don't have they don't have control
over the hidden ingredients that are in
there they don't know how to say hey
don't put that in ours don't put that in
this company make sure you do this make
sure you do that look for the highest
quality they don't do that it's kind of
like they just Stamp Out supplements for
influencers these days that want to
start companies tomorrow and they stamp
it out is what they do as long as that
influencer is wealthy rich or has a
bunch of money or something somehow and
they want to start their supplement
company they just literally oh it's just
like it's like clothing brands you can
go and get your clothing lines made
right to what's out there to what the
the clothing manufacturers be like all
right we'll put your name on it we'll
put the name of your company on and
we'll put it out there
but people don't realize in the
supplement world they're filled with all
these impurities hidden ingredients
undisclosed ingredients
and that's what's happening out there
and it's really sad
so
it's important to know how it works I
want to go into propolis a little bit I
think really that it deserves and flim
bum it deserves a spotlight
so
one of the major problems people suffer
with is immune system issues
anybody who's got an autoimmune
diagnosis or any kind of other problem
anything going on with their immune
system any kind of symptoms they're
struggling immune system wise
and that's important to know
and so what I like about propolis it's
one of these Miracles that we have on
this planet that supports the immune
system
and so it's critical you have the purest
kind
out there that you can find
to actually help
support the immune system
and that's a big deal so we're up
against all kinds of exposures out there
every day we're up against all kinds of
pathogens we're up against all kinds of
different impurities different toxins
and the more load we have on us
the more our immune system has to kill
itself to clean it up
so we take our immune systems for
granted without realizing it many of us
take take our immune systems for granted
and don't realize that our immune cells
are these garbage eaters
inside our body so they're there to go
after pathogens and eat up pathogens our
immune cells are there to go after
impurities and garbage and junk
and to eat it up chemicals metals and
everything else our immune cells are
there to eat these things
so that these things don't affect us as
much or so bad
and so what I like about propolis is it
supports the immune system feeds the
immune system
and that's critical if someone's
actually struggling with anything that's
why it deserves a spotlight
and propolis was
just kind of like this Niche obscure
novelty thing and people did not know
really what it does how good it is how
supportive it is
in the health movement
Tara says I've tried so many supplements
over the years most of them actually
made my symptoms worse Bemidji
supplements are incredible and actually
help me you can really tell the
difference in quality
and there is a difference because when
it comes down to people so many people
are sensitive they're sensitive for a
lot of reasons
and
if they do take supplements that have
alcohol in them and natural flavors
and all kinds of different toxic toxic
additives and they don't you know it's
in there and they don't know it and
they're taking these supplements they'll
instantly blame the herb or what the
name of it is
so if they take a toxic lemon balm and
there's so many of them out there
and they take a lemon balm that has
alcohol in it or a lemon balm that has
natural flavors or a lemon balm that has
all this other junk and garbage or
hidden ingredients and they take it and
they're like well it's not working it's
not helping me in fact I feel a little
bit sensitive it's because of everything
that's in there that shouldn't be in
there that they don't know is in there
so
um by the way what I normally do with
beverages lemon balm is I take a dropper
full and I put it right here
in some water and some honey
so that's how I usually do
this is actually a big mug right here
that's usually how I do like my lemon
balm tea now is I take
the lemon balm now this is an important
um important piece of information about
the lemon balm it's ten to one so you
got to think about it if you pick lemon
balm out of your garden if you pick it
out by hand
and you just get your lemon balm out of
the garden and you dry it
and you have a portion of that lemon
balm like a whole bunch of dried lemon
balm leaves that's one
that's one
ten to one is ten of those
so that's important to know ten of one
ten of ten to one is ten of those
handfuls of herbs and that ten to one is
in here
right in the dropper
this one here
with the hidden ingredients and the
impurities
is a three to one
so it's only three of these instead of
ten
all right so
um I'm gonna take a little sip here and
we'll keep on going a little bit because
this is incredible information you're
growing your own lemon balm that's
that's incredible
so good
okay
so I think we're people what people
don't realize
is they'll hear something out there like
lemon balm is good
but they don't know how much more there
is to learn about it they'll go out and
they'll buy a lemon balm tincture
it doesn't work
and then they move they move on I tried
lemon balm it did nothing for me and now
they have that experience and they have
that reference
and that reference can travel to
somebody else
it's like oh you tried lemon bomb yeah
it didn't work for me doesn't work I
tried it and then this next person goes
oh okay well then I'm not going to try
it either because
it didn't work for you so it's probably
not going to work for me and then that
person goes and tells another person oh
you tried lemon yeah no one doesn't work
I didn't have to try it I just know it
doesn't work
and then it goes on Down the Line like
that meanwhile it all stems from someone
taking
an unproductive lemon balm that didn't
do the trick that didn't help that
didn't work
and so this is the problem in the health
world it's how we can then just go like
where do we go and then we go to
something else then we go to something
else and it's endless I think one of the
most disheartening parts of the herbal
tincture world is the alcohol and
tinctures and I think medical medium
information really blew that wide open
where alcohol is avoided in a lot of
tinctures now because of medical meme
information
which leads me to something else I want
to say
wondering Wishin says I tried an organic
sink
when first starting medical medium after
four days I stopped it made me feel
worse
after aw talked about supplement quality
I tried memories Inc and wow and it was
a game changer can change everything I
remember back in the day liquid sinks
with so much citrus acid and there still
is liquid zincs with so much citric acid
in there which is also hidden in a lot
of um the tinctures hidden in the
supplements citric acid is like in
everything it's not in memory but it's
in everything out there and I I recall
so many people taking zinc the liquid
zinc from reputable companies on the
store shelf and they buy it and they
squirt it in their mouth and they throw
up
they just vomit
just projectile vomit
it literally turns their stomach in a
second they get sick and they just puke
and that's it and that's the reference
right there with zinc
from there on out they're just gonna be
like I can't take zinc meanwhile zinc is
so critical
for the healing process and so critical
for the immune system but that person
may never actually take a zinc again
to help them heal and to be one of those
people where look I just you know and I
tried zinc it doesn't work and then they
tell somebody else it doesn't work so I
want to talk about vimergy as far as
what they have in here
they got organic glycerin in their
tincture bottles
organic glycerin
but there's a word next to it
it's flax
this is advanced
this is a big deal
and this is another reason why I stand
behind these guys there's so many
reasons why I stand behind these guys
you can't touch this stuff other
companies out there can't touch this
it's not touchable
what you'll see is organic glycerin
and then you'll see the word flax
f-l-a
right X
important to know
so it's not junk garbage
glycerin
so you got two options in the tincture
world if you want to try to heal and do
stuff if you want to use Herbal
tinctures to try to move yourself
forward get two options it's alcohol or
glycerin those are your options out
there
how he says can all the supplements be
taken at once that's look that's how I
do it ask your doctor what's right for
you Holly but that's what I do
I'll take them at once
so there's two options we have
if you want to look into the supplement
world
in the tincture world
it's alcohol or glycerin
archangelica says yes I puked from a low
quality zinc
you know the sad part is is I hate to
say this over and over again but I
talked about this many years ago how
people puke from their low quality zincs
but nobody talked about it was like a
hidden dirty Secret
Rosie said yes several zincs gave me
gave many nausea
so
Lindsay says all other zinc Brands I've
tried made me feel super nauseous and
sick memories Inc is the only one I can
take and feel fine
that says so much
so I just want to say back to this and
Jackie says I now keep lemon balm in my
purse for anxiety I tell people keep it
in their purse keep it in their bag keep
it in their car keep it at their office
keep it in the kitchen keep a bottle
wherever you can if you order a 200
order at vimergy.com you get a free
lemon balm almost four ounce bottle
lemon balm and a free almost four ounce
bottle a propolis pure 71 dollars a free
product
that's insane I don't know how they do
it Christina says I have used zinc since
2011 for my alopecia and they always
made me so what a bar face it was it
wasn't before vimorgy zinc that I did
not get that vimergy zinc is the best
one out there used it in the past four
years now
incredible so I want to go back to the
glycerin process
if you're going to take any tinctures at
all if you're going to go to anybody and
take tinctures if you're going to buy
anything out there if you're going to
talk to an herbalist if you're going to
talk to a brand new supplement company
that just put out some tinctures
you got two options
glycerin
or alcohol
both are bad
unless the glycerin
is flax because chances are it's going
to be a really low quality glycerin
that's not flax
you don't even know where it is and what
it is I mean you don't know what it's
dry from or where it comes from and
that's the problem even when talking to
supplement companies be like well what's
your glycerin made from whatever
they'll still kind of have this like
spew
but in the end it's bulk glycerin
and you don't know really the true story
behind it
and when I take the Bemidji supplements
I know this organic glycerin is flax
derived and that right there gives me a
good night's sleep all on its own that's
a big deal I don't see that out there
and that's huge all on its own you guys
I mean seriously
it's just incredible
it really is
so I wanted to run those things by you
guys to let you know that there's a sale
right now vermergy.com it's really a
giveaway I don't know what to call it
it's a giveaway
it's they're giving away 71 dollars of
product for a 200 order
and it's the propolis pure and the lemon
balm and if you want like I tell people
you don't have to know everything about
your healing process or everything about
products in the world you don't have to
know everything but you got to know at
least the foundations and what I see out
there is people don't know the
foundations
you don't have that part and they don't
know that part and that's tricky for so
many
they don't have the foundational aspects
of their health and healing and the
products and the stuff they're ingesting
and what they're putting inside their
body they have a lot of misinformation
and they suffer because of it and they
end up on the Merry-Go-Round because of
it and that's a big deal right there
so free lemon balm and propolis pure
with 200 purchase get your free stress
unless
plus immunity combo right at 200 of your
Bemidji favorites to the cart
step two add lemon balm
propolis pure to the cart use the code
that's there I'm looking at the website
now you guys I'm looking at the website
use code
free Lee so f-r-e-e-l-e-m
-p-r-o-p Dash Vim Vim at the checkout
complete transaction enjoy your free
lemon balm and propolis pure
so good so I tell people
just simply I know people are busy in
their life they got a lot going on and
it's hard to learn everything it's hard
to learn a lot of things because you're
multitasking you've got a lot of
responsibilities there's so much being
asked of everybody in life right so what
I do is I simplify it
nervous system I don't even call lemon
bomb lemon balm I call it central
nervous system
that's what I call it
so I changed the name of lemon balm
in my head
in my life in my mind and then propolis
I don't even call it propolis anymore I
call it immune system
I mean that's what I call it of course
this is just propolis and it's not your
immune system isn't in that bottle but I
call it immune system and that's what I
do it's these simple things too that
like they they just remind you of what
you're doing for yourself
and that's a big big deal too it's the
connection of it like I'm helping my
nervous system
that connection alone is so powerful I'm
helping my immune system link is in the
bio
the link is in the description you guys
anyway
I just want it to check in with you guys
tell you about this incredible offer
which blows my mind
if anything if you're not gonna if
you're not gonna like order anything if
you're not gonna order
supplements from Bemidji at least know
what all of this is what I showed you
here if you just came on board watch
this from the beginning and get your
mind blown
crispy perspective on YouTube I just
took all my beverages supplements first
day of my menstrual cycle so need all
the immune support I can get never liked
taking any supplements and never can
take it daily until memory
because
all those impurities and and added added
ingredients that people don't know about
that are added undisclosed not disclosed
all of that and then the quality
difference
you know I hate that word quality I hate
that word quality because everybody uses
it when they don't have quality
or their quality is low but they don't
have to say low like supplement
companies can say quality we choose
quality from the finest places
but really the quality they're choosing
is low quality they don't have to say
low quality
it's insane Julie Tuesday over there on
YouTube says I've been taking
supplements my whole life but it wasn't
until I started using Bemidji brand that
I actually felt healing results it's a
huge step forward
it really is it's really an incredible
opportunity
it just is someone said can you repeat
the code go to imagery.com you'll see
the code there go to vimergy.com these
in Victor I Amazon Mary ergy.com
and you'll see the code you'll see the
amazing
basically giveaway that's what it is
hit the banner at the top of the website
where it says learn more so hit the
banner at the top of the website where
it says learn more
and that's important anyway guys
check the video out from the beginning
please if you can
and
yeah
this is incredible information you won't
hear this
and other places you won't hear this in
other supplement companies you won't
hear this and other influencers working
for supplement companies you won't hear
this information and that's why Bemidji
stands Above the Rest
it just does hate me
like me take me or leave me it stands
Above the Rest whether anybody likes it
or not out there you guys and I want you
to know that
anyone who's working on their healing
process just always be easy on yourself
just realize it can take some time for
so many people so many people
have a lot of compromises a lot of
exposures it takes time but keep in mind
like in the medical medium books
you can take your healing as far as you
need to go always know that it's there
it's not just
like you try one little thing and that
was it it's there for you to keep on
moving forward the information is there
and just know that you know pat yourself
on the back know that your body loves
you unconditionally and don't let
anybody tell you that your immune system
is attacking your body your organs
just let them tell you but that's not
accurate it's misinformation it's been
happening since the 1950s
misinformation literally since the 1950s
our body's immune system does not attack
organs it does not attack ourselves
it doesn't attack
our body our glands our immune system
goes after pathogens and Invaders and
that's what's happening and then
pathogens
and Invaders are what inflames us that's
what goes after our organs and glands
so if you're somebody that's you know
coming into a place where like what's
going on my body's just destroying
itself my body's immune system is
attacking itself that's so outdated old
crap misinformation was never
scientifically proven ever under a
microscope it was nothing but a theory
keep that in mind
but it's important to know that our
bodies love us and unconditionally and
they look out for us and we just have to
give our bodies what it needs we have to
support our bodies so our bodies can
actually do what they need to do our
immune system can do what it needs to do
and that's a big part of the healing
process
something always to remember that your
body isn't faulty it's not letting you
down it's not turning against you you
don't have a bad body you don't have a
faulty body you're not a bad person
so always remember that your body isn't
kicking your legs out from underneath
you it's not pulling the carpet from
underneath you it's not purposely trying
to take you down your body is actually
fighting for you every day you gotta go
to bed at night and you got to tell your
body Thank You For Fighting For Me
every night when you go to bed and then
when you wake up in the morning City
your body Thank You For Fighting For Me
thank you I will support you in any way
I possibly can
anyway I love you guys
and I will see you guys soon