it's the big day it's the big day Angels
demons and spiritual tools I can't
believe we're here and it's out you can
get it on Audible on Amazon get on
Spotify Apple could find it there have
you guys listened first thing I want to
say first and
foremost a little bit at a time you can
listen all day long take breaks though
half an hour at a time because there's
that much information there and if you
did listen to it and you're like hey I
listen to all seven and a half
hours I would probably say you played
all s and a half hours go back and
listen because there's that much
information and that information takes
time to settle in I mean I can go back
and listen and be like oh my God you
know when you hear about the
Romans ancient Rome and you hear about
demons and you hear about angels and
then did you hear about the part there's
falling angels how they play a role not
Fallen Angels that's another thing
there's falling angels and how those
Falling Angels play a
role anyway I'm here to talk a little
bit about this Angels demons and
spiritual tools is out right now
and what you're going to find out when
you start listening is you're going to
start to find out how it plays in your
life how it affects your life you're
going to be able to start connecting the
dots with certain
things yeah you're going to be able to
connect the
dots you didn't take breaks oh no okay I
see a lot of people are blown away is it
mind-blowing that information from s
so it's it's mind numbing mindblowing so
I want to talk about a couple different
things if you guys are open the Coliseum
part it's
terrible yeah oh I it's definitely
terrible it's evil and hideous and
horrible
absolutely the Coliseum the Roman
Coliseum oh
yeah if you guys just got on here just
waiting for you guys to come on too some
of you guys to come on
here so I want to read a little bit to
you maybe even try to play a clip so
I'll do that too in a little
bit good to see you guys thanks for
coming on talking about how this could
be affecting people's lives did you get
to the part of what is a demon did you
guys get to that part yet what is a
demon I mean that information just blows
my
mind it just
does so okay
so let me see let me just look at some
different stuff
here okay so this is interesting right
here so many people live in a bubble out
there where the thought of Darkness
existing is only meant for the
movies they believe that when things
happen to people in real life you see it
all the time by the way things happening
to people in real
life they brought it upon themselves how
many people it's like no you brought
that upon yourself you did that you
created that so a little girl that's
crossing the street and gets run over by
a car so that little girl brought it
upon themselves like you
know is that how it works it just
doesn't make any sense right freak
accidents they brought it upon
themselves
I mean that's just one thing what about
all the other things too for those who
live with this kind of belief that you
brought it upon
yourself maybe the worst they've
experienced so far was a girlfriend or a
boyfriend cheating on them I mean that's
bad of course that's bad or a mean
coworker causing a problem a lot of
people they quit their jobs they change
their their work status all of it
because of that
or a family member who they didn't get
along with while these things can still
bring about grief and injury people
often don't equate these happenings with
any form of Darkness or even demonic
involvement they don't equate any of
that to it at
all so when something terrible happens
or some is betrayed so terribly they're
not equating like Darkness being
involved they just don't connect the
dots to
that this this alone is when you think
about this is
mind-blowing this information to these
people the thought of demonic and Fallen
beings inherently involved in so many of
the world's problems seems overreaching
and not
reality so when you look at all the
terrible things that happen on this
planet that's
just good people doing terrible things
just for no reason there's no spiritual
connection there's no spiritual war
there's no spiritual
involvement that's not true there is
spiritual
involvement there is a spiritual war
I've been saying that for decades there
is all of
this
and darkness is involved with so much
and a lot of people experience it on
their everyday life in their everyday
life so if you guys came on here I'm
talking about angels demons and
spiritual tools it's out right now so
type in medical medium maybe the link
right there is in the description link
is in the bio or if you can't find it
somewhere just type in medical medium
Angels demons and spiritual tools so
type that in on Amazon audible type that
in on Spotify type that in on Apple it's
released today I heard it was released
like 3 o'clock this
morning I couldn't
sleep I couldn't
sleep not because of excitement about it
being released I was kind of worried
about how people were going to digest
this information how they were going to
take this information in how they were
going to receive this information so
that kept me up for a little bit I mean
I was up like 4 in the morning saying oh
wow Spirit of compassion did we do the
right thing did we do the right thing
like the whole bit you
know so that's what it looks like right
there I don't know if you can see that
over there on IG can you see
that is what it looks like Tik Tock
can't believe Tik Tock let me
back they banned me a while back and
they let me back
in but who knows they might they might
reban me
so that's right there you can just order
it
now
so there's there's some great stuff to
talk about you guys I'm going to cover a
little bit of it I don't know how far
you got into the audio it's 7 and 1 half
hours take it a half half an hour at a
time Cold Light spring says I love it no
doubt my family has a family demon or
more the family demon section inside
this
audio is just an Awakening all on its
own so when you get to that part whoa I
mean you might be like oh my God this is
unbelievable you can have loved ones
that you love and everything and they
can be
affected by this lineage of family
demons and that is one of the most
powerful one of one of them anyway most
powerful points in this entire audio is
that right there alone the amount of
turmoil people go go through the amount
of turmoil they go they go through in
their life with different family members
and different things that have happened
in the family things that go back like
generations and it's still like a stain
on their Consciousness their memory
memory their grandfather
great-grandfather things that have
happened in their
lives and you can kind of Trace back and
almost kind of like say oh my God I
could see where a demon was involved I
can see where Darkness was involved why
else did this happen or whoo look at
this if we're not aware that demons are
possibly involved in matters that affect
our
lives or inv involved with other people
who could be in our lives and how they
react and treat others that's
interesting how they treat others how
they react and treat others or involved
with freak accidents and bad luck it's
just bad luck H that's all it is you got
bad luck that's
all that's not really what it is or
involved with peer pressure you think
peer pressure is demonic the amount of
peer pressure that's out there things
that have happened I mean when you
listen to this
audio Checkmate that's right I see that
right there
Checkmate the when you hear about that
Spirit of compassion gave me all this
information about
Chess and one of the spiritual tools
which is Checkmate wait till you look
into that and see
that I've been dying to talk to you guys
about
this and the whole peer pressure thing
you know when I was in that in the audio
and I was I was working with Spirit of
compassion on that and listening about
peer pressure and how demonic peer
pressure is that it's not just the term
demonic on how demons are involved in
peer pressure and how some of the most
terrible things happen with peer
pressure people's lives are altered and
changed forever or they're just dead
because of peer
pressure and demonic forces were
involved God this just unbelievable
I must admit there is so much fear about
what's going
on on the national
stage I wasn't looking forward to this
audio I felt like I couldn't handle more
scary things but truth owers so thank
you wow it's on IG
if we're not aware that demons are
possibly involved in matters that affect
our lives or involved with other people
who could be in our lives and how they
react and treat others or involved with
freak accidents and bad luck or involved
with peer pressure or involved with
mental health and addiction and suicide
do you think demons could be involved
there in any one of those
three you got to you got to hear this
audio you guys have to hear this audio a
bunch of you guys might not even know
that there's an audio you got to check
it out and you have to hear
it but at the same time um it's not for
the faint of heart and at the same
time just a little bit at a time I mean
a half an hour at a time take a break
take a little break as you go as you go
through
or involved with the disturbing news
stories we hear about serial killers
assault and violence so demons aren't
involved in
that or involved with the things going
wrong on a world scale there's a good
chance we're going to blame the wrong
thing now I want to just hit that for a
second there's a really good chance
we're going to blame the wrong thing if
we don't understand the spiritual grow
GD
and wait till you guys read about the
Grid or hear about the Grid in the audio
wait till you guys hear about
that Jess good to yeah finally the day
came good to see
you so the whole thing with the grid
wait till you get to that part is how
you know spiritual forces travel and how
that works that's mind-blowing all on
its own just that part part slavka says
thank you Anthony I just started
listening the audio it is
mindblowing it is a miracle God bless
you God bless you
too there's a good chance we're going to
blame the wrong thing if we don't
understand what's happening in that
spiritual realm spiritual grid if we
don't understand what's going on
there or even possibly blame ourselves
and that's a really important factor to
why it's critical to have this audio
it's so important this information is so
important you guys know I've been saying
this for years where we can't blame
ourselves that's how the system is set
up the darkness wants us to actually
blame ourselves the system is set up so
we can blame ourselves the health world
is
rigged so that we blame ourselves too
like we created it we created our
illness we created our problems right
that whole
thing then what happens is anything that
bad happens anything to like I
manifested like manifestation that's
that must be something I brought to
myself I created upon myself something
bad that happened right all of it that's
why it's critical to have this
information to protect yourself this
isn't just
about you know
Forefront unique
unbelievable information about the
spiritual realm which it is it isn't
just about that it's about how do we
protect ourselves like how do we protect
ourselves
this is something that is so important
to have in our
lives and believe me I'm not going to
get a medal for this and I'm not going
to get an award for
this because when you put out this
information when you put out this
information it's going to piss somebody
off out there is you put this kind of
Truth out there when you whistleblow on
demons and you whistle blow in darkness
and and that world the spiritual world
and the physical one here and you
whistleblow that stuff yeah no it's it's
it's really
intense there's a good chance we're
going to blame the wrong thing or even
possibly blame ourselves when crap
happens we could
even wants us to go into a deep dark
rabbit hole
how far have you guys gotten into this
audio I just want to ask you guys a
question like like how far have you guys
gotten into
it so I'm just I'm flipping around a
little
bit I wanted to just run by you guys
anyway if you just got on here it's out
Angels demons and spiritual tool s light
of Lights light of light life of light
says have family friends I know have a
family demon
alcoholism in all generations and nearly
every individual dot dot dot wondering
if their demon clung to me as well after
I became closer to them as an adult the
family derms and that's another point
the derms when you listen to this audio
you learn about the
derms the family tree derms you'll learn
about the
derms that's a big one all on its own
one of the first things you learn in
this audio is demon is a word that came
later it's not even the real word or the
real name of these
entities this just amazing information
Monica right there says I'm all in
binging okay just binging binging
warning binging warning Penny says it's
addictive it really is it is so I'm
going to talk about the addictive and
binging
warnings if you get through it really
fast you might get a log Jam up here CU
there's that much information because
it's it's it's information that's never
been exposed like there's hasn't no
one's been exposed to this information
it's all brand new it's from above so
that alone is really intense because
technically what happens is information
that's out there has been circulating
the spiritual world gets circulated
circul meaning
like
Spirit to that people doing this this is
so brand new it's going to be
intense and it's going to be it's going
to be a shocker
so you have to kind of like pace
yourself and then look if you get
through it go back start again start
fresh and start listening this isn't the
kind of audio where you listen to it
once and you're like okay that's it
because the tools are in there it's
critical information to understand you
want to become an expert you know how I
always say that with all the information
that comes from s so you want to become
your own expert yeah you do you want to
become an expert on this in the
spiritual world you want to be a
spiritual world expert with this
information and you're you're going to
know information nobody knows out there
you're going to be an expert at it over
time but you have to study it and you
have to learn it so you have to listen
to it again and again you have to get it
into your Consciousness to protect
yourself you have to get it in and learn
it so
important I'm two hours in I just saw
that that's
just almost done with part two
you're at fallen angels falling angels
whoa whoa that's intense only the first
chapter can't wait to
continue amazing I'm reading comments
you
guys yep just finished the first chapter
wow
wow yep 2 hours you're 2 hours in three
hours in whoa just an hour for you you
guys are cruising through it it's
intense are you guys taking
breaks lissy says Anthony I'm three
hours in trying to Pace but it's so
good well thank you thank you for like
pacing yourself CU that's important it
really is and I'm trying to tell
everybody it's really important I'm
saying this
because it it's addictive and you'll
keep on going right but but taking what
you've learned to kind
of digested
assimilated this information is just so
powerful now here's here's something
interesting right here okay so I'm not
here to convince anyone that demons
exist
you hear the information you learn it
you tell
me you can believe in demons or you
don't have to believe in demons at
all it's fine with
me demons would prefer you don't believe
in
them that's what they would prefer
because that's what works best for
demons so they can do more damage on
your life in your life more damage to
people you know more damage to people
around you cause more problems on a
world scale cause more problems in every
way possible you not believing in demons
that's that's great for demons it's
actually really good for demons that's
the whole point they would prefer you
don't believe in them they would rather
have the experiences in someone's life
that are not agreeable to be blamed on
people blamed on you blamed on people so
you're blaming a
person when both of you have been
duped by a
demon demons would
love if the experiences you have that
are not agreeable are blamed on people
happen stance blamed on happen stance
freak
accidents instead of anybody thinking
about the possibility that demons even
exist oh they don't exist they don't
exist demons don't exist don't even need
to think they exist exactly don't worry
they're not affecting you on any level
or your family members or anybody else
in your life throughout the years but
yet that's what they would love for you
to believe that's the thing is with this
information it's so powerful you become
empowered and
now you're learning how to conquer
Darkness it's just amazing
I Mark just a couple little notes in
here too you
know the information in this audio is
also not about
Superstition this is interesting there
is such a thing as Superstition there
is most people are
superstitious do you guys agree most
people are are you know
superstitious that said the information
we are exploring here is not
Superstition so when you go through this
audio and you listen to the seven and a
half hours it's not Superstition that's
not what this
is information from above when you hear
it and you connect if you guys just got
here check it out Angels demons and
spiritual tools it's out on Apple it's
an audible it's out on Apple it's an
audio it's on it's an audible on Amazon
you can get it there just type in
medical medium Angels demons and
spiritual
tools you can get it you know you can
get it off of
spotify and you may be already signed
into all these things just this is just
free then can listen to it free the
whole bit really really
incredible while listening to this audio
about demonic forces
don't get tangled up thinking that it's
about being
superstitious having to knock on wood
after you say something you're concerned
about is far different from the works
that demons and Fallen Angels do on this
planet so knocking on
wood is a lot different than what's
happening in the spiritual world the
Demonic forces the dark Forces the
Fallen Angels the falling angels and
what's happening and what they're doing
out there on a world scale too so you
can knock on W all you
want it's not going to tap into what's
going on around you or what's happening
out there this isn't sup
Superstition so I'm just just cutting
through a couple of little notes I had
there's so much information in the S and
1 half hours like I can't crack it all
like right here it's just impossible I
would have to be on here for probably
100 hours over time to crack into it to
talk ersay over there on IG says you
have answered so many questions aw wow
and that's the thing when you get into
this whole audio you're going to be like
oh my God like I can't believe how many
questions are being
answered it it's a dream come true
really just hearing it from from s so I
was like getting answers to questions
that I haven't even thought to ask it
was just coming together
Chi says over there at IG it's
validating a lot of
plus a lot of plus filling in gaps
whoa so I want to I want to um play for
you this Enlightenment
section just a little bit this this
little so I'm going to play this
realizes what the term Enlightenment
means
means enough goodness and
Consciousness and compassion when you're
alive that it lightens your
soul so I'm going to play this okay you
guys get it right here we're live by the
way no one realizes what the term
Enlightenment means it means enough
goodness
and
Consciousness and compassion when you're
alive that it lightens your soul so you
rise when you die so Enlightenment is
really a description of an elevating
Soul after you pass away a soul that
travels
upward the more enlightened that soul is
the more it gravitates upwards
the term Enlightenment really means the
soul is lightweight and not held down by
the gravity of Despair and darkness and
Despicable nature the gravity of
trickery and deceit of constant
betrayal Enlightenment means spring up
even if as a living person a soul
experience betrayals and battles with
darkness that could still rise up
when someone is not a good person their
soul bears that weight it's not
lightened it's holding toxic
baggage not the type of baggage of
what's happened to the soul the baggage
of what that Soul has
become true Enlightenment is compassion
and understanding someone's
suffering that makes the soul extremely
light
so it Springs upward
fast sometimes with the help of angels
possibly versus the soul being weighted
down and if the soul is not springing up
not enough Enlightenment is there it's
not being guided up on its
own so I wanted to play that for you
because that was one of my questions too
like what does Enlightenment even mean
and so powerful like the information
that came through and I I'll just read
it too I wanted you to hear it so you
know so that was on that's that is right
there the
audio Angels demons and spiritual tools
and you could find it like I said
audible on Amazon right now Spotify you
can get it off of Apple can find it
there but just get ready prepare
yourself maybe sit down maybe get some
lemon balm tea like I said said many
times in the past about anything that's
int tents get some lemon bomb tea that
would be really good fasten your seat
belts for
real definitely be sitting down when you
hear this for sure sitting
down no one realizes what the term
Enlightenment means because that's one
of the things that I got from SSC that
just just blew my mind it means enough
goodness and Consciousness and
compassion when you're alive when you're
alive
alive that it lightens your soul so you
rise when you
die that's that's Enlightenment it's not
the enlightenment that the spiritual
movement talks about now or you know
being enlightened enlightened in some
way having that Enlightenment it's
entirely different well Janna
says see laureli says who wrote the book
audio um Spirit of compassion's
information from above on the messenger
I took the information and compassion
when you're
alive Soul so you rise when you
die Enlightenment means having enough of
that compassion in your life time now so
that when you die it allows your soul to
spring up and Rise if your soul isn't
springing up and
Rising if it's not springing up and
Rising
say the enlightenment's not
there we're having like Tech problems
all kinds of funny stuff but I think
it's cleared
up and I want to say it again because
it's it's that
powerful so I saw somebody with a
question just now saying what do you
mean
so what's in the O what's in the audio
when you actually hear it okay and you
listen there's a part about
Enlightenment it's really powerful but
it's important because it plays a role
when we die when we leave this place I
know that young people think they'll be
here forever I get that I know young
people who feel like
indestructible and they just feel like
they'll probably be here forever you
know that that feeling you know when
you're 18 years old or 19 years old or
something but time goes by quick 100
years from
now we all leave 150 years from now
we're all leaving and when that time
happens Enlightenment is critical so
check this out I'll read this no one
realizes what the term Enlightenment
means it means enough goodness and
Consciousness and compassion when you're
alive that it like en your soul so you
rise when you
die so Enlightenment is really a
description of an elevating Soul after
you pass away a soul that travels upward
that's what enlightenment truly means
Spirit of compassion
says the more enlightened that soul
is your
soul the more it gravitates upwards so
you're not stuck here so you don't stay
here so the more Enlightenment the more
enlightened your soul
is the more it gravitates upwards so
you're not stuck
here the term Enlightenment really means
the soul is lightweight and not held
down by the gravity of Despair and
darkness and Despicable nature the gra
gra ity of trickery and deceit that
bears weight on the soul and keeps the
soul heavy and keeps the soul down so
after we die our soul is weighted down
with that deceit and that trickery it's
weighted down by that gravity of that
despair see guys I'm seeing someone said
you're saying the audio is cutting out
in YouTube go to rumble if it's cutting
out on YouTube so make sure you go to
you go to
rumble I'm I'm live on Rumble right
now Rosanna says demons are trying to
stop this information and this live I
feel them here wouldn't doubt it but
they didn't stop me from putting out the
audio and I worked hard on that and
spirit of compassion
did and and my publisher worked hard on
it too God blessed them and we got it
out and demons aren't going to like that
information out there indeed Fallen
Angels aren't going to like it dark
Forces aren't going to like it negative
energy negative entities aren't going to
like
it so the term Enlightenment really
means the soul is lightweight and not
held down by the gravity of Despair and
darkness and Despicable nature the
gravity of trickery and deceit of
constant betrayal Enlightenment means
spring up it means spring up even if as
a living person a soul experience
betrayals and battles within Darkness
they could still rise up that doesn't
stop them from rising up when someone is
not a good person that's different when
someone is not a good person just think
about that for a sec you're a good
person you're you're a good person but
when someone's not a good person their
soul bears that weight it's not
lightened so when somebody's a bad
person a terrible person cold-hearted
just a really bad person their soul is
going to bear that weight they're not
going to spring up it's holding toxic
baggage not the type of baggage of what
happens or what happened to the soul the
baggage of what that Soul has
become that's what it is true
Enlightenment is true Enlightenment is
compassion and understanding some
someone's
suffering that makes the soul extremely
light so it Springs upward fast with the
help of angels possibly versus a soul
being weighted
down that alone like takes time to
really understand and take that in I
know you guys get it you're but there's
a lot of people out there you're going
to have a hard time with that because
there're so intense there's so much
there in that piece of scripture alone
and the thing is about this information
from SSC when we dive into it I talk
about the medical books being scripture
like Health scripture and there's
spiritual scripture in there too this
right here is a whole another level of
scripture it's spiritual scripture for
sure it's from above it's answers to
questions that are mind-blowing
questions you may have had maybe your
whole life maybe questions you might
have had
recently but there's a lot to take in
here in the 7 and a half
hours I know someone asked like who
Who's the who did this you know audio
who did this me Anthony William I'm the
guy who did the audio it's information
from
above take a listen so many of you guys
can listen for free I'm pretty sure like
if you're signed in already to Spotify
or you know Amazon or apple and you can
listen to this for free I mean it
doesn't get any better than that how
incredible is that basically it's pretty
much for
free
so and Spotify is only available in
certain parts of the world so maybe you
don't get it in your part of the world
but maybe you get the other
options but
yeah but I would just go to audible on
on Amazon or go to Apple
so I want to I want you to hear this
other part too if you guys can for a
minute want to spend some time with you
guys so this this part is what is a
demon so these
traits are extremely self-centered
self-absorbed
selfish demons only care about
themselves and any Havoc they can wreak
to obtain self-satisfaction
demons have no compassion for others
they're anti-omp passionate no
compassion toward life itself not even
compassion toward animals no compassion
toward the sick or suffering no sympathy
no empathy no compassion they're
self-serving or fallen angel serving
only demons have these traits because
these were the traits they had when they
were
humans saw somebody say no sound I think
they were on YouTube go to
rumble you can't hear me say that I'm
sure but hopefully you try another
platform it's always fun to get schooled
by S
so all right so this this part here is
really
intense so if you guys if you want to
know I'm Anthony William this is Angels
demons and spiritual tools it's out now
you can look for it type in medical
medium Angel angels demons spiritual
tools you can do that on you know
audible Apple it's an original
audio um audible Amazon or apple or
Spotify okay what is a demon a demon is
what human soul becomes after death if
that Soul was completely engulfed by
certain traits when they were a living
person so what I got from Spirit of
compassion concrete just solidified
information when I just said what is a
demon and that information is
people people become
demons it's really sad it's disturbing
in a lot of ways
it's
terrible but humans become demons so
that's that piece of information that's
really interesting and they become
demons after death if their soul was
completely engulfed
and there you
go on YouTube Rumble you guys that's
what it looks like
I'm seeing questions and I'm like wait
till you guys wait till you guys hear
the audio I'm seeing certain questions
I'm like do you guys hear the
audio Yeah right then in their demon
form these traits stayed with them so
think about this okay so humans become
demons and then in their demon form
their human traits stayed with them in
the demon form these traits stay with
them demons are extremely
self-centered
self-absorbed that's interesting
self-centered self-absorbed selfish
demons only care about
themselves and any Havoc they can wreak
to obtain self-satisfaction so humans
who get self-satisfaction
and doing some bad things have the
potential to become demons when they
leave here but it's more than that
because it's there's more information
than that so when you hear that there's
nuances there's details you got to hear
the audio for it
all so demons only care about themselves
and any Havoc they can wreak to optain
self-satisfaction Demons have no
compassion for others no compassion
whatsoever they're anti-
compassionate no compassion toward life
itself not even compassion toward
animals it's important to know so when
humans were in their human form when
humans were here their soul was in their
physical human form here they had no
compassion for animals they became a
demon later after
death no compassion toward the sick or
suffering no sympathy no empathy no
compassion they're selfs
serving or Fallen Angel serving only so
that's another thing on its own so in
this audio you're going to hear about
fallen angels and falling angels too
there's two different things there's
falling angels and Fallen Angels they
are two different things and then
there's God's angels so that's important
to know and in this audio you're going
to learn about all three of
those but a human being
here a terrible Soul a terrible person
can die that way not grow not move
forward spiritually die become a demon
and I talk about the details on how that
happens it's really intense in the 7 and
1/ half hour audio they become a demon
and then they're either self-serving for
themselves as a demon like a rogue demon
or they are working for fallen angels I
talk about it in
detail demons have these traits because
these were the traits they had when they
were humans
a human soul is eligible to become a
demon after death if that Soul while in
a living breathing human was partaken
partaking in some disturbing and
uncompassionate practices and enjoyed
the harm or suffering within those
practices did you guys hear that right
now you're learning how a demon becomes
a demon you're also you're learning what
a demon is right now from Spirit of
compassion's information that's how
mind-blowing this is
a human soul is eligible to become a
demon after death if that Soul while in
a living breathing human was partaking
in some disturbing and uncompassionate
practices and enjoy the harm or
suffering within those
practices that's just like a tiny bit of
information compared to what's in
this audible on Amazon or audio you find
it on
Spotify it blows my mind it does so I
just wanted to give you guys a little
bit of what's happening with the release
of this I was up early this morning I
couldn't
sleep primarily because I was partially
worried cuz when you guys get this
information now understand this this
information is really intense so when it
gets in there and it gets in to your
Consciousness you start becoming
empowered but you start seeing
things you start seeing
things that sometimes we don't see and
we're being affected by but we don't
realize it I mean this is powerful
information there's Tools in here too
wait till you get to the tools how to
protect yourself say at all all that
silly stuff of micro doing but this is
something to micro do little pits at a
time small dosages
of this
information so anyway check it out when
you get a
chance carine says hi Anthony I just
started
listening thank you thank you for
shedding the light and
Truth Lisa says says this thing is
seriously
amazing sa H says I'm so empowered just
learning about the Checkmate wait till
you get to that part right
there I'm really really happy you guys
have this Sharon says oh yeah it's
packed I'll have to listen lots of times
every line is
packed every line is a lot of
information every paragraph is a lot of
information it's just really intense you
guys I'm going to say it over and over
again and it's warranted it really is me
saying it over and over again is
warranted it truly is chrisy Moore says
so much more going on than we could ever
know OMG explanation
points MMA music says I can't stop but I
have to listen
again lra
144 I listen the first 30 minutes so
mind-blowing I am so grateful for this
information I saw you at the Cafe
Gratitude event thanks for
coming Jen saying listening to it now
over there on
YouTube Jeremy k k says this is such a
great great audio
book Christina says I got to the first
tool to disempower
Demons I keep saying to myself I will
take a break but then go straight back
to it I love it it's amazing information
thank you thank you thank
you some over there on
IG incredible you guys
Alex says Anthony I broke down today
thank you for your sacrifice and
providing this sacred information you
helped me get out of a dark place and
these audios brought more
clarity
wow it's
powerful see guys when you get a
chance Sheila says incredible how we get
to know the truth no more guessing games
about the spiritual world did you
get so the The Ether The Ether grid the
information based on that wait till you
guys get to that part
seriously and you know what
too if when you tell somebody else Hey
look check this out listen to this give
them if you can can you can you do that
too can you give them the thing where
just a little bit at a time okay can you
tell them like half hour at a time
digest it simulate
it try not to binge all the way through
if you do go back start again and just
do a little at a time the information is
that
that powerful unique
Forefront it's of the light it's
mind-blowing the tools are there to help
protect people it's just an incredible
thing well all right you
guys I'm going to
go
and take one hour at a
time one half hour at a
time I see no I saw a couple of people
binged it the grid is mind-blowing Anna
it it really is truly
mebe 787 mebe I saw you can't decide to
keep listening or relisten to previous
part that's true too like you can listen
you can listen to a previous part
seaweed hero good to see you on
here Amanda says this audio makes me
want to be a good person even more even
more so now because I don't want to
become a demon
when you listen to the when you listen
to this information right you'll see all
the details in there and all the
nuances this
information will definitely better any
Souls
listening in so many ways because it'll
Empower you it'll give you
strength it'll answer questions it'll
protect you this information so
important and and you can you know when
you look into this and you listen and
you'll see how many times do you see
people do this or that and you're like
whoa now I know what happened it's it's
that powerful that
powerful the most
original so Paula over on N says the
most original Cutting Edge mindblowing
audio it is cutting edge
and it is original and I'm honored you
you feel that way and and see that truly
I'm honored I really
am over there um Blue Jay I'm going to
work much harder on enlightenment now
that I know what it is and that's the
thing like people say the word but they
don't know what it is and asking Spirit
of compassion what enlightenment means
and getting that information and that
answer alone is just so incredible
really when I think about it I was blown
off my seat with that
information like having that information
everybody says Enlightenment
Enlightenment what are they talking
about somebody doing yoga on a rock
somewhere out in the you know Wilderness
or out in the desert and they're
enlightened it's like it's like when you
ask the question and you learn what
enlightenment really means then you're
just like oh my God and then it's a
about it's about somebody being a good
person but why because that compassion
and everything else right it's and you
guys have I mean the most compassion out
there this book has helped me have more
compassion for
humans whoa it's
incredible Leila over there this audio
is
premium Soul information whoa that's a
compliment
so
hears see Lindy over there I can now
protect myself better in this
world I've been so naive this
information protects people it does
having this information helps especially
if there's a sense of being naive in
some way because of the way this world
is and so forth it's nobody's fault it
just happens but then when you learn
about out what's happening out there
then you're like oh my God I'm empowered
I know this information
now you guys if you just got on here so
I saw a bunch more people come on
um check it out medical medium Angels
demons and spiritual tools this is it
right
here see if you guys can see
this Reena
this was the most profound and
mind-blowing spiritual information I
ever heard thank you so much for sharing
aw thank you for being here thank you
for
listening you
guys truly
honored
nine I'm so grateful for this audiobook
just downloaded it thank you so much
amazing
Wonder Woman Enlightenment please hit
the like button for aw yeah I I very
rarely ask you just helped me ask hit
the like button and remember what I
always say you don't like the show Hit
It
Anyway Shar McDonald says can't wait to
listen to the audio
I'm excited about you listening I really
am
truly BV aaro it's always great to get
the truth even if it
hurts Karen Churchill will there be a
spiritual
book will there be a spiritual book
number
two that's your question
[Music]
Kathy Lewis where do I get the
ebook I'll show you right here what it
looks
like audible Amazon you can get it
there Spotify you can get it
there Apple you can get it
there incredible okay guys
I'm going to sign
off I can't wait for you guys to
listen you know get
a a portion of it at a
time and just let
it
process like Let It
process I've already heard an hour and
it's amazing powerful
information whoa over there on IG
da okay you guys love you
much I'm really happy about this I'm
happy about you getting the information
to protect yourselves and that's the
whole point so take a listen listen to
those spiritual
tools thank and over there in IG see
Nemo says thank you so much aw truly
appreciate you and the fact that you
always
paint a Target on your back for us God
bless
uh yeah more so than people
know all right I love you guys be good