you guys we were on amazon live earlier
incredible show because i had i had the
best time all right powerful show about
emergency food
tips
food
shortage tips really good ideas and
everything was really cool it doesn't
mean there's a food shortage that's not
what it is it's like emergencies right
blizzard storm power goes out
anything like that right
you know and hurricane or
you know the grid goes out or solar
flare or whatever and all of a sudden
everything's all messed up for a while
or you just got the flu
or you don't feel good and you can't get
to the store for a while so it's really
cool the show was really fun check it
out right link is in the description
link is on the on on the bio right there
up tik tok and it's the amazon live show
i did today you got to check it out
if you get a chance it was really fun
and i only did half of it because we had
a tech glitch because we had so many
people pouring on we crashed the system
so we crashed amazon system so that we
just had so many people pouring on it it
was getting crazy and then just for some
reason their system got overloaded and
it all went down
so there's gonna be another round of it
a part two or another round of it so i'm
gonna do that i just want to let
everybody know that was part one and it
was fun as heck and i was
about to make the scrambled eggs
and i didn't get a chance to make the
scrambled eggs man so don't worry we're
gonna get to that i gotta show you the
scrambled eggs
because i think you're gonna like it dr
fonz says the scrambled egg recipe i
think you're gonna like that scrambled
egg recipe
so and i had like three or four more
recipes i was making for you guys but
listen you should check it out because i
already i made pasta i did a whole bunch
of stuff i want you to get a chance you
know when you get a chance check out my
amazon live medical medium cooking show
on amazon live where i have the medical
medium cooking show and i did the food
emergency food storage
tips which is really cool and
because you know the food storage food
shortage because everybody should have
something in their pantry they should
have a little something even if it's a
little something right there and there's
some cool stuff i was showing everybody
that i have in my pantry and i have them
there for a reason
so anyway i wanted to show you guys and
and have you take a look at that but
today we're talking about
fear of being sick you know one thing i
hear all the time
is you're pretending to be sick
so you're pretending
to be sick
are you really sick
are you guys really sick is it really
that bad do you guys have that many
different issues is it real do you
really have anxiety
do you really have depression
are you just pretending are you really
that sick right i mean how many times
have you guys heard that at all out
there where it's really just you know
you're pretending to be sick you have a
fear of healing
anything like that
so heidi m says you were just starting
to talk about foods for pets when you
were cut off exactly and i was going to
go into it too it's going to be really
fun i know you guys when you get a
chance check out the amazon live medical
medium cooking show when you get a
chance and it was so great talking about
emergency food storage food you know
tips
for uh food shortage and all of that the
link is in the bio link is in
description
how many how many times have you guys
heard that out there because i i've
heard that out there for years people
got a fear of healing
so maybe you just have a fear of healing
maybe you're afraid to heal right
did you ever hear that one
or
maybe you're creating it like are you
creating your sickness are you creating
it with your mind
is that what you're doing is that why
your life kind of stopped and just
crashed
is that why you know you couldn't feel
good anymore and you all the fatigue you
had kristin wallace says i was blamed to
be pretending to be sick for so long
oh my god have cancer you've saved my
life
i'm so glad you're here kristin so glad
you're here and and i know so many
people are blamed that they've been
pretending to be sick for so many years
is it our mind
is that why you're sick
did you make it happen
did you create it
you know i mean that's still happening
big time right now
you know before anybody even knew about
viruses and stuff like that and all that
and everything medical medium talks
about of why people sick people people
are suffering why they're sick
it was really heavy duty everybody
always says you're sick and we don't
know why you're creating it
you must be the reason why you're sick
it's you it's your fault you can't keep
it together because look at that other
person
you know look at that other person and
how strong they are check out that
athlete that athlete's unbelievable they
can surf
they can do they can go anywhere they
can do anything
they can hike up mountains they could do
anything they want they can ski
right
they can play ball they can do
everything right look at that athlete
that athlete's overcoming everything
and what why can't you
how come you can't overcome something
why are you really are you really sick
come on right you can't do that or what
sure you're not an athlete you're not
this you're not this big athlete but why
are you sick
and then you know the world set up
to make it look like
a
athlete has like this willpower
that trump's yours
you're sick you're weak
you got chronic fatigue syndrome you got
lupus you got ra
you got severe eczema you've got tingles
and numbness on your body
you don't feel good you have migraines
and
maybe you're just you're just kind of
maybe maybe that's just i don't know
because yeah the athletes man they got
this little power they overcome
you just got overcome you know i can't
tell you how many times i've heard this
throughout the years
is i've heard trainers say to their
people who actually got sick you gotta
overcome it you gotta push through come
on push through keep on going you gotta
do it
wild lovely one says my older son
thought i was just being lazy
lazy
crazy
right
weak
making it up pretending lying
lying is another one right there that's
a big one all on its own people have
been told all those things and i'm so
sorry you were told that just breaks my
heart it really does but i've seen
trainers like push through
you can do it
you got the strength
what do you mean you're fatigued and now
you're having a panic attack
what do you mean you you can't function
oh i don't i can't deal with i can't
deal with you you're mentally you don't
have the mental strength
trainers have done that for years they
don't know because unless someone's in
your shoes
unless someone's in your shoes would
they really know laura says mind over
matter yeah mind over matter it
why don't you just mind over matter and
stacy says stacy berg says amazon live
today was amazing i can't wait to part
two wasn't that insane then amazon live
you guys you should follow me on amazon
live it's the medical medium cooking
show when you get a chance you won't be
disappointed and go to medicalmedium.com
after that and sign up to my newsletter
so you won't know when my part two of my
amazon live is coming right
so yeah this is so important right
lee says the omega juicer is incredibly
wonderful to use what a great job it
does like the ferrari of juicers
i said it was and it is meaning i said
it was incredible it's my favorite i
love it and i'm so glad you're actually
using it and you're happy so what does
it mean when we get told you guys that
we're the reason you mind over matter it
right
you get somebody who's not sick
they're not sick
cop says yeah my own husband says it's
because i don't work out
what happens is i've seen this i've seen
a spouse
right you guys a spouse that doesn't
have chronic fatigue syndrome or any
other condition or autoimmune that's
that's debilitating in some way like
keeping them down right and then so
they're able to work out and they're on
the elliptical and they're on the
peloton
and they're spinning and they're
whatever they're doing and they're
looking at you and they'll be like hey
honey
why don't you just why don't you try to
do this
what do you mean you're sick what does
the doctor say
oh you should go to the doctor then
hasn't the doctor fixed you
no well the doctor says he doesn't
really know what's wrong with you or he
does or what why don't you just get
working out that'll fix it it'll take
care of everything
that happens all the time
all the time lemon balm love danielle
says you just want the attention that's
another one i've heard over and over
again
i know michelle l says try harder
and
exactly you just want attention you're
an attention seeker how about that one
you're a whiner
how about that one okay how about that
one guanalupe says i love the juicer too
you know and that's the thing that's the
challenge right and that that you know
that takes the person who's suffering
and struggling it takes them spiritually
so much further though than anybody else
because you spiritually grow because not
only are you struggling with what you're
up against
physically
right
what you're up against you're also
struggling with all this you get
you're struggling with all the crap you
get i mean what the heck
it's unbelievable how much crap we get
right
eileen says doctors don't believe you
either and that's a whole nother level
of it all doctors don't believe
anyone either when they're struggling
and suffering and you can't identify it
like you can't like you can't see it
but the new age is taking it to a new
level because you've created it
i want to be sick i want to be bedridden
i want to be on mattress island i'm
creating it i must be using my thoughts
to take myself down that's one part of
the new age that you know focuses on
that you see it everywhere out there
lacey says my counselor said to fake it
till i make it
you know i think
and it's not funny but that's actually
that's actually a good one because i
don't think i've heard that one
i don't
ken says i was down but i'm better than
ever after doing celery juice thank god
thank god you're doing so thank god you
found the celery juice
thank god you're doing you're doing that
thank god you're taking care of yourself
right
and you found the information
okay
you know michelle elliot says yes i get
lots i get tons of attention in my bed
laugh out loud alone
exactly and that's another angle people
who are struggling with chronic illness
people with that are struggling
with chronic illness
they don't get the attention everybody
thinks they get
even the young people i can't tell you
how many moms and dads i've talked to
over the years because doctors would be
like look um the parents they have sick
kids i need advice so i talk to the
doctor and say here here here's you know
this is this is what what i think can
help you to help your patients and
and it would be the same thing over and
over again where even young people
it gets kind of canceled out because
it's like is it the boy who cried wolf
is that what it is is this the boy who
cried wolf
and they start getting numb to it so
everybody around everybody gets numb to
it
young adults the same thing it's like
the parents if they're lucky enough to
have you know parents that are
supportive and all that right then all
of a sudden it's like um
yeah we don't know what's wrong with you
you've been to a lot of doctors already
you say you have this anxiety condition
you say you have fatigue but is it
really what it is honey like is it
really what it is
and everybody gets doubted it so the
chronic illness thing game is like
everybody gets down and alicia says
women always told they're faking it for
centuries now
just get called crazy
alicia yeah crazy lazy you're making it
up you're creating it so one of the
hardest parts i have with this
is first of all i know you're not faking
it i know you're not making it up i know
you're not creating it
i know you're not creating it
it's not like you're sitting there
creating it like i'm working on creating
this right here i'm gonna make sure that
i get really sick there's no question
i'm going to make sure i get really sick
that's what i'm going to do and you know
you're not creating it that's not it at
all
and it's critical to know this this is
an important live use to talk about this
you know m von doom says i've come to
value the people who believe my symptoms
so much
yeah
it's important it's important you have
somebody that believes what's going on
yup each other what the heck
you heard it out of the horse's mouth
tonight
what the heck
okay
it's just fun
but look the bottom line is you guys
you're not making it up
you don't have a fear of healing
i know
you don't
have a fear of healing andrea says we
prefer attention more than our health
yeah right like that's that's what you
want exactly you prefer just getting
attention been being forced to lay in
bed because your condition's keeping you
on the couch it's keeping you in bed
you're on a mattress couch island you
can't function good you can't get into a
car you're struggling you're suffering
you'd prefer attention better than than
just being stuck right not being able to
live the life to where you want to live
it right now at your fullest optimum
possibilities
deborah says or your family is just
pretending you're fine and they
completely ignore you
and you are isolated alone that's a big
one i've seen that too i've seen that
for so many times over the years i do
i think
what happens is the reason why medical
medium has always talked about this and
this information medical medium and
spirit of compassion has always told me
to be wise about this like understand it
and
and understand what people are going
through right and i i think that i've
always done that i've gotten a lot of
crap for it though for a lot of reasons
cara says then you get the medical gas
lighting the medical gas lighting is a
whole other angle so think about that
think about how many obstacles you get
when you're a sick person right when
you're somebody suffering with a mystery
illness or a chronic illness just think
about how many obstacles it's like land
mines you're like okay you're cruising
along here and now here you go you're
trying you're you're struggling to fight
for it you're fighting for your life and
then boom the doctor gaslights you and
tells you okay this and this and they go
see a psychiatrist and you're fighting
for your life you're fighting for your
life and now your husband or or somebody
else says yeah you are crazy you do need
to you do need a psychiatrist try that
try these pills and all of a sudden you
get a dangerous reaction from the pills
and now you're fighting for it and
you're cruising along and now you get
sick now you got the autoimmunes getting
worse no one understands and all of a
sudden your other family members or
friends are like i can't hear your
symptoms anymore i don't want to hear
about it i don't want anything to do
with any of it now you're fighting for
that and now it's just one obstacle at
another and it just keeps on going
and it keeps on going and then the
invisible illness part is so hard
it's so hard when it's an invisible
illness
neil rimmer says
the worst part is you still have to work
you still have to get up every day and
try and push through oh my god
you have to try to juice you got to try
to feed yourself you got to try to get
what you need you got to try to get the
water you need you got to try to keep
yourself away from any kind of exposures
that are really toxic you got to try to
work you got to try to take care of your
family you got to try to you know still
counsel your friends and be there you
have to try to do all these things and
fight through and fight through and
fight through
you guys are my heroes
you need to know that
like when i think about it all when i
really think about it and i think about
what you guys have gone through and i
think about it all
man you guys are my heroes
for real
people who are not experiencing chronic
illness they don't know what it's like
to be in anybody's shoes they just don't
nicole says i'm grateful for this
message to support the chronicle i've
dealt with it all my life family
partners doctors it's in your head quote
you have to push through it you're
looking for attention you're a hyper
contract quote
i totally understand i do
this has been a big part of my journey
and why i actually try to help people
with a chronic allele and have all these
mystery symptoms
michelle says i've had to stop talking
to people jessica said i had cancer and
the doctor laughed at me and said i just
have gas
she was so disrespectful the third
doctor found it and that makes it even
harder it's just unbelievable how that
works
yeah
ruby asked a question but you can
rewatch live on amazon yes you can
re-watch it on scroll down when you get
there and scroll down you'll see the
live i just did it today i think that's
how you do go to go to medical meeting
cooking show on amazon live
right or to check out the link the links
in the bio that's how you go directly
there i gotta make sure i give you the
right information so you get there
okay
the mercy seat says as men were always
told
quote be a man
but it's hard to be feel like a man
at one third strength of your health
yeah be a man
fight for it are you weak come on
alexandra sophia i never felt understood
why i'll be anybody until medical media
books info so you just weren't
understood
i understand i mean so many people are
not understood so this is something that
really gets to my core it really does
because this takes this is like the salt
in the wound this is like kicking sand
in somebody's eyes when they're down on
the ground that's what this is and the
system set up to do this and the system
trains
everybody around us
to really make this more of a sore point
andrea lee says appreciate the
conversation invisible disability it's a
big problem i appreciate you being here
andrea it's i'm so happy you're here it
means the world to me that you guys are
here tonight i know this isn't a topic
that hits everybody's core but it hits
mine and i know it's hitting you
you guys
and i know you guys feel it because you
guys are dealing with it tara appleman
good to see you here um tonight
incredible
cara i i did the western way and i want
it to die
it made me so much sicker lost 18
kilograms
my hair was falling out
now i'm on medical medium protocol and
slowly improving baby steps
incredible incredible you just you just
get the baby steps count you guys which
i want to talk about for a minute too
i really do if anybody just got on now i
what i mentioned earlier is check out
the amazon live
i did today the link is in the bio link
is in the description you won't be
disappointed it was really fun i was
making recipes on the medical mean
cooking show
and follow me on there too so you can
know when i'm doing the next one and it
was about survival food because what if
a storm comes what if something happens
what if it's a solar flare moment and
everybody's grid goes out for a little
bit a couple days what if something
happens what if you're not feeling well
or you get the flu and you feel like you
can't get to the store i always keep a
bunch of things in my pantry just just a
whole bunch of cool things so i can be
like hey i could make this and not have
to go out i could survive on this for a
good week you know i can and it's really
cool to do that and it's really a great
show honestly it was probably the
funnest the funnest show if funnest is a
word the funnest show i've done
you know in a long time that's that's
what i felt you guys i hope you you
check it out
so
and it's it's foods that don't have the
msg it's foods that don't have
preservatives it's foods that are safe
it's foods that don't have natural
flavors it's foods that don't have
citric acid it's foods that don't have
gluten it's foods that don't have all
those things it's really cool it's like
survival food packs to go on the road
too like when you're traveling you can
do so much with it like it's so cool it
really is
so
what the heck frederick says
kathleen singer i deeply appreciate your
guidance when purchasing supplements
there are so many crappy products out
there thanks for all you do i'm making
progress for the first time in four
decades kathleen you're probably using
the vimergy which is the incredible
stuff that i always talk about that i
use and always show and everything the
vimergy supplements nothing beats them i
haven't found anybody that has beat them
yet with quality so yeah and it makes a
difference to heal it truly does
we're told we have a fear of healing
that's what we're told you guys
well
when a dog gets sick
does a dog have a fear of healing that's
what i want to know
anybody have a dog that was ill yeah
do dogs end up having to go to the vet
yeah
are dogs creating it with their thoughts
because i want to know i was scratching
my head the other day
when i heard
somebody i know that i haven't talked to
in years that reached out
and said
that somebody told them they were
creating their sickness
right
in the same conversation they told me
they took their dog to the vet the other
day because their dog was sick
so i said
did they tell your dog that your dog's
creating his illness too
that's what i asked
and the person was like what
what do you mean
i said
did the dog create
the sickness or was the dog lazy
was the dog a liar
was the dog lying
was the dog making it up
was a dog
trying to get attention so the dog was
faking being sick
was the dog creating it with the dog's
thoughts
so he said he said poopoo would never do
that
that's what he said
poopoo would never do that pupu wouldn't
create that
pupu would never make that up
poopoo would never do any of those
things
that's what he said
i said well so what about you
i wouldn't i'm not either
i'm not either
it's kind of insane right
it's insane
what i've noticed here on planet earth
is the most craziest crap can happen
and we just have to live in it
the most unsensible stuff can happen
that makes no sense at all there's all
these spiritualists now most spiritual
people
just go to a yoga class i get nothing
against yoga i tell people to do yoga
all the time i'm like you love it go do
it but just go to a yoga class
and someone will say oh you must be it's
it's you're just you're not wired right
you have to master your thoughts you're
sick
you're sick because you you can't you
you're you're not doing something right
in here you need to go see this person
you need to go look up this website you
need to go watch this documentary you
need to go and do this
and what happens is
you hear that all the time out there
it's like it's it's constant it's like
but no one realizes
no one realizes
you know
like exactly
does your cat
create it with your cat's thoughts does
your dog create it with your dog's
thoughts
does a four-year-old
create being really sick
no a four-year-old an eight-year-old a
ten-year-old wants to be playing
wants to be living their life doesn't
want to be suffering from any kind of
condition and either does any adult
nobody ever wants to be sick or down in
out
nobody wants a cold
even though there aren't no colds
anymore and i said that to you guys many
times
the flu is the only thing that was out
until the recent plague
right and the recent plague brought
about brought about the flu family a flu
family
line right but the point is is there was
there aren't no colds anymore but do you
want a cold i've seen people say you
just wanted this cold right now you
needed some down time to do some healing
so your body took on the cold purposely
your body took on the flu purposely
that's just what you need it you need it
to be down for three weeks with the flu
and go through that that's what you
needed you know you're you're and that's
a whole nother thing i've heard too you
so true kara said so true
right have you guys heard that too pk
good to see you i loved your interview
on the unity health congress
they got so mad and passive aggressive
when you did them no
no one manifests their illness left out
loud laugh out loud
i don't think that makes anybody happy i
i totally understand they don't like
that every time i've said that nobody
manifests their illness
i've gotten so much flack i've gotten a
lot of hate too
because what happens is is just
you you're not allowed to
be in the world of truth when it comes
down to mind body physical emotional
health all of it you're not allowed to
do you have to you have to do whatever
they're there they're doing out there
you have to
if if they're telling you to drink apple
cider vinegar you better dry i better be
promoting it i better be like oh yeah
apple cider vinegar is good i don't want
to go against all those podcast doctors
and everybody else
um who are selling it yeah no apple
cider vinegar is great um yeah green tea
is great you should be doing your green
tea it doesn't matter if it's a
psychoactive drug and it's going to make
you sicker somebody with chronic illness
oh do your green tea because i don't
want to step on any toes um oh yeah of
course you're manifesting your illness
yeah you're sick on the couch you
haven't been able to work or function in
two years that's because you're just all
effed up in the head
and you created it with your thoughts
you need to be rewired um
yeah because i have to play that game
because if i don't everybody's going to
just come after me and i'm never going
to survive in the health field you know
like i'm never going to make it in the
health field
i've made it this far
i haven't made a lot of friends i made a
lot of friends
that love the truth
but also
not made a lot of friends because you
know you're supposed to
be really really submissive
right you're supposed to do whatever
everybody else is doing like yeah
telomeres are the reason why everybody's
sick um yeah you need lots of meat to
stop you from aging um
yeah uh
you know
look they'll tell you you just need to
work on yourself that's another thing
too
they'll tell you you need to work on
yourself meanwhile to contradict
themselves
and say that they're perfect you're
perfect how you are well that's my
favorite one
here's my favorite one
you need to work on yourself you got
you're you're creating it you're causing
it
you're causing your sickness you need to
work on on bettering yourself but no
you're perfect how you are
everybody's perfect who they are see the
game how about that gaslighting
psycho cult game
that's a really that's a really good one
barbara says barbara milano says what
about scrambled eggs i was going to make
the scrambled eggs on amazon live and
then we had a tech problem there to so
many people coming on the whole system
crashed over there at amazon and we were
crashed out of here
and i was going to make some killer
scrambled eggs that would have knocked
your socks off and i'm gonna do a round
two so i hope you guys sign up to my
newsletter barbara please sign up to the
medical medium newsletter go to
medicalmedium.com or the link is here in
the description right there or in the
bio sign up to my newsletter so you guys
know where i am
one of my favorites
in this whole you're creating it with
your thoughts
just so you know
maria says and the condescending tone
people talk i hate it completely
the most incredible pieces of of just
trickery is
you're creating it and manifesting it
you're the one you're you're the reason
why you're sick emotionally mental
physical all of it it's because of you
you can't master your your thoughts
you're creating it you're weak you have
to rewire you have to learn all the
spiritual tricks to try to you know to
get to superseats overpower everything
empower yourself and correct yourself
right
to say it's all you and you're screwing
up but then they'll say at the same time
you're perfect everybody's perfect
how you are you're perfect who you are
don't change anything
love yourself you just need to love
yourself you're perfect
but at the same time you'll flip it in
the same sentence but you're screwed up
so you better work on it
and that's what they do
lorraine l good to see you i apparently
made poor life choices
is what somebody told me
right
they'll either tell you that lorraine or
tell you that you had your head chopped
off in 1587
in france
they'll tell you that too
you know and that it's karma so let's go
into the karma thing i think it's time
we hit there i know a lot of you guys
believe in karma
i know you do
okay i'm not saying i believe in it i'm
not saying i don't believe in it that's
not what i'm doing here okay what i am
telling you though all right
is your suffering
usually gets blamed
this is here's one right here
on karma
you did so bad in your last lifetime
you deserve your ass picked
seven ways to sunday in this lifetime
okay you gotta watch out for that one
don't get pulled into that one whatever
you do all right that 100
i don't believe in if you believe in it
i respect you
we don't judge here spirit and
compassion and i we we don't shame you
we don't judge you if you believe your
suffering
is because you screwed up really bad a
lifetime ago or two lifetime agos
right and that's why you suffer and you
have severe acne debilitating eczema
psoriasis
ra chronic fatigue syndrome lupus
multiple sclerosis als neurological lyme
wilson's parkinson's or whatever else
they can give a name to right
okay
and you believe you have all those very
things because you screwed up bad in a
past life or you screwed up bad in two
lifetimes ago and you deserve
to have your
butt kicked
that is definitely not accurate i can
promise you that it's definitely not
accurate you can say hey anthony you got
your opinion i got mine i believe i
deserve this karma i believe i have this
karma and that's why i'm suffering aw i
get it you have your opinion we don't
always have to listen to aw you know of
course not you don't have to listen to
me on any level but i can promise you
this it isn't because of something bad
you did in a past life or two lifetimes
ago that's not why you're suffering
the reason why
the industries love when people
scramble for answers and pick on
themselves i have a fear of healing it's
my fault i created it it hides what's
really making everybody sick
it hides
the caffeine addictions which just
slowly just ages people and tears them
down it hides right it hides that it
hides
the injuries from the pharmaceuticals
it hides that it hides the toxic heavy
metals
it hides the chemical warfare placed
upon us every single day it hides the
radiation exposure upon us when we go
through the airports
people you know how people are worried
about cat scans they're like whoa it's a
lot of radiation it is a lot of
radiation but if your doctor tells you
have to get a cat skin of course go get
a cat scan but you know people are
really worried about cat scans being a
lot of radiation right this is a good
thing to talk about right now
you get a cat scan when you go through
that airport
we get a cat scan
you get 400 chest x-rays when you walk
through that airport all you got to be
doing
is walking past that baggage going in
right there
going in that radiation machine that
unregulated insane amounts of radiation
streaming out of that thing and then
you're taking your baggage and the
things glowing in the dark
and then you put your clothes on after
you that were in that baggage and you
put them on and you put basically a
radiation blanket all over your whole
body you're getting by the time you're
done with that whole trip you just had a
cat scan or two
there's all these other reasons why
everybody's sick
and it gets blamed on you
i love you guys i'm gonna go to
instagram we'll see what we're gonna
talk about there i might talk about this
i might talk about something else go
into instagram i'm gonna turn tick tock
back on i'm gonna turn telegram back on
just know that
i care and i know that you guys have
suffered and struggled and you've been
through a lot and this is just the tip
of the iceberg
and i know it i know i didn't cover
enough i know there's a lot more to be
said
and i know you guys have suffered a lot
more than anybody does alicia underwood
says the same people who tell you you've
manifested your symptoms or the same
ones who try to sell you they're bad
supplements too and
yeah amen
so true
anyway you guys
i believe in you guys stand behind you
and with you god bless you and i'm going
to go to ig
and shoot my mouth off
just kidding
i'll behave i love you guys