doing the heavy metal detox cleanse
challenge it's going to be a two day
challenge it starts tomorrow this is the
preliminary
right here this is it this is the
pre-cleanse it's about getting
everything ready getting the things we
need
and you might be saying
why do i have to do the heavy metal
detox cleanse what's the point of
joining in what's the point of having
fun
with all of us
i don't need it i don't need to get any
what
what are you talking about metals metals
where
metal is that aware
but what no one really realizes ticks
spasms ocd tremors anxiety depression
heart palpitations vagus nerve issues
phrenic nerve issues
all kinds of stuff like
personality disorders
depersonalization
bipolar
all of this metals metals metals and
i'm telling you it's getting crazy out
there people have so many different
problems right now and
when you get the metals out when you
start getting the medals out
life changes and it starts to change
fast you got to get the medals out it's
critical really critical
so many people don't realize
how many metals they have in their brain
stem how this interferes with their
vagus nerves how this interferes with
their trigeminal nerves facial nerves
i mean the whole bit how it interferes
with all of it so
this is an important time right here
this is the preliminary this is getting
ready for the heavy metal detox cleanse
do you have your book
critical to have you have it go to the
library get it for free or amazon.com us
51 off 16.99
the heavy metal detox cleanse is in this
book
more than that's in this book right but
the heavy me mm school time mm school
time
rose the the
metal cleanse is in here
so important
right there michelle l brainstem exactly
people don't realize that they got
metals in their brain stem that's what
they have they got the metals in their
brain stem
and they don't know it and they have the
metals inside their brain you got
anxiety you can't explain boom metals
you got depression you can't explain
boom metal see personalization
eating disorders
are you throwing up eating your food
throwing it up eating your food throwing
it up right bulimia anorexia
metals
metals everywhere mystery nausea because
you don't know it's the vegas nerves
nettles if you guys just came on here
and tick-tock
i'm just letting you guys know
heavy metal detox cleanse is coming up
we're getting ready for it you have to
have cleanse the heel go to library get
it for free if you need to or just be
there just be there it's free it's free
it's free it's free it's free it's
unbelievable you got to think about that
and i'm going to be sharing so much
information of why we're sick ticks
spasms tremors right
all of it so it's an important time to
to get into this cleanse we're going to
get ready for it what do we need you
guys got to hang around because i'm
going to show you what you need i'm
going to show you
what you need
to do this cleanse
you got your cilantro here you got your
wild blueberries here you got your
lemons here you got your oranges here
all of it is important to know got to
have the book right
it's cleanse the heel 51 off at
amazon.com us
amazon.com us 51 percent off it's 16
okay doreen connor says the heavy metal
detox cleanse has given me my life back
you guys doreen's saying it has helped
her
and it can help others too so many
people are getting help from this
cleanse we're doing it tomorrow's day
one of the cleanse
[Music]
sue says i've been committed to this
smoothie for a year now heavy metal
detox cleanse right there right on
youtube
been committed to this movie for a year
and no longer rely on any medication for
my bipolar and anxiety symptoms
god bless you aw
that's incredible
dr sherry
dr sherry green
good to see you so
tomorrow starts
the heavy metal detox cleanse this is
the preliminary day this is about
getting prepared understanding why
you're getting the metals out we're
gonna cover that
you're gonna talk about why you're
getting the metals out of your brain and
brain stem anxiety depression bipolar
schizophrenia
depersonalization eating disorders
bulimia anorexia mystery nausea heart
palpitations tremors ticks spasms
do i need to say more
eczema psoriasis vitiligo
the old friend reached out to me and
said look i'm ready to finally get rid
of my vitiligo
ready to finally what do i need to do aw
what do i need to do i said the heavy
metal detox cleanse you have to get the
aluminum out of your body
that's how you get rid of your vitiligo
it's like aluminum what do you mean
aluminum aluminum
how many fluoride treatments did you
ever get
how many fluoride treatments did you get
my friend said fluoride treatments what
do you mean i said do you realize how
much aluminum
is in your brain from your fluoride
treatments since you were a child
creating that vitiligo and other
problems
it's like all right i'm on board i'm
going to do the heavy metal detox
cleanse i said good because it starts
tomorrow
so here we are today you guys we're
we're talking about the brain a little
bit we're talking about how we get
metals in there i'm getting everybody
prepared make sure you have a copy of
cleansing heal that's where the heavy
metal detox cleanses you guys
janine says what can i do if i cannot
access wild blueberries anywhere or
powder and you've got no ability to do
anything throw blackberries in there
it's not going to totally do the same
but the miracle part of the heavy metal
detox
smoothie
is you're gonna have three out of the
five if you do four out of the five
amazing if you can do five out of the
five incredible but if you have to leave
out the wild blueberry because that's
what you have to do but you got your
cilantro you got your spirulina you got
your barley grass you got your dolls
right
you're doing really good okay until
someday you get your wild blueberries in
there and you got that in there
seriously
so let's figure this out
okay
i'm in my third year of the heavy metal
detox movie and fourth of cj
so addicted to those they make me feel
so good can never thank you enough
anthony we love you so much
wow regina incredible
i'm so proud of you it's amazing on
facebook thank you for being here i'm so
glad you're here
i'm glad facebook's actually letting a
few people in
amazing fantastic
all right
let's talk about this
how many people you know
have an eating disorder how many people
you know have ocd
just think about it
how many people you know got eczema
psoriasis
how many people you know got
depersonalization how many people you
know they're jekylled and hyde
one minute they're jekyll one minute
they're high
what about their jet they're like yeah
things are going good
next minute like
next thing you know they're like yeah
things are going good things are going
good day later
[Music]
next thing you know they're on they're
on top of the world like i'm okay i'm
okay things are going good next day
toxic heavy metals
and people can't pinpoint they don't
understand it personality disorders
toxic you don't think anybody has a
personality disorder believe me they do
lissa what is the personalization
right
what is the personalization
feeling numb
you don't feel anything
you don't you you can't connect
you can't connect to yourself you can't
connect to others
others it's like are you there are you
there it's like a form of depression
but yet you don't know you're depressed
you don't know you're really depressed
or it's a feeling of always feeling like
you're missing out on something you're
missing out on something you don't know
what it is you're lost and you can't
find yourself or find out where you're
going depersonalization
you feel lost all the time you feel like
you're supposed to be somewhere else but
you don't know where you're supposed to
be or you feel numb and you're just
laying in bed when you wake up in the
morning and you feel kind of dread
inside of you you don't want to greet
the day and you feel numb these are all
different versions of depersonalization
smith and pepper said that's me for sure
jekyll and hyde or depersonalization
right
so it's important to get the medals out
it's a critical time this is the
preliminary
time to get us prepared
i got everything right here to talk
about how we should get prepared we're
going to talk about metals how we get
metals how all that happens we're going
to talk about it really important right
there what are your reviews on amalgams
the fillings can we do heavy metal with
amalgam fillings absolutely if i had a
whole bunch of amalgams in there i would
be doing the heavy metal detox cleanse
because you're trying to get metal
that's escaping so you're trying to get
mercury that's escaping that's what
you're doing so
if you're somebody
right
that you got all that mercury filling
silver fillings in your teeth or had
them at one point in your teeth
ow
ow oh my god
if you had if you're somebody that has
all that
in your teeth right
or had them keep in mind that it's
you're not trying to use the heavy metal
detox movie to get the amalgam out
you're you're using it for the bleed
the bleed over right the filling is
bleeding over
it's outgassing
out pocketing so you're catching what's
leaving that's what you do when you're
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie
right there okay
if you're somebody that had braces
someday or you had braces a long time
ago right so you had the braces it's a
lot of metal and it gets into our system
it gets into our nerves it gets into our
throat it gets into our thyroid
so we're trying to get medals out that's
what we're doing
sarah
okay sarah on youtube so thankful for
this cleanse i'm off all of my anxiety
and vertigo medications i've done this
cleanse every single day since august
first it's a part of my everyday life
now and you got off
of your your anxiety you've got your
anxiety better you've got all that
better i'm so proud of you
so proud of you incredible so let's go
into it a little bit you guys ahmed says
heavy metal detox smoothie on youtube
helped me so much in my dark time and my
mother thank you so much
incredible you're here i'm so honored
you're here that's incredible okay
santara's here healing said her
depersonalization was really really
intense growing up i'm trying to find
your comment again it's going there it
is my dear personalization was insane
growing up didn't feel real and so
disconnected from myself centaurus i
know that that can happen it's i'm so
sorry you went through that
mary e said feel like you are outside of
your body looking down this is the
personalization you guys are describing
it better than me you guys are
describing it way better than me for
sure
and people have they're they're
struggling with that depersonalization
so look if you guys just came on here
you guys came on here and tick tock i
mean i know we're live on youtube
facebook telegram we're live on
rumble rumble we're live on all kinds of
places brianna
yes i give it to my 11 month old and
three-year-old every day incredible so
proud actually i'm really proud of them
and there's they're actually they're
actually drinking it that's so good
they're eating the smoothie amazing i'm
proud of your kids
special kids
see you guys it's important to have
the cleanse the heel book
get it free at the library it's a free
cleanse
or you can go to amazon.com us 51
off
16.99 costs more to print the book it's
a medical textbook it has a heavy metal
detox cleanse it gives you in detail
what we're talking about here you guys
also i want you to like
when when hey when you're doing the
cleanse tomorrow if you feel up to it i
want to post every like anybody's story
want to post them if i can
so tag at medical medium hashtag medical
medium but you have to do both of those
you have to tag at medical medium and
hashtag medical means so i can see it if
you don't do both of those i won't be
able to see your story i won't be able
to see your posts because i want to post
and i want to do posts and stories
incredible dr faun
good to see you good to see you
so here we are right here okay so we're
just making a mess right here like usual
when we do lives
and we're live on tick tock as well
all right
let's go
so on tick tock share your stories as
well share it
share your healing experiences and
stories on tick tock if you guys can
about your heavy metal detox cleanse
amazing let's go into it a little bit so
what do you need let's get prepared what
do we need
you need your frozen wild blueberries
your frozen wild blueberries
get your frozen wild blueberries if you
can
important
if you can't get frozen wild blueberries
try to get a wild blueberry uh powder
you know while blueberry juice is
something you can get too let me see if
i can grab one right now
so while blueberries is something you
can get
i got a stash
i got a stash of it right here got the
wyman's wild blueberry juice right there
okay
so that's at shop.weimans.com
you got to have your barley grass juice
powder
okay and you gotta have your spirulina
and you guys know i work with wyman's i
work with them
i'm not sponsored by vimergy
right
but
i work with wyman's letting you know so
there's that now here's the vimergy
right here here's where
the heavy guns are okay so this is where
the heavy guns are they're in the barley
grass juice powder
they're in the spirulina
powder
that's a big part of getting the metals
out do not get confused with okay
lorella
don't get confused with chlorella
don't get because chlorella doesn't work
i'm going to let you know i'm just
dropping that right now so you know you
have to have the spirulina you have to
have the barley grass ready barley grass
juice powder
not barley grass
barley grass
won't do the trick it has to be the
juice powder
that's what travels beyond
and into the bloodstream to the brain
here's how it works if you do barley
grass
you're not going to get the barley grass
to the brain it's 99 of it's gonna stay
in the intestinal tract you have to get
the barley grass juice powder
very important
all right spirulina it's another one
right there
spirulina critical
now this is the best stuff there is
out there okay i'm not sponsored by
vimergy it's just the best stuff i'm not
an ambassador for vimorgy i'm not
sponsored i'm not the owner of the
company
but the stuff is that incredible
this is the gold right here
it's this type of spirulina that vimergy
actually has
that makes the difference i'm letting
you know okay that's the one right there
okay
and the stuff is incredible right
we're getting the medals out brianna
says the smoothie saved my life no more
depression anxiety and panic attacks
medals create panic attacks unexplained
panic attacks brianna that's amazing
here's the barley grass juice powder
right here
that's where the gold is at it's not
barley grass because i don't want you
guys making mistakes
one of the mistakes is barley grass it's
different than barley grass juice powder
so i'm letting you know this is the
stuff this is where the gold is at for
getting metals out right here
all right so that's the vimorgy if you
guys don't know the vimergy company is v
is in victor i am as in mary ergy dot
com
themergy.com i'm not an ambassador i'm
not an mlm person i'm not a pyramid
scheme person
i don't own the company and i'm not
sponsored but the stuff is that
incredible it really is so i'm just
showing you i'm i'm actually trying not
to spill it everywhere too because
because once that that stuff just drops
everywhere it's going to be on on the
cutting board and everywhere else so on
the table so
you got to have these two so here's how
the heavy metal detox smoothie works you
have to have these two
if you can
you gotta have
the dolls
so this is the dulce liquid so this is
what i use
okay i'll drop two dropper fulls you
could put one dropper full but i put two
dropper fulls of adults into the
smoothie so that's something you might
want to be prepared with this is also a
vimergy.com product visa victor i am e r
g y so you know where to go vimergy.com
if you guys want to help anybody out and
let people know
so this is the dulce liquid so i drop
this into the smoothie this
is a metal remover in the gut okay
that's important to know it's the dolls
kelp doesn't do that
i wish kelp did
but it doesn't
so it's and it this is incredible for
when dolls is hard to find because if
you can find some adults you can use the
dolls here's dolls right here i got a
little bit
right but sometimes this is hard to find
so then
i love the liquid i just use the liquid
anyway i'll put both in there yvonne
says no more pms with medical medium
protocol incredible
that's so so wonderful it really is
so we're talking about dolls right now
thank you for for sharing that yvonne
thank you for sharing that very much
so we got the dolls
right the energy dolls we got the
spirulina
memory spirulina we got the barley grass
cheese powder
these are the highest quality levels of
this if you can find if you can't find
this stuff and you use some other barley
grass make sure it's a juice powder
right the prevention realm good to see
you love how gentle but powerful this
cleanses that's the key that's the key
right there so
one of the reasons why the cleanse works
is because it's powerful
another reason why it works is because
it's gentle
it makes it so you can do it it makes it
so children can do it it makes it so we
can get metals out right
so
five of these ingredients work together
synergetically synergistically they work
together
systematically
to get the metals out of the brain and
brainstem and neurons and out of the
liver and out of the organs and out of
your endocrine glands and out of your
thyroid and out of your body and that's
how people get better and move forward
which is so important right there
so we're talking about the wild
blueberries that's one thing you got to
have the wild blueberries these are the
frozen wild blueberries but do you do
the best you can if you don't have this
did you try to get a wild blueberry
powder if you don't have that try to get
the wild blueberry juice but getting or
if you don't have any wild blueberry
throw some blackberries in there it
won't do the same but it helps the good
news is you have the other ingredients
you have the dolls right and you have
these other things okay
here's the other thing you can start
with a small amount of the smoothie so
you can start with a smaller amount of
the heavy metal detox smoothie you guys
you can start with with a small
amount
right so when you make your smoothie you
can do a smaller one if you're sensitive
if you're somebody who's sensitive you
do a smaller one
it's incredible because it's for
sensitive people to begin with because
people are sensitive because they have
all these metals to begin with their
nerves are all jacked up that's what's
happening so people are walking around
their nerves are all jacked up is what's
happening right
and
they got the personalization the anxiety
they got the depression people got
schizophrenia they got bipolar they got
mania
or somebody's just like
when they're up they're like manic
they're manic and manic and manic a lot
of people just have anxiety and they'll
have a panic
and they'll have all of that to the
panic and it feels like it feels like
they're just all over the place all
through their bodies so that's a whole
nother thing right there that people go
through
right
so
i'm making some room over here
power of compassion when i first started
medical medium i did exactly the same
mistake i used barley grass powder not
the juice powder thank you for letting
everybody know this is why i have to say
it over and over again this is why it's
a critical piece of this
it can't be the barley grass powder and
i'll tell you why barley grass powder
is scratchy
it scratches the lining of the
intestinal tract because it's a
dehydrated grass
this is a juice powder and it's not
scratchy
it dissolves quick absorbs fast
assimilates instantly it gets into your
bloodstream fast and it doesn't irritate
the lining of the intestinal tract
barley grass can make somebody go oh i
tried that medical medium smoothie
that's awful
wow
and then they tell somebody else online
like yeah don't do his stuff it bothered
me
and then someone else who had
schizophrenia that could have healed is
like okay i won't i'll listen to you and
then they got their and then their
schizo for the rest of their life
marjorie said
yep haven't had a panic attack since
starting medical medium on facebook
thank you marjorie for being here that's
so important
panic attacks
are brutal for so many people you go
numb your arms go dumb you feel like you
can't even leave to the next room you
feel like you're trapped
you can you know people pass out i
always tell people you pass out from a
panic attack you're gonna be okay
because you're gonna wake up and be okay
sue says i made the mistake with the
barley grass at first
still was healing with the other four
amazing because you were then when i got
the vimergy barley grass juice powder i
really started to heal because you
elevated it to that next level right on
sues right on uh youtube thank you
exactly did you get do you guys hear
that
it made that much of a difference so
when it's the vimergy one it takes it to
that next level
it really does
it does
what i love about the vimergy company is
they know
they understand people's sickness and
chronic illness and supplement companies
don't know
really or understand or can relate or
anything they don't have that they're
just like robots supplement companies
are robots they put out stuff that are
trendy to try to just get things sold
there's a difference when you're
creating things
to stop illness
that's an entirely different thing and
that's what the vimergy company does
that's why i stand behind their stuff
100 and i've become friends with them
all along the way because of what
they've done i try to become friends
with all the other supplement companies
but you know what they say to me we're
not taking our natural flavors out sorry
aw we don't want to talk to you anymore
and then another supplement come we'll
we'll talk aw stop telling us to take
your sip to take citric acid out of our
supplements go somewhere else i'll be
like fine i'm not going to recommend
your stuff that happens all the time
because they don't want to come clean
selena says
aw i have dulse flakes is the is the
right amount two tablespoons you can do
you can do whatever you feel but i would
personally i would go with you know one
tablespoon is what i would go with so if
that was me selena and i had the dull
flakes i would do one tablespoon
definitely and then there's a dulce
liquid if you ever get the dulce liquid
do two dropper falls of the dulce liquid
right there but it makes that much of a
difference i'm trying to show you guys
how much it makes of a difference right
let me give you a rundown on spirulina
okay
right
so i used to recommend another spirulina
company because at the time it was all
that we had out there right
and then i found something in their
bottle of spirulina something that was
not a good thing i contacted the
spirulina company that i recommended to
all these people for quite a while for a
good few with a good few years right
contact them and said it's aw the
medical medium okay i've recommended
your stuff for years
to a lot of people i found something in
my bottle i need a call back immediately
because i need this looked at right now
because i'm about to just boom stop
recommending this
and they didn't call me back
they didn't call me back
and that's why this is the only one i
recommend right here and now
and that was it
teresa
so here's the cool thing
questions in the
medical medium
you know heavy metal detox cleanse we're
doing tomorrow and the next day we're
doing two days right questions
answers of those questions for the heavy
metal detox smoothie the cleanse itself
are amy cleanse the heel i'm going to
give you what i can right now make sure
you have cleanse the heel go to the
library get it for free it's a free
cleanse or go to amazon.com 51 off
teresa says i signed up for your
newsletter twice but i am not receiving
any check your spam
check your spam
check your promotions and check them on
your desktop
check them on your desktop
if you can that's what i would do it's
important
right
i'm doing exclusive videos on my
newsletter link is in the description
you guys tic tac link is in the profile
exclusive videos and by the way i'm
doing exclusive videos on tick tock i
just want everybody to know just really
good videos on tik tok right now
exclusive and snapchat exclusive videos
on snapchat too by the way i'm so happy
i opened up a snapchat account i don't
know what i was thinking i guess i just
you know forgot and snapchat is freaking
awesome and i'm leaving telegram audios
too exclusive telegram audience just
letting everybody know what i've been up
to so everybody knows so we're in the
preliminary part of the heavy metal
detox cleanse day one starts tomorrow
day two is after tomorrow right i'm
showing you guys what you need right um
kelly good to see you
i'm showing you guys what you need cena
says cinnapang says how about bloating
after taking heavy metal detox for over
a half year so what it is is you got the
bloating right that's what's happening
it's not the heavy metal detox causing
the bloating you have the bloating so
you must have the bloating with other
things you're eating other foods you're
eating other things you're doing heavy
metal detox smoothie is there to pull
out the metals right that's its job to
pull out the metals and chemicals too
okay
but we still have to build up your hcls
if that was me i would want my ac my hcl
built up so i would be doing my celery
juice 32 ounces every day to attack that
bloating so i'd be doing my celery juice
right okay so the heavy metal detox
smoothie isn't the heavy metal detox
cleanse the heavy metal detox cleanse
right takes it to another level plus
there's bloating protocols
in here so that's another thing too
there's actually you've got to find your
true cause of your bloating find out
what it is learn what your bloating is
caused from is it from your hcl being
too low is it from your liver being
sluggish and stagnant what other things
do you have going on in your diet that
are actually bogging down your liver and
there's protocols in here for bloating
to look at and do and add to it the
heavy metal detox smoothie
is not meant to be this ant type loader
it is actually meant to pull metals out
so you get rid of all the heavy metal
conditions right anxiety depression
panic vitiligo eczema psoriasis
depersonalization
mania bipolar ocd ptsd right it's it's
meant to get all that cleaned up and
fixed
[Music]
all right
let's talk let's talk shop
we're doing it how do we get metals
right well let's finish up we're talking
about the different things we need so we
talked about we need the barley grass
juice powder we need the spirulina we
need the wild blueberries i talked about
why it's critical to use the vimergy
brand if you can't use the vimergy brand
make sure you try to get a barley grass
juice powder somewhere and if you do
pick a spirulina i hope you don't pick
some of the bum companies out there so
do your best to try to get the right one
if you can
so
cilantro is something that's really
important
and we have the cilantro right here we
got a celery stick somewhere attached to
it there we go
so we got the cilantro
if you don't like the taste of cilantro
you got some metals sure you can love
cilantro and still have metals but i do
find when someone doesn't like the taste
of cilantro they have the metals more in
this region of their body
if someone likes the taste of cilantro
they may have metal somewhere else it
could be in their brain or their liver
or intestinal tract right it could be
there
okay so that's something to know
but if someone doesn't like the taste of
cilantro we're talking about metals
being somewhere near the hypoglossal
nerve okay the hyperglossal nerve in the
mouth that's important to know right
there so what i'm going to do is i'm
going to move this back over here
there we go
nice
so let's take a look
a lot of people go i don't like cilantro
i don't like the taste of cilantro
yucky
awful a lot of people do that cilantro
is terrible tastes like soap it tastes
like soap to me
that means you got your mercury close to
the hypoglossal nerve
that's what it means
you got you got your mercury
close to that nerve
and it's throwing off your taste buds
right there
that's what that means
so many people have metal in them
you guys like perfume
guys love perfume
you know when people wear it
you smell it
it's loaded with toxic heavy metals
load it with toxic heavy metals do you
guys like cologne
you guys like the smell of cologne
every time we smell cologne we just got
a whiff of metals going into our system
they vaporize in the cologne
toxic heavy metals that cologne
toxic heavy metals
you guys like tuna fish
i got a nice can of tuna fish right here
i took a label off so i don't get a
letter from the tuna company
pat
pat eldridge says
my husband and i had the plague in
august we have done the morning cleanse
ever since lemon water 32 ounces of
celery juice heavy metal detox smoothie
have my husband on the prostate protocol
remarkable results
i made the mistake of getting a
bioidentical hormone pellet in november
experienced major hair loss from it have
been doing hair protocol ever since
thank god incredible so glad you're here
amazing
okay so we're covering a couple of other
things right now so let's go into the
let's go into where do we get the metals
stay away from copper
st do you guys like my copper necklace
my copper arm bracelet right here i got
my copper
copper or bracelet you like that i'm
gonna start wearing this every day i'm
gonna do that i'm gonna wear copper all
over my body i'll do that right and then
i'll wear it i'll wear it for a few
years and all of a sudden
i'll just be like
having some serious problems get copper
poisoning to the brain stay away from
copper devices copper products copper
anything copper is not healthy for you
the trendy world of
get copper you know canisters get copper
water canisters get copper this
you know what's sad
you know what's that
no one ever
is held accountable or responsible
for that person who listens and drinks
out of a copper thermos for the next
five years
and they lose their mind
from neurological symptoms
no one's responsible in the trend world
no one's responsible for alkaline
ionizer water machine poisoning
anybody who drinks out of the alkaline
ionizer water
machines will end up with neurological
problems and no one's held responsible
no
because the metal plates
flake and that metal that the
electricity hits inside the ionizer
water machines oxidizes and flakes the
metal
and they will go insane down the road
with heavy metal poisoning and
neurological problems
including tongue problems ear problems
face problems everything under the sun
from alkaline eyes on our water machine
and the thing is no one's get held
responsible same thing with the copper
stuff and the copper drinks and the
copper this and the copper all of it no
one's held responsible no one's held
responsible for the fish oil
recommendations from all the different
practitioners to the podcast doctors you
know i'm new to soon so 10 ways you can
get your health back check out my
youtube channel i'm dr rick
i'm doctor stewart
i'm doctor
try my fish oil because it's important
and i have a lot of other doctors using
fish oil too everybody try my fish oil
but no one's held responsible for when
this crap gets into the brain
because it's loaded with methyl mercury
homeopathic style inside fish oil i
don't care whose fish oil is i don't
care if a martian
the planet mars comes down
and says here's your fish oil from mars
pure no mercury in mars
it's still got mercury in it
all right so here's how fish oil is made
and processed
right
they don't use one type of fish unless
it's something like a krill oil which is
still loaded with toxic heavy metals
they don't use one
type of fish with your fish oil
they use
hundreds of fish hundreds of fish heads
fishtails fish fins shark fins yep guts
of fish all kinds of different
by-products from the fish industry all
those fish
all those fish sticks
that are in the freezer department
okay
of different kinds of fish all those
heads and tails went into
a truck
drove to a factory to make fish oil and
they threw it all in the same
container
heads and tails of different fish
flounders in there juicy grouper in
there
just everything in there
and that's your fish oil
i smell something really nice right now
ah
i smell wild flowers
i love the smell of wildflowers oh it
was my scented candles
i just got five more scented candles
the smell of fake wildflowers is so good
i know
toxic heavy metals in the worst way air
fresheners too in the worst way
all right all right
let's get it together
we need some oranges
for the heavy metal detox smoothie and
cleanse we need some oranges that we
need okay so we got some orange we need
some bananas
bananas
bananas if you don't have them we'll
still try to make the smoothie just
might not be as fun we need some bananas
okay
we need apples all right
we need our apples right
so we got to have our apples lost one
all right
we got them now
we need our apples the apples aren't for
the smoothie the apples are for part of
the cleanse you have them in in the
middle of the day or mid-morning i like
to have them sometime mid-morning i have
an apple have another one later on right
so lemons for lemon water right we need
that lemons for lemon water
need our lemons first thing in the
morning we have our lemon water boom we
squeeze it in there do not do hot water
with your lemon
right
brittany says can you talk about anxiety
and how this cleanse can help yeah let's
talk about it now we can talk about
lemon water any old time
right
we can talk about lemon water any old
time so let's get our little friend over
here let's move let's make some room
right here okay
that's what we're gonna do
you guys just got on here please watch
us from the beginning
watch it on rumble from the beginning
watch it on telegram from the beginning
you can watch it on youtube from the
beginning but watch it from the
beginning if you can could possibly
watch it on facebook from the beginning
but they seem to be doing funny things
to all my videos
the cleanse starts tomorrow heavy metal
detox cleanse challenge starts tomorrow
make sure you have your book for people
who just got on here you might somebody
you might be somebody who just got on
here now so that's what you need
so let's talk about anxiety let's head
there now okay so we're gonna grab our
dummy over here
right
now we're going to be careful with this
dummy
okay
this dummy's guts are about to fall out
right here
so they're about to pile out right
so you got your vagus nerve you guys see
this on tick-tock you guys okay over
there on youtube
okay you got your vagus nerves
right
so
your vagus nerves
it's come out of the brain stem
and when they're inflamed
when they're inflamed all right right
there
right the brain stem down in here when
the nerves are inflamed
okay anxiety starts
now your brain stem can be slightly
inflamed with mild inflammation
and that will create an anxiety right
there you might even get like heart
racing
because of the vagus nerves receiving
information that's trailing down there
all right
so that's one way the brain stem being
inflamed or the vagus nerves themselves
can be inflamed
toxic heavy metals
can cling to the vagus nerves and the
brain stem
keep that in mind
all right they can cling to the vagus
nerve and the brain stem
toxic heavy metals can also get into the
brain itself
and they when they get into the brain
itself right
they can attach to neurons
when toxic heavy metals attach to
neurons
they can short-circuit neurotransmitter
chemicals and electrical impulses
anxiety isn't just one size fits all
anxiety your anxiety is different than
anybody else's anxiety and your anxiety
is different than anybody else's anxiety
and your anxiety is different than
anybody else's anxiety but metals play a
role and this is very important
everybody's anxiety is different you
guys there's no anxiety disorder or
anxiety problem that's the same in any
one two three four person they're all
unique and different
that's why i like medical medium
information it's to customize so you can
you're going to have a different form of
anxiety that means when you use the
heavy metal detox smoothie
it's geared to getting metals out of
your vagus nerve if that's where they
are and causing your anxiety or if your
metals are in your brain stem
causing your anxiety
right
or if your metals are in your neurons
inside your brain
causing anxiety so if they're inside
your brain
medical medium heavy metal detox cleanse
is geared
for the person who has them inside their
brain
in the brain or on the brainstem
or on the vagus nerves themselves
how do they how does how does have
having metals create this when you have
metals in your brain your short
circuiting neurotransmitters electrical
impulses sending down signals down the
vagus nerves that are causing that
problem right
that's one right there one way
um
eo fruits and vegetables says i suffer
from panic attacks following six months
of keto
you're not the only one that suffer from
panic attacks following months of keto
it felt like i was in a tornado of my
own thoughts and the room was spinning
haven't had one since starting medical
medium two years ago and i'll tell you
why because the keto diet is not
the keto diet is a one size fits all
approach
terrible approach
that's a one size fits all what you'll
notice is medical medium information was
only customized is the only one out
there that was customized for people
with all their different problems and
then so what happened was because of
that
the one size fits all groups like keto
and everybody else they decided to you
know attack medical mediums saying
medical mediums one size fits all that's
funny because medical medium is not
and never was
so
medical medium is not just plant-based
it's not just animal-based that proves
it's not one-size-fits-all just all on
its own right there
all right let's get going here so what
happens is your vagus nerve runs down
and travels down through the body and it
attaches itself to the stomach it
attaches itself to the intestinal tract
to the colon it attaches itself to all
the abdom all the organs in the abdomen
right especially it gets down here to
the intestinal tract and colon
so when that vagus nerve is
hyper-inflamed or partially inflamed or
low-grade inflamed
you're going to have mixed signals
coming down and these mixed signals are
going to come down and you're going to
get panic you're going to feel like
you're heart racing sometimes so let's
take a look right here take a look at
the heart
toxic heavy metals inflame the vagus
nerve or brain stem or brain creating
heart palpitations right here could you
guys check out the tic tac video i did
heart palpitations
after this live you guys have to check
out the tick tock exclusive tick tock
video i did on heart palpitations if you
can
it's really a great thing to do okay so
if you if you can do that that would be
amazing so you guys on tik tok check it
out when you can you guys probably
already know about it anybody who's not
on tick tock check it out later an
exclusive video so let's go now
so as the vagus nerve travels down here
okay as the vagus nerve travels down
here
it's also sending messages to the heart
giving you that heart palpitation of the
heart racing so if you have panic part
of that panic attack is your vagus nerve
creating that heart to do this
that's part of the panic attack right
there
that's what happens heart palpitations
the same way it can send a signal to
the heart that flips the heart like a
fish
like this
and then you feel your heart go in your
throat you're like oh my god what was
that
and it almost makes you cough you have a
heart palpitation that could be the top
of the heart because the vagus nerve
sending a master chop power and you're
and you almost choke
because that heart palpitation feels
like it went into your upper chest up
into your throat
right
so you can have heart palpitations and
you can have
panic or just anxiety here's another
thing with the vagus nerve right here
with anxiety so when you have toxic
heavy metals if you guys just rolled in
we're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse starting tomorrow this is the
preliminary we're talking about what we
need all the stuff we need and
everything stick around so you can hear
that again
but right now we're talking about the
vegas they're being affected by toxic
heavy metals so when we have toxic heavy
metals like mercury and copper
right
and mercury
see the fish oil mercury
when we have toxic heavy metals
that come from colognes and perfumes
toxic heavy metals in our brain and
nervous system our vagus nerve our brain
and our vagus nerve we get mixed
messages right down here to the heart
causing heart to be afib mysterious afib
mysterious tachycardia
mysterious ectopic heartbeat mysterious
heart palpitations
right then we get other things that are
mysterious we get anxiety with tightness
of the chest how many of you guys have
ever experienced tightness to the chest
with your anxiety
have you guys ever experienced that
tightness of the chest
right
it takes metals
in your system
for that to happen so many of you guys
had that tightness of the chest right
so that's the vagus nerve
being slightly inflamed creating that
tightness of the chest it's the vagus
nerve being slightly inflamed creating
tightness at the chest i'm letting you
guys know right there
okay
trisha marie says i have beth bucks as i
have so you guys have um callie says me
explanation points ahmed says uh me tara
appleman says oh yes 100
kelly z says i have horrible
right
and christina says yes
okay tj says yes so you guys have
christy says yes
right donna says me okay you guys have
experienced this rhone green says it
cannot catch my breath sometimes so you
get you can't you feel like you can't
get air into your lungs so what happens
is the vagus nerves because of toxic
heavy metals
the vagus nerves when they get inflamed
you guys
you feel like you can't get that deep
breath in i suffer from anxiety for 54
years
gina says you feel like you can't get
that deep breath that you feel like you
can't breathe you feel like you can't
take in that air and it could even get
you in the throat elizabeth
elizabeth said that was me and tightness
of the throat oh it's awful
be open to heart it said yes
be open-hearted good to see you by the
way you leave comments on youtube but i
always read them so it's ah it always
makes sense
and so we get the tightness of the chest
and all that yvonne says anyone here
that doesn't believe in mm leave
that made me laugh don't make comments
that are negative he has saved my life
in many other people's lives
i went to 13 doctors and no one tested
me for ebv most doctors know nothing
about chronic illness he's the only one
who teaches the truth about chronic
illness and it and its causes because he
cares
he makes
zero money when we are sick
but guess who does make money when we
are sick think about it right i'm
thinking about a lot of things podcasts
doctors make a ton of money like you
know there's all kinds of people that
i'm just big pharma
yvonne
incredible on facebook
yvonne master i'm andre you're uh
honored you're here truly and it means
the world
and what happens is people go to 13
doctors and you went to 13 doctors and
it's brutal and i and it is and it's
hard to it's it's
i don't
you have to be a special person
yvonne right and you guys know this if
you went to all those doctors
you went through a lot
and you can't measure that
any you any of what you guys have gone
through any of it it's not measurable it
goes into the spiritual realm
you guys have been through hell and back
many of you it goes into the spiritual
realm you guys are spiritual powers now
because you because what it is is you
can't measure that what you went through
only
from above that's who sees that okay god
sees that the angels say that christ
sees that
the light sees that the creator sees it
whatever anybody believes is what i'm
saying sees that of what you went
through
can't be measured down here
julie says i just got a new couch and
because of all the chemicals sprayed on
it that's rough
i get this tightness in my chest and
shortness of breath is this the same
thing yes so what it is julie is what it
means is you got the hypersensitivities
right so what i tell a lot of people and
and and a family member who a family
member of mine came to me like back a
few years ago and said look i need these
medals out i'm ready and i'm like all
right let's do it
and what happened was right before that
they had the metals in their system and
it takes time to get the metals out and
the metals are also in chemicals that
are on like new couches and all that
stuff and what happens is it triggers
our vagus nerves so when we breathe in
that chemical there's certain chemicals
they spray on new furniture not all new
furniture but a lot of furniture they
spray these new chemicals on there and
the new chemicals they
they trick out our vagus nerves because
their vagus nerves are already
hypersensitive from everything we've
been through including metals and all
that
it really is
that's really what people go through so
we're talking about metals we're talking
about why to get them out we're talking
about how we get them we're talking
about the vagus nerves phrenic nerves is
another one too vagus nerve is my
problem patty says okay
yeah yeah i mean
and the thing is is phrenic nerves is
another thing too okay phrenic nerves
run through the chest they come off the
spine area they run through the chest
they run they run off the spine up here
they run down
phrenic nerves get inflamed olivia
westman says what should we take for
heart palpitation so we have the heart
right here
okay
so
heart palpitations that are mysterious
that are derived from neurological
they're mysterious they're derived from
messages coming
from
the brain or brain stem
right
or vagus nerve so these are messages
getting skewed along the way before they
get to the heart and then when they get
to the heart
they do this
right here
see
it's like morse code
all of a sudden an electrical impulse is
going to the heart in a different way
and so now we're getting the hard part
so here you are you're going along
you're going along you're going along
and then
what the heck what
what the heck was that
oh my god what was that
i gotta get to the hospital right now
it's my first set of heart palpitations
and every time someone gets the first
set of heart palpitations they run to
the emergency room and they get all the
tests and everything's checked out well
another one
okay
so i'm going to move
my dummy over and we're going to run
through the protocol a little bit
see you guys
stay in there please
if the guts fall out of my dummy it's
not my fault
it's just the way the dummy's made
there's no hook in there okay you guys
let's run through it if you guys just
came on here we're doing the heavy metal
detox cleanse starts tomorrow with a
two-day cleanse make sure you have the
cleanse the heel book i'm just reminding
you watch this video all the way to the
beginning watch it from the start so you
can learn all this information okay by
the way cleanse the heel is not just a
heavy metal detox
cleanse it's over 200 symptoms and
conditions inside this book with caught
true causes protocol supplement dosages
and other cleanses
it's so you can customize your problem
what's wrong with you it can be
customized so you can get what you need
51 off amazon.com us get one if you can
or go to the library and get it for free
right
it's not one size fits all medical
medium information is far from that it's
the opposite
and that's why so many people heal
so many people heal from the medical
medium cleanses like the heavy metal
detox cleanse because it's customized
for all these different conditions
so what happens when panic attacks turn
into fatigue
if you check out medical medium cleanse
to heal you can learn what i always tell
people okay
is you take the symptom
that's bothering you whether it's panic
attacks which is anxiety right you go to
that section you bring the book to your
doctor if you want or you go into the
other symptom fatigue so now we have
fatigue so let's go to that symptom
mimi says i got rid of afib with medical
medium protocols god bless you that's so
that's so important keeping radical fats
out was key for me yeah those fats thank
you thank you for being here
quick run down you guys let's go this is
the preliminary to the heavy metal detox
lens that starts tomorrow
meltdown says i got rid of my anxiety
last year after doing the 369 advanced
cleanse i just feel like a different
person now it's so scary what the metals
do to us 369 cleanses in here
all right
so let's go run down what we need lemons
for lemon water you can't do hot lemon
water if you do hot lemon water you're
ruining the flushing power of the lemon
you can have lemon in your tea do that
at another time
if it's hot okay
oranges you need oranges to put into the
smoothie into the smoothie right that's
what we need
we need cilantro
we need wild blueberries the key
ingredients cilantro wild blueberries
we need the dolls that's the vimergy
dolls these and victor i miss and mary
ergy dot com that's adults liquid right
here i'm not sponsored it's just the
best stuff ever you put two dropper
folds in you can put one dropper full in
i put two in
right there there's the dolls let's go
you need your barley grass cheese powder
not your barley grass barley grass juice
powder
you need your spirulina so this is the
vimergy stuff the good stuff
i talked about earlier why it's so good
just part of why it's so good right
we need those you need your celery
because if you want to do the cleanse
you want to do your celery juice don't
add anything to your celery juice no ice
no milk
i saw someone leave a comment and they
said they'd put milk in their celery
juice and i was just like
and i said
i said the spirit of compassion
this is what i said the spirit of
compassion
blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah
blah milk
blubber
that's not originally mine by the way
that is not mine the blah blah blahs are
not mine
i just thought i would do it all right
let's go
need the bananas
that's important okay if you've got
dulce without the liquid you can go with
adults if you can find dolls right don't
do kelp
not irish sea moss or anything or cmos
that doesn't get the metals out so
important to know apples need those and
eat those during the day
right that's important right there
um
i don't know these are just some of the
stuff we're getting the medals out
we're going
so there we are
we got a lot to do you guys by the way
exclusive videos on tick tock exclusive
videos on snapchat
check out my newsletter exclusive videos
on the newsletter you get them every
sunday
right sign up to the newsletter link is
in the descriptions you guys link is in
the profile right there important to
know what's going on marianne zuma says
my family loves uaw yay thank you for
all your time efforts and love of
humanity
honored
honored honored you guys
the cleanse
starts
tomorrow
now i just want to say
it's one thing to say
right
you got the toxic heavy metals in you
it's creating the panic
anxiety
depression depersonalization alzheimer's
memory loss
pain and suffering
eczema psoriasis
mania bipolar ocd
it's one thing to say the metals are
causing that and how they cause that
it's another
thing
about what you guys have gone through
with your ocd
and your depression anxiety the
personalization and your memory loss and
your brain fog and all these other
things
what you guys have been through and
lived through and are living through now
that cannot be ignored it has to be
validated and it has to be understood so
one thing
about the metals
and the cause
it's another about understanding what
you guys have gone through rising out of
the ashes and some of the hell that you
guys have been through with all of it
and i'm honored
to just be here with you guys right now
because of that reason alone if there's
nothing else it's just you guys have
been through hell and back
it means everything to me
because i respect what you've been
through and your journey and know it
wasn't easy
i'm heading off to ig and i'm turning
tick-tock back on
and i'm turning telegram back on and
we're going to be there in a little
while
love you guys