we're live live live live we're live
facebook youtube tick tock clubhouse i'm
excited
making some mashed potatoes it's really
easy on the tummy if somebody has
gastroparesis or
they have crohn's or colitis or some
kind of other intestinal tract problem
intestinal cramps if you're someone that
has
spasms and lots of gastritis and all of
that so it's really helpful
it's just a simple meal nice and simple
so i'm gonna make that i got some peas
right here look at that
these are frozen peas that's what they
are okay got the pan going i'm gonna get
pan a little hot they were talking about
overeating by the way
talk about emotions emotions with food
talking even a little bit about
how it works when you're trying to eat
healthier and you're around family and
friends and how
hard that is i want to mention that
again a little bit so we'll talk about
that too and why do we
overeat why do we feel like we have to
overeat how come we're so
hungry so many people are so hungry
stress plays a role i'm going to talk
about the adrenals a little bit i got
some adrenals right in front of me right
here
got some kidneys too stress plays a role
with that
and it can get us mixed into a whole
bunch of eating disorder talk
and eating disorder issues we feel like
we have eating disorders or
we feel like we're struggling with our
foods people don't understand this
people don't get it and i mean there's
so many different places it all goes
so we're talking about some cool stuff
good to see you guys coming on
excited awesome happy to see you glad to
see you too
glad you guys are coming on incredible
so there's there's lots to cover i'm
excited i'm gonna get the pan hot right
now
you guys i'm making a mashed potato with
some peas
and it's a simple dish you can throw
spices in there if you want you can do
that you can throw onion powder in there
you can throw garlic powder in there you
can throw a little garlic in there too
if you really want i'm keeping it real
simple
to show that that you know for other
people who are sensitive garlic or
sensitive with onion or something that
they can have it's so
simple how cool is that it'll be fun
though it really will be and it'll taste
good too
and if you really wanted to add a little
bit of sea salt or
a little bit of a high quality salt
because you're doing salt anyway
because i realize i can't get people off
of salt
if i want to get them off of salt that i
can't get a lot of people off of it
it's like salt salt salt on everything
salt and all the food
lorraine l good to see you uh glad you
guys are coming on really do
lorraine wow man you i all i know is
i've been reading your comments on
youtube
and my mind gets blown because
i think i think someone's on there i
think it was some dude on there and he
was really nice guy
he was a really nice guy and he was
talking about how
on youtube he was talking about how i
think of whatever is that
that medical medium information can help
some people
but not help others and you were like
well it depends on how you look at it
there's so many different options
there's a thousand different protocols
you can customize it to what's happening
in your life
and and that's the difference and the
difference is that
you can heal with the information
because there's so much you got the
spiritual information
you got the the physical causes you've
got supplements and dosages
and so i think people jump the gun a lot
and they'll say
like you know i didn't get better on mm
when when millions have around the world
and because they applied the tools they
applied them
so it's really a matter of like reading
the books
learning and healing
so you got cleansed heal by the way you
guys i mean that's on sale on amazon.com
us
it's really incredible 16.99
this is 17 on amazon us the
medical medium that's got plague
information in there too i think what
happens is that a lot of people were
stuck
they were stuck inside the house they
were stuck
home and they were locked in so many
people were locked in
and stuck with the plague and everything
and they were just eating
and eating and eating with the stress
and then eating and i don't blame i
don't blame anybody it's just it can
happen
but food courtney good to see you glad
you came on
you guys are coming on tick tock we're
live at tik tok facebook youtube
clubhouse i'm excited to be here
lots to cover talk about emotional
eating talking about overeating
talk about why we feel like we have to
overeating insatiable appetites
or how can we keep on going for that
second and third helping
depending on what's happening there and
how you can do fruit and the difference
there on when you do fruit what happens
with there
lucy cone good to see you too because
fruit people say well hey look i can't
eat a lot of fruit i can only eat a
little bit of fruit because i don't want
to have so much and they don't realize
they can have more fruit
like what i do i'll have three or four
mangoes
uh in the morning i'll you know mid
morning i'll have three or four mangoes
and a friend of mine a friend of mine
told me how can you eat three mangoes
like what are you what are you doing
like three mangoes isn't that too many
calories i'm like are you kidding
how many calories you're eating and and
what you're doing you're eating all
kinds of abominations when you go out to
restaurants
when you're doing this and that i'm just
eating three mangoes you know
yeah lorraine lots of interesting
conversations truly but
but i gotta tell you you really hands
down and know the information i know
many of you guys do
dr fon another expert medical medium
information
good to see you glad you guys are coming
on glad you can catch it i know you're
busy
you're busy in your busy practice and
everything so what happens is our brain
overheats you guys our brain overheats
that's what happens your brain overheats
it does heats up someone razzes you
someone's putting pressure on you hey
what are you doing today how come
you know maybe it's your parents maybe
it's family maybe siblings maybe it's
friends
someone's putting pressure or you've got
a busy schedule like
how am i going to get this done how am i
going to get that done i'm overwhelmed i
got to make this phone call i got to do
this
how am i going to survive what am i
doing in my life and you know whatever
is happening
it's it overheats the brain boom
electricity is going on electricity is
going on right
and now now some other stuff happens too
electricity is pumping through your head
so what happens
and your adrenals start pumping
brain starts overheating adrenals start
cranking
cranking that's what happens right there
to everybody
okay and then here comes the food here
comes the food maybe
maybe you're somebody avoiding the food
maybe you're you're doing the caffeine
you're
you're cranking the chocolate the matcha
tea maybe you're cranking the coffee
espressos and you're trying to
avoid the inevitable you're trying to
avoid
you know eating and then when you do eat
at the end of the day
it's a whole bunch of stuff and so we're
gonna talk about glucose mineral salts
how that's missing
uh how why we get so hungry in our
brain because that's where the hunger's
really really stemming from
it's from the brain liver too it's
another one i'll cover that a little bit
so let me just get going with the food
too
a little bit so good
good that you guys are coming on what
happens to
almost everybody is insulin resistance
is stopping sugar from getting to your
brain
right there so that's happening to
everybody really so
you got glucose right so
okay you guys got the glucose
so everything you eat that's a
carbohydrate you eat some fruit you have
some
whatever you have like potato fruit if
you have something else that's sweet
right whatever it is that glucose is how
your brain functions
right there it's that glucose glucose
has to get to your brain
it's hard to get to the brain when all
this fats in the way so when you're
eating all this fat
it's hard to get the glucose to your
brain
the fat stops the glucose from getting
to your brain
that's what happens you get the insulin
resistance
your cells want to take in that sugar
but the fats in the way that's how it
works
so you're gonna inevitably overeat
because your brain is gonna be starving
chris good to see you
yeah mangoes you know i'll do two or
three manuals in the morning
right heard from someone that the brain
needs fat not glucose it's
misinformation out there
that's a sad thing so michelle michelle
brown thanks for that comment
of course you're going to hear that but
did you know that your brain
check this out you guys did you know
jerry says i definitely used to feel
like that especially around my period
since 369 since the medical meaning
three six nine it
it disappeared completely because when
you're doing the 369 you were getting
glucose
and you were getting mineral salts so
glucose and mineral salts okay that's
what you guys were getting right
and we're doing some medical medium
school you guys cool with that
you guys cool with a little medical
medium school today are you guys alright
with that are you guys sick of school
what's up so that's because you're
getting
your mineral salts and your glucose and
that was stopping
the want for overeating so that really
helps so
check this out you love medical medium
school lissieco good to see you today
here's an important thing to understand
right we're told that the brain needs
fat
that's misinformation the brain needs
sugar in five seconds if your brain
doesn't get
glucose sugar in five
seconds it starts to die
you will die if your brain doesn't get
sugar in time
did you know that did you guys know that
very important to know okay
so let's cover that a little bit now why
is there so much misinformation out
there
it's really sad because no one knows why
anybody's sick so then if no one knows
why
no one's sick no one knows what causes
chronic illness no one knows why people
are suffering and struggling and you
learn that
when you get sick you learn that fast
you learn that when you don't get better
better
and you just keep on spiraling in
sickness and you've been to your 10th
functional medicine doctor and your 10th
specialist
and your 10th neurologist and you can't
get better
and you realize nobody knows why
anybody's sick and no one really they're
all just it's all guessing games okay
and what happens is if your brain
doesn't get sugar in under 10 seconds
it starts to die guess what
if your brain doesn't get fat within 10
seconds
it starts to heal it starts to heal
interesting interesting okay
think about how important that is if
your brain doesn't get sugar
within 10 seconds it starts to die
really important information really
really is
get a little seam in this pan try to
cool this pan off a little bit too
have that baby pump in okay
your brain is made out of hardened
glycogen you guys
glycogen you know what that is
sugar your brain is made out of sugar
it's only got traces of fat in the brain
did you know if you eat a brain it's
sweet
did you know it's sweet
it's actually sweet it's glycogen
that's been concentrated and hardened
glucose running through the brain is the
only way
to truly keep the brain alive you remove
it
you die that's it interesting
isn't that incredible right so where did
the theories come from about your brain
needs fat
it was a theory to sell
products fat-based it was a trend
a trend so it's like well your brain
needs fat because there's fat in your
brain there's a little bit of fat in
your brain
a little bit other than that brain
tissue is made out of glycogen
you know it's disappointing really when
i think about it
like how come people can't get it right
out there what's going on out there
and back to the same thing nobody knows
why you got hashimoto's thyroiditis
nobody knows why you got eczema
psoriasis did you know i saw somebody
i saw somebody that someone showed me
something right
that someone took medical medium
information
which is that psoriasis is caused by
toxic heavy metals
copper specifically right and they took
that and they get incited back to
medical medium there's no study
there's no science behind it and a
doctor
put it on his thing that psoriasis toxic
heavy metals right
well the only reason why the doctor knew
that was because of medical media books
and information
okay it's almost like so you don't have
anything on chronic illness unless you
take it for a medical medium
fact that's what i'm seeing out there
it's really sad or they'll just say it's
all in your gut and in the end you'll
just stay sick
libya says he supports people who eat
meat too
it's all about healing for everyone yeah
this isn't
this isn't vegan propaganda anti-animal
protein
uh campaign propaganda cold white spring
good to see you
so good to hear the voice of reason
again i'm honored truly cold white
screen
but here's the thing i feel the same way
about you
because when i read your comments i'm
like voice of reason
there's when i read your comments cold
white spring it's always like yeah
voice of reason you know
darlene says oh my god i'm eating a
potato wrap right now it's funny yum yum
lemon balm love hey
another voice of reason podcast doctors
always steal
mm info fact
podcast doctor so we steal medical
medium information i'm going to take the
skin off the potato first of all
i always eat the skin on potatoes so
it's an incredible nutritious part of
the potato
absolutely but i'm making a fun mashed
potato dish
right so i'm kind of removing some of
the skin on here
podcast doctors steal
medical medium information it's not
published anywhere else
the medical medium books right and
they take it so now all of a sudden
psoriasis is caused by toxic heavy metal
there's no study
they haven't discovered in science
it came from spirit of compassion that
the cause of psoriasis
is copper a toxic heavy metal it's cause
of partly cause of
eczema two right so
when it comes down to everything like
information about the brain if you want
to know more about the brain
you're not going to hear reason out
there because when they say your brain
needs fat
and your brain is made out of fat two
strikes against
the industry right there they alter the
fraud industry the fraud alternative
industry
problem is with the alternative industry
basically most of it's all fraud
and you know all my friends are
alternative doctors
incredible ones though at least they
they they know the difference right
but and then there's the conventional
system too is is fraudulent
it's completely fraudulent especially in
the virus world
really fraudulent and with virus
all it's always the wrong information
about viruses
the wrong information about all of it
i'm taking the skin
off of these potatoes you guys uh
you guys coming on here i'm honored
you're here we got lots to talk about
right and we're making some mashed
potatoes i got a pan that's hot i got
frozen peas right here so i hope you
stick around for that it's an
easy recipe it's gentle on the system
i'm only peeling the potato not because
skins aren't good for you they're
incredible for you that's actually an
amazing part of the potato
but this is more of hey it's a comfort
meal i'm making some comfort food since
we're talking about it because that's
the other thing too
making some comfort food since we're
talking about overeating we're talking
about
uh emotional eating too right
and how stress plays a role the brain
gets hot
so you guys check out medical mean
podcast at apple podcast
you know if you can catch up on some of
the episodes the blood draw episode is
really critical to know
because you're just going to get caught
getting too much blood taken from you
you're going to lose your immune system
part of your immune system it's going to
make you susceptible to other problems i
think
i have to bring up the blood draw
problem once in a while because if i
don't
if i don't people are just going to
forget they're going to get their blood
tests
the doctor's going to take too much
blood
and you're going to get you know five
vials five full vials seven full vials
eight full vials of blood and
want to remind everybody if you guys can
tell everybody about the blood draw
podcast episode
maybe share the link or let people know
it's medically podcasted apple podcast
because what happens is there's a whole
bunch of people i hear every day i just
had 27 vials taken and just had 15 vials
taken i just had 12 vials taken
and it's like okay great a big part of
your immune system was removed
now you're more susceptible to the
plague that's happening out there
one of the reasons why the plague got so
annoying was because of
all the blood draws prior that was a big
reason right there
all the blood draws prior right
and people just they were going into the
plague
with a weakened immune system just from
blood testing alone
just from blood testing alone so i
peeled some potatoes here took the
skin off these are steamed by the way
these are steamed potatoes
they're not raw steamed potatoes it's
the only way to cook a potato really
that's the best way to do it it's having
a steamed potato so i'm giving you kind
of the rundown on that right there
let me mash these up if you guys got a
second thank you for coming on here lots
to talk about
susan gabriel said i recently told a
technician
only two have files she said it wouldn't
be
enough i said it's plenty she said okay
you fought for it you fought for it
you you fought for it you took control
over your health and you fought for it
and you won
you won and it matters it
matters austin good to see you it
matters
it really really does because
when you get that blood taken
you lose your immune system you do guess
where the immune system is
it's in your bloodstream i love when you
hear
the whole thing of the theory of your
immune system's all in your gut
it's not all in your gut it's not your
immune system isn't
micro biome that's not your immune
system
i bet you i'm pissing off somebody right
now i'm sure because there's so much
brainwashing and the colts out there
about you know your immune system being
all in your gut all in your gut
everything's in your gut
all the zelda all the gut products and
the gut potions
and the gut powders and the gut tests
where you do the stool samples and
you're looking for all the gut
microbiome issues and everything else
meanwhile people just don't get better
they don't get does that fix your
hashimoto's thyroiditis because i'm
scratching my head over here
does that fix a four-year-old's eczema
that's raging
and the four-year-old can't even the
skin's cracking off the four-year-old
the mom and dad are in
perils does that fix that i'm just
curious
um you know the gut gut health is isn't
isn't everything for immune system the
immune system is in your bloodstream and
i've i've talked to doctors recently
about this and they said well tell me
more about this because
because the the trend is your immune
system is all in your gut
yeah there's a lot of immune system
around the gut for sure but the majority
is everywhere else in the body it's
protecting your brain it's in your
bloodstream
so your immune system is in your
bloodstream that's the whole point
your blood circulating every single
vessel every single organ in your body
and it has to have white cells and white
blood cells in it it has to
that's how you stop a pathogen from
going to the brain that's how you stop
infections that's how you stop sepsis
that's how you stop
blood uh poisoning and then you've got
bacterial infections in the blood and
then you just die of sepsis in the
hospital it's because your immune system
is all in your blood that's the majority
of it there's a large amount in the gut
not in the intestinal lining and that's
the big issue right there so if you want
details because details matter it's not
your microorganisms
that are inside your gut creating your
immune system it's not good bacteria
that are
inside your intestinal inside your
intestinal tract that doesn't create an
immune system
i'm just letting you know good bacteria
has nothing nothing to do with creating
immune cells so it's important right to
know that
so yes you have you have white blood
cells
your immune system is circulating
throughout every blood vessel around
your gut
every blood vessel around every organ
but it's not inside your intestinal
tract you guys got to get that part
straight anyway
okay you got your you got your lymphatic
system right your lymphocytes
so that's another place that that's
another place right there your lymphatic
system and it circulates around your
torso
most of your lymphatic system is around
your torso right so you got your
lymphocytes
but that's not the lining inside your
gut
that's not your good bacteria
microorganisms inside you god this is so
important to know details matter
because here's what's going to happen
you go to your gut health doctor he's
going to take 20 vials of blood and
destroy your immune system
while he's telling you how your immune
system is all in your gut
you don't see the irony that because i'm
kind of like scratching my head on that
one i'm like okay um
okay you went to the you went to the
doctor
all right he took 20 vials of blood
specialists he's a gut health guy too
functional doctor whoever it is and he
took you know 18 miles of blood
he just annihilated your immune system
for the next three to six months
killed your red blood cells for the next
three to six months it takes a long time
to get these blood cells back it doesn't
take three days
and but yet he's telling you
everything's in your gut so here's some
gut potions here's some gut powders
here's some gut whatever
let's do here's your let's talk about
microbiome
and meanwhile just wiped out your immune
system does that make a lot of sense to
you
so you want you know you wanna you seem
finding me good to see you
chris you said you love this stuff it's
good information isn't it
especially when you're already
compromising here you are sick think
about that right
think about that guys just think about
that for a second
right you're already sick you already
got exomus rises hashimoto's r.a
lupus neurological lyme symptoms
everywhere vertigo tingles and numbness
body pain
aches and pains you feel like you're 100
years old you don't feel good you got
brain fog you got headaches
what else what else jaw pain neck pain
teeth pain what else is going on you
guys you got
all these compromises anyway right
plantar fasciitis digititis you got all
these issues
everywhere your feet you got problems
with your body you're hurting
and what happens is right you get all
that
okay we're already compromised so we go
to the doctor
and then we get eight vials drawn seven
vowels drawn ten vowels drawn
and they're removing our immune system
but see no one knows what's wrong with
you so you go to your good health doctor
he doesn't know why you're sick
he doesn't know you got epstein-barr
shingle sedimentary virus streptococcus
you got toxic heavy metals he doesn't
know that
so you go there he doesn't know what
causes your hashimoto's
but then they remove a whole bunch of
your immune system and then start saying
oh you got to get your gut it's all your
got your immune systems and your gut
it's like okay you know
i mean you get half files
look check out medical mean podcast at
apple podcast check out the blood draw
episode if you guys get a chance check
it out medical mean podcast apple
podcast
the uncensored version and
you know hey guys i'm going to do the
brain meditation tonight so that's on
the podcast check it out medical being
podcasted apple podcast the brain
meditation i'm doing the brain brain
i scheduled the brain meditation for
tonight for me narashini good to see you
and uh it showed it good to see you so
i'm doing the brain meditation let's all
do it together tonight
i'm probably gonna do it three times
tonight i'll probably do it earlier in
the night middle and middle
like a little later and then probably
later in the night too
probably gonna do it midnight is what
i'm gonna do
midnight ish so if you do it at all
you'll catch it at one of those times
and maybe we can all connect maybe we
can all connect while we're doing it
medical media podcast apple podcast
that's the uncensored version
all right mashing some potatoes right
here
if everybody's so smart how come nobody
picked that off the blood draw thing
i've seen people go downhill and lose
their lives over it people with
neurological lyme they almost never
recover
i mean they just get the blood drawn out
of them you know how they start
recovering they stay away from the
doctor for a little while
and they're home they say you know
what's sad because they're not getting
blood drawn
and they're not getting every last bit
of their immune system squeezed out of
them and then told their immune system
is all in their microflora
are you kidding microflora is not your
immune system that's your not your
lymphocytes basophils monocytes
pills because i didn't know
i'm trying you know what i'm scratching
my head here you got all these brilliant
alternative practitioners brilliant
doctors nutritionists
dietitians and everybody else and i'm
scratching my head because microflora is
in neutrophils basophils
lymphocytes whatever monocytes
white blood count killer cells i'm
scratching my head on that one are you
guys
because there's microflora all your
immune cells because i'm kind of
confused here
are you or am i or am i just stupid am i
just stupid
i got it wrong i'm confused on that one
so so when they take your blood
you know why i'm talking about the blood
draw thing because here's what happens a
little time goes by people forget about
it or they didn't learn about it and
they're getting life sucked out of them
and then they're
they're going backwards and they're like
it was the celery juice
i had 16 ounces of sugar juice for a
week and all of a sudden i was feeling
kind of sick you just got eight vials
pulled at the doctor's office that week
i haven't been here in a while what has
it been over a week now you guys i know
how long it's been
but um
but i made a promise to myself that i
was gonna
at me so that means the handle anthony i
was diagnosed with graves disease on mm
info since november my symptoms are so
much
better my thyroid has shrunk so much
incredible like incredible
i mean you know what that right there
that right there
tomorrow morning i'll wake up 4 30 in
the morning quarter five spirit of
compassion is going to be talking to me
and you know what i'm going to think
about that at me
i'll think about that like you know what
we help somebody else with graves
austin have you been writing the next
book yeah busting my arse
busting my arse on that that's what i've
been doing
yeah totally totally
yeah a book that's unmatched
a book that's gonna blow the roof
blow the roof off this house off the
ceiling or whatever
blow the roof off the universe
a book that's gonna blow the roof off
the universe
okay i mean seriously it's it's
it's the book's gonna be
insane uh and i'm only saying that the
spirit of compassion is giving me the
information in my mind is being blown
every second
when my mind's being blown i'm like whoa
so what happens is we get addicted to
adrenaline that's something
well first of all let me just go into
the brain a little bit more just a
little touch more about the brain
let me cover that a little bit more
i'm just making sure these are mashed
and they look really nice i'm mashing
some potatoes right here it's a comfort
food right here for people
it's great i make it for family
too sometimes
so we're told that the brain
needs fat and it's made out of fat wrong
right there i'm sorry but it's wrong
science battles itself constantly by the
way okay
you know what science said about
caffeine
back in the 80s top science science that
could never be disputed
conventional science it could never be
disputed you know what
conventional science said in 1980s
caffeine will cause heart disease
caffeine will worsen all your
neurological diseases
caffeine will cause diabetes make it
worse and worse
right so that was the studies that came
out in the 1980s did you know that
so the studies that came out in the
1980s
were were straight up about caffeine
causing all this damage right
but then the caffeine industry said
we're gonna do our own studies
so as the years go by it's like caffeine
is good for you
cacao is good for you coffee is good for
you
right and so they went against
conventional science whose science is
right
science battles science all the time i'm
actually going to talk about it on
instagram later
if you guys come to me with to instagram
later
i think we're going to really kind of
rip into that a little bit
you guys are are up for it i got some
limes i got some lemon sitting right
here
i'm gonna use that in this so we get
addicted to caffeine our adrenals go
crazy our adrenals go crazy
right here okay we get addicted to fats
we fat ourselves with death there's no
fat in this dish
i get it you guys eat avocado it's okay
eat avocado
you guys eat teeny it's okay those are
healthier fats right they are
some of you guys are eating chicken it's
not the healthiest fat we know that
right chicken fat clog up the heart
kill you down the road right i'm not
saying you can't eat chicken
the reason why medical medium
information is pro people who eat animal
proteins too
is because chicken isn't going to feed
all the viruses
that keep everybody sick so if you're
somebody that's into chicken yeah you
can have a little bit but you eat too
much chicken you can kill yourself
but i've also seen plant-based people
kill themselves by eating too many nut
butters
and too much fats and too much oils
they'll kill themselves too
but get themselves sick down the road
have a heart attack you don't think
plant-based people don't have heart
attacks
yeah they have heart attacks they eat
too much fat everybody's eating too much
fat and then we fat ourselves to death
and now we're told oh god have fat
healthy
much fat as you can your brain needs it
did you know fat stops glucose from
getting to your brain
and your brain dies within 10 seconds of
not
getting that glucose i told you guys
that a couple minutes ago
so
i want to finish this a little bit okay
so when you're doing all the avocado
nuts and seeds nut butters oils
right when you're doing all that
avocados nut butters
oils right when you're doing all that
okay
you're stopping glucose from getting to
the brain at its maximum
so it's always like a like a lesser
amount getting to the brain
and you get hungry fat makes you want to
eat more and more fat people say sugar
makes me want to eat more and more sugar
oh no that's sugar with fat
that makes you want to eat more and more
sugar that's sugar with
fat that makes you want to eat more and
more sugar that's what that is okay
that's important to know got some mashed
potatoes here i'm going to put some lime
in here
mashed potatoes in the pan right
see if we could squeeze this slime i'm
having a problem here with this one this
one's slippery
potato can be a little slippery when
it's on your hands
tik tok the handle not the app
tick tock the handle says
seeds so that you're talking about flax
seeds
look you can they're healthy they're
healthy fats flax seeds and avocado if
you guys are gonna eat fats that's the
ones to do sesame seeds
hemp seeds pumpkin seeds those are the
best ones sunflower seeds are good too
right
you can do that but keep in mind if
you're sick
too much fat is not going to let you
heal all the way
animal protein or plant-based keep that
in mind
animal protein or plant-based animal
protein people are now eating avocados
and nuts and seeds they didn't used to
eat
eat all that but now they do
and but keep in mind about this this is
important
that
got some mashed potatoes in here a
little bit i'm gonna put some peas in
here too
keep in mind that the more fat you dump
in your system
the less glucose gets to the brain so
you're gonna have eating
like eating issues you're gonna be like
i'm hungry
all the time that's your brain saying
i'm hungry because you're not letting me
get enough glucose
you're not giving me three mangoes when
i need in the morning you're not giving
me the heavy metal detox smoothie with
the glucose with the bananas
you're you know in the industry wants
you afraid of bananas be open-hearted
good to see you
the industry wants you afraid of bananas
right
the industry wants you afraid of that
they want you they don't want you eating
bananas
they don't watch eating bananas no way
can add a little bit more water to this
that's what i'm gonna do the industry
doesn't want you having bananas they
think it's too much sugar
so what's going to happen is you're
going to be on fat fat fat
and then you're eventually going to eat
the bad sugar is what you're going to do
you're going to have the bad
sugars what's going to happen so
adding a little touch of water to the
mashed potatoes which will eventually
dry up
but you need it when you're putting in
some peas
and that's a thing there too so i'm
going to pop in some peas into this
pan's going to get nice and hot there we
go
you have to add a little bit of moisture
into the pan or you get a hash brown
a hash brown pancake so that's what
you'll get
ashley kevin good to see you i said no
no it's so nice to see you too as well
okay
so we're gonna make some mashed potatoes
like we're doing
i have some lettuce here too i just put
some lime in there i'm gonna pop some
lemon in a little bit as well
it's a basic dish so what happens is if
you're not getting critical critical
needed nutrients to the brain
on a regular basis the brain will go
deficient and if your brain goes
deficient of glucose if it goes
deficient because
we're eating too much fat fat
blocks sugar from entering brain cells
but the survival of life allows some to
enter
some to enter but we go into a
deficiency
is what we do that deficiency makes us
now hungry and then
we're doing more fat or bad sugar with
fat because their body's like why am i
sugar craving but yet you're eating fat
with sugar why am i sugar craving but
you're eating fat with sugar
you're still blocking the glucose from
getting to the brain
is what you're doing see how it works
that's how it works
tom posky says do carnival peep
carnivore
people survive because of sugar in the
meat
it's how they survive sugar in the meat
it's not enough
it's not enough it's not enough because
because you got fat in the meat too but
you survive on carnivore
you can you can survive on carnivore
because
the the sugar meats meats meat has sugar
in it i love when people say well i'm on
a sugar-free diet i'm eating just meat
i'm like that's funny
because the cow had a lot of sugar in
its blood
and that red meat is all sugar and
that's what that is
sugar and eggs or sugar you know why
there's a lot of sugar in eggs
you guys know that eggs are sweet when
you have an egg they're sweet did you
know cheese is sweet too
let's cover the egg the egg's an
important one as far as like sweetness
okay when you have
an egg you'll notice it's kind of sweet
right it is there's a reason why it's
sweet
it's sweet because glucose is how the
chicken
the chick can actually start to become
a chicken like grow develop
glucose is critical you don't have
glucose
ain't gonna be a baby chick listen to
the bo
the podcast episode medical being
podcasted apple podcast i'm juggling a
lot of things here you guys
forgive me forgive me listen to the
fruit fear episode two if you're afraid
of bananas if you'd be you know if
you're lost in the world of fat and
protein
this is an anti-animal protein uh talk
we're doing right now this is an
anti-plant-based
vegetarian vegan talk it's not it at all
you can fat yourself to death as a vegan
and a plant-based person
you can still get a heart attack down
the road you can still stay sick and not
heal
you can still just you can easily fat
yourself to death you can salt yourself
to death
you can you can do a lot of things that
aren't good
and here's the deal right
the details matter if someone's stuck in
this vicious cycle and they're just in
this vicious cycle vicious cycle they
can't break out of it they're overeating
they don't feel good they're overeating
they're told to eat you know healthier
fats they're eating more of that too
but they don't know how to break from
this they don't know how to recover
all these little pieces of information
and critical needed details all matter
right now that we're talking about
okay so what i like to do
right by the way you guys medical
meeting morning challenge morning
cleanse challenge
this week coming up it's gonna be
thursday friday
saturday that's what i'm shooting for
the medical medium morning cleanse
challenge it's going to get crazy i'm
going to be doing lives on thursday
lives on friday lives on saturday
we're going to be doing the medical
medium morning cleanse challenge
i haven't promoted it yet i haven't
posted about it yet but
i'm just giving you guys a 4-1-1 that's
the goal right there
the more stress you're under the more
glucose you need not the more fat you
need
the more stress you're under the more
sugar you need for your brain
but we end up craving pizza so we crave
the bad
sugar we end up creating ice cream so we
crave the bad sugar
we end up craving uh spaghetti
because because we we you know but
there's fat on everything with this
sugar
your pizza is fat and sugar so the sugar
never gets to the brain
mashed potatoes are coming out really
nice right now
so the sugar the glucose never gets to
your brain because you're doing too much
fat
but we end up craving the pizza again
and then again and again and we eat
ourselves sick and then we crave it
again and we eat ourselves sick
then it's nachos night then we're doing
nachos
because we're craving all that cheese
and that corn chip
we're creating nachos we're creating
we're craving that
that corn chip and the cheese then we're
craving tacos because we're craving that
cheese on top of your corn corn tortilla
your corn shell
taco shell
then you're craving a hot dog a
cheeseburger because cheese in the bun
all that sugar
and then it keeps your adrenaline
pumping because your adrenaline's like
holy crap
you're gonna kill us you're putting so
much fat in your system you're gonna
kill our heart that's what you're gonna
do
you're you're gonna you're gonna destroy
our hearts
that's what you're doing i got a heart
right here
you keep on doing the pizzas you keep on
doing the ice cream
you got so much fat going on here that
your adrenals are now pumping
24 7. there's your adrenals you're
pumping 24 7.
thin out the blood thin out the blood
that person's killing themselves
we gotta thin out the blood because the
heart can't pump through all that fat
the heart can't do it right austin like
the heart can't pump all that fat
that's how it works
so your adrenals are pumping got a lot
juggling around here
this is getting crazy over here your
adrenals right here you see this
you guys in clubhouse the adrenals i'm
holding right here
they're jumping in adrenaline because
it's trying to thin out your blood did
you know that your adrenaline is a blood
thinner
you dump in more fat your adrenals got
to release all this adrenaline and now
you're addicted to fat and adrenaline
all of the same
mix you can't break it
fat high is real maggie portola says
oh damn right it's real ho ho ho ho is
it real
i got to put some you guys i got to put
some peas in this really quick
just please bear with me you don't have
to have a lot of peas
these are some frozen peas i'm gonna put
some here not all of these this is a
pack of frozen peas
right there you go
cali smith i'd love to hear some tips
on how to get yourself to eat more of
the healing foods
when you don't enjoy them
you got to bring in the fruit because
fruit is satisfying in many ways because
it's so sweet
it's actually not really that sweet when
you think about it a banana doesn't have
that much sugar in it but it's but still
it's sweet
sweetness counts when it comes down to
that papayas mangoes do some watermelon
watermelon you guys i hope you're
starting up the watermelons you do that
on an empty stomach in the morning is a
great time to do it so i got some peas
in here i'm gonna put a little lemon in
here too this is coming out really good
you got to get some fruit in there and
you got to get some mineral salts in
there
trace mineral salts the celery juice
takes time to learn how to love
the the celery juice for a lot of people
you know it doesn't seem like it's fun
to eat
drink it's fun to drink so i got some
peas in here i'm gonna get these
[Music]
cooking got some mashed potato some
beautiful piece in here if you guys can
see that right there you guys see
it's right there this is a comfort food
if you want to put sea salt in there
because you
again a lot of people are going to eat
salt every day it doesn't matter what
medical medium says doesn't matter if
medical medium says be careful about
your salt so you're going to eat it so
just
put some sea salt in there if it's going
to do could put some black pepper in
there if you really want
you can do that cayenne pepper is a
great one for here too
putting cayenne pepper in here onion
powder is a great one
you can really make this taste so good
taste buds change over time when you
incorporate pieces in we need some
willpower too
takes a little time to get the willpower
going where
taste buds change they develop
you end up liking those mangoes you end
up liking those grapes cherries apples
bananas
peaches plums nectarines melons
honeydew melons crenshaw melons
watermelons
need i say more
but we're taught we're taught to keep
our addictions around did you know that
we're taught that if you want to lose
weight you better just stop eating
and you better get on caffeine and then
now you're on caffeine all day long and
you stopped eating and now you're eating
your one meal a day at the end of the
day that ain't gonna last long
you'll burn those adrenals out they'll
come crashing down down the road
all kinds of problems will happen you'll
age fast because you're running on
caffeine all the time
your adrenals will they will not forgive
you
when you caffeine them to crazy land
when you caffeine your adrenals to crazy
land when you caffeine the heck out of
them
over the years then when you do eat
you're dumping in all that fat whether
it's plant-based or animal-based
you know spirit of compassion is the
voice of reason not me
i'm just i'm just delivering the message
adrenals are working hard anyway you're
up against a little bit of stress
you had a breakup maybe you're falling
out with a friendship
maybe a business partner maybe a family
member
maybe a sibling some stress there our
adrenals are already
under stress were you driving on the
road and had a little accident boom your
adrenals are running for a day and a
night
we already have adrenals pumping all the
time we already get little bits of fight
or flight all the time they're working
overtime so all of a sudden let's just
dump a whole bunch of caffeine in there
and just blow them the out
just blow those adrenals out just
annihilate them let's just do that
now make sure let's just do a lot of
high fat too and soak up that adrenaline
and then get it you know addicted with
adrenaline get dictated with the fat
let's make sure we do lots of chocolate
too
let's go into our happy place and tank a
bunch of chocolate
i get it i get it life is hard but we
have to do some things to take care of
ourselves too
we got to do some celery juice dr fon
might as well face it we're addicted
i get it so you dump
all the fat in your adrenals are pumping
to thin it out to try to save your life
every day your heart is trying to pump
your blood and it's really
thick and it's trying to pump it pump
and pump and pump it but there's so much
fat in the blood
that's hard to pump it and then adrenal
drainage
adrenals have to release more adrenaline
to thin out that blood and thin out that
blood
and then all to try to get glucose to
your brain
always try to get some glucose here
because guess what in five
seconds if the brain doesn't have
glucose it starts its journey of death
in 10 seconds it can die 10 seconds
without glucose your brain can start
dying
tissue when your brain starts dying
without glucose 10 seconds
10 seconds
yep yep
less than that 10 seconds is just
starts with that lesson so we're taught
to be high chasers are you guys high
chasers
right i got some peas in here they're
they're i put frozen peas in here such a
simple dish frozen peas come on we're
getting frozen peas
alex lange aw sometimes i feel better
when i eat fat
like avocados or seeds sometimes i feel
worse
alex good to see you honored you're here
what happens is when we eat fat
we get the adrenaline surge we get the
adrenaline surge
because the adrenaline has to thin out
thin out the fat it has to thin the
viscosity to level us
break it down the consistency has to
break that fat consistency down
that's what happens um
you know basically
so you need gasoline
to break down that butter
i'm not telling you eat gasoline that's
not at all what i'm saying is your
adrenaline acts like gasoline
to break up that butter you drop down
some bread and butter
you eat a stick of butter you have
butter in a dish you got butter in your
pan
you got i don't care how wholesome the
butter is i don't care i don't care if
you went out there
and milked the cow and churns your own
butter
it's still going to be filling up your
bloodstream so that your adrenals have
to
thin it out it has to thin it out
because when you have too much fat in
your bloodstream
too much fat in your bloodstream you
can't get all the glucose you need to
the brain so you go
you go you go 50 glucose to the brain
now you're 30 glucose to the brain
now you're less
i get it again medical medium the
medical medium channels
they're not so fun because it's when you
go when you go and you're looking at
other stuff it's like oh that makes
sense the immune system's all in your
microbiome no it's not but it make
it just it seems like a happy place wait
a minute i need lots of fats because i
need fats for my brain
that's great caffeine is actually good
for me i should do some matcha tea and
everything because i'm tall
it's good for me i can have some vinegar
on everything i eat because apple cider
vinegar
is good for me it's like it's endless
it's endless
misinformation to put everybody in kind
of a happy station of health so hey
i'm doing healthy foods i'm doing and
then when you get sick
you're totally effed over totally
by all the people that actually was just
like giving you all that that meaning
like the people at the top giving you
all that information that's wrong
people die of strokes and heart attacks
all the time at all ages whether a
plant-based vegan vegetarian alike
pescetarian i don't know come up with
something else right animal protein keto
carnivore
carnivore i i i worry about carnivore
the carnivore diet for people
i worry about people with it because
carnivore diets the atkins diet and it
and it really killed a lot of people
um that's what i was told
you know the it's just i was told that
by a lot of doctors this is looking good
here
over the years that they saw a decline
in their patients with done
unlike the atkins diet i was told that
all the time so this is done i'm going
to put this in a bowl
the carnivore diet's the same thing it's
just a remake of it
you know reason why people feel a little
bit better they feel a little bit better
um this is a real comfort for sure but
here's the thing the butter's not in
here
okay the butter's not in here now if
you're gonna be someone and you're gonna
eat that anyway and i'm not gonna be
able to stop you from eating it every
day three times a day right i'm like i'm
just telling you maybe bring it down
right i'm not trying to say i'm just
trying to punish you guys
be the food police or something that's
not it i'm just saying if you're sick
and you've got symptoms you've got aches
and pains you've got chronic fatigue
your brain fog is off the chart you've
got
anxiety crippling anxiety you've got
depression you've got depersonalization
you've got
whatever whatever is going on lower the
fats
yeah you need other tools too you need
your cellar juice you need your heavy
metal detox smoothies
you need your supplement protocols you
need to know how to take the b12 like
people are afraid to take b12 because
like well my b12 registered pretty good
on my blood test well
i talk to doctors all the time and i'm
like well what is your brain
what blood tests determine what what
kind of b12 is actually in your brain
there's no blood test that could
determine that
did they stick a needle inside your
skull right into your brain draw it out
and be like yeah your brain
brain has plenty of b12 nobody knows
nobody knows how the central nervous
system works out there but what i get
from spirit of the compassion is you've
got to have your b12
that's got to be the right one of course
that's the vimergy by the way i'm not
sponsored but that's the vimergy b12
so
i'm just saying that a lot of people are
taught a lot of bad habits and we're not
taught anything from the start that's
that we're not taught
how to eat right from the start that's
the whole thing
you know what's funny if you were taught
how to eat right from the start
okay if you were taught how to eat right
from the very beginning
all right you guys you would
you would there'd be a whole different
game going on
whole different game going on so if
everybody was throwing the cheeseburger
if you were taught how to eat right
right from the start
for years like everything the
institutions taught us how to eat right
medical science and research taught us
how to eat right which they don't
obviously right
institutions taught us how to eat right
school systems taught us how to eat
right
our families taught us how to eat right
because of that being passed down right
if we all knew if we all knew how to
take care of ourselves
well a couple things would go wrong
terribly the medical industry would just
collapse so they can't have that they
need you to eat wrong
you know and i never did i ever tell you
guys
there's a whole bunch of plants in
alternate medicine you know what plants
are
no plants are there experts
planted in alternative medicine by
conventional
the conventional industry the medical
industry to try to keep on
feeding people the bad trends and and
ingraining it in everybody
so that you stay sick so there's molds
and plants all in the industry
alternative industry you guys don't even
know it
the friendliest faces you guys have no
idea
and they they were given money they were
given deals deals were made contracts
were signed
and they were put out there to make sure
that you hear the same old crap
your brain needs lots of fat that's a
great way to make sure your alzheimer's
gets so much
worse down the road you can add hot
pepper to this right here so i got some
hot peppers in my hand
this is um some super chilis i grew
these myself
so some super chilies there garlic
powder is another thing you can put on
here onion powder is another thing you
can put on here
but that's mashed potatoes with peas
the peas aren't cooked to death they're
just you know they're lightly cooked in
here right
and just so you guys know i'm doing the
medical medium morning cleanse
challenge thursday friday saturday it's
from cleanse to heal
so if you guys don't have the book you
might want to pick up the book for the
morning cleanse
so amazon.com1699 it costs more to print
the book out it's a medical textbook
with over 200 symptoms and conditions
i'm just giving you a 4-1-1 on how this
book works you can get it free at the
library too if you can get a copy that
way
thursday morning doing the medical
medium morning cleanse challenge
it's from cleanse of heal so if you got
you know if you don't have a copy maybe
grab one and borrow one from a friend or
ask someone to share theirs
a lot of people have two copies so
anyway amazon.com is on sale too in the
us and it's on sale i think other places
as well
let's get the heart out of the way here
and i'm doing the brain meditation
tonight if you guys want to join in
it's not going to be like online or
anything i'm just going to be sitting
sitting in my living room actually with
the brain meditation i'll be laying down
in my living room and i'm going to go to
medical media podcast at apple podcast
and i'm going to listen to the brain
meditation episode
i'm going to do it three times tonight i
need it
desperately personally because i'm doing
double time on writing a book and trying
to get the deadline into the publisher
i'm i mean i am working
it's why you guys saw me disappear
because when the deadline
gets worse and worse and closer and
closer i start freaking out
became working harder and harder harder
and my adrenals are going
my adrenals are doing this but you know
what i'm doing for my
stress is i am doing the mineral salts
let me show you what i'm doing
let me let me show you guys what i'm
doing okay then i'm doing it right
here's what i'm doing i'm doing my
celery juice
course right okay i'm doing my b12
that's what i'm doing
i'm cranking my microc cranking it
for my stress right now because i'm
trying to get the book deadline in boom
book deadline done
right i got the magnesium going right
that's the energy
magnesium right there okay that's what
i'm doing to
manage my stress right now i'm doing
like for me you ask your doctor what's
right for you but for me
i'm doing six capsules of magnesium
three capsules twice a day
sometimes i'll do four twice a day i'm
doing 10 capsules twice a day
of the micro sea of emergency i'm not
sponsored i'm just telling you what guys
i'm doing to manage stress
i'm doing six dropper fulls of b12 right
now every day
to manage my stress because of the book
deadline i can't wait to try oh my god i
can't wait to get that thing in because
then i can tell you guys what it is
um that's what i'm doing that's just a
few things i'm doing just letting you
know
so listen doing the brain meditation
tonight medical queen podcast alpha
podcast but here's where i'm going i am
going to
ig instagram i'm turning tic tac back on
and i'm turning clubhouse back on
and i'm going to instagram i'll be there
in probably 10 minutes i just gotta
clean up the set
just a little bit and get ready um
i'm in a spicy mood tonight so i don't
know what's going to happen on ig
someone said the other day you think you
watched him on youtube and facebook
well and then you think he's going to do
the same thing on ig well no he never
does
something happens in ig and i got a bone
to pick with science
and research lately because they're
screwing up everywhere everywhere
science research is screwing up
everywhere so i got a bone to pick with
designs research probably going to talk
about it on ig
i love you guys i'll see you then okay a
few minutes
so just keep on looking out instagram
medical medium page i love you guys
dearly
and we're going to cover this topic
again too because i know i was
you know what on i'll talk about
more of the emotional eating stuff and
the overeating stuff a little bit more
margaret valentine good to see you
awesome you guys on tick-tock i love you
too
and i'll talk to you guys soon