say it again arugula potato asparagus
salad it's gonna be really good so a new
recipe
for the medical medium new edition can't
wait for you guys to
read this book that's the recipe right
there you see the potatoes in there but
i got a lot going on right here so i'm
excited so it's gonna be great and you
know what we're talking about we're
talking about
why you should avoid certain foods
and how come not just why how come what
are they
what to avoid if you want to make it to
the finish line
if you want to make it to that place of
hey i'm better
i got all these symptoms better i got my
condition better i got my hashimoto's
better i got my lupus better i got my
lime better
whatever it is you're dealing with got
me my acne better my eczema better
it's good to know what you should avoid
and for what reason
we're gonna talk about that so this is
gonna be a fun one and i'm making some
food right now you guys i better get
going on this food because
this is going to take a minute so i'm
making arugula
asparagus potato salad it's going to be
fun good good to see you guys
uh sally arnold great to see you amazing
so glad you're here
love you too um
and uh incredible incredible
so look you guys i'm gonna be chopping
up some stuff right here i'm gonna start
steaming
some things i'm gonna steam some
brussels sprouts so let me start
getting those going i'm going to cut the
brussels sprouts in half
okay so i'm going to do and i'm going to
steam them up cut in half so
they'll steam up quicker that way too
bettina says i got my hashimoto's better
after following your protocol
incredible so proud of you very very
proud of you
okay because um you can take yourself as
far as you want to go with your healing
process you
just you just have to do the stuff
you've got to do the work
i'm chopping some brussels sprouts right
here
so we're talking about why foods
cause problems why you should avoid them
what foods are they and i'll tell you
right now okay you guys
if you don't know what foods to avoid
you're just gonna get yourself in
trouble and
end up doing those foods again we're all
not perfect
you know we're going to get into trouble
we're going to eat something we're
probably not supposed to eat or whether
we know it or not
it's just going to happen but i want you
guys to know
what to look out for keep an eye on
stuff you know so that you're staying
safe when you
want to be well if you guys want to make
a choice and say look i want to eat this
food i know
aw says this food isn't good i know aw
says this food is going to be a problem
but i want to eat it well you're making
the choice
okay you're making the choice that's
you're right but what if you don't know
you know why everybody starts eating
gluten again
yeah i'm off gluten i stopped gluten but
yet they ate gluten
yeah i'm i'm gluten free i'm gluten free
i had it last
week but i'm gluten free
yeah i know i had gluten like twice last
month you know i have gluten like three
times a week but i'm still trying to be
gluten free you know
you know why people don't stay
completely gluten free because they
really don't
know what it causes what it contributes
to
what the problems are when you're eating
gluten and why they're sick and what
their symptoms are caused by
if you don't know any of that you're
just gonna be like yeah yeah what the
heck i'll have some gluten right now let
me do that
let me do that somebody said disappeared
where are you
um i'm on youtube live so if you guys
get booted or kicked off or the
or the the app is acting weird or
something there's a glitch on facebook
just head over to youtube
because i'm youtube live right now um
michelle you ate arugula asparagus and
potatoes today
whoa i can't believe it then again you
eat really good
i know you eat really well um
i know that so
so anyway you guys so what you're
looking at right here is you're looking
at a meal that doesn't have radical fats
because okay michelle sounds like he
didn't have any radical fats today it
sounds like he didn't have any milk
cheese butter
eggs sounds like he didn't have any
bacon it sounds like he didn't have any
kind of pork right
didn't sound doesn't sound like he had
any chicken or any beef it doesn't sound
like you had nut butters
doesn't sound like you had you know
seeds and nuts and sunflower seeds and
hemp seeds and
peanut butter and macadamia nut butter
it doesn't sound like you had any of
that doesn't sound like you had olives
doesn't sound like you have oils
coconut oil sesame oil olive oil tahini
right
doesn't sound like you had any of that
and
but i know that a lot of people do i
mean think about what everybody's eating
and maybe as
people have avocado toast then they'll
take a couple tablespoons of peanut
butter
and throw it in their smoothie maybe
they'll throw it on their acai bowl
maybe they'll throw it on their oatmeal
right did you guys have oatmeal this
morning any of you
okay and you'll throw fats on there now
see i'm
i'm not gonna be able to stop you guys
from eating fats every day you just guys
most of you guys are just gonna do it
and you're gonna do it continuously
every single day and there's there's no
stopping you it's not like
i'm not trying to be like you know
a problem and be hey you shouldn't be
doing that shouldn't be doing that it's
not it it's just that
it's good to take a break when you can
maybe take a day off
maybe do one of the cleanses and cleanse
the heel and and take a
week off maybe do the 369 advanced and
and all that
because what happens you guys are doing
all this fat
and all that fat builds up in the
arteries all that fat builds up in the
veins and that's what happens there
michelle says i got my hashimoto
antibodies down from 404 to 33 following
you
amazing i'm so proud of you i'm so so
proud of you
um what happens is when you're doing the
fats every day when you do the pork when
you do the bacon when you do the milk
cheese butter when you do
the nut butter cisco is plant-based too
this isn't
you know just because we say we're
plant-based say we're
vegan right or say vegetarian or
something or simple plant-based right
it doesn't mean you're safe from getting
all that plaque and all that buildup
inside your heart inside your valves
inside your veins
because you're not it builds up in
everybody everybody gets it in there
next thing you know it
they hit the microscope shoved up their
leg through a vein
it's going up there they're looking for
collapsed arteries collapsed veins all
that stuff
next thing you know it you're getting
stints put in and
you know and you get in trouble so it's
good to
take some take some breaks on the fats
because guess what there's fat in
everything
there's omegas in these brussels sprouts
right here
yep there's omegas in the brussels
sprouts that i'm putting in here
there's a magazine here so i got some
brussels sprouts here i'm going to do
some asparagus too i'm steaming up
brussels sprouts
steaming up asparagus that's what i'm
doing right now
let me get these going here steaming
these up
any advice to heal adrenal fatigue
and this book is packed with that
information there's an adrenal
fatigue chapter in this new edition
check it out amazon.com
the book's coming out literally in a
couple weeks link is in the description
um it's really comprehensive on the
adrenals of how to restore them this is
where the adrenal snacks came from
all of that so many ways of of
recovering adrenals and i'll talk about
adrenals a little bit too
why i got you guys here i'll do that
look you can go to get the book out of
the library if you want when the book
comes out just ask your library to stock
it or find it or something
and try to get it out for free if you if
you don't have the money to
to get the book right now
you can totally do the library that's
fine guys i'm putting asparagus in here
to see you know chopping up some nice
asparagus
steaming up these brussels sprouts
steaming up these asparagus
this is great you guys just came on
making the arugula
potato asparagus salad
all right so i'm going to steam these up
got it on max so we're doing that
noelle now only have i healed so much
not only have i sealed it so much you
indeed you open to the divine
to know who i really am that is the
greatest gift so basically
incredible that's incredible i mean you
know what one thing i can tell you is
when you're healing symptoms and
conditions
like you did and then you spiritually
grow and you spiritually heal
and you spiritually move forward and you
know you learn
who you truly are and your soul heals
from wounds you know a lot of people
have betrayal inside their soul they got
a lot of hurt they got a lot of
broken trust they have a lot of
different things that have happened in
their life emotionally
and they go through hard times and it
also can come
side by side with chronic illness any
kind of chronic illness you know when
when you're healing that chronic
illness you start healing everything and
you just really
get in touch with who you are and heal
and i'm so proud of you
i really am so you guys let's talk about
foods
not to eat so joanne says i love all
these foods but hard to
hard for me to eat so look you take one
day at a time you eat what you can
you feel like leslie says five to six
years following no no foods but
digestion
has tanked why will this be hard to
digest
so what's going on in your life are you
really stressed out and know that if
we're really stressed out our guts
don't want to digest properly i mean if
anything's happening any kind of stress
any kind of financial stress any kind of
other stress
anything like that and our digestive
system gets really
really um exhausted from that you know
our nerves our vagus nerve gets affected
so a lot of times when we go through
anything in life
any kind of any kind of trauma any kind
of struggle our
vagus nerve tightens up it tightens up
and our digestive system just has a
difficult time
um are you eating a lot of grains those
are little actually you know a lot more
difficult to digest
are you eating a lot of meat are you
eating a lot of fat
all that's difficult to digest so is
your
digestive system tanking
because there's any milk cheese butter
ice cream
eggs bacon too much chicken too much
beef any processed foods at all
any any of that maybe you're eating
really good but you're
you're eating too much avocado um think
you know just i'm trying to help you be
your own detective here
and are you doing chocolate nutritional
yeast are you doing vinegar you're doing
apple cider vinegar are you doing
caffeine
all these things can really tank the
digestive system
and they can tank them over time they
can do that they can
they can tank the digestive tract over
time so if you're doing any kind of
caffeine or chocolate you can tank your
digestive tract because
not only does the chocolate is at high
in fat but
what happens is the caffeine hits the
adrenals really hard and once your
adrenals start to weaken
start to weaken start to weaken
digestion starts to weaken the liver
starts to weaken
because when our adrenals are really
overrun and overtaxed by caffeine
our liver just starts to get overburden
overburden overburden so then the
digestion eventually starts to fall
apart
but really i mean have you tried the
monoeating cleanse
have you tried the mono eating cleanse
have you tried the potato monolithic
cleanse
the banana papaya monolining cleanse
have you tried any of that so that's
what i've always recommended other
people
to do doctors and stuff doctors come to
me and they'll be like what do i do
about
this patient and stuff with mono eating
cleanse and they say well yeah we're
doing it it's starting to work
and and what happens is it's easy on the
digestion it helps you restore your
adrenals back it helps to restore your
digestion
but you might want to consider you might
want to think about
what are you doing like are you doing a
lot of fats is that happening
are you doing is that going on um
and it's not just the fats it's even
more than that is there vinegar in there
kills the gastric
gastric glands so when we do acetic acid
like apple cider vinegar
even if we do it once every couple of
weeks we basically
wipe our stomach lands clean
in a negative way we just we just bash
them we just
wipe them out so they're they're exhaust
they don't have any more gastric juice
because they
they lost it all from the acetic acid so
when we drop down a little bit of
vinegar
a little bit acetic acid our stomach
glands they just
spill their guts they smell everything
they have left
and and then they're just done that's
acetic acid it does say i'll just have
some apple cider vinegar here let me
just
let me just do some apple cider vinegar
and meanwhile
the stomach glands they're just these
tiny little glands
that produce your stomach acid your
gastric acid these
tiny little glands and when you throw in
that apple cider vinegar
they almost explode i mean literally
did not literally almost explode but
they do explode every gastric juice they
can possibly muster it up and they just
spill it all out and then they're just
white they're wiped out
and and they sit there wiped out and
then
it takes days to restore and then we do
apple cider vinegar again or vinegar
again
and and it takes a lot of mineral salts
are you doing enough celery juice
are you doing celery juice every single
day are you restoring
those stomach lands and getting them
back so yeah our digestion can get wiped
out it can get wiped out easy if we've
already had
years and years of high fat years and
years of vinegar
years and years of caffeine if you did
caffeine 10 years ago
and you don't do it anymore and you did
alcohol it's 15 years ago
and you did nutritional yeast that you
did apple cider vinegar
10 years ago and you know and you've
already been on the high fat
year after year who hasn't everybody is
the digestive system is going to get rot
wonky wonky wonky wonky and then when
you try to heal it you try to heal it
a lot of fats are being used it's like
hey avocado's healthy let me eat that
every single day
let me make avocado toast hey nut
butters are healthy let me do
lots of nut butter let me do almond milk
all that almond milk all the oat milk
right
and then our finally everything just
goes
done everybody's like done just
exhausted your liver is exhausted
adrenals are exhausted stomach glands
are exhausted and everything's just
done and that's what happens and then
you might have some pathogens going on
you might have some streptococcus
might have a little bit of strep like my
little strep
model right here there it is
what people don't realize and science
research doesn't know
is bacteria and viruses
there's a little virus right here okay
bacteria and viruses eat food so when
you're doing some gluten
when you're doing a little gluten this
is a piece of lettuce it's not gluten so
i don't have any gluten in this in this
house but say this is a piece of gluten
right here
right so it's floating around floating
around it's in your liver
or it's in your bloodstream and you got
that streptococcus oh you don't have
strep
i heard somebody just say they don't
have strep i did
and i didn't hear it myself through my
own ear i heard it from spirit of
compassion
somebody just said spirit of compassion
said that
they don't have strep so this is a waste
of their time
that's what spirit just said to me um i
should probably tell you guys more about
what spirit says to me as i got to do
all these lives it's actually really
hard um
but guess what you do have strep if you
had strep throat when you were a kid
you got strep got acne you got strep if
you ever had a uti
yeast infection you got strep any kind
of chronic sinusitis you got strep
everybody's got strep even if the
symptoms don't come out
uh bladder infection kidney infection
whatever
and is that gluten swimming around in
you
right that strep bacteria likes to
gobble
it up i don't know if this can actually
and it just it absorbs it right up
it absorbs it through the membrane the
gluten went right in there how do you
like that
the strep bacteria just absorb the
gluten wow
and munching that right up munching that
right up right and then all of a sudden
that streptococcus gets nice and strong
nice and strong and then it goes up into
the derma a little bit higher and all of
a sudden whoa i got cystic acne now
i just broke out with a little cystic
acne here a little cystic acne here acne
here
and that's because of strep but guess
what the doctor's going to tell you
you're hormonal and that's why you broke
out with your
with your acne because they don't know
it's streptococcus they'll think it's
hormones because they blame everybody on
hormones everything's on hormones
hormones hormones
and but what happens is if you're going
through a period of time where you're
actually
are hormonal in a sense for your cycle
or menstruation or anything like that
you your immune systems drop so when
your immune systems drop the strep can
get stronger
that does happen but it's not the
hormones causing it it's not how it
works
cystic acne isn't something that for
centuries
women had this is new acne
is actually new so you mean to tell me
all those hundreds of years women didn't
have hormones
did women just develop hormones in the
last 60 years because i'm confused about
that one
did women just develop hormones in the
last 80 years
because i'm confused because guess what
acne wasn't even on the list anyway
got some bacteria here and what that
bacteria does
that bacteria loves to eat
viruses love to eat got a little bit of
epstein-barr in you whoa it loves the
love to eat that gluten yum yum yum
there's over 30 there's over 30
varieties of shingles there's over 60
varieties of epstein barr
and there's and there's over 50 groups
of streptococcus and hundreds and
hundreds of strains of strep
and everybody's passing them around
i got a friend that's like i just don't
feel good these days i don't feel good i
feel really tired my throat's really
sore
i said what you've been doing i don't
know i don't know why i have this i
don't know what's going on and
what's happening did you meet anybody
yeah i'm dating this new person
i said you are yeah dating this new
person and
doing a lot of kissing i'm like okay
well
did it come on after that yeah it did
well i think you need to clean up that
strap
i think you picked up a new strip you
know um
you can pick them up from the public
bathrooms you can pick them up from the
public toilets you can pick them up from
restaurants
i mean people get more probably the most
strep comes from
relationships and the and then i'd
probably say the second
is public places like restaurants
people prepping your food um
just strap just go strap just drips off
of people's heads
chefs in the kitchen they're just the
kitchens are 100 degrees in a lot of
these restaurants and
sweat is dripping off their temples with
strep in it and dropping in everybody's
food
here you go you got your you got your
salad here it is
get it to the table as fast as possible
ring that bell
are you guys i'm steaming up some
asparagus and brussels sprouts
jennifer can you tell me about oxalates
my friend says they are in plants
fruit that makes her sick
well may as well just quit all fruits
and vegetables
never eat any fruits and vegetables ever
again and then you'll end up on the
carnivore diet where it's just
meat and uh my god
then you'll just age really fast because
there's no antioxidants there's no
anything
so i'll give you a little rundown on
oxalates oxalates is a theory
it's a theory with no science behind it
so
that's one of the problems with all the
theories
is they get everybody in trouble um
there's no real scientific study since
everybody wants a study hey everybody
wants to study here study there's no
scientific study that actually has shown
or proven
in any way on any level that an oxalate
causes any kind of issues with someone's
health not even possible
they haven't even found a link they
haven't even found
once there's not one study that can show
someone getting oxalates from some kind
of food and having a problem it doesn't
exist
so it's a theory number one number two
um oxalates yeah they don't cause a
problem
um but and it oxalates and fruits and
vegetables don't cause a problem
but you know what happens is when you're
really sick or you're you're
you're you you're really toxic and you
eat some fruits you eat some
leafy greens you eat some vegetables
you're gonna start cleansing possibly if
you're really toxic and your liver is
really toxic
and you might experience something but
yet if you gobble down some eggs
the eggs just turn to glue and they seem
like they go fine they seem like they
work fine you eat some eggs it's like
it's just turns into this gluey glop
that sits in the middle of your stomach
and
sits in the middle of your digestive
system and finds its way down over time
and that gluey glop feels kind of easy
and comforting and feels all right but
when you're really toxic
and you're you're you know you're eating
you're eating arugula look at this
beautiful arugula right here you're
eating
butter leaf lettuce every day and you're
really toxic and you're eating
you're eating basil it's antiviral
antibacterial compounds you're eating
basil
you're going to start cleaning some
stuff up you you have some onion which
you're gonna get that sulfur that kills
bugs
and you're doing your lemons right and
you're cleansing your liver
you're gonna start feeling something if
you're really really toxic and you know
what if somebody put a spook in your
head
like oh it's oxalates that's what's
going on
meanwhile the funniest thing is the
oxalate theory comes from people
that the people they don't even know
what's wrong with people they don't even
know why people are sick they don't know
why people have hashimoto's they don't
know why people are sick with anything
they don't know why people have any
conditions
and so why is everybody an expert
why is everybody an expert about things
like oxalates and leptins
come on you're an expert you don't know
why people are sick
oh they're sick because of processed
foods oh that's that's that's
sick from processed foods that's why
they're sick
there's a lot of 80 year olds eating
processed foods their whole life they
ain't sick
somehow there's 85 year olds 89 year
olds eating gluten their whole life
they're not sick you know why
gluten makes somebody else sick and
doesn't make somebody else sick it's
because
the 89 year old didn't have all those
bugs all the streps and all the epstein
bars and all the shingles and hhv-6s and
h8v7s and simplex ones and simplex twos
they didn't have all those so
it's not lectins it's not oxalates
there's real reasons why people are sick
i love these theories that just co
i don't know it's just incredible really
i guess everybody has to play guessing
games when they don't know why anybody's
sick
so it just goes around and then they'll
blame it on jeans
blame it on jeans blame it on the body
attacking itself so all our genes went
bad
or your jeans are bad now your child's
jeans are bad now your kids jeans are
bad
all our genes went bad in 20 years
[Laughter]
thousands of years ago by it all our
genes went bad
it's unbelievable
i think i just saw a question was it a
bone marrow question
what about bone marrow failure
amanda you know i've given a lot of
information about that too
a couple of different a couple of
different clinics medical clinics over
the years i used to lecture a lot
and see a lot of doctor friends and
medical clinics and stuff and
and i used to tell them it's always the
toxic heavy metals so
uh bone marrow failure is
it's mercury it's aluminum inside
the bones a lot of mercury inside the
bones
a little bit of lead inside the bones
that's where we get in trouble a lot of
fluoride inside the bones a lot of
fluoride inside the bones
all right so i'm steaming these up
anyway so you guys what to avoid well
i'd stay away from gluten
right some of you guys are probably like
that's a no-brainer
you know but everybody just seems to run
back to it they're back on it
one way or another they're doing gluten
again and the reason why i think is
because they just don't know really what
happens and
like i was showing you before gluten
feeds every bug there is inside of her
body
esther says why do younger
people have these bugs
there's a lot more aggressive bugs than
ever before mutated strains
they get passed around a lot more now
than they ever did in the past
um you know that that's
that's that's how it goes the bugs have
mutated
they're more they're more uh virulent
so that's another thing too spreads so
much easier
years and years and years ago the first
couple of epstein bars the first few
epstein bars over the years didn't
really spread so easy
but they also manufactured a lot of new
bugs so they manufactured a lot of new
bugs
so the private medical system
um it's a little virus right here a
little little epstein-barr to show you
guys
the private medical industry
manufactured a lot of new bugs
and they've been released and these new
bugs have been released
in the last probably 40 years
they've been raised on eggs so
pretend this is an egg when you got a
little bit of egg matter floating around
in your body
and you got the epstein-barr virus
especially a mutated one
one of the newer strains you're gonna go
in and eat that egg
there you go and the egg's gone it's in
the virus
the virus multiplies easier so why are
people
why are younger people sicker now with
pathogens
is because just in the last 30 40 years
they really let out a lot of them the
private medical industry really let out
a lot of new epstein bars a lot of
mutated versions also
when they go from person to person to
person as the years go by
they mutate and they become a little bit
more virulent a little bit more virulent
a little more virulent
they spread easy too in restaurants not
as easy as they did years ago i mean
much more easier than they did years ago
in restaurants
there's a lot of reasons these are just
some of them
now we have toxins like we never had
before we have so many toxins and
chemicals and pollutions and
we got not just pollution we're talking
about air fresheners and
and scented candles drop the immune
system so we're losing our immune
systems now too
so the younger people are sicker than
ever before with viruses and bacteria
epstein bars and shingles because their
immune systems are dropping
more so than ever before in our history
because they've never been exposed to
the chemical companies to the degree
they are so
children now are eating chemicals 24 7.
they're they're eating scented candles
it's just breathing it in it's going in
their mouth they're eating air
fresheners
colognes perfumes aftershaves the worst
thing to have
in the house dad throws on some
aftershave and hugs hugs his child and
that aftershave is so toxic and immune
system lowering
so these this is just this you know we
have the toxins we have now and the
heavy metals now too
that are in all of this and in the
pesticides the herbicides they're
spraying
more mosquito spray for no reason
more mosquito spray more um
west nile spray more fungicide on
highways
more herbicide in parks than ever before
in our history
it's fire retardant all over people's
beds all over clothing
fire retardant on couches it's all about
killing our immune system so chemical
companies want to destroy our immune
systems apparently
and then you have more violent strains
of epstein-barr more mutated versions
more mutated versions of shingles more
mutated versions of hhv-6 h827
off the chart the simplex simplex won
the cold sore
everybody has that there's like
there's a dozen of those now easy dozen
of those mutated now not everybody's
simplex is the same simplex i remember
i remember uh years ago somebody come in
to me for help
and they had a simplex they they went on
a date and
you know after the date they had a
simplex
on their tongue and
it never went away it just it was a
mutated version it stayed there
it stayed there for like ever and they
asked the other person did they have
anything like that because they were
like where did this and the other person
said yeah i didn't disclose it to you
and i didn't tell you but
i've had that on my tongue too for like
the last 20 years
anyway and those cold sores when they do
go away on people
they're still in your system they go in
the trigeminal nerve they cause
trigeminal neuralgia a little bit
shingles does too but it causes problems
what i'm saying is we need to do things
about it we can
we can clean this stuff up it's nothing
it's not about being you know you don't
you don't have to be afraid of bugs
that's not it you just you just clean
them up and you don't feed them
you don't feed them eggs that's an egg
yolk
it's not an egg yolk but you don't feed
them you don't feed them eggs you don't
feed them gluten you don't feed them
milk cheese and butter
and you can you can clean them up
some are harder to deal with some are a
little bit stronger some have
a little bit more mutated some are a
little bit more aggressive some people
have more toxic heavy metals in their
system some people have more
toxins in their system some people have
lowered immune systems because of these
things
and it's a little bit harder but yes you
don't have to fear anything you just
have to get better
do the right stuff and get it out of
your system clean up
knock the stuff out kill it off is what
you do
and you kill it off you knock it out of
your system and you move forward and you
heal
um
what is the pan you're using check out
my directory medicalmedium.com
i got some kitchenware on there
medicalmedium.com
uh there's a kitchen kitchenware
directory
so i'm steaming up i don't know if you
guys see this
steaming up some asparagus some brussels
sprouts
they're just about done i'm making a
salad i'm gonna cut up some potatoes now
i'm gonna do that
i'm doing the arugula potato asparagus
salad if you guys just came on
um is it right there
medical medium new addition
and that's that's what i'm making right
now
incredible having you guys here now what
i'm doing is
when i'm what i like to do in a pan is i
like to steam these up in a pan
and only put a little bit of water so
the water eventually goes away
and then they kind of get a little
toasty in here so that when they go on
the salad they're not going on the salad
dripping wet with water
right that's the way i like to do it
instead they're like getting nice and
toasty now i got the pan on high
the water's already been evaporated
they've already done some
steaming in the pan
and now they're getting a little toasty
there's still some moisture in the pan
so i really like it that way
so let me start making a salad let me
get some greens together in a bowl
i'm going to chop up some butter leaf
lettuce let me show you what i got you
guys
some butter leaf right here on the other
side i have arugula
i'm going to chop up a little bit
i see my neighbors spraying the local
council spraying around parks and rivers
and they aren't even wearing mask or
gloves people children and animals are
all around them it makes me so angry
yeah
did you know and i've seen this
did you know what's on the barrels of
that stuff it's a skull and crossbones
skull and crossbones did you know the
guys that handle the barrels of chemical
that actually eventually gets diluted
and put into you know sprayed and put
into parks and all that
that same chemical they die really young
it's a job you only have for like 20
years and then you're done
you're done it's horrible
you know i i've seen photographs of
those barrels
skull and crossbones
i mean seriously skull crossbones on
those barrels
i'm not kidding and guess what
chemical companies want your babies to
have it all over them in the park
they want your babies to have it all
children
chemical companies i truly believe
want people poisoned why else would they
put their
deadly chemicals in parks and why
would counties and states and
villages and wherever you live around
the world
why would they let that happen can
someone tell me
[Music]
because i've always said it's a sick
world
see money says viruses can't live in
carnivore blood that's why the carnivore
diet works for autoimmune
well so if you're on a carnivore diet
wait viruses can't live in carnivore
blood does that mean that okay so while
you're on the carnivore diet i get it
i get it um
this is not true viruses feed off of
toxic heavy metals and when you're a
carnivore
you're not eating any foods when you're
doing the carnivore diet you're not any
eating any of the foods to get the
metals out
so all your metals are sitting inside of
you and the viruses will feed on the
metals
yeah i i give you this though i give you
this
you're not eating well you might be
eating eggs if you're doing eggs on a
carnivore diet you're feeding the heck
out of those viruses
big time if you're doing raw cheese on
that carnivore diet you're feeding those
viruses
just say if you're doing eggs you're
feeding the viruses okay
right there now if your carnivore diet
is corn fed
it's corn fed you're feeding the viruses
with the meat you're eating
make sure none of your meat you're
eating in a carnivore diet is corn fed
okay and um but yeah i get it you
removed your gluten you removed your
milk cheese butter probably
uh if you're doing the butter you're
feeding your viruses so you
i know people on a carnivore diet
they're doing butter you're feeding the
viruses they're doing eggs
feeding viruses if you're only doing
meat and meat only and you're eating
just the animal flesh and that's it
you're still going to have toxic heavy
metals feeding the viruses in there
and then you end up getting symptoms
later so you can be on your carnivore
diet doing okay and then you get
symptoms later it happens all the time
because eventually the viruses will
still feed
and here's the other thing too if you're
on a carnivore diet and you're not doing
any fruits and vegetables
and you're not cleaning up the liver
your liver is just going to get more
beaten down more beating down more fatty
more fatty and then more fat building up
in your liver and
your fat the fat builds so much in your
liver that you end up having a problem
and then boom you're
you're sick anyway with other problems
you got gout
and then if you're on a high fat diet
non-stop because you're just on
carnivore
so you're eating the high-fat diet
non-stop you're burning out the adrenals
over time you're going to get some
adrenal fatigue and you're going to
end up binging on some kind of
carbohydrate
i'm not ranking on the carnivore diet
i'm just saying that
you don't have a free pass on a
carnivore diet
i look you don't have a free pass on a
vegan diet
plant-based diet animal protein diet
there's no free pass on any of it
because if you're doing all these fats
on a plant-based diet here so you don't
have a free ticket if you're doing all
this vinegar you don't have a free
ticket
if you're doing all this nutritional
yeast you don't have a free ticket if
you're doing all this caffeine you don't
have a free ticket no one has a free
ticket and they realize they really
really
really avoid everything and then clean
up what's happening
chopped up some arugula right here you
don't have to chop this up
but i i want to
i don't care what diet you're on i don't
care if a martian
arrived on your back porch on a little
spaceship
and gave you a brand new diet from outer
space
if you don't know why you're sick or
what causes your symptoms
it's not going to be enough it's just
not going to be enough you have to know
what the cause of your problem is your
symptoms
why you're sick you have to that's a big
part of it
so i got some butter leaf lettuce i got
some really good right here
um so i'm gonna start putting some other
i'm gonna start cutting an onion
let's do that bev asked what oils do you
cook with
none nada
[Music]
don't need to just a little bit of water
you don't have to cook in oils
you know that whole rule of cooking with
oils
is really not necessary these are fat
free meals so that you can get a break
and your liver can get a break once in a
while so you can just take a break i'm
gonna slice up this onion right here
um you can do white onion
i like red onion too so i'll do red
here's a white one right here too
um but i'm gonna cut these nice and thin
so i like keeping these fat free
that's what i like to do because there's
but there's fats like i said earlier i
said i
think i said earlier there's fats in
everything there's fats in brussels
sprouts there's fats in
asparagus there's fats in lettuce butter
leaf lettuce has omegas in it as i was
telling you guys earlier
so i'm cutting up some onion right here
gonna put some red onion on the salad
got some red onion so let me start
putting some potatoes in here
i'm gonna cut these up
is there a test for viral issues
mean there's some basic tests you can
see if you have a
infection of epstein-barr see if you
have some epstein-barr titers
but to be honest
they don't know what viruses do
and just so you know there before
medical medium books were published and
medical medium information came out
um they didn't even know epstein-barr
had a afterlife
epstein barr has an afterlife causes
hashimoto's thyroiditis
causes ra rheumatoid arthritis causes um
uh lupus causes lyme disease
they didn't know that you know
epstein-barr had an afterlife
and the publication of this book the
first edition
the publication is first edition that
came out years ago
uh busted out the truth about what
epstein-barr does and everything and how
you can get the
reactivation you can get you know the
virus comes back
comes out of dormancy again and sits
inside your liver and all this stuff now
science research is actually taking it
seriously years later after i've already
published the information
and so it's interesting
but they didn't even know they had no
clue
you know they thought epstein-barr was
just mono when it went away and that's
it
so
so i'm bringing the bowl over for now
okay i got this virus in the way right
here i got to move him
it's a cute little bugger that virus
move these asparagus over so here's the
salad i'm making right here
barbara butler i just joined what do you
use to wash your organic vegetables
look if i'm gonna cook them i use hot
water
so i use hot water i get a big old bowl
and put some hot water in it coming out
of the sink
i use an unscented mild dish soap
i like to do that too
and in the water just a couple of drops
i massage the vegetables massage the
greens
rinse it out a couple times and i'm good
that's what i like to do
massage your fruits and vegetables
so i'm gonna put some asparagus in here
i still got some other things to go in
here too i got lemon
i gotta make the dressing
terry says you're helping make
vegetables look yummy incredible
incredible i'm really excited about
these actually
annette says can you explain driving an
adrenaline surge
lays
um can you explain driving
and adrenaline surges well adrenaline
surges
can happen we always have mild
adrenaline surges
so we always have mild ones whatever we
do so anything we do
all right our nervous systems are always
hyperly attached to adrenals
you get a phone call and you're nervous
about the phone call your adrenals are
going you're getting an adrenal surge
you get some bad news on your phone
somebody texts you maybe it's a friend
or not a friend and they
and they and they say some terrible
things on your text or something and now
you're just you're just shaking you're
shaking
and you're just like oh my god and
you're sitting on your couch looking at
your phone like what the hell just
happened and you're shaking that's
that's adrenal surge get some
i mean anything could happen you hear a
knock on the door and you're like wait a
minute
i thought i had a package delivery is it
stolen and all of a sudden you get an
adrenal surge because you think your
package
that was delivered was stolen where's my
wallet i can't find it oh my god did i
leave it at the grocery store you get
adrenal surge
so you adrenal surges all day long right
you bump your head on the cupboard and
you're like oh my god is this a
concussion
this really hurts i feel an egg growing
on my head i got to get some ice
should i run to the doctor should i call
the emergency room you get your adrenals
are surging
it's just it's non-stop right so i'm
just saying so and then
the caffeine that's a big one right
there that's that's every time you do
caffeine
you just put caffeine in your system and
the surges don't stop
they don't stop you guys you eat some
chocolate
those surges don't stop that's like you
know if your package
wasn't stolen or you've lost your wallet
for five minutes and you found it your
surges stop
right but man caffeine it's got this
evil twist to it
once you get it in your system your
adrenals have no choice they're sitting
there panting
they're panting they're surging they're
surging they're surging you can't stop
it
it's just it'll surge for a day if
caffeine will make them search for three
days
it just it'll make them search a little
less when you're when it's wearing out
but they'll still be surging it's like
people live their life with their
adrenal surging
forced by caffeine and i think they're
getting energy from caffeine i'm gonna
put some um
basil on here i got this beautiful basil
leaves right here
and what's really happening though is
their adrenals are just
just getting beat to crap really are
from from from the caffeine
so that surges them right there that's a
big deal and then the high fat diets
this meal right here won't surge
it won't surge cause adrenal surge
this meal won't it just can't there's
if you dropped two tablespoons of olive
oil on here
and threw some pine nuts on here right
tastes amazing probably right threw some
tahini on here
all that fat would then start thickening
your blood right when it gets to what
right when you eat it it gets down in
here and now it starts to surge
the adrenals start to surge because the
fat is starting to absorb into your
bloodstream and once the fat starts to
absorb into your bloodstream
your adrenals have to release all this
epinephrine to thin out your blood so
your heart
so your heart doesn't have to pump so
hard
all that fat you put in it just makes
your heart pump so
i get it it's okay to have some tahini
i'm not
anti-tahini i'm not anti-hemp seeds
anti-peanut buttery anti
almond butter i'm not anti pine nuts
i'm not anti avocado i'm not anti oils
and if you love animal protein
i support you but what what i'm trying
to say is we don't stop
no one gets a break it's 24
7 it's fats fats fats fats fats every
single day and no one gets a day off
your liver doesn't get a day off your
adrenals don't get your day off
your heart doesn't get a day off i mean
i mean seriously your heart is up
against that non-stop
so nothing gets a break so it's like
more fat hey more avocado oh the next
day comes peanut butter and my oatmeal
next day comes olive oil on my salad
next day comes
lots of chicken at night it's it doesn't
stop
pork chicken beef milk cheese butter
eggs
let me have an egg well there we go lots
of fat again it just doesn't stop
so then your heart is like it just
doesn't stop and your heart has to pump
it has to literally pump all that fat
through and your adrenals have to thin
out the blood
it's just and then the plaque builds up
the plaque
all that plaque later on you're seven
years old you got plaque on the arteries
the veins
veins start collapsing let me put some
of this on here you guys
putting these beautiful pieces of
asparagus on here and then the other
thing is toxins absorb in all that fat
every time
uh fat toxins fat soluble
fat toxin soluble they just absorb into
each other like
perfectly so i'm putting a little bit of
uh some brussels and some asparagus on
here this is beautiful right here it's
potatoes
this is looking amazing it really is i'm
going to drop some thyme on here that
teaspoon of dried thyme
put a little bit of that on here
and i forgot the parsley i still have to
put some parsley quarter cup of parsley
on
sorry you guys a little bit of thyme
wasn't easy to come out let me chop up a
little parsley
okay and i got it right here all right
i'm gonna chop this up so
my job is just to teach you guys
to give your body a break get the
healing foods
know what causes symptoms and conditions
give you every chance to heal
no one else is doing it i mean it's
crazy it's it's like
you'll listen to the best podcast guys
or the best health gurus out there and
they don't even know what causes
sickness they're too busy reading matcha
tea studies
looking for some special antioxidant
matcha tea
paid for by the caffeine industry and
then they'll end up thinking it's just
your genes anyway that's why you're sick
and they won't be trying to get metals
out if they are they're trying to do it
because
i brought it to light spent 35 years
teaching people about toxic heavy metals
um it's not because i'm special
that's for sure so i'm gonna put some
lemon on here i looked everywhere
tell me where to find your 369 protocol
um get cleanse the heel if you can get
it from the library if you can't afford
the book even though it's on sale
amazon.com it's 16.99 incredible price
um it's a medical textbook but you can
go to the library get it for free
and 369 cleanse the advanced cleanse
uh simplified cleanse original cleanse
and you can pick the one you want
the answers are in the books
but you know and what i love about these
foods is
is that they're healing foods but
when you combine healing foods with the
fact that you remove the foods that are
troublesome
then you're moving forward you know
so let's uh let's put a little lemon on
top of here
so basically i'm going to use a strainer
so the seeds aren't going in here
a couple tables a tablespoon of lemon is
fine on here
i can't wait to eat this thing
here's the other thing about all the
fats you keep on doing all the fats
every day
all you do is cause corrosion with the
toxic heavy metals that are in your
brain so let me show you this
so metals are heavy
and they don't just stay in the
bloodstream that's why they can't find
them no one can really find them
and you get blood tests for it and but
metals are heavy so they sit inside
organs so they go deep inside organ
tissue this they go deep inside your
brain and that's when the ocd starts the
bipolar starts anxiety depression starts
the personalization starts
schizophrenia starts whatever starts and
um emotional ups and downs that can't be
explained
all of it so you get the toxic heavy
metals and they sit inside the brain
and um and then you eat all the fat so
gobble down all the pork and the chicken
milk cheese and the butter and the eggs
and the almond butter and all the seeds
and nuts
and the peanut butter and oils and the
coconut oil and what happens is
all that all that fat in the bloodstream
goes around the metal it starts to hit
the metal and then the metal
oxidizes fat causes the metal to oxidize
and then it bleeds over into different
parts of the brain and different
different tissue and then your
conditions get worse over time worse
over time
and electrical impulses have a hard time
getting through the metal so it starts
to get shocked in there
and
so so here's a half a brain
so on this half of brain you got little
metal deposits see i put these little
deposits here these are big ones so this
is just a demo that's not what it looks
like
you can't see the microscopic metal in
brain in the brain
unless it causes so much corrosion over
time or it's a large enough deposit and
then it causes a gray area gray spot
dark spot
or or some type of crystallization on
the mri eventually as you as you get
older
and blood tests aren't accurate for
finding metals and
here they are so electrical impulses are
firing through your brain they're
hitting the metal deposits and it's like
it's like what's wrong with you are you
okay today honey
i don't know what's wrong with me i'm
just really pissed off i'm angry and
i don't know i feel really emotional and
is your bipolar back
uh i don't i don't know i just gotta
leave i gotta get out of here
and what happens is electrical impulses
are just go they're hitting the toxic
heavy metal deposits
and it's like oh my depression is so bad
today it's
so bad i don't know what it is and
that's corrosion from the toxic heavy
metals moving into
other tissue and my anxiety is through
the roof i feel like it's going to like
give me a panic attack and it's
got me in my gut and it's and i'm
freaking out inside and my anxiety is
out of control and i can't breathe that
my chest is tight
well that's electrical impulses hitting
all those those metal deposits right
and and alternative medicine they only
know how to get toxic metals out of
people they're just sending people on
wild goose chase with charcoal and
and collagen and matcha tea i mean it's
it's unbelievable
um and you know and and with with
anxiety you can have low-grade viral
stuff depression low-grade
vital stuff you gotta have metals it's
always metals metals are always involved
and so and that's that's a problem right
there so
you guys know about you know i mean if
you i didn't give you any solutions for
metals tonight but
i usually show you the spirulina i show
you the barley grass juice powder
cleanse the gila i talk about here the
heavy metal detox cleanse there's a
heavy metal detox cleanse right here
so i mean if i just if you guys feel
like you didn't get enough info on that
just now let me just
um that's the spirulina i use that's the
vimergy spirulina
uh v is in victor i am ergy and that's
the barley grass juice powder i'm not
sponsored
but that's what i used in the heavy
metal detox smoothie every day and then
the wild blueberries
i'll show you guys another time and uh
so anyway i got the lemon in here
i'm going to put a little honey on this
too you can do maple syrup
or honey i'm in the mood for honey
tonight
i've been doing some extra maple syrup
late lately so i'm going to put a little
drizzle of honey
on top of this
let's get this on here
so i mean that's what happened so people
are walking around with all kinds of
different
um issues left and right emotionally
mentally got the anxiety to depression
and then they get the parkinson's too
when the tremors and the ticks and the
spasms and the tourettes
and what about yeah what about the
tourettes
laura marie are the potatoes cooked
yes they are they're steamed potatoes is
what they are so if you want to know
they're steamed potatoes
there it is that's the recipe in the new
edition
link is in the description you guys
so there's the brussels sprouts the
asparagus
and the arugula of course butter leaf
lettuce i put in there the basil i'm
really excited about this dish
and this dish is fat free
it's fat free i mean how cool is that so
you guys check out medical medium
podcast at apple podcast 17
episodes docus docuseries style episodes
it's free
i got meditations stargazing meditation
moon meditation
i'm either there for you the brain
meditation picking fruit meditation
and then you can check out the episodes
b12 episode potato episode you gotta
listen to those the egg episode
chemtrail episode if you want the fruit
fear episode
neurological symptoms episode brain fog
episode
and chemical like the air fresheners
there's 17 episodes check them out
they're they're new
recent and more coming pretty soon
there's an anxiety episode too
medical meeting podcast at apple podcast
to check those out
i'm heading over to ig and tiktok the
meal is done
i love you guys and are you coming to ig
and tick tock
because let's let's let's do it darlene
says love the podcast
awesome i'm glad you're listening to him
lunell they're all packed with info
thanks loon
awesome um good to see you guys
i see some of you guys from youtube some
of you guys from facebook
margaret valentine good to see you
margaret i see you leave comments all
the time on youtube
thanks for so much support you're
supporting others you're always being
helpful
um incredible you guys
i'll see you later head over to ig and
tick tock
at the same