hello it's Anthony William medical
medium great to be here at autoimmune
answers live webinar and uh thank you
for being here uh absolutely this is
really exciting it's important because
when it comes down to our health there's
some pitfalls and things in our way
barriers and other things that if we
don't learn about it's hard to get past
our conditions or symptoms or illnesses
so when it comes to Healing information
means everything now the information
you're going to learn on the webinar and
and you know our future webinars and uh
the webinars of the past the information
you're going to learn it's it's
important to know where it's coming from
it's coming from a Pure untampered
Source a clean source and if you're
someone who just you know you never knew
who I was or you don't know my story or
history um what that means is is that I
was given a gift since childhood start
started with the age four at age four
and I was given a gift to hear a voice
perfectly clear to provide a clean
source of information help out people
have dedicated my entire life to decades
and decades now to helping people heal
um and overcome their illnesses and get
the answers they need and I'm saying
this because it's important to
understand the information here doesn't
come from interest groups or medical
funding with strings attached or botched
research with lobbyists medical
lobbyists inter Al Kickbacks persuaded
belief systems persuaded belief systems
that's serious private panels of
influencers that no one knows about in
the world of medicine I'm talking about
Alternative Health and health field
payoffs both of conventional alternative
medicine or trendy traps you know when
when you deal with fads and trends that
that are out there but they're really
sand traps and I'm saying this because
it's important to know that the
information we're going to cover is not
involved in any any of that it's a clear
clean source of information and why is
this important because I'll tell you why
because when and this is you always have
to know this the one of the reasons why
we're not healing and and why there's
hundreds of millions of sick people
billions of sick people on planet Earth
right now is because we're kept from
knowing about certain truths because
there's a reason for that there's a big
reason for that and I'm going to cover
and to go into it a lot deeper and when
science and research does their studies
both alternative and conventional
conventionally there's funding and money
behind it and they have to come out and
in many ways the studies have to land a
certain way they have to land on all
four feet and there and many times
there's a thumb on the scale if you know
what I mean if you know what I'm talking
about that thumb on the scale because
you don't want to piss off an interest
group or somebody's interest somebody's
money that went was funded into
something and you want to make sure
outcomes come out the way they're
intended to come out regardless if it's
good for you or bad for you and that's
the problem even the truths that we have
from leading experts right now the
information's tampered it's tainted so
even good-hearted good-hearted really
amazing you know immunologists and and
every and different people in the field
of medicine whether it's oncologist when
it comes down to can or or you know our
science and research are best people
their hearts in it and our doctor's
hearts are in it and we have some
amazing things scientifically uh you
know discovered now that are helping
people but when it comes down to chronic
illness it's separated I'm going to tell
you right now it's it's an entirely
different situation and when it comes
down to autoimmune autoimmune disease
autoimmune symptoms and conditions and
the whole term autoimmune when it comes
down to that that's a whole different
ballpark from heart surgery that's a
whole different ballpark from you know
science and research in so many
different fields of medicine that are
doing incredible things that we that we
rely on that we love that we need and
but there's there's two two You Know
Places there's two places one place is
chronic illness and we don't have
answers we don't one place is chronic
illness the other place is you know uh
black and white black and white medicine
science and research where it's black
and white where we rely on so much of
that so and the bottom line is when it
comes down to chronic illness and
autoimmune and all the different labels
that's a different story that's where
we're in the dark and the information
that is out there is contaminated most
of the information out there is
contaminated now ho ho ho how can I say
that that's a big deal to say it's just
the truth and I'm going to cover why
it's the truth and how it works and how
we can protect you that's the whole
point you know when I was given the gift
to have this clean source of information
a source that isn't persuaded by all the
things I just talked about right there
and and that's real that stuff I just
talked about everything I mentioned is
in alternative and conventional medicine
both you may say well it's not in
alternative medicine that's he's talking
about conventional medicine where you
got the internal Kickbacks and you know
persuaded belief systems private panel
influencers Health peel Health peel
payoffs and Bot research and strings
attached and everything else that must
be conventional he's talking about no
I'm talking about alternative to
absolutely in both fields of medicine
when it comes down to chronic illness
chronic illness autoimmune chronic
illness and
autoimmune so and and that we're going
to we're going to go into all of it now
I really mean it when I say fasten your
seat bels because this is going to be a
ride um so let's get into it so
get ready cuz we're starting now and
we're going now if you you know if you
live in an apartment you or House or
wherever you live kak condo apartment
house everybody lives in different
places some people just live over you
know they live in their their their you
know sisters or brothers basement they
live wherever they can live you know
wherever we
live and um or our friend's house or
wherever we live and live our life if
paint was starting to flake off the
walls okay just for some strange reason
you know the paint's recent it's meaning
the paint is not old it's a new paint
but it's starting to flake off the
walls and and you call a carpenter and
the carpenter comes he says I don't know
I don't know why that that paint is
flaking off the walls there and then all
of a sudden say your ceiling started
leaking and it was leaking water
but there was no really answer to it
because all the piping and all the
plumbing seemed fine and it was just
okay the plumbing was fine everything
was good but the leak was just always
there seeping through the
ceiling and then the
floors the floors started to get weird
where they're starting to move a little
and the floors were moving because you
know it was just kind of
crumbling so the apartment you're living
in or the house you're living in was
kind of falling apart when it's not
supposed to be and you got your your
Carpenter or contractor whoever in there
and they're in there and they're looking
at it and they don't know
why because it's kind of a mystery it's
it's a it's it's a serious mystery
because we can't find the water leak so
there's no plumbing leaking but yet you
got water seeping through the
ceiling the floors are crumbling
but everything seems to be sturdy
underneath there and there's no reason
why the floor should be
crumbling the walls the paint is flaking
off the
walls now if the landlord if you're
renting and the landlord said look I
don't know what this is this is a
mystery I don't understand what's
happening you got to be doing something
wrong so you're living in here what are
you doing that's making this happen what
are you doing that's making the paint
flake off the
walls because I don't know why it's
flaking off the walls so obviously
there's something you're doing I've
never seen this before so a landlord
would be saying I've never seen this
before I've had lots of apartment
buildings and I've never seen this
happen it's got to be something you're
doing and I'll call the carpenter
carpenter came down there I says yeah I
agree there's no there's no leaks the
plumber says there's no leaks leaks the
piping looks good but the ceiling's
getting wet it's got to be your
fault and whether you live in a home or
an apartment it's your fault that this
is
happening now would that make a lot of
sense would that make a lot of
sense well they don't know what's wrong
they don't know what's wrong or what's
going on with your house or your your
apartment or where you're
living so would it be right if it was
blamed on you if it's a mystery leak if
it's a mystery
problem but that's what's happening with
autoimmune you start getting
symptoms and you can't figure it out you
got a mystery rash you got mystery
symptoms you got mystery
fatigue mystery
dizziness and mystery
inflammation well it's got to be it's
got to be something going on with your
body it's got to be you and you're going
to be saying well hey it's not my fault
I'm not doing anything to create my
sickness I don't think I'm living my
life and I just started getting sick
things started
happening but when we have
autoimmune we get told something we get
told our body is attacking
itself that our body is attacking
itself that's what we get
told so it becomes our fault so miss
conditions that happen in our health
that happened in your health it happened
in your life are they're your
fault it's your body's fault that's what
we're
told and here we are come on now I mean
look what year it is look how far we are
and look where science and research is
look at the technology that's out
there and the best the best that can
come out right now the best that can
come out right now in
medicine your body is still attacking
itself so autoimmune we're told
autoimmune means our body is destroying
itself it's going after
itself our B's targeting
us and that's autoimmune and that's
where we are today and you have to think
about that I mean is that where you want
to be is that where you want to be in
your life you want to know your body's
attacking itself whether it comes down
to
Hashimoto's we're told our body is
targeting our thyroid
tissue so our immune system is screening
antibodies antibodies are actually going
after our tissue and destroying our
cells and destroying our our
thyroid our immune system is basically
going after and targeting our
thyroid when it comes down to
Hashimoto is that where you want to be
because it's not the truth by the way
that's not the
truth and it's like that that with exmos
orasis it's like that too the body's not
attacking the body's not attacking the
skin even though the Skin's inflamed the
body's not turning against the skin but
we're told that systemic
lupus we're inflamed throughout the body
mysteriously inflamed throughout the
body we're told our body's attacking
itself that's what lupus is it's an
autoimmune problem and we're going to
cover a whole bunch of different things
whole bunch of different illnesses and
autoimmune this is as we're in
here cuz this is a big deal look I take
this serious I take autoimmune so
serious it's it's it's I mean I really
really really take it to heart I take it
personally I take it
seriously when it comes to Healing our
health I'm going to tell you right now
that if you believe your body is
attacking
itself you got a barrier in your way a
major barrier in your way
a huge barrier in your way so when it
comes to our healing our health I'm
going to tell you right now and if you
believe your body is attacking itself on
any level and there's no
cure it's a huge
barrier we can talk to the leading
experts and they say well there's no
cure to autoimmune we can just control
it there's no cure to autoimmune that's
not true the problem is nobody knows
what autoimmune is they don't know what
it's caused they don't know what these
symptoms and conditions and these labels
that are given to
people
ra you know systemic lupus Ms Celiac fgo
alcia psoriasis colitis Hashimoto
Addison's Graves disease Su disease type
1 diabetes hepatitis A B C
D sertic
arthritis and it goes on and on
they don't know what's causing those
conditions those conditions get
labels because of the different symptoms
and the different you know things that
people are going through they get
labels but it's all a mystery complete
mystery so what science and research
chalks it up to when it comes down to
Healing your health it's your body
attacking itself and that's what it is
and there's no cure and that's where we
are right now in this time in history
when you would think we would be so far
along and so further into healing than
ever
before and we're not I was told by my
source when I was a child that you're
going to see some things
happen and I said what does that mean
and spirit said you're going to see some
things happening I said what spirit says
you're going to see people getting
sicker and sicker and sicker and and and
I'll tell you right now when I look back
from Child childhood to now it's
unbelievable of what's
happening and how many people are
suffering from symptoms if you look at
how many people are in the US alone just
say three roughly 325 million or
whatever it is 325 million people in the
US alone
280 of them are dealing with real
symptoms and
conditions 20 million more are dealing
with some kind of symptom that's also a
mystery there's virtually 10 or 20
million people only in the
US that are not seeing too many symptoms
meaning symptoms that come and go here
and there depending on what it is and
really have okay enough Health we are at
a place and time that's unbelievable in
history never
before and one of the biggest problems
and one of the biggest barriers in the
way is it's all going to be chalked up
to autoimmune one way or another that's
where it's going to be chalked up to and
it's going to be
also right in front of everybody where
it's your body's fault it's your body's
fault your body's letting you down it's
your fault that's what's going wrong
that's what's happening your body is
destroying itself so when it comes down
to our healing and our health I'm going
to tell you right now if you believe
your body's attacking itself and there's
no cure that's a massive barrier in your
way we're going to crush that barrier
destroy that barrier we're going to
knock it down we're going to push it
down in the ground we're going to clear
the way for you because if we don't
clear the way for
you whether you're getting benefits or
not from from an expert anywhere or
whatever it's still going to be in the
back of your mind and it becomes poison
I'm going to tell you right now that
it's poison and it's injected into our
thinking into our thoughts into our
beings into our
Souls is what it
is we live inside our body just like
when we live inside our apartment or our
house you have to understand something
when you're living in your house and
paint's peeling off the walls and
leaking ceilings are happening and
there's no real answers and you're stuck
inside of it and someone's telling you
that it's your fault or it's your your
you know it's
literally yeah it's your fault
and there's no
answers then that's bad enough but see
when it's our body itself and our soul
resides inside our
body okay our soul resides inside our
body and we're told our soul is told
that's your that's your thinking right
there big part of your thinking your
soul and you're told hey no it's it's
your listen it's your body attacking
creating anybody's it's your body
attacking your
thyroid these Auto antibodies attacking
the
thyroid and and we're you know we're
going to do a whole you know leading
experts in thyroid are going to say oh
it's triggers we're going to do the
triggers and and we're going to do
things you'll start feeling better sure
and some people do because they take
away gluten and they take away things
and they start taking care of themselves
and they start seeing differences we're
going to talk about
why but you still have in the back of
your mind outdated information I'm going
to tell you right now the leading
experts in thyroid the leading experts
right now in thyroid and in autoimmune
in
general still believe the body's
attacking itself they just think
triggers are are are telling the body to
attack itself and that's not
true and they believe the body's
attacking self so no matter what even if
you you get benefits from the leading
experts I'm going to tell you right now
somewhere in the back of your mind it's
going to creep up and cause problems
because it's in there it's injected like
poison and that's what we're removing
today and that's why I said fasten your
seat bels because I swear to God if that
poison is in your symptom it's going to
mess you up it's going to mess you up
over time somewhere someway down the
line with your autoimmune with your
Celiac with your viilo with your
alopecia with your psoriasis and eczema
with your Colitis with your Hashim modus
with your Addison with your Graves which
your suance with your type 1 diabetes
with your lanceros with your aers dangel
syndrome it's going to mess you up along
the way one way or another and that
poison has to be extracted from you
literally extract it from you spirit
said to me today when you do this live
webinar you make sure somehow some way
with all you have in you Anthony William
you let people know the body is not
destroying itself because whether they
realize it or not it is out there the
information is out there and it is
poison and it seeps into us when we deal
with anything autoimmune the term
autoimmune itself is that poisonous
because it means turning against you
that's what it means and spirit said you
better get everybody right on this you
just
better and I said I I'll do everything I
can I said I'll do everything I can
everything I
can so if you're told by the latest
experts in the in the health world and
books and internet and everything else
that autoimmune is still attacking still
autoimmune is still you know your body
is still in autoimmune but hey look
let's eliminate triggers and and get you
in the right way so you can do better
and get past it it's still not good
enough it's still not good enough is
what I'm telling you and that's the
difference right there in what I meant
at the beginning no interest groups and
medical funding with strings attached
and everything else of Bot research and
kickbacks and persuaded beliefs systems
I meant it because what I'm trying to
tell you guys right now is that is
Tainted even the most leading best
information that's out there now in
everything including thyroid and
everything else and it is Tainted it
whether the practitioner or the doctor
or the good-hearted person knows about
it and I get that I get that you know we
only can do what we can do but I'm
telling you I'm taking you somewhere
further I'm taking you further out I'm
taking you in a better place and it has
to be that way that's what I'm here for
that's what I'm here
for now if you know the truth if you
know the truth and your body isn't
attacking itself if you know the truth
it's attacking something else your body
is attacking something else it's not
attacking your organs it's not attacking
your glands it's not attacking your skin
it's not attacking your body if it's
attacking something else that's not your
body you will have the greatest chance
of of really healing the barrier starts
to come down the barrier starts to break
down the barrier the barrier that's been
put in our way back in the
1950s put in our way in the
1950s that's the barrier that was set up
old grandfathered law the barrier of
your body attacking itself because signs
and research still isn't up to par on
what causes your symptoms and conditions
you guys because science and research is
not up to level to what's happening and
why you feel like you do and why you
have those pains and why you have that
fatigue and why your Skin's inflamed and
why you have the butterfly rash and why
your thyroids inflamed thyroiditis and
everything
else because science and research isn't
there yet at
all it's grandfather in and rooted to
these old thought processes that get in
your way because funding when into them
at the time and no one wants to break it
it's like estate planning it's like
trusts it's like the trust you can't
break
it it's like massive corporate trusts
and different things in that category
you can't break them they're written in
papers those papers are in vaults vaults
those papers are protected and a lot of
these old laws in the medical field have
to be passed on even to your greatest
expert that's alternative right now that
he or she still has to believe the body
is attacking itself because it's it's
grandfathered in with trust it's
grandfathered in back in the 50s or 60s
or 70s and it can't be broken because
interest groups paid for it they paid
for
it I'm telling you how it
works so then you carry the poison and
your children carry the poison so when
your child has a thyroid problem that's
your child's body attacking itself
that's how poison this is it's it's it's
dark it's dark just going to say it I
told you to fasten your seat pulse
today
and so you need to know to protect your
children your
children to know that it's not your body
attacking
itself and it's so incredibly important
and to know that labels are just
names they might make us feel a little
better they might give us identification
so we can you know we could if we we
need disability we got a name that the
insurance company will accept all that's
important but the label still don't cut
it they don't cut it as far as knowing
what's going on and what's wrong but if
you know the truth and your body is not
attacking itself and not destroying
itself your body is not going after your
thyroid it's attacking something else
something else it's going after
something else in your
body if you know
this you just took it to a new level
you're extracting that poisonous
grandfathered law that sits in there
that sits in there to take you down
because I'm going to tell you right now
because research and science doesn't
know what's going on with your health
deep inside with your bodies it's better
to blame it on you it's not good to
blame it on research and science we're
not allowed to do that you're not
allowed to blame it on research and
science not at all not at all
you're not it has to be blamed on you
you have to take the hit you have to be
the Fall Guy you got to be the one your
children have to be the ones that take
the hit they have to be the ones because
research and science don't know what's
going
on so then you got to take the hit it's
your fault so hey when you have a
thyroid problem it's your fault as
you're driving away from the doctor's
office it's your
fault whether you know that consciously
or not in the moment it is going to be
subconsciously in there and creep out
and creep out over time and then you're
going to be like what is my body doing
it's letting me down my body's letting
me down the wrong track my body is
totally giving up on me my body's faulty
it's genetic my genes are screwed up I'm
messed up it's all going to come through
whether we like it or not this is yeah
this is Hardcore stuff we're talking
about
today because this stuff is like a
dangerous spider
it sits inside us and it has to be
removed now if you
know check this out okay if you know
that your body is protecting you it's
protecting you it's looking after you
it's on your side it's not letting you
down at all it's riding on your side
it's for you it's there for you it loves
you unconditionally it cares about you
it's by side if you know your body is
working for you it's working for you and
it loves you and it loves working for
you something different's going to
happen something different's going to
happen that's just a piece of it it's a
big piece of it this the foundation
we're talking about the foundation right
here the guts of the foundation we're
not messing around if you know your
body's working for you and it's on your
side and you're ready for this take it
to the next level to Next Level so you
got these symptoms you got these
conditions you got these diseases you
got these illnesses you got all this
going on you got multiple sclerosis you
got systemic lupus you got Hashim Modas
you got colitis you got psoriasis you
got whatever it is you got going
on there's a real cause to why it's
happening there's a real cause there's
something really going on there now
here's the next level if you know that
your body is not only not only loves you
and is on your side and is working for
you and is there for you and is is
working hard and not giving up on you
and is connected to you and connected to
God and connected to everything and your
body's there and it's after something
else though it's after an Invader it's
after an Invader because here's what
autoimmune really is it's something
that's in our system that invaded our
system that our bodies out to destroy
and out to kick its butt and out to move
it out of the body and that's what's
going on and it takes it to a new
level
so when it comes down to lupus for
example lupus is a viral Condition it's
a virus the body's not attacking itself
the body's not going after itself the
body's not attacking kidneys it's not
attacking any part of the
body it's a viral Condition it's a virus
that wants to attack a kidney or the
virus that wants to attack tissue it's a
virus that causes the trouble it's a
virus that
that actually eliminates poison too so
it eliminates poison it creates poison
it's a virus that causes the attacking
now you might think that's scary but
it's not scary I'm going to tell you why
because when you know you got an
unwanted house guest that your body's
kicking
out it's a whole new game it's a whole
new game you start winning the game fast
I've watched thousands of people win the
game over and over again over the
Decades of my life I've watched
thousands of people heal from the worst
stuff you could imagine I don't care
what it is from the worst situations
from being in wheelchairs sick with
mystery conditions mystery multiple
sceris mystery everything and get up and
walk and live their life and they're out
there gardening and they're driving in
their
cars I've seen people with the worst
symptoms and the worst conditions
recover over the years because they knew
information that was finally real not
grandfathered in and and hidden under
bureaucracy of of the medical world
hidden
under funding old funding and old trusts
and everything else involved and then
poisonous information spread to the
leading Health experts right now that
that use fruits and vegetables and say
stay away from gluten talk about
triggers and they talk about great stuff
but they still are they still are
missing the greatest point that stops so
many people from healing the greatest
point of all time for us for our
children which is the body does not
attack itself it's attacking something
else it's going after something else you
see right
right and and it's important to know
this so what happens is with say
Hashimoto thy itis your thyroids
inflamed because there's a little bug in
there there's a little bug in the
thyroid that got in there happens to be
the Epstein barv virus that slipped into
the
thyroid and that's what's creating the
inflammation not the body the body
creates antibodies to go after the virus
itself to be working with the immune
system itself hand in hand to go after
the virus the body does not create one
harmed cell
there's nothing the immune system can do
to create one cell that will harm your
body on any level your immune system
will not harm a single cell of yours
that has to be known that has to be
impregnated within your soul in your
mind it has to be there you have to have
access to that you have to have access
to
that so what's happening like with
hashimotos thyroiditis you're your
bodies after a virus that's the virus
Epstein bar that gets into the thyroid
now leading Health experts that that
actually recently took my information
over the years of how Epstein bar causes
the thyroid problem they're still too
afraid to admit that that autoimmune
isn't the body attacking itself they're
still too afraid to leave those
grandfathered laws because they're
afraid it's going to it's going to get
them to look bad out there maybe they'll
hinder the careers or something like
that don't want to leave that thought
process but what they do is they do say
well Epstein bar could be a little bit
of a trigger oh so can this and so could
be no that's not it it's the virus
itself that gets into the thyroid this
is way more advanced this is way more
serious and when it comes down to your
health do you want to know the truth do
you want to know the truth or you just
want to know like just the skewed
tainted versions that or the nontruth or
misinformation or misconceptions would
you rather have those would you rather
have all those and that's a people live
by that's what they're using that's what
they're out there doing I think you
would like to have the truth I want the
truth I would love the
truth so when it comes down to
Hashimoto's the virus gets into the
thyroid and it's wreaking the Havoc
that's causing the
inflammation and then your body's trying
to your body's not
inflaming or or attacking it's meaning
your own tissue it's going after the
virus the virus is inflaming the virus
causes
inflammation when it comes to aer's
danow syndrome connective tissue
problems that's a viral condition as
well that's not a genetic condition
where the body is attacking itself it's
not a genetic condition where the body
is attacking
itself that's a virus condition too so
I'm trying to give you examples ra
rheumatoid arthritis is a viral
condition your swollen joints your
swollen nerves stats of virus
fibromyalgia which is now being chalked
up to be autoimmune is Epstein bar
creating
inflammation in the
nerves you know I saw a commercial
recently and it was like oh fibromyalgia
it's it's um research in science we uh
we believe that it's just overactive
nerves here we are what year are we in
and
fibromyalgia is just it's is
overreactive nerves that's that's what
it is meaning that's what research and
science believe it
is Fibromyalgia is caused by one bug
only it's caused by the Epstein bar
virus now not every every autoimmune
condition is caused by Epstein bar no I
mean there's the shingles viruses
there's hhv6 there's all the different
viruses that cause these there's heavy
metals combined with them we're going to
cover a little bit of that there's toxic
heavy metals there's chemical agents
there's other triggers but these other
triggers feed viruses and that's another
problem no one understands yet is that
viruses eat they eat viruses feed off of
food research and science will not
showcase that information they haven't
discovered it and if they do Discover it
they sure as heck aren't going to let us
know because it will prove everything
wrong to what they've already funded
before in the past back to that silly
thing I have to tell you guys is once
those strings are attached and once that
research is funded a long time ago once
it's been grandfathered in you get
totally shaked
over you get totally shaked over that's
what happens here once all that's
happened once those internal Kickbacks
happened 50 years ago 40 years ago 80
years ago whenever it was that research
was done and someone said viruses don't
eat anything that's not how they
recreate once that was put out there
it's hard to
change so even if research and science
discovers that a virus feeds off of
mercury it feeds off of mercury they're
not going to tell you it has to be me
that tells you because I'm the only one
that released that information out there
yet in
history but that's the whole point what
was the gift I was
given I was given that gift so I can
give you this information I'm relying on
getting that information to
you so triggers are things that feed a
virus that causes autoimmune so if
you're eating gluten gluten is something
that a virus will feed on that's Unknown
by research and Science and no expert
knows that yet and if someone did speak
of it it came from originally from this
Source it's important to
know that it's the triggers that feed
and instigate and break down the immune
system system allowing the virus to get
stronger so like in Lupus if you're
eating gluten and gluten is flaring up
more butterfly rashes that's because the
gluten feeding the virus that's
releasing a poison causing the butterfly
rashes see the virus feeds off of food
creates poison causes the rash exmos
orasis that takes the virus inside the
liver it's a liver problem where the
virus resides Xmen psoriasis is not the
body attacking the skin it's attacking
the Derma attacking it's not doing that
what xoras is is that's a toxin it's
called a dermatoxin and I'm not talking
about the dermatoxin where science of
research classifies a dermatoxin say
when you get something poisonous put on
top of the surface of your skin and your
skin reacts that's called a
dermatoxin I'm talking about an internal
dermatoxin that Spirit has provided me
with the information with that doesn't
exist somewhere so if you go on you're
and you're on the internet and you're
looking okay dermatoxin oh wait what's
this no that's not the dermatoxin we're
talking about so it's important to know
this so you don't get lost out there the
dermatox that I'm talking about is when
a virus feeds off of certain foods that
create a different poison that leeches
out from the liver goes into the
bloodstream and surfaces through the
skin causes ex and
psoriasis in this case there's a couple
different viruses mainly the epine bar
those sits inside the liver feeds off of
high levels of copper old levels of DDT
cuz DDT is still everywhere still in the
it's still in in the reservoirs still in
everybody's drinking water just so you
know DDT still in everybody's drinking
water I hate to say it but it's true in
life changeing Foods I talk about the
unforgiving for maybe some of you are
familiar with it maybe maybe a bunch of
you haven't seen that book yet but the
unforgiving four one of them is DDT and
its cousins pesticides that's one
another one is heavy metals that's
another one the other one is the viral
explosion which we're talking about now
the
viruses and the other one is
radiation what happens is viruses like
an Xmen psoriasis you have a virus
inside the liver it's feeding off of
high levels of copper old DDT some other
garbage it's producing a dermatoxin
specifically that irritates seriously
irritates skin inflames it devastatingly
and it's it's it surfaces up to the skin
and inflames Flames the skin really
bad and that's with exus Isis but it
takes a virus feeding off of something
is what I'm trying to tell you and
that's that's so far ahead of science
and research right now it's it's not
even funny it's so far ahead years ago
when I was younger I told spirit I
laughed at Spirit and I said spirit I
don't I don't believe you science of
research they got it all under
wraps I mean we're talking science and
research because you know why because on
TV when I was a child I saw a rocket
ship heading to the Moon you know that
whole thing
Nassau now I was like there's nothing
Spirit there's nothing you can tell me I
mean there there's a rocket ship going
up into space we went on the moon
there's there's you know there's there's
space
shuttles and I said to Spirit there's
nothing you can tell me I said to Spirit
I was I was trying I was being you know
silly I said there's nothing you can
tell me that's Advanced that isn't here
there's nothing in health that they
haven't figured out they got it all
wrapped up they got a cure for AIDS they
they'll find a cure for AIDS tomorrow
they got it wrapped up spirit said no no
no no no silly silly
boy silly boy you have no idea and
spirit taught me and spirit said no
that's not how it's going to
be
and I mean look at the technology we
have today but yeah children are sick
with autoimmune moms are sick they can't
feed their kids take care of their kids
they can't even hop in cars and drive
because they're too dizzy to drive
because you know and they have all these
different
diagnoses including Lyme disease Lyme
disease wasn't classified autoimmune
because of the fact that they they they
singled out a bacteria which by the way
is still really flawed and anybody who
knows book one of medical medium read
the lime chapter and you'll know about
lime more than any anybody
will but the bottom line is it's going
to be all falling into categories into
autoimmune because as years go
on research and Science and medical
communities are going to be like well
you know Ms is now autoimmune cuz we
really don't have our hands on it we
don't have our finger on the pulse
Celiac is autoimmune you know vitil Lego
any Vio anything to do with skin
anything to do with you know lupus
anything type 1 diabetes we don't have
our we don't have our handle on it so
it's all got to get filed into
autoimmune
category and it's going to keep on filed
in then new labels will be created too
and keep on filed in because it's it's
got to be your fault it's your fault
it's your body attacking itself it's
nothing else than that it's your body
attacking itself and leading experts in
the alternative field to be like well
you know it's immune system problems
because you know and it's triggers and
and all this no it's more than that it's
it's what I'm telling you right
now but the foundation has to be in your
hands you guys it has to be where you
know your body isn't destroying itself
when you know you got an Invader that
you want to kick out of your home and
when you want to kick that Invader out
of your home something changes and
something
happens something happens with your
immune system it gets the strength it
needs your thoughts in your mind and in
your head and in your brain in your soul
your thoughts go to your immune system
and you say haha I knew you were you
were your immune my immune system was
working for me I knew you guys were
working for me I knew my body wasn't
harming myself I knew something else was
inside of me that was going on that I
want out and kicked out I I knew it this
Foundation is critical for you to heal
it means everything I promise you that
it means
everything seriously I promise you
that so when that message transfers to
your thoughts to your brain to your to
your soul to your immune system it gets
your body to eliminate the poison that
virus starts to break down it starts to
break down because it gets a message
fast
you know what it
is that you know what it
is and if you start robbing food from
the viruses that create autoimmune tags
and labels these illnesses and
conditions when you start robbing food
from these viruses so they can't
multiply so they can't continue to
poison
you in the thyroid healing book there's
over 80 symptoms and conditions like EXP
exp laain in detail and about how it's
occurring it's very important to
understand and we're going to cover a
lot of that right now
too so with Xmen orasis I covered a
little bit about how that works with the
virus with lupus lupus is the Epstein
bar Epstein bar we talked about before
you heard that comes in different shapes
and sizes different strains different
mutations different varieties different
groups I've been able to classify these
groups cuz I can't rely on science to do
it so we classified these
groups and with
lupus which is completely not even
diagnosable you have to understand it's
diagnosed by the eye all the different
in inflammatory markers that we use for
testing lupus and
ra those those are just inflammation
markers testing levels of
inflammation that's what those are for
um cative protein you know Ana an the
nuclear antigen all those are just
they're just for testing for levels of
inflammation but the mystery is still
there and with lupus it's Epstein bar
and the problem is with how it works is
I've said this before that almost every
autoimmune disease is eventually going
to be filed into just Lyme disease
category because that's how confused
everybody is they're so confused it's
going to be pushed off I bet you some of
you listening have been diagnosed with
lupus M and Ms and then finally lime it
just gets pushed off into Li I'm not
saying that's right either it's not
right but the point is it gets pushed
off everything's going to be pushed off
into it and that's how it's been that's
how it's
going so with lupus it's about also high
levels of heavy metals Mercury lots of
mercury having the virus epsteen bar
feeding off of mercury creating a lot of
neurotoxins in you know causing
butterfly rashes causing damage to
tissue in the body causing weakness
causing fatigue causing reactions all of
that multiple sclerosis that's also I'm
covering the Epstein bar varieties
anyway multiple
sclerosis 100% Epstein bar coupled with
toxic heavy
metals and you know and and with
multiple sclerosis you can get the
lesions on the brain most of the time
almost all the time that's not even
what's causing people symptoms is is
some of the different dark spots there's
a lot of people with all kinds of
different spots inside their brains I'm
talking about people that are walking
around every day that don't even know
there there's so much going on inside
people's brains there's all kinds of
calics there's crystallizations there's
uh dark spots brown spots there's white
spots there's there you know deposits of
heavy metals there's deposits of of of
um MSG there's deposits of chemical
solvents there's all kinds of different
things in everybody's head and a lot of
times it comes up whether somebody has a
symptom or not in a CAT scan say someone
can't tell you how many times people who
have come to me over the years say yeah
I banged my head I banged my head on my
car door pretty hard so I thought I'd
get a an MRI my doctor recommended an
MRI cuz it banged my head pretty hard
and they found a little spot in there
that spot apparently was there all this
time I can't tell you how many people
have different spots in their head and
and but it's not causing it's not
causing their symptoms what happens with
multiple sclerosis you get a whole bunch
of people with mystery multiple
sclerosis with nothing showing up in
their brain you get a whole bunch of
people with stuff showing in the brain
but it's Epstein bar and deposits of
heavy metals that are involved it's a
virus and deposits of heavy
metals
um and you know alopecia is an
interesting one because that's an
adrenal condition where there's
different hormones in the adrenals that
are undiscovered by research and Science
and one of the hormones undiscovered by
research and Science in the adrenals um
is responsible for keeping your hair on
your head and when that diminishes and
science research will never know it
diminishes CU they've never tagged it
they've never discovered the the hormone
so so that's how hair falls off with
alopecia and alopecia can come back when
you keep on you know healing your
adrenals and all the different stuff we
do for adrenals here at Medical medium
um we keep on going Hashimoto like I
said before that's a virus entering into
the thyroid and there's a way of
cleaning that out I don't like just
management management is taking away
some triggers like gluten and so forth
and living a better lifestyle which of
course we all want to do I don't like
just relying on those for
managing conditions I like knowing we're
going after something I like knowing
we're going after something and in the
back of my mind I'm not thinking my
body's you know betrayed
me because that's what we're taught
instead I like knowing we're going after
something because I like the truth the
truth matters I like knowing we're going
after a bug so like with Hashimoto it's
not about just getting symptoms better
that's that's great we want that but we
want to make sure that 10 years down the
road it doesn't flare up again no matter
what fancy expert showed us a new pull
away triggers protocol and some you know
New Tricks about how to minimize or
break down hashimotos or anything I want
to go past that I want to go way past
that you guys I want to do what I've
done all these years I want to go after
the virus inside the thid kill it off
kill it off so that down the road your
Hashimoto can't come back so your
thyroid doesn't fall apart like that
house that mystery house condition I'm
talking about at the beginning of this
whole webinar where the Pain's peeling
off the walls but it's brand new paint
the water's leaking the ceiling but the
Plumbing's fine I don't want want that
happening 10 years down the road I want
to go after that virus and kill
it yeah I know it sounds pretty pretty
tough sounds pretty tough but that's
what happens when you know that's what
it is you can go and do it so then you
can come up with your plan you can come
up with your game plan so not only is it
it taking away
triggers removing triggers that feed a
condition we're going way above and
beyond that we're realizing that the
virus can feed on things that causes
Hashimoto and that that's so far
advanced in ahead of everybody it's not
even funny I'm saying that so you don't
get lost I'm not saying that because I'm
trying to be Mr big man I'm saying that
because you don't get lost because you
can you can leave here and be like oh
look at this and and that's what anybody
can do that's normal human nature I
totally understand it's so easy to do
that but I don't want you getting lost
you have to know that you're going after
a bug and you're going after and you're
killing it and that's the whole point
that's what it's about so that you don't
have a thyroid with nodules long down
the road that keep on growing because of
Epstein bar causing Scar Tissue so you
don't and calcification so you don't
have a condition let eating away your
thyroid down the
road and in one year sure you got your
your numbers better at the doctor's
office doesn't mean you don't have the
virus cleaned up that's the whole point
it can come back but it can't come back
and it can't haunt you when you know the
truth that your body's not attacking
itself because if you don't know that
down the road two years from now you be
like oh here it goes my body's my body's
attacking itself again because my loose
blus symptoms are back my thyroid
symptoms my numbers are off again even
though I got great results from the last
expert that told me to remove some
triggers and I got great results but all
of a sudden my numbers are climbing
again because hey my my body might be
attacking itself again
right I mean I bet you some of you have
been through that already some of you
I'm not probably not all of you but some
of you have probably been through that
already you're probably nodding your
head like yep I've seen that you don't
want that happening you don't want it
coming back you don't want it creeping
back up and you don't want that whole
poisonous thought saying well you know
here goes my body again betraying itself
I had it under control now my body's
betraying itself again no your body's
not betraying itself it's not attacking
itself can't say that enough and we're
going after the problem that's what
we're going we're going after the
problem so when it comes down to it
comes down to like Celiac right Celiac
or remove gluten you got this genetic
problem chocked up the be genes it's not
genes it's not genes Celiac is
inflammation in the intestinal lining
from bacteria and
viruses that's what that is and if you
eat certain foods protein from certain
foods like gluten and so forth it can
feed the virus or the bacteria and
create a mysterious
inflamation and throw everything off I
mean it's just it's that
simple it's that simple so it's
important to understand these
things colitis is the shingles virus
that's the shingles virus sitting inside
the lining of the intestinal tract
that's what kitis is the colon It's the
shingles virus sitting inside the lining
of the intestinal tract
it's a virus sitting
there and that's a colitis is so when we
take away dairy products and we take
away gluten we stop feeding the virus we
start getting it better but you need to
know that colitis isn't your body
destroying its own colon that is in the
way of healing knowing that instead you
got a viral condition that you're
working on killing off and
healing
see it matters to know your your game
the goal the goal end game it matters to
know where you're going to win winning
matters when it comes down to health and
heck you don't even have to think about
winning if you have the right
information you just start to heal it
happens along the way type 1 diabetes is
an injury to the pancreas not your body
attacking the pancreas type one type
1.5 it's not your body attacking the
pancreas it's not an autoimmune
condition instead it's a viral condition
or it's injured tissue from a viral
condition at one point or even a toxic
bacteria that injured the pancreas at
one
point and that tissue in the pancreas is
injured and that's how type one
occurs it's an injury to the pancreas
not caused by your body very important
to understand you you could always
listen to my my diabetes show can always
listen to
that um so that's important to know too
hepatitis hepatitis A Hepatitis B C D is
all viral they're just different stages
of what the virus is doing to the liver
so all the hepatitis that's not
autoimmune autoimmune liver conditions
hepatitis A B C and D and the term
autoimmune
hepatitis is a mistake All In its own
with research and science they don't
even know what virus hepatitis C virus
or Hepatitis B virus is they have no
idea cuz they've never found it they
only find inflammation and markers and
those antibodies that aren't destroying
the liver antibodies the immune system
is creating for
you to go after a virus involving going
after a virus the virus that causes all
hepatitis is varieties of the herpetic
family and you know mainly the Epstein
bar does the
hepatitis skin rashing
Mysteries most of the skin rashing
Mysteries are shingles variety exer and
psoriasis is can be a hash Posh of a
couple different viruses the Epstein bar
and the shingles both inside the liver
feeding off of high levels of copper and
DDT but a lot of different mystery skin
rashing conditions including lupus are
you know different you know you know
like lupus is is the Epstein bar
releasing a lot of neurotoxin a lot of
Dermot toxin but a lot of people have
both shingles virus and epine Bar in
their system creating a lot of
dermatoxin and a lot of different you
know varieties of of neurotoxins a lot
of these mystery shingles varieties
family of shingles but they won't
diagnose with shingles because it
doesn't have that textbook one
grandfather textbook law you have to
understand like
shingles basically research search and
science believe shingles is just this
one type of shingles the one you see on
on the TV commercials they don't know
there's over 31 varieties that that that
spirit and I have sourced 31 varieties
meaning s I've sourced from Spirit that
have helped people with it's in book one
too I talk about it in book one medical
medium but instead let's blame it on you
that's the whole point let's blame it on
you guys that's the fall Fallout it's
all blamed on us all mystery illness is
blamed on us that's where it
goes and then not only blamed on us but
if you go to the best alternative
practitioners it's blamed on what we're
doing that's not good enough either look
you're hearing it from me I tell people
if you're doing this and you're eating
dairy products and you're eating
eggs and you're eating gluten and you
know and you're doing this and that it's
not good you're going to hear that from
me but you're going to hear something
else because you're going to be feeding
something inside of you that is causing
this condition I condition you're going
to hear the truth and it's not your body
destroying itself but research and
science wants you to believe your genes
are faulty you got bad jeans jeans are
so seductive in a way because they suck
you in jeans are so
tantalizingly you know like alluring
because it's genes it's like it's it's
science hey hardcore science we we're
made of genes we got these hereditary
traits we're but you need to know on
none of these illnesses I have mentioned
here have anything to do with genes and
many more don't have anything to do with
genes on any level but genetic science
is grandfathered in going all the way
back with the genome projects of the old
days of the
1940s 1950s 19 late 1930s it's
grandfathered in by law there are
documents piled so high up in somebody's
Vault that makes it so you're going to
think genes are going to be the reason
why you and your children are sick and
your grandchild children is sick for the
years to come and it's your body and
it's you and it's your own faulty genes
and they're going to have the answers to
how to fix your jeans it's one of the
greatest greatest mistakes of all time
and it falls into the ballpark of your
body's attacking itself as
well so how do we clean up these
autoimmune diseases and conditions and
and illnesses how do we clean these
things up how do we do what we need to
do what's right taking triggers away is
critical but knowing what you're doing
and why you're doing it is more critical
with it making sure you're eliminating
toxic heavy metals because they feed the
viruses that cause these conditions so
you want to remove these toxic heavy
metals that's important you want to
start bringing in foods like the wild
blueberries you can get the Frozen wild
blueberries you bring those in because
they start pulling out heavy metals you
want to bring in some spirulina I said
it before in book one and I think in
book two life-changing foods that
carella is not as good as spirulina
spirulina removes metal holds on to it
longer and helps get it out of the body
carella drops it
instantly I said this in the books and
then I recently saw on the internet
somewhere someone who
even read my book still saying
that no Corella is better it's way
better the science behind it you name it
I don't care about science and research
I care about it in a lot of ways but I
don't care about it when it comes down
to your chronic illness because it never
has it right when it comes down to your
chronic illness I'm just being honest it
never has it
right and you want what's going to work
s sparina really takes out the metals
it's not sloppy it doesn't drop the
metals cilantro is a great one
but you want the metals out so that's
one thing you want to do but always keep
in mind that when you're dealing with
autoimmune just any sense of it
regardless of what it is meaning you get
a diagnosis whatever that could be
whether it's Hashimoto or anything or
anything else we discussed already um
the different names and labels and
diseases and illnesses whether it's
eamus rasis Hashimoto whether it's lupus
whether it's rheumatoid arthritis always
keep in mind that heavy metals
they're not the cause of Lupus they're
not the cause of
Hashimoto and they're not the cause of
different things they're just they're
they're a food heavy metals are a food
and always keep that in mind that it's
it's a food just like when you're eating
a
food it's the same thing so when you're
eating the eggs that feed an Invader
that feed a pathogen that feed a virus
causing lupus causing Hashimoto being
able to get that strength and causing
Hashimoto when you're feeding that virus
with a food it likes to feed off of or
it likes to eat when you're doing that
realize that there's also other foods
and heavy metals are that food and
that's you know that's the whole thing
is the heavy metals the Mercury the AR
arsenic um cadmium lead nickel nickel's
another one that's really out there it's
inner system alloy
um steel actually steel you know what is
steel it's steel can be a different
blend of different things but it's the
it's literally these things can get into
US Mercury being the worst aluminum and
um and so and as far as when it comes
down to uh labels like meaning labels we
get given we were given for you or
diagnosis for a condition and realize
that whatever it may be that's in the
autoimmune field or Arena that we want
the heavy metals out of our system we
want the heavy metals out of our body
because it's an additional food is what
it is like the copper like you know too
high of copper inside the liver when it
comes down to examon psoriasis for a
pathogen to feed off of for a virus to
feed off of so that virus will feed off
that copper so you want that you want to
lower your metal load so not just lower
your spiral load like I always say with
all the different things it's lowering
your metal load lowering lowering your
heavy metal load and when you're doing
that I like the heavy metal detox
smoothie that I've always recommended
it's on the blog I got a Blog with it
you know the whole bit you guys know um
sure many of you might have known that
and you know it's the spirulina it's the
vimer barleygrass juice powder um it's
the Atlantic uh sea vegetables the
Atlantic
douls that that's also incredible to
have in there the
cilantro and the Frozen wild blueberries
all of these work together they all work
together it's just one doesn't do all
it's they all work together because they
hold on to the metal and take it to a
certain degree certain part of of
eliminating out of the body that takes
it to a certain degree of eliminating it
out of the body and then that next thing
grabs onto it that's how it works that
next um like the barley grass then grabs
on to it then the dols takes it down to
the end you know and the cilantro is
extracting it from organs then the wild
blueberries extracting it from the brain
all these things matter and so the heavy
metal detox is a great a great um way to
pull these Metals out over time doesn't
happen in one day although metal leaves
in one day heavy metals toxic heavy
metals are leaving in one day they they
they're leaving the body in one day when
you start drinking that they start to
leave the body in that one day but they
they it's a slow process a slow process
and then the body needs its time to heal
and the virus needs to be the viruses
and pathogens need to have their cut off
where they're not getting fed anymore
all this matters and it all helps to
eliminate autoimmune something to just
be focused on to something to really
think about the other thing is you you
don't want foods that feed the viruses
that create autoimmune you don't want
Foods doing that you don't want eggs I
know eggs are considered a perfect food
I mean I have to tell you how many times
how much information I put out about
eggs feeding viruses they're literally
they incubate a virus that's what they
do I don't care if they're free range
pasturised in your backyard I mean free
pasture past pasture you know like
they're just able to walk in grass and
Peck away it's all better better than a
conventional egg that's contaminated 10
time 10 with it injected hormones and
aluminum God forbid everything else but
the point is is that eggs in general no
matter what and where they feed all the
viruses they really instigate lupus PCOS
they're really terrible for PCOS
it's it it's sad when I see some of the
best doctors out there like no you got
to eat eggs if you got PCOS you got to
eat lots of protein lots of eggs it's
disastrous for ovary issues dis asterus
it also feeds every virus that creates
literally every different virus every
different bacteria that creates every
autoimmune condition that's labeled
autoimmune out there with
confusion and those eggs can really
feed the viruses so we have to think
about that we have to be cautious about
it try to keep them out the best we can
now if it's the only thing you can eat
and you got no money and you got no way
to survive and you got a friend that
gives you eggs and that's your survival
I'm on board 100% then we do other
things we do other things along with it
I'm on board 100% we'll do other things
but if you can and you have the
resources and you have the ability to
keep eggs out of the diet you got to do
it how it works is the virus looks for
egg material what's egg material
hormones that are naturally in eggs
natural hormones natural hormones that
are in eggs not n injected ones not
foreign ones natural ones that are from
the chicken inside eggs looks for those
and it feeds off of
those and it uses it as fuel it turn
it's a steroid to a virus that's what
it's like it's like us doing human
growth hormone it's a steroid literally
to a virus that's how it works dairy
product same thing it's very similar
keep away from all Dairy so yeah sure I
mean there's practitioners out there now
that know better better they've learned
over the years that okay we got to take
away Dairy we'll get your Hashimoto
better we'll take away Dairy too but no
it takes more than that it takes knowing
everything I talked about it takes it
all you don't want to feed once you know
you're starving out the bug that's
creating your lupus your aer's dandro
syndrome your ra rart arthritis your
your Ms multiple sclerosis your Celiac
your vido your alopecia your psorisis
your your eczema your colitis your
Hashim Modas your Addison your Addison
by the way which is also a condition
that's that's viral 100% Graves
hyperthyroidism is not the body
attacking the thyroid it's it's the
Epstein BS one of the mutated versions
of the Epstein bar that's recreating
that's actually causing inflammation and
then the thyroid the thyroid is being is
being scarred from it from the virus
itself scarring up the thyroid thyroid
and that you need to know that's how it
works with Graves I'm going explain it
in more detail over time shog syndrome
type 1 diabetes hepatitis A B C D lyan
sclerosis stic arthritis and more all
these different conditions there's bugs
that are feeding off of stuff and once
you starve the bugs once you starve the
bugs of what they like to eat and then
you go after the bugs and you build up
your immune system and you also go after
the bugs you really become freed from
the
autoimmune confusion you become freed
from it over time and you heal over time
your neurological conditions your
neurological symptoms get
better all of them start getting better
tingles numbness aches and pains
floaters in the
eyes all of it can start getting better
anxiety
depression inflammation rashes
severe fatigue all of it can start
getting
better so let's talk about um what we
can do secret weapons here you know
supplements are critical they are
critical a lot of people though that are
so inflamed they can only handle so much
I mean go to your doctor go to your
practitioner that you love and Trust
bring them this information bring them
the supplement information if you need
to ask them about it you know work with
somebody that you love and that's always
the best way to do it anyway
but but there's a lot of things that
need to be understood one is severe zinc
deficiencies zinc
deficiencies is be is caused
by the viral issues that cause the
autoimmune labels and diseases and
conditions so getting your zinc in a
better place is a huge step huge step
makes a big difference talk here
practitioner about zinc I mean get the
right zinc we have um um like you know
this this page the page that you're
looking at right now make sure those are
the supplements that you're focused on
because they're the best supplements the
best kind the best variety the best type
they don't have poisons in them they
don't have all the citric acid in them
they don't have they're the right kind
that work it's a big that's a big thing
I do have to say that supplements matter
the kind they are the ones that spirit
and I research and make sure that are
the best so people get the best results
so on the page you'll see you can you
know click to find the right supplements
for this webinar that you know are safe
and then know that work the right ones
but you could always talk to your
practitioners about anything about
dosages or anything else but you need to
know um you need to know that zinc is
critical for
autoimmune anything
autoimmune that means all the conditions
symptoms all that zinc is is important
because what zinc does is it shuts down
viruses it slows down viruses it slows
them down when you put a little bit of
zinc the right kind that we that we have
listed a little bit of zinc in your
mouth the right kind it goes to the
thyroid and the upam bar that's sitting
in there causing hashimotos thyroiditis
or any kind of hypothyroidism or any
hyperthyroidism that virus gets hit hard
hit real hard we can't function with
with the right kind of zinc in the body
not to mention the zinc increases your
immune system's ability to fight fight
more for you so that's one thing the B12
the B12 is is important now hey you're
going to say well I know about B12 hey
this expert said about B12 I'm talking
about the right kind still to this day I
don't think the best practitioners are
us even using the adenos sil cobalamin
the methyl cobalamin with adenos Sil
cobalamin when it comes down to
autoimmune any conditions any symptoms
that we talk about all of this when it
comes down to it you have to have the
methyl and the adino they have to be
both that's what matters the adino silab
balamin has everything to do with
something that goes wrong which is the G
mutation thing it's not a g mutation
okay methylation is not a gene mutation
you can listen to the show um you know
the radio show on that next time you you
know you have a chance but methylation
problems are caused and the gene
mutations that occur on on blood work
it's which is really just an
inflammatory test it's not even a real
gene mutation you have to understand
it's caused by a viral condition viruses
cause methylation problems in order to
heal a methylation problem it's not just
the methyl folate you need you need the
adinos silab balamin combined this is a
secret weapon to stopping and healing
autoimmune problems is you need the
adinos sil cobalamin mixed with the
methab follow in is something that
nobody knew about I mean literally I've
been I I waited for the first one to
ever come out and then I've been the
person to get the information out about
it it's so important and what that does
is it helps to repair methylation issues
methylation issues or is a liver problem
because someone's been viral so long
creating autoimmune symptoms and
conditions that's really I'm going to
give you the nutshell on methylation
it's a liver condition it's when a liver
cannot um cannot
redesign chemical compounds to make them
more available for our body to use to
help heal and get the nervous system
stronger get the immune system stronger
so that's what's happening and everybody
with ra and lupus and Ms and Celiac and
even Lyme disease and Vigo and
everything we got here everybody body
has a condition where there's a lowgrade
viral issue deep inside the body or a
pathogen deep inside the body and it
usually resides in the liver many times
causing methylation problems over time
and this gets completely misconstrued
completely um um thrown off by the
medical research and science people and
they don't understand that it's because
of this viral condition Crea creating a
tremendous amount of poison toxins in
the liver so the liver
cannot do what it needs to do meaning
rearrange chemical compounds create new
chemical compounds that attach to other
chemical compounds that we ingest or eat
and combine and make methylation
possible in a
nutshell so the denal cobalamin the
methab balamin is great way these are
great starting
points for doing what you need to do if
you you may you may say hey I've been on
B12 I'm not better no no it's got to be
it's got to be the this kind this be the
dino soab balaman comined okay so that's
important to know um so that's one
secret weapon if you can handle sparina
you know a lot of people are sensitive
they can't handle any kind of
supplements where they get sensitive and
they don't like it or it doesn't feel
good in their stomach or they feel like
they don't feel good from it you know
spiralen is really good that's another
great one vitamin C now if you're into
animal products if you're into you know
make sure it's the cleanest animal meats
you know and whatever you eat I would
stay away from chicken um if you're an
into animal products I would probably
keep it a little salmon if you're if
you're okay with that and uh maybe some
grass-fed beef if you really like that
and maybe some you know some wild game
or something if you really like that but
here's the deal if you're into animal
products don't over eat the animal
Foods because you need room for all the
other secret weapons for all the fruits
and vegetables you need room for the
celery you need room for the celery
juices you need room for the smoothies
you need room for the fruits you need
room for the berries you need room for
the greens you need more room for the
cauliflower the
vegetables do not be afraid of I can't
believe till this day
still there's all these alternative guys
out there and gals talking about how
stay away from cabbage stay away from
broccoli stay away from broccoli Rob
stay away from col flower stay away from
um kale with a thyroid condition
meanwhile what's in those actually kills
off the virus and that's that's an
example right there of what happens when
you don't know what's causing a problem
so with Hashimoto thyroiditis if you
don't know there's a virus actually
causing the problem and you're still in
the dark in Antiquity land back in in in
antique times of of information back
where it's outdated already I mean this
new literature coming out is already
outdated right off the press and and
right there believe stay away from these
gorog genic Foods these compounds that
are in these Foods don't they don't even
realize that what's in that food kills
off the very virus that's causing your
Hashimoto thyroiditis you don't have to
worry about the quen compound once once
you know these people they don't know
that you get in trouble you keep away
from kale which is incredible for any
kind of condition autoimmune condition
incredible for any kind of viral
condition so kale and broccoli you you
can't be afraid of those you have to
bring those
in but it give you some simple basic you
know powerful ways you know cucumber
juice a great way of healing from any
condition that's especially like all
these different autoimmune conditions
because it helps flush out toxins that
the viruses are creating that's another
reason why people are so sick they get
the combination of the neurological
fatigue the combination of the fatigue
and the rashes and the head spins and
the balance issues and the floaters in
the eyes and the tingles and numbness
and the anxiety and they get all these
different combinations and the weight
gain and the adrenal fatigue and
everything else they get all these
different combinations of
problems a lot of it is because you have
the pathogen and you have all the poison
it's creating that's creating all these
different symptoms it's completely a
mystery to all medical research and
Science and the best experts telling you
right now and one way of flushing out a
lot of the poison to make it simplistic
and make it easy for you so this doesn't
so this isn't overwhelming as you get
your cucumber juice going every single
day and you get a celery juice going
every single day you start removing
those poisons the celery juice the
mineral salts and the celery juice start
to clean up the liver they start to
build up your hydrochloric acid start to
strengthen the bile so you can break
down bacteria and viruses that are
inside the intestinal tract that cause
colitis it all matters so you get the
celery juice you got the cucumber juice
it's one example right there and you got
the Smoothie where we're going to we're
going to talk about that we got for you
as well that you'll see later and so
these are some of the things to be you
know to work with so some other things
with with autoimmune that are really
helpful just just basic founded
foundational pieces nettle leaf tea
nettle leaf and lemon balm nettle Leaf
capsules are fine um lemon balm tea is
really good these are powerful things
now remember when you drink a cup of
lemon balm tea when you drink a cup of
that and you think your body's attacking
itself it's not going to Harbor the
power as much as it Harbors when you
drink that lemon balm tea knowing that
there's a phytochemical in the lemon
balm itself that's going after the virus
that's attacking your body it's not you
or your body attacking it's the virus
and that lemon bomb tea is killing it
that lemon bomb tea is actually killing
off the bug or whatever bug you have or
pathogen that you have that's causing
your multitude of symptoms and diagnosis
and millions of doctor bills and
everything else and and sadness and
depression and and everything you've
been through there's a bug in there and
when that lemon bomb has a phytochemical
and it's destroying and killing that
virus in that bug
directly
Everything
Changes Everything
Changes being straight out everything
changes right
there so you got to have that in your
hand you have the power of that in your
hand so I like I like for you know I
like the lemon balm I like the nettle
Leaf nettle Leaf is an anti-inflammatory
do you know why it's an
anti-inflammatory you know why if you go
and look up like herbal stuff out there
and some top herbalist they'll be like
oh it's
anti-inflammatory it's anti- this why
why is it anti-inflammatory because
nobody knows you know why it's
anti-inflammatory because it kills
something it kills
something it's killing the
bug that's trying to bother you invade
you that's why that's how it works
that's how it works you know turmeric
same with turmeric why is turmeric
anti-inflammatory how's that possible
why is it anti-inflammatory well it's
got a flight of chemicals in there
science researchers looking into
turmeric they're finding different
alkaloids in turmeric they're finding
different you know different things that
can actually get inflammation down
that's not it no it's got phytochemicals
that are poisonous to bugs that keep
people's joints inflamed that keeps
their backs inflamed like shingles going
after somebody's back and sciatic neres
sciatica caus you know it's deep
shingles in there you don't even have to
have the rash at all I talk about that
there's there's non- rashing and there's
rashing and that's the turmeric
phytochemicals going in and killing off
lowering a viral load lowering a viral
load man it's a whole new world it's a
whole new world when you connect the
dots when you have the truth it's a
whole new
world
so Foods I want you guys to you know I
want you guys to work on squash having
that in your diet winter squash is
really good Buttercup Butternut get
those in there very important pumpkin is
actually amazing for people you get
pumpkin seeds are good too don't be
afraid of pumpkin seeds they're very
supportive for um for antiviral stuff
because they do have a little bit of
zinc in them and that's supportive but
when it comes down to autoimmune you
want the solid
Basics you want to pull out the heavy
metals you want cilantro an herb in your
diet you want the Frozen wild
blueberries Frozen wild blueberries are
a miracle on their own because they not
only pull out heavy metals out of the
brain and out of the liver and out of
the body but Frozen wild blueberries the
wild blueberries not the cultivated kind
the wild blueberries have antiviral
Inhibitors in them that means
phytochemicals that don't kill a virus
necessarily but stop it from functioning
dumbing it down that's the power of the
wild blueberry and you want want to dumb
down the viral issues you want to dumb
down what's behind all these different
autoimmune conditions if you're someone
today that
says hey look you didn't cover my
autoimmune condition you mixed missed
mine I'm just going to tell you right
now everything applies what I'm telling
you the foundation applies not only the
foundation that applies but knowing the
information that I'm talking about
applies it all applies to what's
happening with you so you can start
getting better so you can turn the tide
so when you have a really good
practitioner out there you got somebody
you love you got a practitioner you got
a Healer that's working with you already
with your autoimmune your conditions
your symptoms and everything you can
then say hey look this is the
information I have now too combined with
the help I'm getting the assistance I'm
getting out there it's going to help
it's going to change the game it's that
important it's that
critical so on on foods and different
supplements herbs like rosemary thyme
thyme tea is really good for any kind of
autoimmune a little bit of time tea
don't be afraid of that rose hips rose
hip tea great for autoimmune as well we
talked about the liposomas that's
important if you can't you know get the
liposomas we'll do the
Esty but you can do a little bit of
liposomas C to get a little bit in you
every day vitamin C improves your immune
system we know that and improves the
white count we know that but here's what
else it does vitamin C helps pull out
out all the poison that the viruses in
the pathogens and even bacteria are
creating all that poison that's creating
rashes and dermato toxins creating
butterfly rashes creating problems all
all in the body creating fatigue
neurological fatigue from all that
neurotoxin all that poison that's
involved with
autoimmune and vitamin C helps grab on
to that and and Pull It extracted out of
the body pulling that poison out of the
body you guys and getting it out of your
system so vitamin C is really important
and vitamin c does one more thing
somebody doesn't know about one more
thing it's starves a virus it gets in
the way of a virus feeding on what it
wants so let's go back to Foods if
you're plant-based and you're on all
fruits and vegetables it's incredible
from when when you're dealing with
autoimmune it's incredible so if you're
somebody that's plant-based and you're
worried that you're you're not getting
enough protein don't go that direction
realize that being plant-based is really
helpful for autoimmune now if you're
somebody who's not plant-based and you
have autoimmune and you're doing the
animal products like I said keep away
from dairy keep away from eggs keep your
you know keep at the highest quality
leanest uh protein you can find animal
protein you can find you know make sure
you do that and keep it down to a
minimum don't have protein three times a
day unless it's the only thing you got
and and you feel it's the only thing you
can eat but the point is is try not to
do it three times a day cuz you need to
make room for those wild blueberries you
need to make room for the wild blueberry
smoothie you need to make room for the
other Foods you need to make room for
the lettuces which are incredible for
autoimmune red leaf lettuce butterleaf
lettuce that's amazing for autoimmune
that alone right there
radishes dear Lord I think I I think I
heard from somebody that there's
something out there that radishes are
bad for autoimmune or radishes or bad
for thyroid or something like that I
think it was bad for for thyroid that is
absurd that is absolutely insane
radishes are a miracle food the radish
greens kill all viruses the radishes
themselves push out poison out of the
body the radishes themselves help heal
thyroids all this is important so think
about radishes make salads if you're
into animal protein make room for salads
too okay that's important get get your
you know um and look I say this to
vegans and vegetarians too there's
vegans and vegetarians that eat bread
and cheese all day well not vegans but
there's vegetarians that eat bread and
cheese all day I'm like where's your
salads where's your fruits well I just
like really this I just like this bread
and just cheese and and and that's what
I like that no that's terrible that's
terrible so you want to make sure you
have your salads you want to make sure
you have all your fixings on your salads
you want to make sure you have your your
chopped up Celery on there you want to
make sure you have chopped up chopped up
um cauliflower pieces in your salad
that's important butter Leaf red leaf
lettuce arugula arugula is a secret
weapon another great secret weapon
towards Epstein bar make sure rugula is
in there put cilantro in your salads
partially amazing for autoimmune amazing
for knocking down viral loads get
partially in there too that's really a
great great great thing to do think
about some different fruits to try if
you're afraid of fruit and you have
fruit fear and you're trapped in the
fruit fear because of the misinformation
that's out there try to incorporate more
apples try to bring in the wild
blueberries try to bring in a little bit
of melon in the morning just a little
bit don't eat a ton of it just eat a
little bit try a little very important
what does it do flushes out a lot of the
poison that the viruses
create fruit sugar does not feed viruses
just letting you guys know that it does
not feed viruses and bacteria fruit
can't feed bacteria corn syrup can corn
can okay eggs can Dairy can canola oil
can pork can if you're into animal
products I totally respect it and uh
just make sure you have I'm not an
anti-animal product um but just make
sure that you have the salads going on
and make sure you bring in some fruit
somewhere in there just don't eat a big
fruit pie right after you had a big
steak that doesn't really work that way
make sure your steak is you know try
well you know it's like you're not
supposed to put a chocolate cake after
after a steak either okay you're not
supposed to put too much after a steak
um just when I tell people if they eat a
big old they be eat big old steak for
dinner they should just be sipping tea
sipping tea for the rest of the night
because you just you don't have a lot of
room there's not a lot of room and with
fruit it fruit has a lot of water
content so you need more stomach space
so you need more stomach space
vegetables have water content so you
need more stomach space I tell people
keep your your proteins lean try to have
4 ounces and then this way you can have
room for a salad if you have 12 ounces
of animal protein it's there's not a lot
of stomach space for a salad salad takes
a lot of space is what I'm saying it's
high water content where is the medicine
the medicine whether you're animal
protein or your non-an animal protein
the medicine is in the fruits and the
vegetables always remember that and the
leafy
greens um and that's how you combat
autoimmune and what you'll see now is
the experts they've changed their their
Foods they've changed their food laws 10
years ago you wouldn't believe what it
was like now you know their food laws
are they have these healthy avocados in
there coconut oil they have salads
whether they like animal proteins or not
and they're getting people results but
let me tell you something it's even
though they're getting people some
results this is the information you need
this is the information you need to
really conquer some serious problems to
really conquer some serious autoimmune
to understand it and what's going on and
about the truth about your body not
attacking itself because this takes it
to a whole another level this is way
more way more ahead of the curve this is
way more ahead of the
curve when you're driving you want to
know what's in front of you you want to
know what's around the corner you don't
want to just be driving
blind you don't you don't want to drive
blind it's one thing you don't want to
do and that's what this is about this is
about being armed this is about being
armed with truth with knowledge this is
about having a shield this is about
having information that's powerful this
is about this is about knowing what's
around the bend so you can actually
what's around the bend so you can
actually protect your family your
children yourself so you're not driving
blind so you can see so you can
see and seeing is important when it
comes down to healing and seeing what's
going on behind
autoimmune and seeing what's happened
with it all make sure you get other
berries into your diet too make sure you
get the raspberries make sure you get
the if if you only have conventional
blueberries if you only have the big old
I call them the big old silly
blueberries they're not the little
blueberry the powerful medicine
medicinal blueberry from uh Maine the
main wild blueberries the Canadian wild
blueberries if you don't have those wild
blueberries you can't find them in the
Frozen Department get the uh cultivated
blueberries fine fine fine they still
have something to offer it's nothing
like the uh wild blueberries but still
they have something if it's all you got
it's all you got get the
raspberries get the raspberries get the
blackberries blackberries regular
blackberries just blackberries you buy
in the pint size the little clamshell at
the at the organic market they still
have more power than
clamshell regular cultivated blueberries
they still so get the Blackberry over
the blueberry but when it comes down to
the wild blueberry that's a whole
different game you get those frozen wild
blueberries out of the freezer section
that's medicine so you get the
blackberries you get the strawberries
are okay if you're into strawberries
don't be afraid of citrus if you if you
feel like you can eat citrus get some
oranges and you it's incredible as an
anti-a autoimmune antiviral food even
though some even though it's shunned and
banned out there there's a lot of foods
that are shunned out there bananas are
shunned out there now bananas are
incredible for colitis incredible for
for celiac incredible for multiple
sclerosis incredible for Lupus
incredible for ra incredible for
Hashimoto incredible for Addison
incredible for hepatitis amazing for all
the different hepatitis and liver
problems and liver conditions elevated
enzymes and liver everything going on
with the liver bananas are important so
bring those in they kill off bacteria in
the intestinal tract if people are
worried about sibo and intestinal tract
bacteria and everything else kills off
bacteria sweeps it out so don't be
afraid of banana too so I'm giving you
all the different things about foods
that can give you a good foundation to
what to do and it's really important
careful about oils try not to to overdo
oils try not to overdo olive oil try not
to overdo coconut oil you don't want to
have your food inundated with too much
oil you got to be you know use it
sparingly have some hem seeds have some
pumpkin seeds have a little bit of
coconut oil a little bit of olive oil if
you want but be be light on it okay you
know if you're into walnuts you can have
some walnuts these are all good foods
they don't feed the viruses that cause
autoimmune you can have them in there
but make sure you got the leafy greens
make sure that they're in there in your
diet dandelion greens really great for
autoimmune they help with the liver they
push out poisons that create all the
different autoimmune symptoms so Danny
lion
greens I still call it autoimmune in a
sense of saying autoimmune you guys know
the truth about it right now you
understand right now what's going on I
mean I still use the term because
everybody knows it by that
term but really you know it should be
called called something else it should
be called virus immune not autoimmune it
should be called virus immune I talk
about that in the thyroid healing book
you guys I promise you this book isn't
just like a concept and a couple hundred
pages and you read it and you put it
down and that's it that's not what this
is this is packed jam-packed with so
much truth I talk about the th if you
don't have a thyroid anymore you can
still heal they can still heal if you
don't have a thyroid anymore I talk
about if your thyroids been killed off
radioactive the Isotopes radioactive
iodine or if your vir if you had your
thyroid removed that there's still
tissue left in your that's left because
they can't remove all your thyroid and
it's still working for you and I talk
about the Undiscovered hormones science
of research has discovered that the
thyroid produces that's only in thyroid
healing and those undiscovered hormones
are in what's left over in tissue if you
had your thyroid removed and still
communicate with the
body so you can still still heal even
when you're missing a thyroid even when
you're missing half your thyroid or your
thyroid was removed you can still heal
and here's the thing all in all it's the
virus that caused the thyroid problem to
begin with and that's what's giving you
your symptoms anyway so we go after the
upstein bar that caused your virus to
have a that caused your thyroid to have
a problem for it to be removed so you
can still heal I can't tell you how many
people over the years that were missing
a thyroid that had all their symptoms
and the doctor be like well because
you're missing a thyro thyroid you're
still going to have all these symptoms
we got rid of all the symptoms as if
they didn't even have a thyroid problem
anymore because it was something else
something else that nobody knows and
that's what this is all about with
autoimmune it's like that with all
autoimmune it's something else in there
that nobody knows about in research and
science so if you're missing your
thyroid you still have a way to heal and
all these foods and supplements matter
when it comes down to that
um MSM a high quality MSM um that's also
really important so high quality MSM
that's important for um um for any kind
of autoimmune a little bit of that is a
good thing silica that's an important
supplement for any kind of autoimmune
that people are going through silica is
really
important that's a great one so always
you know consider that licorice licorice
is very anti- epscene bar very
antiviral excuse me licorice can really
help knock out and kill off um viruses
so licorice can actually really knock
off and kill off viruses it's
really uh you know an
antiviral in one of the greatest senses
so you know you can try some licorice
too it's fantastic for so many different
varieties of of
autoimmune lysine lysine a basic
Foundation a foundational amino acid
which hinders and stops the herpetic
family family viruses Len alone I've
seen get rid of so many different
symptoms and people that are dealing
with mystery autoimmune with different
labels and everything else attached to
it so elene is another thing to consider
too along the way you can take a little
bit of it even if you took some vitamin
C consistently every day a decent amount
of it if you wanted to lysine a decent
amount of it you can up your dosage you
can talk to your doctor you can up it
very
high lysine
and you got the vitamin C you got a
little bit of licorice you got a little
bit of
zinc and some of the other things we
talked about and the methyl cabalin
dinos cobalamin B12 we talked about and
you have some of the different things
you're already building your foundation
powerful
Foundation to turning the tide you're
attaching that powerful Foundation along
with the truth about what you now know
about autoimmune and what your body's
really doing for you and how it stands
behind you and it's not trying to harm
you or hurt you and it's there for you
100% And that's the power of how it
works so other Foods zucchini is really
good summer squash is really good very
good for autoimmune keep those in there
you know like incorporate these wherever
you can steam cooked vegetables are fine
that's good too you don't have to be raw
steam cooked vegetables are good if you
really like those that can work if you
are are afraid of grains because the
world's anti-rain right now but you want
grains or you still eat grains keep it
to Millet and quinoa Millet and quinoa
those are the two that are the least
antagonistic see what happens is that
all grains have been lumped together as
being Sinister because what alternate
practitioners are discovering is that
the gluten is is is is uh worsening
symptoms in people so so they find that
gluten is worsening symptoms in people
so they think gluten is the responsible
they don't realize that gluten is
feeding a virus or a pathogen that's
causing the person to have their
symptoms conditions their rashes there
whatever is going on so then they deem
all grains
Sinister so it's an anti-rain
world now I don't like a lot of grains
what I'm saying is if your symptoms you
know if you're not severely autoimmune
symptom you know symptomatic where
you're getting so you're so viral you're
not so viral immune that's what I'd
rather call it really you guys is viral
immune you're not so viral immune then
you can do probably quinoa you can do
probably a really good steel cut oat
maybe you could Pro meaning if if you
like that you can do um some
Millet as a possibility and you can try
those incorporate those if you really
want have those with vegetables and so
forth and that could be okay you can
also get away with some black beans you
can also get get away with some lentils
so lentils and black beans so those two
are good things too so whether you eat
animal protein or you don't eat animal
protein whatever you know whether you're
vegan vegetarian or you eat you know uh
animal protein you can incorporate these
in if you're really viral IM immune you
know you don't have to bring these in
you bring in more fruits and vegetables
and be better but these are still a
possibility for you so listen just know
that I stand behind you 100% with
everything you're doing anything you're
doing for yourself taking walks taking
care of yourself trying to exercise
trying to live your life trying to take
care of your family doing all the things
that you do I stand behind you I want
you to become an expert I want you guys
to become an expert you need to know
this this is so important to me that you
become an
expert and you really know what's
happening and that's what this is about
because it's going to protect you and
your loved ones and your children and
your family and your friends it's going
to protect them so you can heal thank
you for being here during this webinar
know that I stand behind you I love you
I wasn't given this gift for me it
wasn't given to me for me it was given
to me for you that's what it was it was
just it's for you it's for you only and
um I love you God bless
you