avocados that's what we're talking about
because we did the avocado episode of
the medical medium podcast you guys at
Apple podcast you can also listen to it
on Spotify
dude it's really really good you have to
listen to it that's what I just told a
friend because he loves avocados I love
avocados too I'm making a medicinal
guacamole this is different than any
guacamole you've ever seen I need you to
know that this is a medicine guacamole
there's a difference right there this it
just guacamole with a little squeeze of
lime on there and a little pinch of salt
and a little garlic in there and that's
it which is fine it's fine
this is medicine guacamole it's a
medicinal guacamole and I'm going to
show you why it's a serious herbal
medicine guacamole if you're gonna do it
if you're gonna have something like a
fat like avocados right if you're going
to do a fat like avocados make it into a
medicine if you can right
wait a minute I just see it coming right
there Jeanette says I was living in LA
in the 1980s incredible I know what
you're talking about oh my God someone
understands you heard the podcast
Jeanette you get it you know what I'm
talking about
blown away just telling you right now
you guys got to listen to the episode if
you can and on Tick Tock you guys check
it out if you can too the avocado are
you avocado toast episode you guys are
gonna love it you're gonna love the
episode I promise it's filled with
information that's important to know it
really is hello I love avocado I love
avocado too hello good to meet you I
love avocado too yes I do as well
santara's healing good to see you oh my
God I finally made alive woohoo I'm
awesome I'm actually blown away you're
here too incredible good to see you aw
love the new podcast and your influence
or imitation was spot on laugh out loud
don't make me do that imitation right
here don't make me do the invitation
right here I'm not gonna do it right
here
you've got to listen to the episode to
know what that was the influencer
imitation
yeah
so
KU said hi from Malaysia I really like
your post and show I love avocado too
amazing so glad you're here you guys I'm
making a medicine
guacamole I want you to see this this is
how I make my guacamole you may not like
how it tastes if you make it like this
you might not like it but you might love
it you might not like it but you might
love it either way you guys this episode
the avocado are you avocado toast
episode is something you don't want to
miss medical meme podcast link is in the
description I'm gonna make an avocado
toast no not making avocado toast I'm
making guacamole a killer one and I want
you guys to see it right
so you guys learn how some medical
professionals were taught to avoid the
avocado
in medical school it wasn't first of all
you guys know in medical school I've
talked to hundreds of doctors over the
years
in medical school they didn't teach you
about food and diet right we know that
and they don't don't get fooled they
still don't teach it now I don't care
what any but doctor says I talked to
doctor just graduated recently and said
what they teach about food men and
everything and diet and I was like oh
yeah that's really great and lame as
it was terrible so check this out
right
in medical school right all these years
instead of just teaching about food
which they didn't like having at least
some courses in that Medical University
instead of doing that they said stay
away from avocado it's toxic it's
poisonous it's toxic it's bad for you
that's what they said that was the
training I talk about it in the episode
understand why the avocado went from a
feared food feared man you guys need to
know the avocado was feared it was beard
I'm serious I'm just being straight out
about this this is no joke right here
feared food to to all of a sudden now
one of the most trendiest of all trends
of all Trends right avocado gotta have
my avocado toast gotta have my avocado
avocado and every single food right
I talk about why most Mexican
restaurants used to not sell guacamole
think about that one right there
all right now I know what you're saying
okay because there's a lot of experts
out there people that are like okay no
I'm an expert this and that they're
saying no way that's not possible hey W
that's not possible Taco Bell has you
know has guacamole right that's not even
possible Mexican restaurants across the
board even like Homespun Mom Pop have
guacamole you're wrong man there's a
Mexican restaurant around the corner
they got lots of guacamole you're just
no you're wrong dude that's what people
think right no I'm right I'm sorry but
I'm right you gotta hear the podcast
Episode by the way Mexican restaurants
did not sell guacamole because no one
ate it and no one liked it and no one
cared about it so they wouldn't buy
avocados and then try to make guacamole
and let it sit and rot when a mama pop
Mexican restaurant needs to survive
dollars and cents count for survival to
pay the help to keep the restaurant in
business right
and no one was eating guacamole they
would make guacamole no one would eat it
Mexican restaurants did not sell
guacamole I'm just letting you know they
did not sell avocado it was not on the
menu it was never on the menu bottom
line boom I'm just telling you in case
it's very important to know
um Apple podcast right and Spotify link
right there on the bio so check it out
in the description too and in the bio
check out avocado are you avocado toast
right Lorraine L good to see you loved
how you laid it all out in the podcast
extremely interesting and I felt so bad
for you in part oh
I am so glad you're here right
yes centaur's healing insane times it is
of course it is so let's take a learn
that there are times to use avocado in
times not to when you are sick
what
if you're sick learn how to use avocado
and learn how sometimes to not use
avocado people always say to me now
they're like you hate avocado aw you're
against fats fats fats fats you don't
even like healthy fats you're bad you
don't know what you're talking about aw
you don't know anything about health aw
you're not a doctor
right meanwhile no
as I said in the podcast I was pushing
avocados and getting the beat out
of me over it because people were saying
you wouldn't believe I was in I was in a
big health food store many many many
years ago like close to 30 years ago
doing a presentation on Avocado right
because that health food store actually
got a bunch of avocados because it was
rare you couldn't find them you couldn't
buy them anywhere
right and I did a presentation and some
guy went bananas he went berserk and he
knocked over everything and he kicked
the avocados down the aisle and he just
he went crazy because he said they were
toxic and poisonous and that's what he
learned in Alternative Health you guys
need to know something in alternative
medicine you weren't allowed to touch an
avocado in Chinese medicine
acupuncturists would never allow you to
eat an avocado
that's what it was like and guess what
no one's held accountable never never
instead everybody's just an expert you
just go with the trendy times and go
along and now you're an expert doesn't
matter what kind of crap you created
back 10 years ago in your life or 20
years ago and you're like no one's held
accountable at least corrected no one
right and instead they change they morph
like a chameleon they morph like a
chameleon and they shed their skin like
a snake and that's what people do they
shed their skin like a snake oh I was
telling you that three years ago oh no
that's not me now watch my new posts on
social media here's what I'm doing now
oh sorry I led you the wrong way years
ago because I'm a snake and I shed my
skin that's what I did I'm gonna shed my
skin like a snake because that's what I
am I'm a snake and I'm gonna trick a
whole bunch of other people and we'll go
down a different path and then I'll shed
the skin I'll be like oh hey everybody I
just put out a new post this is what I'm
doing now don't worry about those
YouTubes I did five years ago that were
completely contradictive and different
anyway
I had too much avocado that's probably
what it is today right Lisa said it was
always chips and salsa Lisa you're right
it was always chips and salsa by the way
if you guys just came on here
I'm talking about the avocado episode
avocado are you avocado toast medical
meme podcast at Apple podcast link is in
the description you guys on Tick Tock
link is in the bio right there you guys
can't miss the episode it's incredible
and it's a great episode all right I get
it I'm biased right because it's it's my
episode I put it out not true totally
Spirit of compassions episode as well
and he did amazing job Candace I love
how you don't put anything in a box your
information is straight truth this is
truth it will heal you Candace I just
want people to heal I want people to get
better the whole bit truth is truth it
will heal you Candace amazing incredible
right Michelle L they weaponize it
boom
yep exactly it weaponized everything and
that's what they do right so avocados
right every time I would hold up an
avocado years ago because I've been
doing this for over 30 years every time
I would hold up an avocado
and say this is something you guys
should eat this is something somebody
should eat it was always kicked out of
my hand basically it was considered
legit you guys for real okay it
took a lot of years teaching a lot of
people and you guys know I talk to a lot
of people throughout the decades and how
to teach that many people in health I
can't tell you how many people that are
actually now people people need options
to get off of other heavy foods and I'm
going to cover that in the next moment
but I want you to know right
that I taught a lot of people in the
health industry that you'd be very
surprised to know right that are older
now
that were staying away from avocado in
the Alternative Health field
that I taught throughout the decades to
do avocados
and to talk about them and to preach
about them and lecture about them and
get the word out that's how much work I
had to do
and right it is what it is
Lynn Fouts good to see you
um I love the message at the end of the
avocado podcast extremely empowering
knowing how food empowers you and
assists you
and assist you for who you are when one
follows what the body needs via mm
information thank you with gratitude you
guys I'm making a guacamole but but a
medicinal guacamole see now avocado what
what we're talking about here now what
you'll hear in the podcast episode is
it's an incredible transition food this
is a transition tool this is to get you
off of a bad fat right
is to get you off of a bad fat and in
the episode I talk about how the fat in
an avocado is different and has nothing
to do with Omega-3s sixes and nines and
that whole BS thing it has nothing to do
with that
the fat is a different viscosity it
keeps the blood a little thinner and
that's the reason why it's an incredible
transition tool to get you off of the
bad fats not about Omega-3s and omega-6s
it's not about that I know the vegan
doctors are talking about that now
because they have a theory
from studies that always get proven
wrong over and over and over again I
don't know if you guys have ever noticed
that constantly in medicine both
alternative and conventional the
theories come out the trend goes around
and then it gets debunked and then they
found out it was wasn't even studied it
wasn't even proven and then boom on to a
new Theory then on to a new Theory the
big Theory now is omega-6s are the bad
ones that's the bad ones right so an
avocado has a bag of six in it right but
avocados are still incredible for you
right it's always contradicting
contradicting the point is is the fat in
avocado is thinner they don't know that
part science research food science does
not know the avocado fat is thinner the
viscosity is different and because of
that and because it has sugar in it with
it combined so it's Nature's way of
putting sugar and fat together the right
way right because of that it's healthier
there's a healthier reason for the that
it's less of a thicker fat it has a
different viscosity it's got a thinner
nature to it it allows sugar to do its
thing because there's sugar in the
avocado as well but it's an incredible
transition tool too to getting someone
off of the bacon off of the eggs off of
the dairy products off of the cheese off
of the meat off of all that kind of
stuff the avocado is a transition tool
to get you off of the bad stuff and
that's what I talked about all these
years I'd be like
avocado get rid of that block of cheese
move that block of cheese out and bring
in the avocado
red eye banana aw well avocado combined
with potatoes cause insulin resistance
depends on healthy your liver is okay
all depends on how over the years your
liver's been beaten down stagnant
sluggish any kinds of problems or
anything like that that all depends
there too on your liver so
if you're somebody and you've been
through a lot with your health you got a
stagnant sluggish liver you've got weak
digestion weak bile reserves you got
weak hydrochloric acid right there
you're all kinds of buggy you've got
pathogens you got toxic heavy metals
you're not well you have a lot of
different diagnoses or problems or maybe
you're just somebody with just weak
digestion and in a liver issue right
that you don't know about like a
pre-fatty liver and you don't even know
where you're pre-diabetic and you don't
even know it because of your liver then
yeah if you put potato and avocado
together it's not the best of the best
because you're putting a you know a
starch and a fat together so when you
put starches and fats together you can
raise your insulin resistance right but
if you gotta if you cleaned up that
liver
right if your liver's clean and it's not
stagnant sluggish and you've got your
bile Reserve strong and you got your you
got your hydrochloric acid strong in
your stomach you've got your gastric
glands built up you got your system
working really good and you're not
bombarding yourself with all these bad
fats you're staying off of bacon you're
staying off of ham you're staying off a
baloney you're staying off a butter
cheese milk and then you do avocado
with potato you're not going to get the
insulin resistance but if you're
somebody that's you're already that
sensitive and you've been through a lot
and you're trying to and you're move you
know and you're on these other also
you're doing all these other bad fats
sure you'll just get insulin resistance
because that's what happens
so that's kind of a quick explanation of
that let's start making a guacamole
Renata says I see some people using that
combination as a detox cleansing tool
that's why I'm asking it's not a detox
cleansing tool when you put
a fat
right a fat with any kind of starch
right or you put a fat in the diet let's
just take it that down that direction a
little bit okay now you're talking about
something a little bit more complicated
here it is if you're going to eat fats
milk cheese butter eggs nuts nut Butters
nut milks avocados right peanut butter
oils meat chicken lamb turkey whatever
eggs if you eat any fat you can't
cleanse so your body doesn't cleanse or
cleanses very little very little if
you're doing a fat right so but it
depends how many fats are you doing and
what kind of fats are you doing right if
you're only doing a little bit of
avocado every other day or a little bit
of avocado each week you've got a better
chance of cleansing all in between but
yet avocado is the best fat Source one
of the best tools one of the best fruits
to use if you're trying to cleanse in
between but always know that fats in
general of all kinds stop the body to
cleanse that's why you have to listen to
the podcast you guys get a chance listen
to the podcast avocado or you avocado
toast because I talk about how if we
have fats in our system we can't cleanse
and heal and that's why sometimes it's
best not to eat the avocado if you're
sick struggling chronic illness in your
suffering that's when we don't use the
avocado right but it's a great cool to
transition people away from the bad fats
that are really preventing problems get
them on a good fat that's going to help
them transition and that's the
difference Uma Cali that's true avocados
helped me to transition from eating lots
of nuts avocado is much easier to digest
that's exactly what we're talking about
anyway thank you for that really good
wisdom you have
amazing right it's a fruit that's why
it's a fruit and that's why which is
incredible I'm making a medicinal
guacamole that's why I'm here we're
talking about the medical medium podcast
at Apple podcast right
so other stuff you'll know get to know
how the fat from avocado can be used as
a transition tool on the path to other
healing tools right we were just talking
about all of that that's why I wanted to
read that to you okay see how one person
may do good on a lot of avocado why
another person may not how about that
Michael Charles good to see you removing
the fats was the key to healing for me
after six months I brought avocados back
into the evenings
boom boom
thank you brother boom right
okay see what the deal is about omega-6
is understand why the medical media
morning cleanse keeps fats such as
avocado out of your morning routine
so that's a whole nother thing too all
on its own you guys right leave your
green salads fat to use and not to use
and I show you the recipe containing
avocado that is a great substitute when
a mom can't breastfeed so that's another
thing too so know that that's in this
episode is it the moms that can't
breastfeed how you can use avocado to
make milk okay and that's the key right
there so I want you guys to see that I'm
gonna make some guacamole right now let
me get working on it
you guys that's the plan so let's get
started we need a bowl first and then I
shall get that bowl now and I am looking
I have one right here
so yeah so I got a nice glass bowl which
I really like for this
I will get another one
let's do that so it's really great
is that
when you listen to this podcast you guys
it's got a lot of good information which
is really good too you know meaning
overall about the avocado in general
that's really helpful too so that's
great
foreign
this is why I like doing live all the
time because I like when things get like
kind of just
strange and messed up all right
I have a bowl
so we're doing some avocado first things
first I always tell everybody and I've
talked about this before too right take
out the butt right here I just want to
show you guys real quick
don't let these fall into your avocado
dish right there see that
don't let that fall in whatever you do
because that's hard as a rock for real
so if you got company over and Grandma
comes over and she loses she loses a
crown or something because she was
eating your guacamole she's gonna be
like really pissed so you take off those
butts right there if you have them on
there you see so that's really important
all on its own right
another thing too what I do is I'll take
the knife
and I'll just do this like a billion
other people probably do and have right
so I opened it
there you go
that now I don't recommend other people
to do it that way but I always stick the
knife in there like that that's one
thing I do and then I just put it right
here on the counter
and I twist it and it pops off so if you
guys see that right there
so I'm going to make an herb guacamole
but it's very potent with herbs a lot of
herbs this is a medicinal version right
because I like turning this into
medicine and that's the deal with what
I'm doing my guacamole I like turning
turning it into medicine that's what I
like to do
I like it nice and medicinal
that's the uh
that's the best the best way to do it so
let's make sure we get it in the middle
there
you know and look you got to remember
the harder the avocado is too right
never pull a pit off with your hand on
the knife I'll show you that too so let
me cut a couple of others now
I like making a big one when I make one
so I'm taking another butt off there
I like making a bigger one
now when you guys listen to the episode
there's all kinds of like pieces of
information in there that might just
skip by you it's always good to listen
to these informative podcast episodes
more than once if you get a chance you
know that's always a good thing to do
right
so never pull the pit off of there with
your hand I've seen people do this
and just literally cut their I've seen
cooking shows out there right
over the years or watch a cooking show
or something and I'm like oh what are
they doing what is that and all of a
sudden you see somebody actually do that
and they take their hand and they do
this
you don't want to do it that way you're
you're bound to get cut especially if
you have a really really sharp knife
right I put it on the board just like
that I drop it down like that and I just
give it a click like
if you guys just came on here we're
talking about the medical meme podcast
avocado or you avocado toast I'm making
some guacamole right here so I got a
nice avocado that's a good one there
don't do the real mushy avocados where
they're rotten
right if you buy avocados buy them green
buy them green great tip
if you buy them like this there's a
chance that they're bruised they've been
squeezed too many times by people
passing by the you know like people drop
them on the ground put them back up
um on the you know on the
you know shelf right there that's what
they do so what I recommend is
buy them green let them ripen
at home that's what I recommend
okay
that's a that's a really pretty one
right
and with this right here remember put it
like that and don't do it by hand never
do this
ow never do that right and you put it on
the board and you just give it a little
click and there you go comes off
and look listen
you don't even have to do this don't
even do it with a knife because I've
seen people do this I've seen people who
just don't have like a good handle on
doing this kind of thing so and they got
a really sharp knife and for the first
time they have a pick here and they end
up doing this and they miss and they hit
their hand right like wow like ah and
then you're on you're going to the
hospital right so you don't want to do
that too you want to be careful so I'll
do one more and you just dig it out with
a spoon we'll do this little one right
here here's a small avocado
right
so
there we go
and you can do a spoon if that's the way
to do it if you want you can also
squeeze it if the avocado is Right ripe
enough because I know a whole bunch of
people are like why don't you just
squeeze it aw you know you can do it
that way too but why don't like that is
sometimes if the avocado isn't that ripe
what happens is it ends up you squeeze
the pit out and you have a lot of the
avocado on the pit still so that's
another reason why I don't like doing it
and I don't when I'm busy and I'm
cruising and I'm trying to get you know
things done in time I don't want to be
trying to like bite it off or take you
know meat off the pit right it's just
it's a Time waster so that's why I do it
the other way so
let me scoop some avocado in here
okay now there is a
myth I call it a myth it's it's really
you know people put the pits back into
the bowl to try to keep the avocado
fresh it doesn't work
it's it's not that the only way you can
keep your avocado fresh is if the pit
wasn't removed out of that half right
so that's different you can't just make
a guacamole leaf and then put a pit on
top of the bowl and expect that to
actually keep it fresh that's just not
the way it works right so I'm putting it
in here you guys could see my halves are
going in here I'm not counting I'm just
making a bigger guacamole versus
um a really small one right
there we go
I don't like my avocados mushy I don't
like them over ripe they can get
fermented fermented causes trouble a
fermented avocado is not only disgusting
it tastes awful not only but it can give
you a belly ache so a fermented avocado
can definitely give you a belly ache so
keep that in mind right so this is a
very thin skin one right here
and you'll find some Skins are thicker
on the avocado some are thinner so
now some avocado varieties you can eat
the skin
some it's not a good idea
okay
so you guys if you just came on here
we're talking about the avocado episode
I just released check out the link in
the description you guys listen to it
later if you want right
the episode's called avocado are you
avocado toast it's informative it's it's
got a lot of information in there about
what's going on Courtney Ann says a fine
array of vegetables from the garden
thank you I'm honored a lot of herbs
here gotta tell you a lot of herbs
sitting here so um I want to show you
those herbs too because we're doing a
medicinal guacamole and this medicinal
guacamole is about using herbs so it's a
medicine guacamole right Olivia Lutz yes
you can be fat free forever that would
be ideal actually I would read the books
people laugh out loud you can be on the
369 advance for a lifetime yes you can
100 accurate information and Powerful
information for somebody who's been
really sick chronic illness and it needs
to heal and they need to be on it for
years to finally get past what they've
been fighting in their life their their
sicknesses and stuff Renata says aw a
bit of skin went in the bowl yeah I know
I know you got good eyes you got good
eyes we will find it if we can I don't
mind if it's in there it's just that
you know if you're giving this to
company or something like that if
company comes over and they're like why
is this chewy piece of skin inside my
guacamole right but yeah it's in there
somewhere okay
so let me get a nice Fork right here for
some mashing
I will use this one okay now I'm not the
thing is like what people have to
understand right is that
this is a perfect chance to put medicine
in your food because
the fat hides
the flavor of really intense herb
amounts like when you're using Rosemary
in thyme so let's go over this a little
bit so I got some thyme right here
it's out of the garden I got some
Rosemary out of the garden too let's
cover this this is medicine right here
this herb it's incredible
now here's what I do now I cut these for
the show so I I took this off my
rosemary plant and I cut these for the
show right but I don't do that I don't
cut my rosemary plant ever I strip my
rosemary plant so here's how I do it is
say this rosemary plant is still here
and like and I'm outside right now and
I'm going up to my rosemary plant
for this show I said well I'm gonna cut
these so let me go and cut these for
everybody for this joke because I want
to show them this all right okay here we
go I cut these this is for the show now
I don't do that
this is what I do even though I had to
do for Joe this is what I do instead of
cutting them I take my hand
and I pull the leaves off but I leave
the stems so let's do that now so just
pretend this is just sitting out there
right
okay I'm outside now right
that's what I do did you see that
so when I'm making my food at home
I leave that stem like that on the plant
and then I have all the Rosemary in my
hand I'll show you a close-up real quick
now the reason why I do this is because
the leaves will grow back on this stem
faster than if you cut the whole stem
and now you're kind of just basically
cutting down and cutting back your
rosemary plant and then you're not going
to be able to use it all the time
because it's going to need to grow and
it could take a long time
so what I like doing is stripping the
plant down so it's something I want to
show you guys right there that I thought
was important
uh you know piece of important
information there
Marianne says aw please tell our friends
why they should wash them first avocados
why bother washing the avocado you can
get all the
germs you want
that's sitting there in the grocery
store and everybody's walking by and
they're all walking by and they're like
who cares they just came out of the
bathroom and he just wiped their butt
um do you know how they wipe their butt
do you know how people wipe their butt
are they good at it
right because
last I've known all these years people
who wipe their butt with the toilet
paper still get everything from their
butt all over their hands
they're not careful
so everybody just going to the store and
grabbing everything yeah and whatnot of
course that's just one thing
oh
lots of sneezing going on my God but
that's okay
you know it doesn't matter if anybody
sneezes on your avocados in the store
either who cares right
don't wash them right it doesn't matter
oh the carriage oh there's only a
hundred varieties of streptococcus on a
carriage handle but that's okay is
everybody pushing their Carriage to the
store they can just touch the avocados
and kind of look for one I'm looking for
one right here oops I Spit on them uh oh
I was talking to someone and spit flung
out of my mouth on the avocados but
don't wash them because you don't need
to wash them just just take them home
from the store and just cut right in
there and make sure your kids and you
and everybody is just eating and
whatever no big deal that's why it's
important to wash them and that's just a
couple of reasons there's a lot more
reasons right
so what I'm doing here right so I'm just
kind of mashing these lightly at first I
don't want to puree these right
okay
and the other thing is the knife
will shove the germs in
so if you don't wash the outside in the
skin the knife is going to drive all the
germs in well that's right there's no
such thing as germs like people think
okay that's why everybody just went
through hell and back for the last
couple years and chronic illness is at
its worst anyway no there's no germs of
course not don't have to worry about no
bugs
suit it makes you stronger to get germs
oh it does oh sure
Susan Janet says I saw someone remove
their mask in the produce section so
they could pick their nose
really and I bet you that one person
that did that probably put the booger on
that produce at the same time so
all right
are you trying to make me laugh because
booger jokes will do it all right let's
go
we have we have stuff to do you guys I'm
making the medicinal guacamole let's
take this serious this is about serious
medicine here in the guacamole rise with
Melton says I never washed my produce
before mm
I'm just glad you're here I'm glad
you're learning so you can learn and you
can do the things you need to do and
protect yourself it matters it does you
guys if you just came on here we're
talking about the medical Beauty
podcasts at Apple podcast you can listen
to it on Spotify avocado the avocado
episode please share it you guys can I
ask you a favor
share the episode if you can like send
it to people
just send it to them right like share it
because what that does is it spreads the
word and they can learn and heal share
the different episodes with everybody if
you can that would be awesome but I hate
asking anything of you guys right
definitely sometimes the same now
everything gets Awash all right so we
have our avocado in the bowl I gave it
kind of just a broken Mash right
to start with I don't want to puree the
avocado you don't want to turn it into
like literally a cream sauce if you
enjoy the show please leave a review on
Apple and Spotify you guys because the
trolls like to kick my butt on the
podcast they've been doing it for years
they'll love to just say the same old
craft and try to knock the rating down
so if you can guys if you can do you
should just leave a review on the Apple
podcast Right medical lean podcast at
Apple podcast if you can that would help
all right
let's get into the herbs I gotta dice up
some herbs don't puree your guacamole
you will have Brown guacamole really
fast okay just letting you know lemon
and lime stop it from browning or hold
it back from browning right
and but you still don't want to puree it
so let's move the guacamole over a
little bit
okay let's chop up some herbs let's do
that now
so I got some Rosemary right here
now this is a medicinal guacamole and
what you're looking at is a lot of
Rosemary it's the way I do it you don't
have to do it the way I do it you can do
it any way you want I'm going to strip
off more of this okay
see how much Rosemary's there look at
that I might even do a little bit more
check that out you guys that's the way I
do it
now this is very Rosemary e for real
okay like this is really serious like
amounts compared to that rosemary plant
that sits on the salmon at the
restaurant you know the rosemary plant
that sits on the salmon in the
restaurant little piece of rosemary
plant you just move it over this is like
a lot of Rosemary
and I chop it really fine is what I do
okay that's how I like it
so I get it to a point where then I'll
chop it a little bit more too
just get it nice and good
there you go
so that's the Rosemary part I'm gonna
scoop it into my hand
and into the bowl
sprinkle it right on top
see how much went in there now you may
not like the taste of this so do less
how about just baby stepping I don't
have to do a lot of that let's get some
more herbs here whoa
what's this right so I took this out of
the garden
that's lemon balm okay now I like doing
a little bit of lemon balm in the
guacamole make it real medicinal the
herbs make it medicinal avocado itself
on its own it's not medicinal enough to
take care of what we're up against right
now in the world of Health meaning the
problems people are up against the
pathogens the metals everything else
that's wrong with them it's not enough
to just eat an avocado as as beautiful
and pure and naturistic that avocado is
it's still got the fat in there and
that's okay it's a better fat but if
we're gonna eat that avocado and eat
that fat let's make it medicine because
we need things so we can fight sickness
and illness here's a little bit of lemon
balm
chopping up a little bit of lemon balm
real quick that's gonna go in the
guacamole Michelle L trolls also getting
sneakier out there with their tactics oh
you wouldn't believe the things they
said they act like they're an mmm
they're an mm follower they act like
they've been like a fan I I got all your
books but you're the worst person in the
world that's what they do
yeah um I want everybody to read this
one star I got all your books I used to
like UAW but then you're really the
worst person in the world so yeah and I
don't like the way you speak
all right so I'm chopping up some lemon
ball Michelle L used it as a vehicle for
herbs you're using the avocado as a
vehicle for herbs right so you guys
that's lemon balm right there going in
that the lemon balm going in
Kathy Kirby so should I not worry about
eating avocado while cleansing all
depends on what's Happening Reed cleanse
the heel if you can make sure you get a
brain saver book too so make sure that's
happening right in the future if you can
that's these these books are incredible
listen to the podcast listen to the I
explain in the podcast episode actually
it's in there just listen to the medical
meeting podcast
all right so check this out you guys
these are garlic chives right here
so garlic chives it's not a chive but
it's a garlic chive right it's got a
different flavor it's got a garlicky
flavor but it's really medicinal so
we're gonna put some garlic chives in
here right
you're making a medicine with your
guacamole when you do this okay
so on Facebook Karen Ryden says my
daughter is an amazing athlete because
of your healing techniques thank you
Anthony I'll tell her I'm really proud
of her incredible
she's like can guarantee you she's
working really hard
can't give the credit to me it's
definitely all she's doing she's working
hard at everything amazing
so I just chopped up some garlic chives
right there
and we're gonna move on to some more
stuff that's incredible she's using
medical medium information
so wonderful she's working hard at it
she's becoming a better athlete very
proud I truly am
so those were garlic chives now we're
going to be doing
some oregano so I got some oregano here
Oregano's got a strong flavor but when
you're using avocado
to mask the flavor intense flavors of
these herbs you're using it
right as a vehicle like Michelle said
that's what you're doing so I'm doing
some now oregano now this guacamole is
getting really medicinal
that might have been a a weed right
there from the garden
so
all right there we go got some oregano
now so let's chop up that
all right so now we have Rosemary in
there we have oregano in there garlic
chives in there
we're also going to put some scallions
in
so we're gonna have that too
now you can chop them up as fine as you
want I like it just fine enough
here we go
perfect
for me it's the way I like it
so let me just give you a little window
in this here's the guacamole coming
together
so far you're looking at a lot of herbs
in there you're looking at the medicine
it's the Rosemary chopped up it's the
oregano chopped up it's the garlic
chives chopped up right there it's the
lemon balm there's a little bit of lemon
balm in there let's keep on going
because we got some work to do Sage
right there incredible
Jane Nicole I biked 14 miles yesterday
on my 63rd birthday because of medical
medium thank you incredible wow you're
over there on Facebook amazing
now I'm chopping up Sage
think about this right here we're using
these potent herbs
so we got sage in there we got rosemary
in there we got oregano in there how
incredible is this right Sage is really
powerful
incredible
culinary Arab right
here we go we got the sage now that's
going in the guacamole let's keep it
going you guys let's get a little bit of
time now this time
I dried out a little bit
right here so I dried this out a little
bit so what I'm doing is I'm kind of
just taking it right off
the stems don't even need to really chop
this
it's dry it's nice and fine I'll give it
a light chop
here it is you got your time right you
guys know how I think about time
you guys know I love it putting that in
the guacamole let's keep on going
scallions
right oh we got some right here look at
this I always Cut Off The Roots I want
to show you guys
here's what I do Cut Off The Roots
I didn't have to cut that I could have
cut back even better than that but I was
doing that pretty quick right so
I like scallions inside
my guacamole
flavors it nicely
hides well as well as you know like if
you're somebody that's really you don't
like that onion flavor
gives it texture too so that's what's
incredible about the scallions gives the
guacamole texture
something in there right
I like my guacamole nice and
like I want things in there right
incredible any particular Sage you can
use the one that you like best for sure
so let's move on we've got some
scallions in there okay here's one
that's interesting
mustard greens you guys mustard greens
now
the World of Food Science
right
believes it's just a green
mustard greens
but mustard greens should be classified
as an herb
it's a mistake it's not classified
correctly out there people don't know
that that is an herb and it should be
classified as such very medicinal very
spicy very strong but really really
medicinal I put mustard greens that came
out of the garden because I'm growing
some mustard greens right now
now mustard greens are really too sharp
for a lot of people they can't eat them
because they're too sharp they're like
oh my God that was like horseradish in
the worst way it was so sharp okay now I
don't cut this up that fine mustard
greens I like because it's a soft green
I like it to go in just like that but
what you guys have to know
is that
that's an herb you're putting in very
sharp but the fat hides it
so you'll see here look how herb that is
like that's herbed out
there's no weed in there
no weed man so it is just straight
herb right good herb so let's keep on
moving
let's go with I think we got to do our
peppers in there some hot peppers
let's get a Cayenne
in that guacamole right now listen you
can make it the way you want to make it
you can just get some ideas here what
about that
you guys check out the medical meme
podcast at Apple podcast avocado are you
avocado toast
check out the episode I talk all about
the avocado stuff that's really
important to know
it's a great episode really proud of it
now that's a cayenne pepper here's a
jalapeno right there that can go in
there too
it's a red jalapeno happens to be much
hotter than a green when you let them go
red like that that's out of the garden I
like to grow peppers um you know I
definitely love growing peppers right
that's a sweet pepper right there and
it's not a bell pepper like this but
it's a sweet pepper I'll show you guys
if you want to see
and so this is
um these are obviously sweeter milder
this got a little bit of spice to it
right so you can cut the back off like
that
take the stem out
okay and then
so I like to cut this
pretty small
I even like the Rind up inside of it
right the pith
the pulp inside of it
I don't want to mince this until it's
too small
I like something to bite onto with this
guacamole this medicinal guacamole
and I'm gonna get that pepper in
all right
incredible
all right so let's think about other
stuff we need to put into that we have
here so I think we cover the herbs which
is really awesome so we got that now
let's get some
lemon
in here actually I'm gonna cut an onion
so looking like I don't know what I'm
doing for a second but I'm looking for
an onion right one here so with this
onion this is a red onion they're
usually bitier they're usually hotter
right
it's not a sweet onion sometimes there's
some yellow onions that are just brutal
right you guys I like to peel back the
spit the skin and I'll tell you why too
it's not that you can't eat those it's
just that they're so chewy They Don't
Really break down right like the skin
I know people like to punish me a lot of
people love that they love the punish aw
and be like the Skins were the best
stuff is hey W takes the skin off he
doesn't know what he's talking about
that proves it it's not gonna follow him
anymore he didn't know about this one
this one person says you gotta have the
skin
right
but I like taking the skin off because
the skin on the onions could be hiding
something
from the market like people like when
they're grabbing their onions and
they're you know or you know stocking
them and they got like bacteria and
other things on their hands and the the
pathogens could get up under the skin so
I like to kind of take a layer off right
now I'm going to put a little bit of
this red onion in there that's that's
what I like to do okay
like to put a little bit of red onion in
don't want it too thick don't want it
too thin
I'm gonna chop that up
flip it around for a second okay
that's going in
listen if you don't like onion if it's
too sharp for you you don't have to put
it in your guacamole you can put just
Rosemary and Sage you guys but I'm
making a really really medicinal one so
let's get the Lemon Let's get the lime
going right so we got some lemons right
there
foreign
which is incredible is
you can put lime in your guacamole now I
don't put a lot of lemon in my guacamole
I'm only putting a little bit of lemon
by the way lemon is medicine too it's
medicinal
for sure okay
I'm not putting a lot of lemon in I
don't want my guacamole watery
don't want it too too wet and watery
that's number one right
okay now check this out though
right
okay lime brings out avocado flavor like
nothing else does it has a reaction
with the sugar in avocado so lime has a
reaction with the sugar and the fat and
avocado so I love lime I like putting a
lot of lime in my guacamole
it's one of one of my favorite things to
do the flavor does it compare I feel
personally
you guys just came on here we're talking
about the avocado episode you can
obviously see I'm just a little pumped
up about that episode released it last
night I hope you guys heard it link is
in the description right
I'm gonna do one more lime so I'm gonna
go with two limes with this with
everything I got in here
someone yelled at me the other day and
said stop throwing fruit around
stop tossing fruit in the air
but I've been doing it you know my whole
life a lot of times the fruit might end
up on the floor something might hit
something I was over a friend's house a
couple years ago and I threw a piece of
fruit in the air
and it knocked over his wine glass which
I thought was funny because I wasn't
drinking wine
and the wine glass knocked over and the
wine went on his carpet
and it was a white carpet
so let's talk about salt that's the next
thing right now if you guys got a second
okay
I feel like that's perfect amount of
lime for the moment
now
everybody loves salt in their guacamole
right or pepper salt and pepper they
love salt
here's why I don't use salt in my
guacamole first of all I'm not a big
salt fan because you don't want too much
salt
in your diet because it ends up building
up it ends up building up in your liver
it can build up in your brain I talk
about that in the brain books you got to
check it out when you get get a chance
and check these brain books out
but the reason why I don't like salt in
guacamole is it sweats it
I don't want everything sweating because
what salt does in here is it sweats the
onion it sweats the pepper it sweats the
avocado so it starts to disfigure it it
starts to pull moisture out of it in the
wrong way you don't want to do that and
then it turns into kind of like a sweaty
slob so I don't like putting salt in the
guacamole I like to use lime as that
salt and then I like to use a celery
stick
as
a tool because it's a salty tool but the
right kind of salt right the good stuff
so
you guys know like I've written books
books about the the sodium that sits
inside celery right
sodium cluster salt it's a different
flavor it's a whole different kind of
composition
so
I don't like to I like it kind of a
hunkier guacamole for me you guys might
like it as a creamy puree
not a big fan of it that way but I don't
want pole halves in here so I'm just
kind of mashing up
the whole halves right kind of breaking
them up a little bit there we go
so that when you stick a cracker in
there if you have guests or something or
you stick something in there a chip
because you know someone might like some
chips that you're not getting like stuck
on a whole half of avocado
right now mixing this up
there we go
now you can put tomato on top you can
put tomato on the side you can do
anything like that
let me chop up a couple of tools one
tool I like to use which I'll show you
right here to actually scoop my
guacamole I'll show you in a minute so
let me start making
um a couple tools here
so here's one tool I use which people
think I'm crazy
but I put guacamole right on a whole
half of onion like that now I know that
like probably doesn't seem right and
someone's got probably something to say
about that I'm sure like but yeah like
you know meaning like because it looks
kind of like so intense sometimes we're
like oh my God how does he do that like
so I take like pieces of onion that are
big pieces like this and I like to use
that let me chop up some bell pepper
that's a great tool to pick guacamole on
right there
so
what you can do is you can make some
some bell pepper slices right here
so I'm just going to prepare these make
a little crudite you can have it with
your guacamole
right got some bell pepper
that's amazing that'll go in
and celery sticks is another great thing
all on its own
guys if you just got here we're making a
medicinal guacamole we actually already
made it okay so I got a cucumber
right here
now you can peel the Cucumber if you
want I wash this cucumber really good
but the thing about cucumbers though
organic produce does have they still use
a coating on the outside of a lot of
um
a lot of them so let me just see if I
can just kind of take down the skin a
little bit
real quick for you guys there we go
not going to take it completely off but
take some of it off
there you go amazing
I don't like using the skin of a
cucumber personally
unless it came out of the garden big
difference right there unless it came
out of the garden and that's another
story right there okay so I'm gonna do
is do some cucumber slices I like to do
that as an option
foreign
sticks that's another way to do it right
so I'll do two kinds
get this ready for you guys
and then I'm gonna actually cut the
sticks right here like that
okay
and get some of them like that
it's an option
all right got some onion pieces here
this is just like a quick rendition of
it like but you can go with this
why is the phone ringing
who's calling me right now
don't they know I'm doing this
so there we go you guys
cutting some celery sticks right now
which is really awesome
foreign
got that covered boom
nice
and of course
you can do some tomato some tomato
slices too
I like to put guacamole on tomato slices
it's one of my favorite things to do
we got that as well amazing cucumbers
tomatoes
get some of those in here
all right
so this is the herb guacamole right here
I don't know if it's the prettiest
guacamole but this is what it is I'll
have you guys take a look okay
so what I'm going to do is scoop some
right in this bowl right here
so this is a medicinal version
if I'm gonna have guacamole I want to
know it's medicine right that's that's
what I want to know
yes you can eat a plain avocado no
problem of course you can
definitely can do that
all right
there we go right there you guys
take a look
so what you see right here is you see
this herb medicinal guacamole right in
the center okay
and then you see some crackers by the
way for people who like crackers check
it out in my directory you guys if you
want to check out wood cracker that is
you can find it on my directory there's
no fat in this cracker at all so there's
no fat in there at all there's no oils
there's no vegetable oils there's
nothing like that in there so that's
important right there so I'll show you
the cracker
so I want to show you this too you guys
get a close-up right there there it is
so you got your beautiful red onion
okay I'm going to turn this around lost
the lost the pitcher there
there you go you got everything on you
got your tomatoes on there
you got your red bell peppers right
so
[Music]
so I'm gonna grab a tool really quick
and I'm gonna take a onion
right here
now I know this probably is hard for a
lot of people to do because onion is too
strong for them but I love it that's one
way I do it right there I'll do that as
an option
right of course you can use cucumber
slices you can use celery sticks too
get a celery stick and dip it in there
which is great
no salt
mmm
there's so many Trace mineral salts
in
all these herbs right mustard greens
have Trace mineral salts a different
kind right lemon balm even has a little
bit of it
Sage does rosemary does
and then with the lime and the lemon
honestly it's incredible I'm going to do
a cucumber one right here you guys want
to stay close up
and get a little bit of a cucumber there
right there
amazing
and you can do a tomato so this is
something I've always done as well
I'll put
the herb guacamole right on the Tomato
if you guys can see on tick tock okay
let's take a look right there I'll put
it right on top of the tomato
and that's I'll eat it too so you guys
see
um
and if you want the crunch of a cracker
right a fat-free cracker
you know
that's an option too
it's such a good guacamole
who the heck is calling me man
this is Dodger all right this is Dr
Jones though we got Dr Jones though
I graduated from the most prestigious
University of all the Medical University
you know what they told us about avocado
they told us that avocado was poisonous
and they're right by calling the right
yes I was in my mansion
I was in my Mansion oh yeah when we were
skiing in the Alps yes and they brought
us avocado and I smacked it out of the
waitress's hand I stepped on the avocado
on the floor and I told the manager at
that place since I donated a lot of
money in the area to fire that waitress
and they fired her
how dare you give me an avocado we were
told medical school that avocados are
toxic and poisonous yeah yeah
oh by the way I'm a hypocrite because
I'm having some incredible guacamole
right here I'm gonna have to let you go
you guys incredible
tone man says I thought you said
fats and carbs are a digestive disaster
rice crackers and avocados right
okay so you have to understand something
if you read the medical medium books
you'll see
the different levels that you can do see
we're not one size fits all tone man
we're not that's the whole point medical
medium information was never one size
fits all everybody can customize their
healing as far as they need to go in the
way they need to do it some people have
a stronger liver some people already
healed
they already healed they did the work
right
some people can do a few different
supplements some people can do the 369
they can customize it and then you need
options for guests so say say forget
free at it right for guests you'll have
somebody that comes over that wants like
ham and cheese sandwiches and you can be
like no have this fat free rice cracker
with this herb powerful medicinal herbal
guacamole right here
it's a matter of like having that option
too for family and friends you might
have
a family member that's going to eat a
bread and butter sandwich so you give
them a fat-free rice cracker they're
gonna eat a gluten-based bread and
butter Cow Dairy sandwich or have the
avocado with bell pepper tone man you
could do that check this out you can
just take the red bell pepper you don't
need to have your rice cracker right
boom that's how you're doing it man
and it's so it's incredible I checked it
out you guys
this is not one size fits all right but
thank you tone man you're amazing
we're being here it's not one size fits
all it's about customizing and there's
people that are going to eat avocado
anyway so guess what
have them eat it in a way that's
medicinal do you know how much medicine
is inside that guacamole right and I
believe in avocados I think it's one of
the greatest transition tools
I want you to know that I've relied on
the avocado I have a connection to the
avocado for saving people's lives I've
been able to get people
off of eggs
so their chronic illness can actually go
away I use the avocado to get them off
of eggs I use the avocado to get them
off of something bad that was holding
their healing back it is an incredible
transition tool I admire it and respect
it Darlene
he talked about this earlier about our
livers and if they are truly bad or off
or not listen to the podcast you guys
medical meme podcast at Apple podcast
check it out link is in description I'm
going to do another live pretty soon
um you guys once you've come along to
the next live I'm gonna do and I'm gonna
try to do an IG live and put Tick Tock
back on and telegram I love you guys all
right
can't wait to do this again I'm gonna
make another one