this is really heartbreaking right here
okay this is what happens when people
don't pay attention and they run over
tortoises and run over Turtles the prime
example is why I try to save them every
single day when I'm out and about and I
have to get this this this guy right
here to a Wildlife Reserve if possible
I've already called one of
them and uh nobody seemed to care so I
have to call another one um but
I have to get this guy the right the
right things he needs and to protect him
because this is this is just this is
Criminal really this is Criminal I know
people have accidents I know that they
they do this by mistake a lot of people
don't do it my by mistake they don't
care they they have a disregard for
animal life and they just run over
tortoises and turtles and and they
actually make a game of it I see it out
there all the time and it's sick and
it's delusional and um Despicable
actually so this guy right here
definitely going to put him in a box get
him to a reserve somewhere and try to
get him help because uh even though his
survival rate
is possibly you know possibly not not
going to be what we wanted to be um his
back legs are are partially
paralyzed but we have to do something
about it so I'm going to work on that
right now already have uh some things in
action right now and um and then I'm
going to take care of I have I have a a
box my trunk I'm going to go and get it
I'm going to go and get it in a moment
get him in the box and then see if I can
Rush up to a place that we care for um
but here he is right here he's
struggling he was run over looks like a
few hours ago the blood is drying on his
back um
truly heartbreaking truly truly
heartbreaking anyway I'm just going to
get working on trying to get this guy
some attention immediately so signing
off so I've already called four places
waiting for responses I'm about to
travel a distance as well but
um but I want them to just be
comfortable walk on the grass a little
bit while I'm waiting for a response
from somewhere but this is what what
happens with Wildlife rescues you may
not hear from them for a day or two but
we just do the best we can and I'll have
to be traveling a long distance and just
searching so probably going to spend the
next day maybe the next two days if he
stays alive which you know God willing I
hope hope he does
so still on hold called eight emergency
places Wildlife uh preserves and so
forth still
waiting um I just want to say this guy
this is killing me at this point I'm
hard I'm actually hard sick and
um but he's got a lot of energy and a
lot of strength left uh so has been
talking to
me um and I've been getting any kind of
guidance from
SSC um and so I'm on hold now I'm hoping
that that this is that this is going to
be
fruitful and um but I'm just trying to
keep them calm keep them
safe uh I I want I want
this
um I want this to be a good
experience where as much as he suffering
he knows that we're trying to help and
we want we want him to survive