oh hey Debbie Barn gr just opened come
on in let's
go come on come on oh I hope you don't
drive me nuts all right what can I do
for you I'm starting to getting nervous
already aw Bar and Grill is open I have
to make a phone call yeah 911 Mrs
Fergenson she fell down the stairs again
Mrs fergon hold on um you guys um just
just just just bear with me for a second
under the bar I got lots of the beverage
as we speak what would you like okay I'm
me just get you all set up here how
about you right there
[Applause]
um oatmeal cookies siloc cybin no oh
hold on another call coming through gr
two cookie three cookie four five cookie
six calm down calm down hold
on you guys I just want to show you a
couple things you guys can contain
yourself check it out W blueberry a
whole case $20 off for a whole case if
you buy a case of the wild blueberry
juice it's $20 off it's a case of 12 use
code wild2 link is description link is
in the profile I endorse y mins because
it's the best stuff there is yeah 911
Mrs fergon she fell down the stairs
again Mrs fergon hold on are you kidding
are you freaking kidding me oh my God
you guys