talking about Soul healing meditations
talking about Soul healing
do you guys know that registration is
open for the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
so make sure you sign up link is in the
description link is in the profile
hope you guys can hear me good
I am looking around
to make sure
the mics are on
just double checking is that mic on over
here
don't see looking here
okay we're ready
nothing like doing it live
there's nothing nothing like it
I'm gonna read a little bit if you guys
are okay with this
everybody is soul searching even if they
don't know it do you know anybody who
Soul search
they Soul searched before they're
soul-searching
anybody that you may know
even if they don't know their soul
searching
even if they don't call it that so it's
not like we're calling it that
says you're living your life and you
feel lonely
you feel scared you feel lost you feel
confused
you feel like you're lacking purpose
you feel like you don't have confidence
or you're losing confidence
but what happens is we're actually
soul-searching
even if someone seems like the most
confident person
like their confidence is over the top
even if someone's ego is just way up
here
I'm the best there is
you're a crap and I'm the best even if
someone's ego is just way up here
even if somebody's pride and ego and
confidence is way up here
they're still soul-searching and they'll
still soul-search
the most spiritual people on the planet
Soul search
the most awakened
people
on the planet
are still soul-searching
you can be somebody you're sitting on
top of a mountain
and you're praying
and you're sitting there
and you're still soul-searching
so many people are soul-searching they
just are did you guys sign up
because the collecting Stone's
meditation journey is going to blow your
mind it's going to be like nothing
you've ever experienced you'll never
forget it
collecting Stones meditation Journey
registration is open
the journey starts July 19th the link is
in the profile and description
when you do the collecting Stones
meditation Journey that I'm going to be
guiding you guys with
through
when you do this you'll never forget it
I promise you
on the seventh day
of the stone collecting Journey
I promise you this
you will never ever ever forget it
it's gonna be a part of your soul in
such a good way it's gonna be so
cleansing and so healing Android users
had some issues with signing up to the
registration yesterday but that's been
fixed and we're in a great place
so check it out and get signed up and by
the way it's free
free
even the most spiritual people the most
together people tle says on YouTube I
signed up oh incredible
pianoleo says yes on YouTube signed up
Elena Alexandra good to see you you're
over there on YouTube I read your
comments
so excited you said you signed up too
so glad everybody is is signing up here
Stacy Russell please tell me again the
name of the book that you will be using
for the stone meditation course this is
it right here
medical medium revised and expanded the
new edition revised and expanded it's
this book right here I'm reading out of
it now about soul searching
so this is the book
Amazon it's like dirt cheap for this
book right now it's just incredible
amazon.com us
get it from any bookstore get it free at
the library
so even if we don't know it or we don't
call it that everybody is soul searching
we Soul search because part of us feels
lost
or we don't feel whole
do you ever have that feeling where
you just don't feel like a whole person
you feel like there's a piece missing
are a part of you that's missing and you
don't feel whole
did you ever have that experience where
you don't feel that
you don't feel like you're whole or
because we feel like we're not living up
to our Soul's potential
how many people feel like I'm not living
up
to the standard that I make for myself
on not living up to my full potential
I'm not living up to my soul's potential
how many people feel that way
we Soul search because of life's
hardships too
heart the hardship scale let's talk
about that a little bit
it's interesting
I've seen people
go through atrocities
and they had
unbelievable hardships
where if they tell someone you don't
even you you can't
even
you don't have words you can't fathom
what that's like
people that have been in difficult
hardships
and those hardships take them to a place
of soul-searching
and then you have people where they had
hardships too
but the scale is so different for
everyone
for everybody the scale is so different
there's different levels of hardships
but it depends on which world you live
in you can be someone who's silver spoon
fed
right great support system not a care in
the world no financial problems
whatsoever
a family giving you support you go off
to private schools
everybody's worried about you everybody
is taking care of you
you don't have to worry about anything
and you can still have a hardship
still have a hardship
and still get affected
like the scale is different for everyone
and then you can be someone that comes
from nothing
and got hit by a train or a bus and
you just climb out of that and you go
but there's hardships the hardship skill
is really interesting I never talked
about the hardship scale I should go
into that more deeply
often a negative experience or a series
of them will prompt a person to feel
broken or depleted who feels depleted
when you go through something
how many people feel like they're so
low on Reserves
they've been through a lot they've been
through a lot of trauma they've had some
heartaches and breakup maybe they had a
relationship breakup and you feel like
your heart was ripped out of your chest
and stomped on
and
you just get wasted from it and your
reserves get really low your reserves
are low
it's a lot of people that feel depleted
from that Alexandria Sophia says what
makes the scale so different is that
karma from past lives really good
question
really good question
the scale is so different you're talking
about Alexandria you're talking about
the scale as far as what makes the
difference of someone having a much more
difficult situation a difficult hardship
versus somebody else was what seems like
a lesser hardship and that's another
discussion too but there's also
how someone
receives that hardship so what I was
saying was you can get somebody that
goes through something terrible
and they seem to be bearing it
and then you can get someone that they
went through something very small
but it feels so bad it feels so bad
there's a scale that happens within
everyone
where's somebody else I'd be like wait a
minute you're you're that hurt over that
and the person's like I'm deeply hurt
deeply deeply hurt you don't understand
me you don't understand who I am you
don't understand how I feel I am deeply
deeply hurt
and someone else would be like I
understand what you're saying but I
don't see why you're that hurt because I
fell off a cliff and hit my head on a
rock down below
and it was a terrible trauma because
someone pushed me off the cliff
but I I've handled it I've tried to get
past it and someone else is like
you know they had a different experience
for something what seems like much
smaller because the hardship scaled you
can't measure it is what I'm trying to
tell you you can't measure it it's
unmeasurable how people feel with their
soul and what's going on inside their
souls Gina says I agree I just lost my
mother quit my job in healthcare and I'm
lost
light blast was great which I want to do
another light Blast coming up but we
have to do the on collecting Stones
meditation journey I just think I was
one of the ten that was last
we want to feel complete again we don't
want to feel depleted we don't want to
feel like our reserves are low we want
to feel complete again
that's soul-searching it can take the
form of attending Retreats going to hear
inspirational speakers because we're
soul-searching seeking advice from loved
ones
signing up to every single spiritual
course in the world and paying two three
thousand dollars or whatever it takes to
just
go sit with the best spiritual leaders
because we're soul-searching
enrolling in therapy or any other number
of other activities that's what we do
that's what people do out there we're
soul-searching we're looking for answers
we feel lost we feel there's a sadness
inside of us we feel like
something is wrong something's missing
it's what we do when we're looking to
heal and Elevate our souls
to strengthen our purpose in life
if you guys just got on here
Jeanette gendrum says on Facebook I
don't have time and money for soul
searching too busy keeping kids and
animals alive completely understand
because you know what you're doing is
survival
it's survival
I actually respect and appreciate that
comment
Juliet says I'm depleted I have had the
most chaotic and traumatizing past
for months
past months
that's what we do when we're looking to
heal and Elevate our souls to strengthen
our purpose in life
your soul resides in your brain
powerful piece of information right
there
it resides in your brain I've said this
before it's why intuitively and
instinctively they would chop people's
heads off and stick them on pikes
it's why they used to Guillotine people
they hate it the most
they didn't just stab them to death
they didn't just drown them they
Guillotine them they wanted their heads
severed off their body
because there was something back in the
Dark Ages
there was something back then
that instinctively told
the human race that something is inside
of here
Cassie Healy says is there an end to the
soul-searching
it's a really good question
and how many lifetimes are we
soul-searching
people don't realize it but we take
all of our experiences
all of our knowledge
we take it with us
when we leave here
because the physical brain isn't the
only place that harnesses
information the neurons and the glial
cells isn't the only place that's
harboring information
the soul is harboring experiences and
information
our soul that resides here
is harboring information from every
single lifetime
I hope it no one's offended if I even
say that because someone might say no
there's only one lifetime that's it
I pose a question to you or pose a
question
if you're in with tremendous respect and
no judgment if someone believes it's
only a one-time thing
we're here we're gone
we have no soul
we cease to exist and that's it
everybody has their right to believe in
anything they believe in
but keep in mind
where is it in the present time right
now
how is it possible
we're all here
on the front line
think about that for a minute
I want to go deeper into that Jake Davis
says I spent so many years after I lost
both of my parents
lost and depleted
after about a month of living in mm
lifestyle
I started to get my life back and felt
like that void was finally being filled
Jake thank you for being here you're on
YouTube
foreign
how is it possible
that we
are on the front line of time itself
right now
think about it every minute that clicks
forward every second that clicks forward
is the front line
we are on the front line right now
you're not in the past right now 500
years
ago
you're not in the future 500 years from
now
you're on
the brink
the edge
you're on the front line pushing forward
into the future second by second by
second by second
well how did you manage to end up here
after billions of years
and katrillions
of people that have passed and gone
they've lived their life they died they
gone
with their life they died they're gone
civilizations
centuries and centuries of people
thousands of years of civilizations
how is it possible with all that
you think we were just chosen to be on
the front line right now
at the very second that's pushing
forward into time
that of all the trillions of people the
billions and billions of people and the
centuries and the thousands of years of
civilizations for some reason were just
picked to be on the front line of time
aren't we special
no it's because
we came around again
Evan says I really hope you are coming
out with your spiritual book that got
delayed by prior events indeed it did
get delayed in fact it was canceled for
the year I'm not even able to work on it
I've lost the opportunity for this year
see Evan says I am looking forward to
that so much I am too I've been kept
busy by a lot of Darkness obviously you
guys are up on what's happened and
what's going on I don't know if you
listen to the medical meeting podcast at
Apple podcast
the last
few episodes I don't know if you've
actually got a chance
but yeah
that was completely robbed from the
medical medium community and robbed from
me to be able to actually
um
fulfill a duty
which is to hand in my spiritual book
start complete and hand in my spiritual
book for this year so we can have that
to the publisher
that never happened
yep
Anya says aw can you share why this time
right now so significant
well think about it right now we're on
the front line of time as we speak all
together in this moment
which means we've
most likely been here before and before
and before and as I was saying before
our soul carries information you might
not be able to tap into it and tap into
your soul and the information that
you've taken over from Lifetime to
Lifetime
but I've learned all this from Spirit of
compassion by the way
you may not
be privy to the information that's
passed on
over and over and over again meaning
into boom another body your soul you
live a life you get all these
experiences in for information you die
your soul contains that spiritual
information all that knowledge
and you may not be able to tap into it
um
that you think we're all here by chance
just by chance
with all those people who have been on
this planet alone never mind how many
people have been on other planets you
think
we've just suddenly have all just we're
here right now by a fluke
hey cold lights ring
tally I suffer from chronic migraines
on IG okay tally says I suffer from
chronic migraines my father is unwell
and it's changed my life a lot I'm so
over the pain medicine that's so
unhealthy for me how do I move past it
and get my healthy life back you're
working on medical medium information
foreign
there's a lot of tools
that so many people have used here to
get their lives back
Cold Light spring
I I read your comments it's gone up now
um
they contacted the journalist right
before brain saver I bet that book was
the target
but the journalists spent so much time
writing and questioning what he was fed
so they only delayed this one
um
your soul also stores your hope and your
faith in your trust so that I want to
talk about a little bit have you ever
had your trust broken
just broken
never had your faith
really tested really test it
you trust your faith your hope
crashed
crushed and smashed
your soul stores your hope your faith
and your trust stores it
all of which help keep you on the right
path that's a mechanism that helps to
keep us strong and keep us on the right
path
ideally
we would have fully intact Souls over
the course of life's hardships though a
soul can become fractured a soul can
become fractured have you ever met
anyone where
if you use your intuitive capabilities
and intuitive strengths
you can almost
kind of like
just see it and understand that the
other person might have some fractures
they get triggered they're struggling
this can be caused by traumatic events
such as the death of a loved one
betrayal by a loved one betrayal by
oneself as well as ongoing traumas such
as the loss of freedom and trust that
comes with experiencing chronic illness
and symptoms so I want to go into that a
little bit when we get sick we then lose
faith in a lot of things we lose faith
in the pharmaceutical industry for one
people have chronic illness they lose
faith in the pharmaceutical industry
medicine
in medical science has a lot to offer
life-saving surgeries
life-saving procedures
but there's this whole massive massive
swath of people
that suffer from chronic symptoms and
conditions
and they suffer greatly and they haven't
been able to find answers and they feel
like their body has let them down they
feel like their body's shutting down
they feel like
um
they can't get better and they've tried
everything and they've done everything
that's really hard for people
when Soul injuries are fresh they can
result in feeling
of being lost
just reading the book a little bit if
you guys want to know which one it is by
the way I just want to
a little reminder have you signed up the
registration came out yesterday please
look out for it link is in the
description link is in the profile we're
talking about some incredible
information right now interesting
information
someone just said on IG I ordered five
of your books incredible
incredible
if you got medical medium New Edition
right here the collecting Stones
meditation is inside of this book
important to have if you signed up to
the free collecting Stones meditation
Journey
be prepared
because I am
giggly with excitement because I know
that you're going to have an
unbelievable profound experience
the link is in description and profile
we can lose connection with oneself loss
of Desire inspiration
to preserve or thrive
persevere or or Thrive or even loss of
life force and that's what happens too
when we just get broken down and beaten
down we feel like we don't have our life
force anymore we feel like we've lost
our life force
and then wounds from hardship betrayal
and broken trust or emotional hurt often
exhaust the person's immune systems
that's another thing too like it's like
I can't tell you how many times I've
seen with relationship breakups
foreign
those relationship breakups
people's immune system just tanks
it's like one too many relationship
breakups and their immune system just
gets so low
because it's exhausting especially if
you're staying up all night you're not
sleeping good you're tossing and turning
you feel hurt you feel that pit in your
stomach and this can drop down our
immune systems and defense defenses
an IG
Vanya says doing the cleanses helps us
heal our souls and the meditations help
a lot too like Moon meditation and soul
light meditation which are incredible
meditations by the way
Margot says is schizoid Soul fractured
collecting Stones meditation by the way
is what we're doing and it's going to
start on the 19th July 19th I'm
forewarning everybody
register now don't miss out don't miss
out tell a friend tell everybody it's
really going to be exciting I have three
stones these are example Stones right
here
these aren't my stones for the
meditation Journey register now you will
need to be signed up to get the daily
videos really important to know
I just have to remind you guys I'm
afraid so many of you are going to miss
the chance of doing the collecting
Stones meditation Journey with me
and then everybody's gonna like where is
it when is it it's over
we did it already right
um chookum says is a narcissist or
psychopath the cause of heavy metals or
broken Soul or personality you can have
a combination correct combination I just
saw a combination easily can have that
yes
crispy perspective over there on YouTube
been feeling so stressed from
relationship breakups and
disappointments and all acne have
sprouted up
Sleep Quality went down so what happens
is when we have relationship problems
and we have breakups our immune system
drops it drops down when our immune
system drops down what happens you guys
is that when it drops down other things
rise up so our immune system
other things could rise up what are
other things well streptococcus that's
behind acne
other things can rise up UTIs straight
that strap that streptococcal and UTIs
boom
it's another one too
fatigue can start up after breakups
because immune system lowers and then
everybody's Epstein bar just starts to
rise up
sometimes a person's soul injury
and resulting emotional state isn't a
physical problem yet symptoms often take
time to build quietly in the background
so a soul injury at an earlier time in
life could be the trigger for future
symptoms of full-blown conditions to
come we're talking about that now if you
don't have the right knowledge and tools
and resources to take care of your soul
and physical body we can get in trouble
that's how it works
let's be clear emotional wounds and soul
wounds are not the reason for physical
suffering
big triggers though big triggers
for underlying susceptibilities which
everybody has
which are caused by pathogens poisons
were up against in the world and heavy
metals that's an example it's a poison
but you are not weak you are not weak
regardless and you're not weak just
because you're chronically sick you're
still not weak strongest people I've
ever seen and let me go into this part
this is important please if you guys
have a second to listen to this
you know how
strong
people who have chronic illness really
are
people who have been sick for years
they're strong
I can guarantee you
that if you take someone who's an
athlete maybe a professional athlete in
football or basketball or
professional swimmer or something right
and they get chronic illness
screaming like a baby
screaming and screaming like a baby
can't handle it for more than six months
can't handle it for more than two months
there's people out there who are
chronically sick for five six years bent
every doctor been to everything they've
been through hell and back but they're
strong really strong they may not seem
strong they can't run a marathon but
then you take somebody who's been strong
their whole life
they run marathons and everything and
they finally get sick they are
screaming bloody murder
because they can't take it for a minute
because it's it's stopping them from
doing what they want to do and and feel
and be indestructible and they can't
handle it there's it's amazing how it
works the most
strongest people I've ever known are
people that have been through it and
they understand and they've been sick
clear done on YouTube says Bend to hell
and back you bet
on IG
fearing fearing a woman says I've lost
my husband July 4th and I can't eat
sleep or manage to have the energy to do
anything in the house all I do is cry
and mourn
God bless you I'm so sorry you're going
through that
a person with a soul injury is
vulnerable
if you ever hear a friend say I'm not
ready for another relationship
I'm still hurting from my breakup
she's acknowledging that her soul needs
time to heal before the risks
of putting herself into the firing line
again right so a lot of people
you know their Soul's been injured you
know they've been hurt
and they're like I can't I can't get
into another relationship I can't start
another relationship
I'm not ready because I can't handle it
because I've been hurt really bad and I
need to be careful and I need to take my
time and I need to do some healing and
rebuilding
along the same lines if you've ever
observed someone who's sick with
symptoms or a condition and hasn't been
able to find answers you may see this
person hungrily pursuing spiritual
learning in any form religion spiritual
gurus self-help books meditation
Retreats breath work it's likely because
that person's soul has been injured from
all of the trust lost along the way and
he or she is instinctively searching for
ways to make the soul healthy and
complete again
it's incredible information Marie says
which book is this
which page am I on
page 394
394.
sometimes soul-searching will bring
people closer to themselves many times
it will leave them feeling more lost
than ever under the guise of help
you may have heard the false theory that
illness is just a cry for attention have
you ever heard that where you're just
crying for attention you're not sick
you were never sick you're crying for
attention you're asking for help you're
asking for attention because you're not
sick
you may have heard the false theory that
illness is just a cry for attention you
may have heard that when bad things
happen to us we cause them by thinking
the wrong thoughts or that someone
something about who you are as a person
is wrong you've heard that too right you
caused your illness that's what you hear
out there that's what a lot of people
talk about it's spiritual movement it's
really bad I have to be honest
that's the one thing actually one out of
many things in the spiritual movement
out there that I I think is really
messed up
anna-lysa Phipps says Anthony is there a
way to tell when you're dealing with
pure evil versus brain toxins
there definitely is pure evil out there
I will not
deny that
I don't know if you ever hear my
telegram messages ever have you guys
are you guys on my Telegram
page
I don't know if you ever heard me talk
on there
it's a lot of fork tongue out there
there's a lot of dark
Ness out there's a lot of people that
have obviously dark intentions there's a
lot of Darkness out there in the world
it's true
if we walk around and pretend there is
no darkness and we walk around and
pretend there's nothing dark out there
going on
if we walk out if we walk around and
pretend nothing bad's happening or
really in some kind of crazy bubble
because that's not reality
and another thing too not everything is
a lesson
to be learned
meaning when darkness occurs right it's
not that you're supposed to learn a
lesson because darkness is attacking you
it's not really that you're trying to go
about your business and do good things
in in life and then Darkness attacks
a lot of people are told that they cause
their illness upon themselves so in the
spiritual movement I see that a lot and
I'm like what
oh yeah you manifested that sickness you
must be manifesting wrong that's why
you're sick you've been to 20 doctors
and you got neurological problems and
Tremors and fatigue and your eyes are
twitching and you've got all kinds of
different problems you must have you
must have done that to yourself through
manifestation you must have manifested
wrong bad thoughts or something like
that maybe you're just a bad person and
you need lots of spiritual growth and
that's why you have all those crazy
neurological symptoms
because you brought it on yourself
you hear that that's terrible because
that's not correct Michelle
Ulrich says aw
I was a competitive bodybuilder and ran
half marathons that's incredible when I
got my autoimmune diagnosis I completely
healed from the symptoms after
discovering medical medium information
it took two and a half years God bless
you Michelle proud of you too you stuck
to it even with all the BS out there
the lies that are out there about
medical medium the amount of negativity
the amount of discrimination
because I hear a voice the amount of all
of that and you've hung in there for two
and a half years despite all of that BS
and cancel culture
and also what is it called a competitor
competitor attacks and takedowns out
there
because they don't like the fact that
medical medium is in the health space
offering free stuff 24 7 including tons
of information for people to heal so
competitors are trying to knock out
medical medium
and medical medium health health space
right even with all that going on and
you hung in there for two and a half
years incredible
me too 787 usually leave comments on
YouTube I haven't seen one recently I
gotta look for them me tube787 the past
three years was a great display of evil
cloaked is good we should remember and
recognize it for what it is how'd you
know it's the past three years
you are definitely tuned in to the lies
and the garbage that's been out there
interesting
yep
I'm going to talk more about it when I
get a chance
yeah
unless you're talking about
the C
out there
which yep
I've said it before and I'll say it
again if you are ill or going through a
trial like a divorce or a loss you did
not manifest it I'll say it before I've
said it before and I'll say it again
come on ew you get it right
you did not attract it
I have to make sure I get that
information out there okay that's
important if you're struggling or if
you're suffering if you're going through
something you didn't Attract it
you're not attracting something terrible
to happen to you or something
challenging to happen to you it's not
what you're doing
you're not a bad person you didn't
manifest hardship
so much incredible information in this
book by the way
foreign
we are coming up
to the collecting Stones meditation
Journey
so I'm just letting you know
it is coming pretty soon we're starting
it July 19th did you sign up to it don't
miss out and I'm I'm nervous people are
gonna miss out because it kind of like
ends up like an ice pick in my ears when
after we do something like this
everybody's signing up we're there we're
doing it and then after it's over I hear
when does it start how come I missed it
what is this collecting Stone's
meditation journey and each one is like
an ice pick going in my ear to my brain
link is in the profile link is in the
description
and registration
is now it's now okay
you deserve to heal
you deserve to be happy
you deserve to feel whole
you do
you deserve it and you deserve the heel
keep that in mind
on IG
anything for ra you're looking at a book
specifically
helpful for ra right here
revised in addition medical medium
your heart serves as the compass for
your actions guiding you to do the right
thing when your soul becomes lost you
can have a busted up soul you can have a
soul that's been through hell and back
you could have a soul that feels
fractured you can feel like whoa there's
nothing left for me to give anymore I
can't give any more I can't right you
can be at that place
and your heart
will be the compass your heart will
actually give you direction for your
actions it'll guide you to do the right
thing when your soul becomes lost
because even if your soul is busted up
pretty bad and you feel pretty down and
you feel pretty beaten down
your heart will then become that compass
and help guide you the direction you
need to be guided
Alexandra Sophia says the heart's
guidance is always right on point
your heart is also a kind your your
heart
is also a safety net
that can compensate for soul injury this
means you can have a tattered soul and a
warm loving heart how many people out
there have a warm loving heart
regardless of all the crap they went
through
how many people have that where they
still have a warm loving heart
no matter what how much they've gone
through no matter how much trust was
broken no much no matter what occurred
betrayal they still have a kind loving
heart
I never give up on people
even if I there's
then say stabbed in the back by somebody
that I know
because
they wanted something out of me and I
said no
even with something like that I still
don't go on the next day saying I'm
never going to trust a single person
again after that
I don't do that
I trust again and I trust again and I
trust again that's what I do and I keep
trusting and I keep on moving forward
that's what I do
when your soul suffers fractures and
losses a strong heart will get you
through
with Selfless Love compassion and joy
until your soul has managed to heal it's
like the heart takes over your heart
takes over while your soul is healing
I like that
I love that it comes from the heart
coldip says
on YouTube can anyone direct me to where
the link is for the stone meditation
please if you're on YouTube check
YouTube links should be in the
description
or
the screen yeah the description in the
video
so look for it don't miss out
I promise you
it's going to be an experience that I
can promise you
you can also find it at
medicalmedium.com
find the link there at medicalmedium.com
don't miss out
I strongly urge everyone to partake in
this because it'll be so fun so fun
laughs
anyway you guys
I just want to say thank you for hanging
out thank you for doing this it's the
summer of healing that's why we did the
light blast that's why we're doing the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
Hannah T says why does God send people
into our Lives who keep betraying us
is our job to give people chances over
and over love unconditionally
look I'll tell you something
it's not God doing that
you guys are incredible it's been an
honor
renata144aw if the heart is hurt can
that block someone from tuning in with
their intuition
it's the heart emotionally hurt
physically hurt
two different things
but our heart either way is still that
Beacon no matter what even if it's
injured physically it's still the beacon
kind of Lights the way
now there are people out there that have
cold dark Hearts I mean that does exist
where they have cold dark hearts
there is that term heartless and it
actually is real unfortunately there are
some heartless people out there it
exists on this planet
Darkness can take over people and
completely corrupt their heart
and then genocide occurs
in so many different levels on so many
different ways
in so many different ways
so that does happen there's some evil
people on the planet and then toxic
heavy metals can affect people too
in so many different ways
but even with that really there are just
some serious evil people on the planet
that do just heartless cruel things and
Despicable things
it's horrible and don't have a care in
the world about human race or suffering
this has really been an incredible
um fun discussion you guys
so I just want to give you one more
reminder don't miss out on the
collecting Stones meditation Journey
as you clean up your body physically
with for example like the medical medium
tools cleans up people's bodies
physically intuition gets stronger and
stronger and stronger
intuition gets stronger and stronger and
stronger
and then these Revelations and then
these epiphanies and then these
realizations come and then
incredible references occur
but people also have free will
and they can be persuaded and
brainwashed very easily out there so
people have free will
and Free Will can
be the greatest thing ever
and it can also get us in trouble of
course and we can be persuaded
seeing interesting comments from you
guys everywhere
the thing is is that with Spirit of
compassion I tend to ask a lot of
questions
to SOC and
I could probably do just in 10 hour live
every day
and we can go into places that
answer a lot of questions spiritual wise
and it would be mind-blowing
but I'll try to get it all in the
spiritual book if I could ever get to it
I love you guys
and uh
bye bye just know that I care and I love
you guys pat yourself on
the back please have compassion for
yourself
don't miss
these events for the summer of healing
so sign up to the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
I can honestly say
you will never forget
this seven day Journey
on your seventh day it will be an
experience
that will live on forever
in your soul
your heart and spirit
don't miss out I love you guys