today which is kind of exciting I
haven't had a chance to talk about B12 I
get asked about it all the time lots of
questions but I haven't had the time
been putting the books up getting those
done and ready so they're out in your
hands working on other things getting
free information out all the time
working on on medicalmedium.com I hope
you're watching this from
medicalmedium.com that would be really
incredible and so all that I'm doing I
don't have time and we get a lot of
questions lots of them and a big portion
of questions are what about B12 you know
how about B12 what's the best B12 like
constantly ask that and I can't address
it every minute I can't address it every
day it's not humanly possible so every
now and then once in a blue moon I have
to be like okay let's see if we can at
least answer some questions help out the
big crowd of people that actually want
to know more about B12 so that's why I'm
here and I want to do more of these
kinds of things too because so many
questions so many concerns and
everything else
so right now that's what we're talking
about so I have some information
in the brain saver books
um if you have these books incredible
then you already know how packed they
are and I have a B12 in front of me
right here that's the vimorgy B12 so
that's the one that I take it's the one
I recommend to family and friends it's
the one that I feel is the best there is
and and I can tell you guys about
vimorgy as far as the four things and I
say this because it's for mind-blowing
things I mean I don't even know what to
say so if you're somebody and you're
looking for supplements out there and
you're wondering what B12 is the best or
you're looking for different things what
you won't find anywhere so before I go
into the B12 information mind-blowing
information which you won't find
anywhere with supplement companies from
what I've seen and learned is that label
requirements allow supplement companies
to hide a small percentage
of ingredients in the product without
ever disclosing it to the consumer so
think about that for a minute so it's
legal for that to happen label
requirements allow supplement companies
to legally have undisclosed
small percentages of other ingredients
in the supplement that you don't know
about right so you won't know about
then Richie says no I won't do that
they say we won't do that we will not
ever have a small percentage of hidden
ingredients that we won't disclose to
our consumer they refuse to do that on
any level so that right there blows my
mind because I've talked to a lot of
companies and I can't get that out of
them
so that's that right there is just
everything to me another thing too
before we go into B12 information and
all that
another thing that's mind-blowing right
thermology products are third party
independently tested
but they keep to that which is
incredible they don't do in-house
testing if you know what I mean in-house
right right so that's a whole other
thing too that's incredible
the other thing is beverage products
contain no alcohol
no soy no gluten no citric acid no
maltodextrin you know what that is no
magnesium steroate no vinegar no
caffeine no natural flavors you guys
know by now about natural flavors I'm
pretty sure right through medical meme
info and other that you know that that
gets out there in the world from mm
books and stuff no natural flavors no
artificial flavors
no titanium dioxide but the mind-blowing
thing about it all
is no alcohol
no citric acid no maltodextrin no
natural flavors mind-blowing
but
here's the other thing no small
percentage of hidden ingredients that
could be virtually anything
and that's
enough for me to be like drop the mic
it's unbelievable and then then there's
the fourth thing
I just want to tell you guys the fourth
thing the quality tears
so what does that mean you if you start
a supplement company today you
say you get some investors or somebody
or you want to whenever you get some
money and you want to start a supplement
company
and then you want to start your product
you can choose from the quality levels
but you can always still claim quality
but no one realizes there's different
quality levels
there's a real high quality level that
supplement companies don't go to because
of price point
see how this works
this is mind-blowing
and guess what as I'm saying this now
supplement companies are probably like
watching this going
[Music]
um
oh yeah well uh because this is mind
freaking blowing is what I'm trying to
tell you
so vimorgy chooses the higher quality
that they can possibly find the highest
quality they can possibly find
and that is something that I believe
doesn't exist out there and so when you
think about that because they don't care
about the price point
if they'll pay more for the best thing
they can possibly find and still keep
the cost down as low as they can and
that's the whole point and so when you
look at those four things right there I
just want to get those out of the way
because those are worth celebrating
they're worth talking about they're
worth like everything to me those four
things so if you're somebody that's on
here you're like what's he talking about
now that's a hundred percent why I
endorse the company and said I will
stand behind you guys with everything I
got I will tell everybody anywhere
anyhow to make sure these supplements
stay alive in the world because when you
take those four things you don't want to
lose that I don't want the supplements
to go away so I can't take them
I don't want the supplements to go away
and disappear so that I don't have this
incredible these incredible supplements
to take when I think about that my
family I got family and friends that
rely on the highest quality and the best
stuff for their health and everything I
don't want that to disappear
I don't want those four incredible
points I mentioned disappear so I'm
gonna income 100 endorse them in the
highest light and tell people about it
and that's how how it works as far as
with that but anyway it's not about B12
and that's what we're here for
so I'm excited you guys
sell the whole bit Iona says Bemidji
admits a strong light frequency into my
house and I believe that you're on
YouTube I believe that because I have a
spiritual connection and it and
obviously you know SOC and everything
else
and spiritually spiritually connected to
everything that goes inside my body
a piece of kale
I could feel it enter my body I could
feel I could res it you know I could
actually
resonate with the frequency from a piece
of kale
so it's like that with supplements too I
can resonate with them I know the
garbage and what's not Catherine
Elizabeth spaniel says vimergy is the
best I used to get an itchy face from
taking B12 I was told that I was
allergic to methyl I have no issues with
beverages B12 even my very sensitive sun
takes memories supplements now the
reason why could be a couple of things
Catherine on that
no hidden percentage of ingredients that
label requirements allow you to hide and
not disclose that doesn't exist in the
vanishing products
that's just one reason why
you you could be experiencing such an
incredible experience never mind so many
others that I could go on forever right
so
these things matter but what happens is
I can't talk about B12 every day
because I just don't have the time or
the energy but we notice that when the
questions build up and the questions
build up and I'm dm'd a thousand times
about B12 I have to spend some time so I
want to give you guys any kind of
mind-blowing information I can about B12
too so I wanna I want to offer that
because it helps with questions and
people's concerns about B12 or
understanding about B12 I wanna B is
informative as I possibly can
because it's all about health it's all
about well-being it's all about moving
forward all of that so and uh Sienna
says love my memory B12 every day my
girls love it too because it's actually
it actually tastes delicious
it does taste delicious with no
junk or natural flavors or anything in
there and it tastes delicious and that's
a whole nother thing it's just whoa when
you think about it
David says I only take memory and the
thing is so
with me it's about it's about that
vibration it's about that frequency
that's a big part of of how I connect to
something too
and so when I feel like the vimoracy
products and I hold them in my hand I
know what I'm feeling you know I'll have
a friend every now that comes over or
meets me somewhere and they're like what
do you think about this
and I'll be like well let me check that
out and I look at it and I look at the
back of the bottle and I'm like dude
there's citric acid in this dude there's
alcohol in this dude there's stuff in
here and then be like and then I'll be
like and then I'll feel it and be like
and you feel it's just dead it's like
this is dead to me and there's stuff in
there and it's like okay well what do
you think about this aw and my friend
give me another product and I'm like all
right let's take a look and I'll feel it
and be like why does why does this feel
wrong and then I've looked turn it over
again and there you see it natural
flavors then you see natural Berry
flavor which you know it's not gonna
then you see this and this you've you've
heard my my episode
the natural flavors episode right
so
all of that natural flavorings and all
that so you feel it in the whole bit Uma
says dude with a laughing face
I want to read a little
if you guys have a second
so
all of here's something that's
interesting that's in the brain saver
book check this out this is incredible
when I saw this line I was like I have
to read this to everybody
I just do
um Amber says member gb12 has been so
helpful for my son with autism I'm so
grateful
right there on YouTube incredible I mean
that that that has so much meaning to me
really does okay so I want to read this
little line right here passing negative
thoughts
can't deplete
your brain cells of B12
so passing negative thoughts right think
about this
so if you got negative thoughts and
they're going through your brain
negative thoughts that are passing
through the brain
cannot deplete
your B12
.
right that alone is just mind-blowing
when I read this in here
positive thoughts
in your brain
cannot
refill your brain cells with B12
so when you're thinking positive
thoughts which I try to think all the
time
I don't want to think negative thoughts
unless Spirit of compassion is telling
me things
about how the world Works what's
happening in the world
all about all of that anything stressful
of course you know which is no fun and
of course life is not easy we go through
a lot in life and I don't want to also
be stuck on any negative thoughts but
what's incredible here
is positive thoughts cannot refill your
brain cells with B12
so negative thoughts
cannot deplete your brain of B12
positive thoughts can't refill your
brain cells with B12
so we can be somewhere on a Mountaintop
we could be praying
we can be in a spiritual Retreat
somewhere and the spiritual Retreat
somewhere
totally relaxing
doing some healing
you know and
still we can't refill the brain with B12
we can take a walk in nature
and we're thinking positive thoughts
while we're taking a walk in nature and
we can't refill the brain with B12
and here's really something that's
incredible right here yet negative
experiences
like betrayal I've experienced that
I mean I experience that a lot
right I mean
I do
betrayal broken trust
losses have you guys had your trust
broken ever
on any level
relationships
world tragedies too
can deplete your brain cells of B12 so
that can deplete us
I have here in the book
so that can deplete us
a B12
so when I got this information from SOC
and I wrote it down
when I was doing the books
so these
points just blew my mind when I even
think about it
because it's so advanced
Nobody Knows the information
so passing negative thoughts can't
deplete your brain cells of B12
when they're passing through your brain
in mind positive thoughts can't refill
your brain cells B12 yet negative
experiences like betrayal which I
experience a lot broken trust losses
relationships and world tragedies can
deplete your brain cells of B12 and even
pot and here's the next thing that's
mind-blowing here in this book
even positive experiences
can deplete your brain cells of B12
I mean how incredible is that
positive experiences with exercise
positive experiences taking nature walks
positive experiences you know where
you're happy lots of happy experiences
can still it still takes b12.
Melanie says that member gb12 is amazing
gives me so much energy and feeds my
nervous system a pivotal tool in my
healing
that's incredible
it really is
so
happiness joy fun play for example you
know if we're playing if we're having
joy in our life if we're having fun ski
trips other active vacations new
relationships so if we go on a vacation
and we're having a fun time on our
vacation we're being really active on
our vacation it takes b12.
like how how unbelievable is that this
information a new relationship so you
found somebody you're dating you finally
found somebody you're like oh my God
this is fantastic this is the right
person for me and you're in that Bliss
that takes B12 so you didn't find the
right relationship or something and you
found somebody in your dating or
whatever it is it takes b12.
say you're just looking for a new friend
you find a new friend and you found this
incredible friend you're like oh my God
I actually have this great friend
it takes me 12.
so relationships New Opportunities take
B12 how incredible of this information
when I just being armed with this
information and this knowledge is
mind-blowing to me Marissa spiritual
says it doesn't matter how spiritual you
are you need the good stuff to heal
that is incredible
it's so true
so when we have new babies
takes B12
a new job someone says hey can you help
me out and you get okay sure and you got
a new job somewhere
it takes me 12.
it all takes b12.
how crazy is that
if you lose your B12 from your brain
cells you can become played out and
burnt out and that's another thing too
if we lose our B12 from our brain and
brain cells
so if we're losing B12 from our brain
cells
we can get pretty played out
pretty burnt out
even if we're playing
and we're having fun we're on vacations
we're on ski trips
we're having fun we're on a boat
somewhere we're on a lake
whatever we're having fun we're on the
beach
we're at a party
we're having a great time at a party
we're still losing
B12 and we can still get played out
and it doesn't mean it's easy recovery
too
so if you have too much fun it doesn't
mean it's easy recovery without B12
that's just incredible information
Linda says wow passing negative thoughts
deplete B12 no actually you can have
passing negative thoughts going through
your brain and it won't deplete your
b12.
and positive thoughts
won't refill your B12 in your brain
that's what it is watch this from the
from the beginning again afterwards but
I'm really happy you're here I'm happy
you're hearing you comment it
okay
if you lose your B12 from your brain
cells you can become played out burnt
out from too much play and not easily
recover you can become drained from too
much fun and need a vacation from your
vacation
it's why a lot of people
they get burned out on their vacations I
know a lot of people out there some of
the most powerful people in the world
they take a lot of vacations
which is which is great
but I've seen
seeing them take so many vacations where
they're burnt out and then
they need a vacation from their vacation
when really they're getting burned out
they're losing their B12 Reserves
a difficult emotional struggle can do
the same so if we have a difficult
emotional struggle on any level we can
get depleted over a b12.
and it can burn us out if we're lacking
B12 that's another thing if you have an
emotional struggle it can burn you out
if you're lacking B12
recovery is very difficult without good
B12 so this is just some powerful pieces
in here let me there's so much
information in these books you guys
you'd have to get the books take a look
at them but I'm just saying
if you if you're new here and all that
these are the brain saver books
amazon.com 40 off right now or go to the
library and get it for free either way
incredible
so check this out
when we step on the gas in our car
and hit it hard
right
and you're just boom
step under gas in our car and we hit it
hard
we're we are relying on the strength of
the nuts and bolts to hold that car
together so it doesn't start falling
apart so every time you're in your car
and you're driving and you want to step
on that gas
you're relying
your life is depending on the nuts and
bolts
you guys the nuts and bolts that are
holding everything together
your wheels all four wheels are held on
by those lug nuts
in the right the lug nuts in the bolts
or your tire goes off
when you step on that gas really hard
you're relying on hundreds and actual
thousands of nuts and bolts holding that
car together
your life depends on those nuts and
bolts
you're relying on the strength of the
nuts and bolts to hold that car together
so it doesn't start falling apart so
when we drive that car and we're
cruising we're on the highway
everything depends on the strength of
that car on everything that's holding
that car together all those nuts and
bolts
when you even think about that same
thing on a plane
if you're flying in a plane and you're
up in the air
it's really a car in the air with wings
that has an engine in it or engines
and it's still all Nuts and Bolts
I know an airplane mechanic works on the
big ones
and he tells me all the time
let everybody that's up there
flying around
if they only knew
it's all about the nuts and bolts the
nuts and bolts he tightens
on the routine maintenance
so when the planes down on the ground he
goes in there
and he's got the air tools and he says
he has to go in there and he says the
bolts loosen up
and if it's a bad mechanic guy that's
working on the planes that's not going
to help because now you're really either
at risk but he says he has to go in
there
in between every now and then on
maintenance
and he says you can't believe he can't
he actually he can't believe how many
bolts loosen up on those planes the big
commercial planes
he says sometimes he finds them so loose
they're almost completely falling out
engine mounts
in the planes it's holding the engines
in
so he goes in there and he has to
tighten up all those nuts and bolts
that's what he does with the machines on
all the airliners it's his job
and he says if people only knew and I'm
not trying to scare you anything but he
says people only knew
what's holding that together when
they're flying he says it's a car but
it's a car up in the air
when we're using our brains B12
okay
that's one of the nuts that's holding it
all together
so just like this guys my friend this
guy's he's actually zipping a couple of
bolts together holding the engine in on
the plane
one of those bolts on that plane is kind
of like the B12 in US
holding us together while we're going
through all this emotional traffic
an emotional BS that we're up against
out there because so much is going on
going at us in life it's not easy Lana
says I've been drinking beverages V12
for over four years along with being on
medical medium protocols and it has
changed my life Bemidji supplements are
pure powerful and the company has
Integrity you're on YouTube Lana I just
I just saw your um comment last night on
the brain shot challenge the day 10 one
I just saw you left a big comment on
there I just want to let you know that I
did see it and read it
foreign
so when you think about it like what's
holding us together
Spirit of compassion
always told me it's like exactly
it's one of those things that holds us
together
so when we're using our own B12 as one
of those nuts and bolts holding it all
together
some people blow through their B12
supplies faster due to different
experiences and exposures using up their
reserves so that's the thing
so if a plane is hitting a lot of
turbulence because of a lot of bad
weather
it's putting more stress on those nuts
and bolts
if we're going through life
and we're hitting some rocky ground and
some storms and some bad weather what's
it using
it's using one of those nuts and bolts
which is the B12
that's incredible that's a way to look
at it that actually helps me when I was
getting that information and putting in
here
so some people though they blow through
those nuts and bolts pretty quickly
because of the rocky turbulence in life
and they end up blowing through the
reserves
I mean that's incredible
to some extent everybody is depleted in
V12 to some extent everybody is depleted
in B12 I know I talked to a lot of
doctors
and I give the information out to a lot
of doctors and and doctors give me a lot
of information too
about it and
a lot of doctors agree with me and say
yes there's no question there's there's
a
a depletion out there
every nerve cell has to have a certain
amount of B12
I mean it's not a positive thing
everybody's depleted but it's incredible
when you think about it
of how it works out there
and the information here is just
profound
every nerve cell has to have a certain
amount of B12 and yet we walk around
with nerve cells that are deficient with
B12
which is a whole nother problem
going on out there
is our nervous systems
the cells themselves
are lacking B12
many of us walk around
with nerve cells
that are mildly depleted to extremely
depleted
and then we can feel that along the way
with burnout
someone just said 100 depletion I saw on
there
so another thing I want to mention which
has always been incredible medical
medium information and worth talking but
there's so much more information about
B12 in here so we're not done you guys
we still got some ground to cover if you
guys just came on here
I'm just talking about B12 because so
many people are asking me about B12 and
I want to make sure I provide
um just really profound incredible
information about it I want to talk
about the metaphysical aspects of
of B12 with us so that's one thing right
there that's important too so we're
going to cover that I also want to talk
about B12 shots for a few minutes I also
want to talk about B12 production
inside here
right there so if you guys still have a
few minutes let's cover some you know
killer information that's really just
awesome and fun too and if you just got
here what you see here is the
is the vimergy B12
okay now that's the big bottle
which is incredible
on its own
so
and I want to talk about also a little
bit with blood testing and b12 and all
of that as well too so that's the next
thing so we got a few topics to cover
but just if you got here and you're
looking at this a lot of people say
what's the best B12 what's the one you
like this is my favorite this is my
favorite
um the brand that's my favorite of all
that's the vimergy V is in Victor i m is
in Mary e r g y.com vemergy.com
and go there and check out their B12
that's your larger bottle
and what's incredible is it doesn't
contain
alcohol
contains no natural flavors no citric
acid no maltodextrin no caffeine no
vinegar no a whole bunch of things that
I see in all the supplements out there
so that's remarkable all on its own and
there's the four reasons I talked about
earlier so watch this video from the
start if you want to know the four
reasons that will just make you go okay
I've never heard anything like it
including
they don't have hidden ingredients on a
small percentage that label requirements
allow all the supplement companies to
have in the bottles and not disclose it
or beverage says no we're not going to
do that we're not going to put anything
in there that we don't disclose
just it's incredible anyway so that's
the emerging B12
and I fully endorsed them
because they deserve it
times 100 I wish I could do more I wish
I can do so much more
like endorse them a hundred times I
don't know I don't know but I wish I
could do so much more because I'm
grateful for what they've done for the
people out there with products like this
so it's incredible so let's go into it a
little bit
where does B12
[Music]
where does B12 come from
our body is supposed to produce it
but we've lost our ability to produce
B12 it's not like it used to be
it's not easy to produce B12 so our body
is supposed to rely on its own
production of B12 right there
right there
right here
we're inside now we're inside the gut
I like this if you take this off it's a
great
it's a great one
blueberry love says beverage is
literally the best
and you can feel too you're on YouTube
amazing
so
the ilium is where we have this
microorganism
community
called elevated biotics medical medium
information about elevated biotics
so that is a big part of how we produce
our own B12 it's in this region right
here but we lose our ability to because
one of the reasons why
because their guts get all chewed up
and we talked about that in all the
medical meaning books but the other
reason why
is because we don't eat produce
that comes out of the garden too often
so if you grow some parsley if you grow
some cilantro if you grow something in
your garden or on your porch or on your
windowsill or on your counter top in
your kitchen
if you grow anything an herb that's
edible
some Sprouts that are edible what will
develop on those Sprouts are those herbs
will be elevated biotics microorganisms
that can go deep down into your
intestinal tract and colon and reach the
ilium
and when it reaches the illum it'll sit
there so if you ever picked an apple off
of a apple tree and you bit into that
apple and ate that Apple there's a whole
bunch of microorganisms on the outside
of that apple skin
which is incredible right
all right let me look for an apple now
that apple is still nutritious still
really good for me still good for you
it's a delicious apple looks like a Brae
Burn I think that's a Brae Burn
great Apple to eat
delicious apple
but it doesn't have the microorganisms
on the outside of the skin unless it was
picked off the orchard
and you were driving home and eating it
and having some of your Apple
but still medically that apple is
incredible for you are still good for
you and it has all the building blocks
everything we talk about the glucose the
trace minerals
hydration right
so good that's a Brae Burn it's
delicious
we've got a crunch to it
but
this wasn't picked at an orchard
recently
and it's and and unwashed
so if I go to an apple tree and I pluck
this thing
and I bite it
or I go to a farm and they pull the end
and they all picked them all and I went
home and I ate it you would get
microorganisms on the skin
this is MM info
those micro radios microorganisms can
find their way deep
to the ilium
right here
they help us produce B12
we don't have a lot of opportunities but
yet it doesn't mean don't eat your Apple
it means you better eat your Apple of
course for a whole bunch of other
reasons so you can heal
if you grow something
on your windowsill like some parsley
and you pluck that parsley and eat it
you just got those microorganisms
it's a big part about how we produce our
B12
I mean how incredible
how so many people in the world are
missing their B12 lacking their B12
that's a reason all on its own also the
world has got become so much more
difficult to navigate through more
stress everything else more challenges
more problems and that so that depletes
B12 right
let's talk about B12 testing for a
couple of minutes B12 testing is really
confusing because a blood test for B12
is a snapshot in time
not to mention
I always have told doctors
that you go by symptoms
versus the B12 test itself so much
you can have somebody with a lot of
neurological problems and symptoms
but their B12 looks like it's normal
and so the doctor then doesn't recommend
B12 to them because the blood test
looked like it was normal
when I talk to doctors and they
recommend B12
for their patient that has neurological
symptoms of their stuff they recommend
the B12
prescribe it or whatever
regardless of what the blood test is
saying and I talked to doctors that do
this they notice improvements
so they're thinking in their head
they're scratching their head
these doctors and are like well the
blood test look normal
but my patient is now improving
because of the good B12
. so then they're thinking well
hey
what's going on here if the blood test
showed one thing and so forth so I've
gone into detail about blood testing in
B12 in the medical medium books you guys
probably know
and I've gone into detail about how that
works
where just because you're higher in B12
does it mean your brain and nervous
system is getting the B12
just because you're elevated on the test
doesn't mean you're elevated in the
nervous system you can have B12 floating
around your bloodstream but not have
enough B12 in your nervous system this
is what I teach doctors and then they go
no wonder why my patient is feeling
better
when I put them on B12 even though their
blood test said they were high in B12
see see how it works
Linda says B12 changed my husband's
attitude now he is more relaxed less
stressful after two years we look we
took memories B12 daily
amazing that's incredible
another thing too you can be low in B12
in your bloodstream
but be but at the same time getting
enough B12 to your nervous system but
you can't see so one thing medical
research and science can't do is they
can't test B12 levels in the nervous
system
so when I talk to doctors and
neurologists
what I do is I talk about that with them
and I'm like yeah well is there a test
that I don't know about
where they can test your nervous system
for B12 levels and I hear it from
doctors all the time no there is an aw
there is not a test
for testing to see how much B12 is in
your nervous system
I go okay let me know when they come up
with that test 50 years from now
but
so we really don't see a lot with blood
tests regarding B12 we don't see enough
of the big picture
and that's confusing so when I talk to
doctors it's always like what are their
symptoms
that's what I'll say to doctors
monitor symptoms because there's so much
gray it's not black and white with B12
blood tests
so let's talk about another thing too
that's interesting
B12 shots
so I always say look do what your doctor
wants to do and do what's right for you
with your doctor
okay I'm showing you just the B12 that I
use every day recommend my family and my
friends right there
um
and you know ask your doctor what's
right for you what B12 your doctor wants
you on all of that
and dosages from your doctor and
everything else
you know consult your doctor for sure
but when it comes to like
my family my friends
they'll ask me should I get a B12 shot
I'll say well not I mean if your doctor
said see you know it's it's life or
death and it's a matter of you staying
alive and your doctor's uh convinced of
all that and they want to give you a B12
shot then just do what your doctor tells
you but I tell my family
and friends that I wouldn't get a B12
shot myself personally
because
and I've talked about this before and in
the brain saver books it's really
comprehensive about B12 shots
so what I've gotten information like my
like what I like my personal opinion and
what I tell doctors this oral is best
so a lot of doctors contact me they want
to learn information they'll ask me a
lot of questions B12 is always on the
list it's always on the list when
doctors talk to me
and I always say well they'll say well
what do you like best aw do you like B12
shots aw do you like B12 oral aw which
one and it's always oral
so anyway let's go into another area
we'll go into this question here that
Joshua Eldridge has why is B12 linked to
psychic ability
so
so let's talk about B12
with metaphysical
so
first and foremost you got to think
about this
B12
right
it's supporting your nervous system
so remember that right there
if B12 is supporting your nervous system
what's in your nervous system
this is your nervous system here
what is that
that's your brain
that's your Noggin
right there
what's sitting inside your brain and
Noggin
your soul
your soul lives on forever
and maybe you don't believe that and
that's okay I hope you still stay here
and hope you're not mad at me for saying
that that your soul lives on forever
I hope I didn't offend anybody either I
mean seriously my apologies if I did
Spirit of compassion just told me that
someone just said no the soul doesn't
live on forever I don't like what I'm
listening to and I I completely
understand
so
but the information I've gotten from
above
and what I believe is our soul lives on
forever past this life
so when our physical body is gone
our soul
still exists
and it travels
and I actually wrote about the soul
in the medical medium brand saver books
so there's sole information in the brain
saver books you guys so we just got here
you got to get these copies when you can
I mean seriously
information so amazing
so our soul when we're alive and we're
physically here sits about here
unless we had a trauma and then as I've
written in these books
soc's information about what happens
when we go through a trauma our soul
exits
we get the out-of-body experience
because when we have a hardship a
breakup or the relationship a loss A
trauma an emotional hardship
a struggle
if we do our soul can project out of our
brain and stay close by
and then we have an out-of-body
experience or we feel like we're
watching ourselves go through it or we
feel like disconnected from it all
now the information in the brain saver
books talks about
what happens here
with this process
that literally our soul can get knocked
right out of us
there's a reason for that it's to
protect the soul so it doesn't become
damaged and injured badly from an
experience we're having here
my boyfriend cheated on me literally
your soul
leaves your brain
you know my girlfriend she cheated on me
your soul leaves your brain
so it doesn't become damaged or too
injured by the experience
or something just happened I just lost
somebody a family member your soul
leaves your brain
so it becomes this out-of-body
experience really
or a protective measure and then your
soul comes back
stays real close by but then it comes
back
so our and I talk about it in detail
though in the brain saver books our soul
resides in her brain and because of that
our brain isn't just physical
it's physical and metaphysical
we have a soul
a subconscious
a Consciousness and subconsciousness
and a physical tissue
there are four things
with our brain
B12
plays a role with all four
I mean
it's incredible
so our brain isn't just our brain
and our soul lives wherever
Tracy says are you saying we shouldn't
wash our fruits and veggies no I'm not
saying that I go in the medical medium
books you'll read in there all about
washing and all that I'm saying that
if you go to the grocery store okay if
you go to the grocery store and you're
like oh well I better not wash
that
food item
because I want to have those those
elevated biotics on there no you that's
not it because 50 people could have
touched that item and that item could
have also had chicken juices tripped on
it through through when it was actually
delivered when it was in a truck your
produce could have been in the same
truck as chicken is because they do they
actually they actually mix them in the
same truck it's not like just a produce
truck all the time it's produce plus
meat plus fish some you know chicken and
you don't know what kind of
contamination could have gotten to the
cases of produce so you do want to wash
your store-bought stuff
because you don't know what's in there
or on there
and then when the produce is on the
store shelves for like a while like the
produce guy puts puts all that out there
and you guys this is all good stuff to
talk about it's critical anyway
and you're putting because if you guys
get food poisoning or sick from some
produce that has something on it then
you'll either be 12 reserves so you can
drop more so it's got we gotta go over
this
if someone stocks all this cilantro up
there the produce guy on the store shelf
it's just his hands are touching it sure
right but then you got people with
rolling their cards by and they go
through them I don't like that one throw
it back in I don't like this one throw
it back in someone could have just been
in the bathroom and who knows how they
washed their hands after they wipe their
ass and it's just like you got all this
going on
and it just yeah and that can happen a
hundred times during the day in the
grocery store 100 people 200 people
could go through all the produce right
you want to wash it
I'm just saying
but I'm talking about like if you go to
a farmer's market
and this guy that's got like a truckload
of kale a truckload of cilantro and it
was all harvested and yes people touched
it but there's a good chance that all
you really need to do is probably give
it just a rinse but if it was sitting in
the farmer's market on
display and and you didn't get there
that early in that morning and 100
people throughout the afternoon already
went through it all to pick what they
wanted and through what they didn't want
back
you guys gotta be careful you gotta wash
it
but if you grow it yourself
that's another story
so if you grow it yourself just on your
windowsill just some Sprouts on your
windowsill just some parsley under
windowsill just a lemon balm anything
you grow yourself right there on your
windowsiller or in your backyard or on
your porch depending on what time of
year is just just whatever right in your
own house and you grow something and you
pluck one little piece of that
there's elevated biotics on that little
piece right there and you don't have to
wash that you don't even have to rinse
it just send it down and you just got
those incredible microorganisms
so back to the whole soul
so it's not just our brain in here
it's our soul our subconsciousness
Consciousness and our physical brain all
four
so spirit and compassion has always told
me
for years
B12 is one of these like metaphysical
nutrients
because it's like those nuts and bolts I
was talking about in the plane or in the
car it's there
kind of hold it all together but what is
it holding together because
it's not just holding together the
physical brain
because the subconsciousness
Consciousness and your soul is still
there too so all four are there
isn't it possible it's holding together
something else
isn't it
I mean
wouldn't it be kind of ridiculous to not
think it is
you got
the construction in here is both
metaphysical and physical
you got the physical aspect which is the
tissue itself you got the subconscious
mind which is another aspect you got the
conscious mind which is another aspect
that's the conscious mind I'm talking to
you with and then you've got the soul
and they all have to work in harmony
and so when I hold B12 like the good
stuff I feel a frequency and a vibration
and it feels good
and a lot of times what I'll do is
always do this when any time anytime
anybody ever hands me a supplement of
any kind
I grab it I put one hand on my head
and I hold it with my other hand
so for years
friends and family members and whatever
have thrown things in my hand like all
right
give it the little run over here like
fine give it to me my hand on my head
why am I putting my hand on my head I'm
trying to make a continuity
so it's all about continuity
continuity from here
to up here to here so when you touch
your head and you touch the bottle
whatever that supplement is
there's continuity between
your brain going down your hand going
down your elbow and your arm right
through your torso going down to the
other arm and grabbing on to the bottle
and the reason why I'm creating
continuity from my brain to my hand is
what I'm doing is creating continuity to
my brain to the bottle
and I see how that feels
and I've held stuff in my hands that
when I did the continuity test
I was like oh no way no way in hell
now I know I haven't told too many
people it's kind of a private thing that
I have
but I try to tell you guys as many
private things as I can I have if you
look back on medical medium information
everything else I've given you guys as
much private information as I could
think of it I can't there's so many
things I do
that I have to make a show out of each
one like I'll do a whole podcast on this
eventually about that continuity thing
that I do I just haven't had time it's
just I can only do so much
but the continuity test is what I do
so I feel
the product itself and this is in
kinesiology
so I know that a lot of you people like
oh that's an easy out it's not that's
not it at all I've been doing this since
I was little and it's a continuity test
it's entirely different so this isn't
about Kinesiology about what your body
needs or doesn't want to want to need or
whatever it is doesn't need or want
or feel right too
this is about the continuity between
literally your brain this is a personal
between yourself with no other person
involved so this isn't like you go to
some kinesiologist or something like
this and they're yanking on your own
that's not what this is you're not being
governed by somebody else's free will
so the reason why
this test
is so powerful is because no one's Free
Will is interfering with my own free
will
this has no judgment upon Kinesiology or
not or acupuncture or naturopathy or
whatever it is that's out there or any
kind of other natural means of of
healing or anything that's not what this
is I'm not pulling opinions and
judgments on it
I'm just saying that the difference is
someone
Spirit of compassion was saying someone
was thinking Kinesiology I'm like no
that's when someone else's Free Will
interferes with your free will
and tries to control your free will
I'm not saying that in a bad way I'm
just saying that that's involved that's
how it works this is your own no one's
interfering
this is continuity between
Me Myself and I
my soul
which resides here my subconscious mind
my conscious mind
my physical brain and the product here
now if you're
depending on your left hand or
right-handed you can go either way and
do it
it's one of the reasons why originally I
first recommended
the number two products by the way
right from years ago
because of that right there insulin's
like what the heck and then I had asked
questions why is it so good like why is
the continuity so good so let's go into
by the way and of course we know why
I've talked about it in the four things
okay
so and you guys know I've endorsed them
because of it all so let's go into this
a little bit so why would B12 help us
intuitively
because SSC has only always told me
helps us intuitively
it helps us it's a nutrient that helps
us psychically
it's a nutrient that helps us
clairvoyantly
telepathically
if that's what you have
inside of you
everybody has a little bit of that some
people have more some people have less
some people it's undeveloped some people
hasn't been developed enough some people
but everybody has that possibility
or they have it but it's just not
upgraded right
like Spirit of compassion always told me
I have to take b12.
and I have to take it for years and it's
not just
for the good reason to take it but for
so many other reasons I'm talking about
like that connection
so anyway
I take it straight I don't even I don't
use it but I take the B12 straight is
what I do taking a dropper full now
and that's the other thing like I know
what resonates and I can feel that
vibration it's incredible
but
we covered a lot of things if you just
got on here
watch us from the beginning because
we're covering like the B12 shots a
little bit we're covering B12 testing a
little bit
and I talked about doctors experiences
with that experiences that it that I've
had with that as well and the
information I've covered that a little
bit too I've also talked about
other aspects of B12 and and of course
the production of B12 so if you guys
just got here there's different topics
there's different
different things that actually you know
view when you get a chance and watch
just great information about p12 in
general
so I'll talk about a couple other little
things that's interesting right B12
helps
prevent vitamin B12 memory loss which is
pretty awesome so B12 helps to prevent
vitamin B12 memory loss
which is really awesome
you know so it helps actually prevent
vitamin B12 deficiency related memory
loss which is incredible vitamin B12
helps to support heart health because
someone was asking me recently and
they're like what about cardiovascular
what about heart B12 does help support
heart health
and then you'll see out there if
somebody would be like yeah B12 puts me
in a better mood it's because it
promotes a healthy mood
which is incredible too and b12 helps
the body make energy from food
which is awesome so that's the whole
thing so you got all these people
they're eating food for energy they're
eating food to create energy but B12
helps their body
make energy from food so it's actually
something that helps the body make the
energy from the food itself so you have
food and what food offers that gives you
energy but
the nutrient itself that sits inside of
us when we take the B12 and we have that
nutrient in us so we have it in US it
actually helps
energy being produced by that food so I
love that all on its own in B12
so the memory gb12 is the
methylcobalamin adenosilcobalamin it's
the two coenzymes
and it's balanced in the right way
so I just wanted to run those by you
guys too it's really cool
David says I want to know too
always mind blown archangela
Angelica says
always mind blown
amazing it's incredible information
check out the brain saver books when you
guys get the chance because if there's
so much B12 information throughout the
book it's something that you might want
to look at when you get a chance I know
that people have so many questions but
it's like hey get the books too learn
learn from the books there's a reason
why there's such incredible information
in there so we can actually all learn
so incredible you guys
all right so
I just wanted to give you a little B
talk B12 talk today because so many of
you guys ask me all the time and every
once in a blue moon I don't know if it
was two years ago I did a B12 talk I
don't know when it was but it was time
especially with everything happening
right now any support we can get when
times are stressful or anything else and
quality matters it's another thing too
so what I was telling another doctor
friend that if you go and you use a
lower quality B12
it
isn't really doing Us justice it's
another thing too
and then also everything I said about
the four things hidden things in there
that you know that they don't have to
disclose there's just so many other
things that just aren't great but
stressful times of the year right now
too and that doesn't help a lot of
people are indulging a lot of people are
partying a lot of people try to dumb
themselves out at this time of year
and no judgment whatsoever on that on
any level like never never ever put
anyone down for what they're eating
ever or or what they're doing or what
they're drinking I never do that I mean
I make jokes about weed and stuff
you know I know like a lot of people are
weed smokers and they make you know
jokes about that whatever and I'm like
yo dudes yeah man I told you I got a
friend that's still on the couch he's
been on the couch for 30 years his wife
left him
he all he did was smoke weed every day
and she finally just moved out and it's
so sad because they were a great couple
that that's besides the point anyway
whatever
and then flu season is here which knocks
us down
so kind of is a good time to talk about
B12 in general because flu season's here
and knocks us down all of that stuff
yeah like you know my friend Bryce right
you guys know my friend Bryce
Bryce it's a big weed smoker right
remember I had Bryce on here remember I
was busy I was you know I was outside
and Bryce came in here and he started
working with you guys
yeah
Chris it says make sense
anyway don't judge anybody for what they
do regardless of what they do
and it's because I know that life is
hard and everybody's jacked up on
caffeine you try to push through the day
smoking weed to try to like you know
blow off their problems and do an
Ayahuasca because you know they're told
that it's good for you oh my God
which is not it's not good for you
either way I don't judge anybody I'm
just saying that there are things we can
do to support ourselves through
different difficult times and everything
else
good Erica true wash it unless you grew
it yourself
Happy Birthday Liam
he's a little boy in the community
amazing
birthdays are very special
yep so happy birthday to Liam
incredible guys I think this concludes
the B12 show which is really great well
unless we still
oh you guys check this out right we just
did 10 days of the brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge 10 days for free
you can watch them over again they're
not packaged up and for sale they're
free medicalmedium.com so go to
medicalme.com go to the menu hit brain
shot therapy watch those videos of the
10 days of Miracles that have happened
miracles of people healing from the
brain shot therapies seriously it's
mind-blowing you guys so check that out
check out medical meme podcast
leave some reviews on Amazon for the
brain saver books if you guys you know
really love them and and all that that
would be incredible too and I have been
reading the reviews you guys have been
leaving and I'm just like mind blown
seriously mind blown I can't even tell
you for real for real
incredible educating myself says the
robots you want me to do the robot that
was during the 10-day cleanse I don't
know if I'm supposed to do the robot
right now you guys I don't know is it
allowed no right no no robot today what
a robot we already did 10 days of it
um
anyway
medicalme.com check it out when you get
a chance
go there
and you guys can see all the what we're
doing to it which is incredible all
right guys
love you greatly I will see you next
time for another great show we will
cover so much more stuff too so I'm
really excited about it and oh remember
a telegram I'm leaving exclusive
messages on telegram which are really
incredible listen to the medical medium
podcast that Apple podcast for those
incredible shows with information that's
mind-blowing right go to
medicalmedium.com
and I'm just excited about helping you
guys out getting as much information as
I can to you keep up the good work check
out the brain saver books get the brain
shot therapy in you as soon as you can
it's all amazing anyway and quality
matters you guys like I said before when
it comes down to supplementation that's
why I stand behind uh member gb12
as well fly on the wall you missed the
fly on the wall we'll do it we'll do fly
on the wall someday I'll make sure all
right guys take care