okay episode 12 b12 you trick or treat
you don't get it from your meat
so you got to check out the episode it's
mind-blowing actually so i'm here i'm
going to talk about b12 a little bit
talk about where we get our b12 from
where do we get our b12
did you know that b12 is one of the most
important
nutrients there is it without it we
don't exist i've talked about how
vitamin c
without vitamin c we can get scurvy
we can get diseased really quick and
just and literally die without vitamin c
vitamin c was completely void of being
in you and being part of your life well
b12 is a big part of that too that's the
big one right there it's b12 but
where do we get our b12 what foods do we
get our b12 in like
do we get b12 from our food the episode
at medical medium podcast at apple
podcast you can't miss this episode
seriously guys this one's a good one
this one's a link is in the description
and i know people
i know a lot of people that heard it
already that are just like okay
okay that one that one right there was
really good so you got to check it out
link is in the description right there
danielle says hi anthony just listen to
the b12 podcast love it
oh so glad you listened to it incredible
it's an important one because we have to
understand b12
it's to protect ourselves and you know
in this day and age with all that's
going on with emotional hardships and
losses
i mean how many how many hard times did
you go through with emotions and
with other people and breakups and i
know people a friend of mine
got divorced and i know all kinds of of
things that people are going through
and it just takes the toll and you could
go through a lot with these different
emotional struggles and hardships and
b12 just we just lose
our b12 we lose it and where are we
getting it from
are we getting it from foods which foods
have it well you got to hear this
episode so it's it you just have to
medical medium podcast at
apple podcast it's b12
trick or treat you don't get it from
meat why do i say that i'm going to talk
about a little bit in a couple minutes
talk about like vegans and plant-based
people where
they're afraid about not getting their
b12 and where did they get their b12 how
do they get their b12 it's a big fear
and i even say i even talk about it in
this episode you guys
i talk about that kind of thing
happening is like you you go plant-based
i'm a huge supporter plant-based uh
movement plant-based diets i'm a
supporter of animal-based diets too you
know clean animal-based diets too and
all that but the point is is that i feel
bad for the plant-based and vegan people
all these years i feel bad for them
because they get attacked with
certain tricks why trick or treat okay
you don't get it from meat because what
happens is they're being told once you
go vegan it's like
okay you wake up in the morning like i'm
starting my vegan plant-based diet i got
inspired by it
my friend got me hooked on it i read
something about it online
and and all of a sudden you know
somebody told me like you're not gonna
get your b12 you're gonna die
where are you gonna get your b12 and all
of a sudden you're like you're in fear
and chaos like
and i talk about it in this episode too
it's really important so
um episode 12 medical medium podcast
at apple podcast the link is in the
description apple podcast
is the official platform where i
launched this new
podcast the medical meme podcast this is
different than the old radio shows
if you listen to this podcast at other
places other
platforms it's not going to be the same
because this is the uncensored version
and i i get it the uncensored version
gets a few people upset
i've seen that before out there already
where i've seen some people
complaining like you know i like it when
you're censored because
you don't say all this this stuff and i
like it kind of like
i don't like hearing about too much
truth i don't really want to hear about
too much truth i kind of don't want to
hear that
and i understand that i understand that
but you know look it's
it's tough times right there in the
world i was looking for a platform where
i could be uncensored on
and anita says loving all your podcasts
um margie says just finished listening
to b12 podcast wow thank you wasn't it
good
wasn't it a good one i mean i listened
to it again today
carolina says i'm so high on b12 my
doctor is concerned
you got to listen to this episode
carolina
check it out and medical mean podcast at
apple podcast link is in the description
carolina
i mean look i i just if the
information's in there when you hear
about it you'll be like what
oh my god when you hear about how it
works like if your b12 is too high
if your b12 is too low b12 testing i
talk about
i talk about everything b12 there but i
also talk about
things just nobody knows that's the
whole point all of this is about what
people don't know
out there and it's really interesting
you guys have to hear the episode
i'm going to talk about it a little bit
more lots to cover about that but first
i wanted to remind you guys
did you listen to the brain fog episode
and did you listen to the neurological
symptoms episode
those are really important did you
listen to the apple cider episode
that's another one um
so joan says my b12 is off the charts i
take beverage b12 every day
you know what happens is that um it
it's it's best to have it you know high
and still do things for it and still be
proactive in doing things for it and
still take things for it you know i talk
to doctors all the time about this and
doctors are at a point really good
doctors out there now they reach out to
me and they want to
understand b12 and they want to know
what's going on because they don't teach
anything like that out there
you know it's like i had a doctor tell
me the other day that they don't teach
that in medical school about b12 and
where to get b12 from and if it's active
and usable is the b12
active is the is the b12 usable and
they don't even talk about that like how
does b12 work in the body
so it's so important um elena says you
were just censored a few times
ha ha ha ha it's funny uh negan fun
hey uh what what hey dr fun
incredible you're here uh it's true i
see people who are not vegans who have
low b12 levels
amazing credible so you know
um so you see it right in your practice
uh amazing doctor right there incredible
doctor
um just just if anybody wants to know
and um
you know you've got an amazing doctor
right there that knows so much about
information
that's healing people and you know the
whole point is it's like
when you go when you when you when
you're plant-based
the biggest fear is b12
you know where's your b12 how
am i gonna how am i gonna survive am i
gonna live
am i gonna get sick is is something
terrible gonna happen to me is all my
hair gonna fall out is
am i gonna get acne now and if i don't
like all these questions it's fear and
chaos with with vegans and plant-based
people and i get it that
that you know look i get it's scary to
go plant-based for a lot of people and
so
the confusion's there but there's a
massive amount of confusion
regarding where we get b12 from our food
okay
so why would plant-based people be told
hey
you got you're not going to have any b12
you're not going to get any b12 from
your food why would they say that well
because fruits and the vegetables that
people eat
right including even leafy greens and
herbs you know
they don't have b12 in them so where are
you going to get it
because meat has b12 in that right mint
meat
chicken has b12 eggs has b12 but don't
get too excited because i want to tell
you something real quick
eggs have b12 and oysters
clams don't run out and eat a bunch of
oysters now
don't run out and eat a bunch of clams
now right and you know you just yeah
you'll get a lot of
toxic heavy metals right so anyway so
shrimp
has b12 so but the whole point is is
that b12
is not the b12 that our bodies
use or utilize that's the trick right
there
on its own so if you're an animal
protein person
right you know and you're like hey
you're vegan
you're not going to get b12 where are
you going to get it or if you're a
you know doctor that you know even if
even vegan doctors i talked to a vegan
doctor last week
that connected with me is like look i'm
a vegan doctor i'm plant-based doctor
my patients are mostly plant-based i
take care of
you know plant-based patients and all
this kind of stuff
and even he was like where did we get
our b12 i was like
huh what where you know
and i was telling them well first of all
where does a meat eater get their b12
and it's like well for meat right
you get it from meat you get it from
chicken get it from eggs
and i'm like no you don't you don't
that's why meat eaters
are also b12 deficient too so just for
the record
you know there's the majority of b12
deficient people are people who eat
animal products and this
i'm not against animal products or
people eating animal products and if you
guys know me by now
i'm all about answers and you can plug
it into whatever diet belief system you
have you guys know how that's how i
am like you can plug in this information
if you want to eat some meat and that's
what you want to do
you can plug it in if you want to be
plant-based it's just about how do we
heal
where's the answers what information can
i give you so you can heal with what the
diet or platform you're on right
you guys know that all about me medical
medium tools are saving lives around the
world that are both meat eaters
and obviously plant-based of course
right and
but anyway the whole point is is like
you can you can be low in b12 and be
eating meat chicken and eggs
and you can also have b12 in your system
from eating meat chicken and eggs but
that b12
doesn't mean it's working for you it
doesn't mean it's doing the things it
does for you and then we get sick down
the road and we start falling apart
things start going wrong we get viral we
have other issues
and then we get in trouble so the b12 is
important for us and it's
it's you know joan says following
um joan says mine is high also so your
b12 is also
high yeah and you can have high b12 now
when you hear the episode
you'll understand like word for words
you'll hear it you'll understand
like what happens when it's high what
does that mean is it good is it bad is
it working for you is it not working for
you
so we can't get tricked by that either
just because our b12 is high
doesn't mean we're utilizing it exactly
or utilizing
all of it from our food it doesn't mean
our food is made it was working for us
it's important
um so yeah so have you guys heard uh the
neurological symptom episode you gotta
check this out so medical medium podcast
at apple podcast
make sure you check these episodes out
the apple cider vinegar episode that one
there too
neurological symptoms brain fog and the
list goes on there's three meditations i
put out so far the moon meditation the
brain meditation
please check those out share them with
other people if you can
eachota said b12 was a mind blower i
listened twice
and then another couple of times to that
poem at the end whoa
wow that's incredible thanks uchoda
amazing amazing
so that the deal is here
is about making sure that you know how
to protect yourself
and your family you know you might be
somebody that wants to stay plant-based
and but yet you're about to leave the
plant-based movement because you're told
where's your b12
you might be somebody that's eating
animal proteins but you're low in b12 or
even high in b12 but does that mean it's
working you're gonna have to
listen to the podcast if you can and
take a few minutes out from your busy
day
and listen and so you can learn about
that too just because
you got you're getting just because when
you get a blood test and it says oh your
b12 is normal
doesn't mean that's the b12 that's
actually
helping protect you so things don't go
wrong like you know skin issues and
other issues too
and a little bit of depression and all
these other stuff because what happens
is that b12 is critical for
your immune system it's critical for
nerve function
so if you're up against low-grade
viruses like i've always talked about
if you're up against you know some
epstein-barr if you're up against some
strap
if you're up against something else the
toxic heavy metals or other triggers i
talk about or emotional hardships
if you're up against some broken trust
issues that you know happen and
betrayal and you know maybe something
else that happened in your life and
you're you're struggling emotionally and
mentally
and the b12 is critical so you gotta
catch this episode it's really important
right there
jill says um the link is in the
description by the way jill says the
podcasts are life-changing thank you so
much for everything
you do thank you for listening to the
podcast i mean
i want you guys to know i i put my all
into these podcast episodes
and and it's they're not they're not
like throwaways because what happens
with podcasts is
you just get a bunch of people together
and you just kind of
you do the coffee talk you know on a
podcast and then
throw that one away let's do another one
another one another one you know how
podcasts work where
just keep on getting people on and just
coffee talk it coffee talk it and it's
kind of like okay is this interesting or
not
i just want you to know when you hear
this podcast the medical mean podcast at
apple podcast when you hear these
episodes just know
that wasn't that wasn't the mindset here
that wasn't
this was about giving you guys
tremendous amounts of information that's
life-changing
like tools to just to really help you
heal
that's what it was about like it was
when i was doing when i was gonna do
when i was gonna launch this medical
meeting podcast it's like wait a minute
you're not bringing all these people on
two three times a week and just doing
coffee talk like everybody does
i'm like no i'm not doing that no way
um it's not going to happen it's not
going to be throwaways you know and
that's the that's a big part of the
podcast world right now
just like throw that away throw that
away it's like cotton candy it's like
quick cotton candy and you throw it away
um these are here for you to help your
friends your family these are here to
turn your lives around these are here to
actually give you
viable information shirley smith i'm
starting to listen to neurological
podcasts i really need help
i'm really glad you're listening to it
it's such an important one
and so so helpful so helpful
um so yeah so yeah so anyway you guys
it's it's medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
julie said i like how funny you have
become and what yeah yeah you know what
i was just holding back
yeah you guys are just you know you're
you're you're seeing the aw
that has the light the more of a lighter
lighter heart you know
um elky says he's always been funny for
sure absolutely appreciate your humor
hey
thanks you're awesome um
dr fun the reference range for b12 is
also not good
so so just looking at the numbers isn't
enough
the brilliant man brilliant doctor i
know you're helping so many people
um incredible incredible
so when it comes down to b12 it's one of
those things that i don't want anyone to
overlook
it's this is one of those must listen to
episodes
because does your health matter does
your wellness matter does your
well-being does your emotional
well-being matter
and so there's when we're missing the
link
with b12 and not understanding it we can
get really in trouble
terry king says your podcasts are
amazing thank you
they're so informative production is
super high you know
i i try to make the production as high
quality as i can you guys like seriously
like
that's the whole point there too is i
just didn't want this to be a throwaway
podcast i get it
when people do podcasts out there it's
just coffee talk throw away
you know and not that the production's
not great because
i get it it's just you wake up in the
morning you do your podcast it's fun
it's kind of hip and you just you
there's
throwaways and i didn't want to do that
i wanted to make sure that this was
literally like a docu-series
like style like something that that it
gives you
you know information from above healing
information
and just in the in the quality was there
so you can move your life forward it's
just that's what it was about it was
like
you know and someone told me they're
like why are you gonna do that why are
you gonna invest
every all your energy your time all of
that into this
why don't you just do what everybody
else does just coffee talk it
you know talk have fun talk crap and
then it gets thrown away and the next
one comes later
um i was like no i don't want to do that
i don't want to do that
nicholas says love the vinegar podcast
every episode i've caught so far
mind blowing good well done aw hey share
it
share it with other people you guys
we're a grassroots movement i don't have
pr and marketing and never did
even though i'm a number one new york
times bestseller with all the new york
times bestselling books
and um you know millions of books around
the world
healing people even with all that said
and done
i still do things that aren't this i
still do things that are
not conventional like i do things like
much different where i don't do the big
pr
the big marketing i'm gonna do any of
that i i kind of like
it's like winger or a prayer kind of
thing or whatever you want to call it
it's like
look this has saved lives the
information saved lives let people share
it to save other lives and
you know and it's always been that way
so share these episodes if you can you
guys know that
constance says love you aw and spirit of
compassion
spread compassion appreciates that um
and
michelle says the podcasts are great
intensity is required
and they're they're intense these
podcast episodes are intense for sure
and i remember when the first episode
came out
i said to you guys you might not want to
hear this and i said that
and i was straight up straight up across
the board
like for real i was like you guys might
not want to hear this podcast
because this podcast is really intense
and over the top with with information
but more than that spooky too
in a way because when you drop truth
there's a lot of people that don't want
to hear it i understand
i totally get that and i respect that um
link is in the description
uh medical media podcast at apple
podcast subscribe so you're notified
it's important so if you're listening to
the podcast at any other platform please
know that it's censored or
you're not hearing the whole thing
little pieces missing you'd be surprised
there's little pieces missing in those
it doesn't seem like it there is so this
is this is the platform here it's
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
link is in the description
um mary says i loved all the details
about b12
incredible i loved all the details about
elevated biotics and b12
this morning yeah oh it's the the
insects right
i talk about the insects and in there
and everything about that you guys got
to catch this episode you really do
and you know it's a halloween special so
that's another one too so it's
b12 trick or treat you don't get it from
your feet
you don't get it from me anyway so
so you wanna you wanna listen to it and
check it out
these podcast episodes are there
you know my heart and soul is in these
and
and it's not something like i'm just
messing with you know
i get it podcast episodes out there it's
just about hey i want to start a podcast
totally fine and let's get some guests
on and let's just ask kind of
questions whether they're not going to
help people or not or anything it's like
hey look
i didn't want to do that i wanted to
make sure that this was
a work a work that was
for people to heal and get their lives
back in a different way like
information and the meditations so that
people have a fighting chance
and you can't play around you got to do
things you got to
do things and for people like it has to
be so
like in this podcast i was like you had
to keep in mind like
what do we need to do to get people
better what how can we do this more and
more
um mj says please do a podcast on hives
and skin rashes please
i will i have one that's in the works
that's i'm working on it i promise
i felt like the b12 one was important i
felt apple cider vinegar was important
because
you might be that one person that can't
move the needle because of that apple
cider vinegar and i have to think about
that of course all of that um
but you guys so this is a really
important one
link is in the description don't miss
this episode whatever you do share this
episode
so people can protect themselves and you
know
we talk about life being hard we talk
about how life's being challenging
now we talk about what's happening and
what's going on out there
we're in a trying time and all this well
who's talking about what we need to
protect ourselves so our nervous systems
don't
go downhill and just and fall apart and
so our mental
stability doesn't start to rattle and
shake because if you know everything and
what about all the hardships people go
through with everything that's happening
out there like who's looking out for
people i want to know
and this episode here along with other
episodes
at the medical meeting podcast about
like who's looking out for people
like who that's the whole point like um
you know we looking out for people or
what are we just doing podcasts because
we want a
fancy podcast and have guests on and
stuff and which is great
but i just said i can't do that this
time like i can't
not that i ever did that i wanted to
make sure you guys
get what you need and that's what this
is the b12
episode is like quintessentially part of
that
that's what i mean this is like an
example of
not messing around you guys need to know
what's going on
you need to you need to have the things
you need that's what it's about
anyway i love you guys um check it out
link is in the description
and take care