and it
bananas
worst food on the planet
are bananas the worst food on the planet
anyway you guys we're live right now you
guys have to hear the podcast by the way
okay the medical media podcast link is
in the description at apple podcast
right
no commercials you gotta hear the banana
episode i'm so pumped up about this
episode
it's a really really informative
powerful episode we're live right now
you guys i'm going to answer some banana
questions i got some banana questions
here i'm going to talk about bananas too
i want to talk about different tips
about bananas hang on for this show i
hope you watch this show because man
we're going to talk about it
and talk about when to eat a banana like
when to eat a banana right we might even
talk about the mono cleanse a little bit
like eating bananas on a mono level and
see how that can help us it's good to
see you guys
incredible that you're coming on here
and
we're going to talk about some of the
silly stuff too about bananas like why
are they so attacked why are bananas
hated so much and on the podcast if you
catch the podcast right that i did
podcast episode you guys
here's what you'll learn on the podcast
so check it out learn how the banana
became one of the most feared foods in
the health world
feared
okay you'll learn that
see why it is that people believe
bananas are bad for them it's another
one
answer the question why did the bananas
start getting a bad rap in the early
2000s how freaking weird
learn the healing benefits of the banana
find out what food science doesn't know
about antiviral compounds food science
obviously doesn't know a lot about
anything because everybody's so sick
right
understand how viruses can affect the
body and what bananas have to do with
fighting them yes isn't that interesting
bananas fight viruses food science
doesn't know that nobody in the industry
knows that right mm info but bananas
fight
viruses baby that's a pretty cool thing
listen about how as the popularity of
the bananas fell the popularity of
chocolate rose
what
chocolate went up up up did you hear the
podcast went up up up up olivia said
great awesome podcast chocolate went up
up up up up chocolate up up up bananas
down down down down down down down
chocolate upgrade people getting sick
people dying people getting sick chronic
illness growing bananas going down down
down chocolate going up up up
and
i think i had some bananas today
i had too many bananas can you have too
many bananas that's not in this right
here
what happens what happens if glucose
okay calm down aw aw calm down
what happens if glucose doesn't get to
your brain in time dude
your brain in time
you got to hear the podcast if you guys
came on here please tell me you heard
the podcast jen coffin says hi ew i
enjoyed the banana podcast
especially the little discussions about
the universe that's so cool oh my god
you guys check out this episode when you
get a chance but also hang out with me
right now because i'm going to talk
about banana tips and stuff like that
little bit
hello
are you there
i can't hear you
i
huh
is there a monkey there
is there a monkey listening
are you
are you a monkey in here where's hello
you guys i want to talk about some cool
stuff even about monkeys eating bananas
right
know the harsh truths behind why science
and research chooses not to invest and
look into the medicinal healing
properties of some foods such as bananas
and of course celery juice
they won't look into celery juice of
course not
never mind bananas right
understand why the industry does not
care about you healing from sickness
they could care less
the industry could care less
if we live or die doctors care a lot of
doctors care but they're not the
industry the industry can care less
they'll eat you up and munch you up and
spit you out and discard you and the
industries don't care
the industries want you on caffeine
caffeine caffeine caffeine and then they
just want you dead afterwards and then
when you die you come back and you do
caffeine all over again you come back
around over and over and over again
like 10 lifetimes 15 lifetimes right
caffeine caffeine caffeine diet
and then come back
as a baby caffeine caffeine caffeine
chocolate caffeine coffee chocolate die
that look die come back as a baby and
you do it over and over and over again
they don't care
gianna says hi uw loved your banana
podcast i was told to avoid bananas to
heal my acne
dear lord
but it was only until i used your info
and ate lots of bananas that my acne
went away thank you as always tiana over
there on youtube amazing thank you for
being here and that that's incredible
seriously
seriously incredible right
and i'm proud of you too you guys you
need to know this like i'm proud of you
i am if you're taking care of yourself
you're eating bananas you're not
listening to the [ __ ] and you're not
getting sucked into all the propaganda
and the crap and the rhetoric to take
down bananas to end up affecting your
health sugar bad sugar sugar is bad for
you sugar's bad for you right
and if you don't get sucked into that
you got a shot to heal it's incredible
you know what i mean
mayor bear says i still love the jokes
please keep it up okay i'll try to keep
it up
you're gonna see i am at your service
i'm gonna come up with another joke as
fast as possible i'm at your service i
am
i'm at your service all right
you guys seriously though like no
kidding around we're gonna cover some
tips about the banana right
we got a baby right here why
why do we have a baby right here talk
about that in a couple of minutes
we have a brain right here can you guys
see the brain right there okay on tic
tac you might be able to not be able to
see that yet i'll show you
you got a brain right here right
and why does the banana help the brain
why is the banana good for the brain
right look at that even fits right in
there just like that why is the banana
good for the brain it's a whole nother
thing too
i see we're censoring on facebook so
censored on there all right i was
worried so the let's see the awakening
of death says i was worried for a moment
when i saw the title bananas have been
my favorite food for years i know the
title i'm so sorry because the title is
kind of misleading banana
worst food on the planet that's the
title it wasn't because i think it's the
worst food on the planet you guys know i
like bananas totally totally
exactly
so all right you guys let's cover some
of the things so first of all just a
reminder link is in the description you
know you guys up there the podcast up
there and tic toc link is in the profile
right of the banana episode you don't
want to miss it it's packed with
information it's so important cold white
spring i know i got a kangaroo up
that's a kangaroo baby right here too
and yes there's a kangaroo up there
fancy that right okay
i got some banana comments too i want to
read those a little bit all right you
guys i'm organized today i'm actually
organized
i have my paper here
right
so i can talk about some of these
comments
okay jovanna says
on facebook your podcast saved me and
got me through bad vertigo
i couldn't move my head either direction
without throwing up my husband made me
celery juice every day in lemon water
and heavy metal detox movie within the
month i was healed from it
i know a lot of people who have been
there man they've been there throwing up
from their vertigo throwing up
getting up out of their bed puking on
the side of their bed because of the
vertigo are you kidding i mean totally
i tell everyone what a blessing celery
juice is and since i couldn't read
moving my head
down at this time i listened to your
podcast on a loop seriously like night
and day i'm honored you can deal with me
you know like that that's incredible
because when i listen to my podcast i go
oh my god because you know you hear
yourself so much or just you just start
to like go mad right your information
saved me and i can't thank you enough
incredible
so an instagram comment right here thank
you for this this is the food i find
myself having to defend most often so
that's
a comment right so that's michelle okay
on instagram
having to defend the banana how is that
possible how did we get there and i talk
about the podcast why are we in a place
where we have to defend the banana how
crazy is that
it's like it's psycho when you think
about it right you got
rosina you enjoyed the podcast you guys
enjoyed the podcast
incredible
so
all right
see victoria rising from the ashes right
this is cool instagram another fantastic
podcast the ending was very intriguing
i'm wondering if you are going to give
us some more insights into some of this
in your next podcast
after the hint you gave us about it in
the last week's ig live thank you spared
the most high
medical medium and the whole medical
medium team bless your heart
i'm working on
an alien podcast episode i'm just
letting you guys know okay
i don't know what's going to happen
when it's released
i think i'm going to lose a lot of
followers
probably
because
alien podcast that i'm going to put out
is not like the usual crap
not like usual stuff where government
bases are harboring aliens
area 51 it's not going to be that usual
crap right
so
i'm not saying that's true or false or
anything i'm not saying that i'm just
saying it's not going to be the usual
thing
so the alien podcast that i'm putting
out
it's going to have some shocking stuff
in there right but it it may shock
people a little too much and i'm not
sure which direction they're going to be
shocked
i mean you'll probably just
lose thousands of followers because of
it but you know what
i'm always at risk of that any time any
time i go against the apple cider
vinegar people every time i go against
ionizer people every time i go against
chocolate people whatever i
lose every time i go against the
psilocybin people i just lose people
anyways nothing i can do
the glam rose says
as fruit and smoothies cause cavities in
children
that's what they are saying
unbelievable the glamorous please listen
on youtube please listen i beg of you
please listen to the medical main
podcast
at apple podcast listen to the teeth
podcast we just did and i have all my
teeth
and they're all great
and um and i'm gonna like i'm like
getting up there in my age
right internet says i'm like 26 or
something i'm not i can promise you this
amy says why do i have histamine
reactions to them to bananas
is it the only thing you have a
histamine reaction to that's it like
there's an actual reaction right when
you have the banana so that's something
to consider too right or
just you're told you have histamine
elevations because of bananas and stuff
like that i know that alternative
medicine is teaching people to be afraid
of banana they'll tell you anything
about the banana right so i'm just
curious that's the only thing that
elevates your histamine on any level or
is it foods you had the night before
that are elevating the histamines and
the bananas or just going in there to
try to clean things up so there's a lot
of different ways of looking at it
people get really toxic and they start
reacting to everything i'm reacting to
bananas now now i'm reacting to apples
now i'm reacting to strawberries now i'm
reacting to grapes now i'm reacting to a
melon now i'm reacting to a papaya now
reacting to a mango i thought mango
would be okay now i'm reacting now i'm
reacting to some mel cilantro man i'm
reacting to cilantro and that's what i'm
reacting to it's what happens is when
you get really toxic you just start
reacting all kinds of stuff
so
yeah so why does everybody have to
defend the banana how bad does it get
because i told you in the podcast
there's some evil seeds planted
purposely into the alternative movements
of functional medicine doctors and
podcast doctors right
and all the doctors rip bananas down and
they rip them down and they rip them
down to the point where they just want
you to eat the green banana where it's
totally green a hundred percent that's
what they want they want it to be like
green and only green the sugars are not
good for you and they just want it green
right
i might have a doctor friend show up
so we'll see maybe in a little bit
all right
so
let's talk about
right here okay
breastfeeding if moms are trying to
develop enough milk
to breastfeed their babies bananas are a
big one right there and not just one not
just a half a banana but if a mom
is worried about breast milk and wants a
full tank
a breast milk
right to go the distance
then it's critical to be doing bananas
bananas are critical for that and not
just one banana once in a while not just
a banana every other day
talking about making sure you're doing
some bananas six seven bananas eight
bananas a day you want breast milk
because bananas really crank up the
breast milk is what they do they crank
the breast milk up so there's a full
tank for the baby critical to know right
there
see
jay from youtube says please let me know
what to do i get real tired after eating
bananas alone nothing else so what
happens is like this right
if you're really tired when you eat
banana first of all you'd never get
tired eating nothing else nothing else
makes you tired so that's important to
know right there so a mango
watermelon a chicken dinner
piece of cheese an egg nothing makes you
tired just a banana so that that's
important so i want you to be your own
detective
i want you to be your own
it's critical you gotta ask yourself
what else is making me tired when i eat
nothing else makes me tired nothing
nothing at all
not that pasta meal that that won't make
me tired at all
not that
that cookie that will make me tired well
if the cookies you know jacket with
caffeine and chocolate chips it's
definitely gonna not make people tired
right but
it's important to know
like is it just the banana so you have
to be your own detective you have to
really look at that because it can trick
you out right there so okay so if
someone has
neurotransmitter problems
if they have neurological issues right
vagus nerve issues they don't know about
neurotransmitter problems they don't
know about lots of toxic heavy metals in
the brain they don't know about right
and you eat a banana you do get relaxed
you can get relaxed so yeah it's
possible the banana is may calming your
nerves
if your nerves are sensitive and
problematic a banana can give you a
temporarily nerve calming effect
which is incredible really very healing
it could be that kind of tired
versus some other kind of tired right
but also look at all your other foods
and what you're doing does anything make
you tired at all but because if nothing
makes you tired and a banana makes you
tired then that's a healing
tryptophan healing effect
neurotransmitter glucose
neurotransmitter chemicals getting to
those neurotransmitter chemicals like
you know that's the whole point all of
it very healing electrical impulses
neurons getting boom
all that glucose
trace minerals and neurotransmitter
chemical compounds doctors say we should
eat high fat low sugar diets for pcos
doctors know everything about pcos
that's why they're stopping all that
pcos out there huh
that's why they're able to fix all that
pcos out there
they know so much about pcos out there
that's why nobody has pcos anymore you
didn't hear about that there's no pcos
anymore it doesn't exist anymore because
the world of doctors cured it so pcos
isn't even out there anymore because
doctors are so smart and science
researchers so smart that they actually
eradicated pcos from this planet
so
did you did you know that did you guys
know that pcos doesn't exist anymore
they actually found a magic pill
the doctors found a magic pill for pcos
and it eliminated it all across the
planet there's not one woman dealing
with pcos anymore they eradicated it
because research and science are so
smart yeah they know everything so you
better listen to them when they say go
on a keto diet and don't have any sugar
for your pcos because they're so smart
they eradicated all pcos on the planet
you guys i think i had too many bananas
today
all right
but thank you for being here i'm not
no disrespect no disrespect thank you
for being here seriously and even asking
a question like that
huh
let's see hot is on youtube
okay me kk maybe the problem is not the
banana but the pesticides i have this
problem with melons but the organic
version is no problem at all it's
incredible maybe you're really really
highly sensitive and maybe it's not even
the pesticide but even something else
christina says i eat four to six bananas
a day just don't mix them with fat
christina
amazing amazing don't mix them with fat
no you don't have to janet kaiser i
found eating one banana a day caused my
blood sugar to jump almost 70 points
let's talk about that janet that's what
we're going to talk about right now
let's go there
you
ready that's because your diet is high
in fat you may not know it but it's high
in fat if you say well aw my diet's not
high in fat okay
uh
let's just say you're a vegan pretend
that okay nuts seeds
nuts seeds nut milks
seeds
right
nut butters
nut milks nuts seeds i'll say it over
again oils
oils olive oil other oils nut butters
seeds oils avocado
say you're vegetarian cheeses
eggs
chocolate
chocolates high in fat keep on going say
you're just an animal protein eater
chicken fish meat say you just like
coconut coconut coconut butter coconut
oil coconut flakes
all of the fat
right
makes it so anytime you put any kind of
healthy sugar in you or any kind of
sugar in you your insulin resistance
kicks in because you got so much fat
pumping through your bloodstream that
your insulin resistance happens it's not
the banana's fault the banana's there to
help heal you and fix you
that's what that is
but if we're gonna eat all this fat
every day chocolate nut butters nuts
seeds oils avocado chicken meat eggs
dairy
nut milks if we're gonna eat all that
fat
what's gonna what's gonna happen oh you
gotta dump in there's a little sugar no
matter what it is
little glucose go in boom insulin
resistance reason why is because your
liver is tanked out you've already
tanked out your liver it's already got a
fatty liver you're already pre-diabetic
you're already pre-diabetic you're
already getting that insulin resistance
this is what you this is what happens
when you eat a lot of bananas you get a
lot of energy it's crazy and i was up at
five o'clock this morning and i went to
bed at one o'clock last night
i got my period back eating bananas keto
low carbs screwed my gut and hormones if
i had a feather
for any time i heard
going back for years now the keto diet
screwed something up
the keto diet true that up on me
if i had a feather man i'd be flying to
the moon
yeah
so let's talk about a couple different
things um
all right
you guys know we're talking about the
podcast right medical main podcast at
apple podcast we're talking about that
olivia lutz says he covers how to eat
what sets it when you're sensitive
cleanse the heel
amazon.com 58
off right now
off amazon.com
you guys have to have cleanse to heal
right
58 off the mono cleanses in here so why
do i have the cleanser heel book with me
right now
because
people who have gastroparesis
right colon problems colitis
crohn's
gas bloating constipation ibs all these
problems
have problems with their intestinal
tracts right
and because of that
in this book right here you'll find a
monocle section which has helped heal
hundreds of thousands of cases of
crohn's colitis celiac ibs and
everything else
mono cleansing mono eating
banana
mono eating papaya mono eating other
things too but mono eating bananas a big
one in there
it's brought a lot of people back
incredible 50 offer get it free at the
library go to the library get it for
free
i don't care if no one you know orders
the book on on amazon go go buy it the
li i mean go get it for free at a
library arena park says i eat a lot of
bananas and no fat and my liver is
healing at that incredible rate okay
arena
i want to tell you something right
exactly you keep the fat out
during a healing process i'm not anti
healthy fats
i'm not it's just that when you're sick
and that liver is sick and that lit
liver is clogged up and you got liver
problems then it's clogged up you've got
the fatty liver and everything and you
go off the fats and you learn how to eat
the foods you need to eat right like the
banana when you're off the fats then
your liver comes back
which is a big deal
any pregnant mamas out there something
to know bananas really healthy for
developing babies inside the womb
critical too
listen to the podcast on how to eat the
banana a lot of people eat them under
ripe or over ripe and it can cause
problems okay so
you know that's important to know right
there
does it matter organic or not
honestly if you can't get an organic
banana i would get a conventional banana
that's what i would do
i would go and buy conventional bananas
darn right
yeah i mean totally would do that 100
if that's all i had and i do do that a
lot conventional bananas a lot of times
this might be a round of conventional
bananas right here if i couldn't find
they were getting
elizabeth
i used to help with liz i used to limit
my bananas now i can eat four to seven
at a time that's incredible liz
liz you're always blowing my mind anyway
and just that's amazing that's amazing
incredible tara appleman had two
perfectly ripe bananas this morning oh
my god
so proud of you that's amazing
incredible
chuckle says hey you're on twitch yay
i'm not gonna do the twitch dance today
no way
can't make me do the twitch dance today
uh-uh not gonna happen
yeah
so yeah all right you guys let's talk a
little bit about different things first
of all just a reminder right now just
letting you know okay
if you just came on here
right
i'm just gonna say it right now if you
just came on here medical mean podcast i
just released banana the worst food on
the planet
the worst food on the planet
david david witchin man integrity
generation just wanted to shout out to
you brother
because you
made me laugh my
ass off the other day
i gotta say and uma you really really
kicked it into gear
and
umakali
i'm just saying you guys made me laugh
like and i needed that laugh that
actually really was a good good timing
for me when i saw that
right
david you actually imitated
the podcast doctor better than i
actually do
way better so anyway
you know you guys ever think about this
all right
think about this
hey david whitson thank you uma made the
edit
yeah
i'm gonna watch it again later
i watched it 10 times
david i actually watched it 10 times
i did
and um i watched it 10 times
maybe even more i watched it over and
over again
i was laughing at heart
right
so
you know
evolution right so you guys let's just
have a little like i don't know let's
just have like
private talk for a second right
the whole evolution thing okay
a lot of people believe in evolution
right
they believe that we were like
in it you know we that we were a snail
and then
from from a snail we turned into some
kind of like other crustacean right
and then
we went from there and then we turned
into like a minnow
and then we turned into a squid and then
we turned into
a jellyfish and then we
somehow were able
to
start breathing in oxygen
right
and we somehow turned into another
creature inside the ocean right
and then when when then from there we
maybe we turned even into a mammal
in the ocean
i don't know
turned into a whale but somehow we ended
up because the evolution science of
research right science research
right they're so smart you know
you can't mess with science research
they know everything they know why
everybody's sick
that's why you know
everybody's
poaching medical medium information of
why everybody's sick right now they're
actually poaching it
anyway signs of research so science
research is so smart right next thing
you know we got on land right and we
started crawling on land right and our
gills opened up right
so another whatever a thousand years and
we've been our gills started breathing
in and then we developed lungs
right
and then now we're on the we're we're
then we became something else on the
right
now we're like
i don't know not a squirrel whatever
like a hedgehog or something
and then we became a bear and then we
became a monkey somehow right
because you guys know evolution right
science research is so smart they teach
that in schools
right so now now we're a monkey
somehow and then as a monkey we somehow
became like a gorilla
right
and then when we became a gorilla
we somehow became a human
i don't know how
they don't know how with their theory of
evolution they teach it as if it's
factual
anyway
right we became
a gorilla right
and it's kind of funny
we became a monkey or a gorilla the
monkey never became a gorilla
so i'm kind of confused about that one
just get just a private talk between us
okay
right
i'll probably get canceled for talking
about this stuff really because you're
not supposed to even talk about like
evolution right anyway so so
okay did the monkey ever turn into a
gorilla no the monkey's like a dick
right different species or something
gorilla's different either way
we somehow came from that
okay
here's here's the craziest part why are
there all these monkeys left over
friend of mine was in costa rica and
there's a like bunch of monkeys down
there it's like
why are they still there
like
has science figured out like why they
just they just aren't developing they're
just not turning into humans eventually
over time like have the science figured
that out right no they haven't
so anyway let's just go into this anyway
monkeys eat bananas
monkeys eat bananas now we care about
primates right
i'm pretty sure the human race cares
about primates right gorillas eat
bananas too right so we're supposed to
care about
right nature
right i saw a commercial the other day
there was a guy like saw a commercial
there was a guy like in a car so i don't
know if it was a car commercial and he
had this like grater on the back like he
had a rake on the back of the car and it
was like this
this hippie dude guy right
which is cool he looked cool
so he was in this like
million dollar car
on the beach
guy had like some long hair or whatever
he was in this like car whatever
and he was cruising on the beach and he
had this rake stuck on the back of the
car and the rake was picking up like
like bottles and stuff he was driving
real fast
the guy was wearing designer clothes
right so you know they're one of those
guys they got a little longish hair
totally decked out with really expensive
shoes really expensive clothes to the
tilt you know one of those kinds of guys
right
i'm not judging them or anything i'm
just telling you i'm giving you the
description
so so he's obviously an educated guy
got lots of money came from money or
something and he's in his fancy car and
he's on the beach driving right and he's
raking up with the rake on the back of
the car you guys saw this and he's
raking up like bottles empty bottles
plastic bottles and he's raking them up
and he's dragging him along and then
after that they show him sitting there
like relaxing like yeah man
i'm like really really
i really hip on taking care of nature
and stuff
and then all these sea turtles were just
everywhere of course they did come you
know computer images of the sea turtles
coming up like there's thousands of sea
turtles coming up to lay their eggs
right
and this guy's like proud of himself and
i don't blame him because he got some
plastic bottles off the beach
right
which is so we're like all about caring
for nature caring about our world caring
about our oceans caring about like ray
reptiles
caring about everything right that's
what we're about we're all about that
right then why the hell
on earth
is all this now food science guys all
the doctors
all the podcast doctors all the
functional medicine doctors
all the food science people
basically telling us we're [ __ ] if we
eat bananas
when they're feeding the bananas to the
monkeys because it's their natural food
oh it's fine for the monkey i thought we
cared about the monkey but apparently we
don't give a [ __ ] about the monkeys and
we don't give a [ __ ] about the gorillas
and the chimps because they're eating
crappy bananas and they're just gonna
die and have liver disease for the
bananas we shouldn't stop or intervene
that on any level we should just let
those monkeys just eat as many bananas
as they want that [ __ ] crap food that no
one's supposed to eat because functional
medicine doctors and podcast doctors and
all the scientists sure know better they
know we shouldn't be eating this because
this is going to kill us this is bad for
us right
this is terrible if we start eating this
but make sure the monkeys are eating it
though they can eat it the gorillas can
eat it and everything else and heck if
they if we are in this evolution stage
those monkeys and grills are eventually
going to turn to humans so why the hell
are we feeding these monkeys and
gorillas all the bananas
well we know they're going to turn into
humans eventually
and then we're just genetically screwing
them up
how's that how's that make any sense to
you guys
so we care about life here in planet
earth hell there's commercials of like a
rich hippie dude in a fancy car with
decked out designer hippie cool clothes
or whatever regular clothes or long hair
nothing wrong with that pull in a car
with this stuff raking up plastic
bottles like he's like totally on it
sitting down relaxing all cool ready to
crack open a corona light
and then you know and then you know
turtles are coming up if we care that
much like we're supposed to care then
why the hell are we leaving
like
the monkeys and the gorillas behind
because they're going to be human
someday because science research tells
us those monkeys and girls are going to
be humans there's no question about it
there's no doubt because science
research is always right
they're always right about everything so
we have to trust science and research
because those monkeys and chimps and
those and those gorillas they're going
to be 100 a human being they're still in
the evolution phase so why the hell are
we doing what science research and food
science and podcast doctors and
functional medicine doctors are telling
us not to do is we're letting all those
gorillas and monkeys eat all those
bananas
and we're supposed to avoid them because
it's so damn bad for us
can you answer that for me
cause i'm scratching my head over here
anyway
you guys got to check out the podcast
episode
because it's cool
you know
it's a good one it's filled in for
information it's packed bananas are good
for the brain
neurotransmitters they're good for your
like your organs your hearts is critical
okay
and
i'm not an evolution fan so i look you
can believe in what you want to believe
in i don't believe in evolution
i'm just saying
but
if if you believe in evolution i support
you 100 i don't judge i don't judge what
you do
okay
right i'm just not a big evolution fan
i think it was purposely kind of put out
there to take people away from the
spiritual aspect of life
is what i believe it was i believe it
was designed to take you away from the
thought that we are spiritual beings and
that spiritual
connection up above
matters and is real and the light up
above matters and is real and i believe
evolution this is my opinion
was set
there in stone and taught in schools and
everything else to take you away from
god the creator the light whatever you
believe in up there the universe take
you away from that to make you think
that you're not you have no connection
up there whatsoever you're just
you were a toad
and you went from a toad to something
else a snail or whatever you went from a
snail to something else and then finally
you became a monkey
and yeah we just left all the other
monkeys behind if that's the case don't
feed them bananas anymore man because if
it's killing us these bananas why are
you giving it to them or letting them
eat bananas out there they should chop
down every banana tree in the
in the amazon
besides the reason you should chop every
single banana tree down and not let
those monkeys and grills ever get a
banana ever since they're so darn bad
for all of us
anyway
which i hope they don't do
but yeah bananas are that good for us
and good for monkeys and gorillas too
they are indeed
okay let's talk about ripeness for a
little a couple of seconds two way i got
you guys
addie case's celery juice and banana
cleanse has caused more bloating yet all
of my ms symptoms have been healing
is bloating a healing reaction so here
let's go into this addy on youtube very
good question and i want to be at
service here okay
here's how it goes okay
right
inside here
is the food from the past
it's the chocolate cake it's the donuts
it's the cookies it's the additives it's
all the rancid fats it's the the
putrified proteins it's all of this junk
in crud that lines the inside of your
intestinal tract so addie this is
important to know right
okay
all in here
right when people have multiple
sclerosis and i talked about this
because i was the first to publish the
cause of multiple sclerosis so it was
the first to publish the true cause of
multiple sclerosis and now harvard took
my information
didn't cite me and they took it seven
years later illegally
anyway
so the whole point is right here okay
that all this junk and garbage is
sitting in here and sitting in here
somebody who has multiple sclerosis is
viral
lots of metals lots of other toxins and
poisons and a weakened digestive system
with a lot of junk inside here i teach
doctors this all the time
when you're sending a banana down there
the banana rolls
i talk about this in the podcast if you
guys haven't listened to the podcast
please listen to it right
so bananas roll and they roll through
your gut
and they're collecting all that crap
toxins poisons petrified proteins gases
and when you have too much of all that
in there you're gonna bloat for a little
bit because it's getting released but
yet you're healing and that's one of the
reasons why
multiple sclerosis symptoms are getting
at bay and minimizing something very
important to know right
elizabeth healthy liz says walk on water
effect
exactly the walk-on water effect dear
apple man i love what you wrote and
cleansed to heal about bananas walk-on
water effect
my god i forgot about that
i can't keep up with it all all of soc's
information
i got a lot of it in here you know what
happened was
darlene listen to your podcast the
ending wow cliffhanger yeah
what happened is
these books right here
blew my mind so much
that i
because there's so much information in
these books
they're so packed these are the
manuscripts right
but
these books the brainsaver books
like
i was a different person after these
were done
two books at the same time
over 600 pages a piece
uh packed with so much intricate
information that i forgot about the
walk-on water effect right and cleanse
the heel
because
there's so much information that went in
here and it was so hard to put to put
these together
that like
it's i forget some of the other things
so thank you for reminding me you will
be blown away you guys when you see
these
when you have these in your hands i mean
seriously
like
i'm afraid
when those get out the industries are
going to be so pissed at me
because they're going to try to steal it
like usually they always just steal the
info from the medical medium books but
when they see that when the industry
looks at that
because that's what they do they have a
whole think tank they have a whole table
of people around a board for them they
they dissect medical medium stuff and
information and then they thief it
theft it away right that's what happened
that's why
all the different things over the years
like the multiple sclerosis thing and so
many other stuff like long c you know
like long c
long hall c medical medium did that
first put that information out first you
guys this is incredible listen i'm going
to go live again
and it's going to be in a little bit so
i'm going to be on instagram
and i'm going to be
on tick tock
and maybe even telegram so either all
three of those we're going to go live
pretty soon and you know what come with
me over there in a little bit and look
out keep your notifications on that
won't even matter because you won't get
notified
but but the point is but still keep them
on the point is we're going to talk
about like how to eat a banana ripeness
don't eat a green banana i'm going to
cover that in the next live coming up
i'll