book live on youtube doing the cherry
smoothie
which is gonna be fun i got the cherries
right here we're talking about
supplements products things that aren't
really helpful when you're trying to
heal
that's an important topic right there if
you're trying to heal
what's in your way what's not in your
way
like what are we looking for with the
potholes death by a thousand
cuts yeah it's serious serious stuff you
guys good to see you guys coming on
we're live on facebook and youtube we've
got a lot of stuff stuff to cover
actually kevin i saw you came on here um
starts with plants i saw you come on
here too cool brooke good to see you
glad you guys are coming on because
we're going to cover a lot of
information we're talking about hcl
supplements
sodium bicarbonate iron supplements
diatomaceous earth particles
whey protein powder glandular
supplements hair skin nail supplements
multivitamins fish oil collagen
charcoal acv nutritional yeast caffeine
corella and more i'm gonna i'm gonna
give you some run downs on those
so this is really an important important
episode
extra important i'm gonna say it twice
three times banana cherry smoothie as
well
medical medium new edition right and i'm
gonna be doing the banana
the cherry banana smoothie which i'm
pumped up about banana cherry smoothie
there it is right there
what do you guys think i'm excited david
which in all the trendy traps i love
that trendy traps that's right that's
what it is
trendy traps they get in the way of us
healing
and that matters i mean really it hurts
us really badly
that's how much trendy traps can get in
the way of our healing
when we're trying to go uphill i talked
about that right the other time
we're trying to go uphill and then we're
getting knocked back down right
it's like here's what it is you're
climbing this
like you're climbing this cliff right
you guys and you're hanging on to this
cliff
and you're literally doing everything
you can you're struggling to climb
you're climbing you're getting to the
top right and right when you get to the
edge of the cliff and you finally get
your hands over it
someone smacks you in the head and then
you
and then you fall back down and now
you're on the ground
or you fell off the cliff completely and
you're dead
or you you literally or you're you're
injured really really bad i love that
number it's stuck on just now right
there
seven seven seven i love that number
it's a powerful number and
so the bottom line is you're climbing
that cliff you're climbing that cliff
you get to the top you get the top your
feet you gotta watch out your feet don't
slip off the cliff right
you're getting up there and right when
you get on the top someone smacks you in
the face again
it's almost like hey can you help me can
you give me a hand i'm here at the top
you guys can you give me some
can you give me a hand over here can you
what you're going to smack
me in the head bam you get smacked in
the head you get dropped back down and
that's what the sodium bicarbonate the
iron subs the diatomaceous earth
particles
the all-carnitine the glandular
supplements the charcoal the acv the
nutritional ease the caffeine
and that's just a few of them gets in
our way hair skin nail stuff
like i said gut powders that's another
one too janet wow it's
exactly exactly so um
i'm going to make a smoothie in a couple
of minutes too but we got a lot of
ground to cover
this one's important because we get in
trouble divine light 77 has been popping
in my life
so much specifically lately 777 so let's
talk about diatomaceous earth particles
you know what's funny
right did a little post about this okay
you guys
and about the things that are in our way
seems like we're major censored today by
the way
um so did a little post on this and
everybody's like wait a minute
wait a minute i take fish oil when did
you say fish oil is bad
aw wait a minute i'm doing nutritional
yeast
when did you say nutritional yeast is
bad aw i'm doing acv
why did you say apple cider vinegar is
bad right um
tammy good to see you yay a little
earlier hi from sweden good to see you
um and white right and uh
plant protein powders when you say plant
protein powders are bad
when did you say corella was bad when
did he say
when did he say diatomaceous earth
particles are bad oh my god
i'm on that what's going on right and
everybody's freaking out and i'm like
i i'm like wait a minute um
uh that's a head scratcher for me right
now um
well uh have you ever seen
uh an instagram or facebook live or
youtube live
uh a medical medium youtube live um have
you ever read a book
uh where did you come from like
where were you under a rock um did you
ever
watch anything i ever did did you listen
to a medical medium podcast
uh right you want the cutting board
robinson it's an amazing cutting board
i love this cutting board it was like
whoa i can't believe it's cutting board
it's incredible
um so yeah and elaine says i love how
you teach i'm honored i'm honored
so it's what do i do i don't know
what else to say how can i let anybody
know
i've done everything i can to let you
know about the trendy traps
the potholes right the the fall backs
i'll let you guys know about that all
the time this is not just all
i mean really the death by a thousand
cuts i don't even know what to say how
many times can i say death by a thousand
cuts
i'm a broken record i'm a broken record
broken record
i'm a broken record broken record i'm a
robot
you just keep on repeating it no one
hears it though like what do i do right
um anyway you guys so i want you to have
this information i want you to be able
to share this information
save some lives protect some lives so
let's head into it a little bit while we
can't
amy says hi from hawaii good to see you
um
david right dave whitchen right so many
potholes it's just incredible trendy
traps robinson okay
trendy traps right and lots of these but
but it's weird you do a post on it and
everybody's on this stuff
are you on are you on the charcoal are
you on the apple cider vine let me ask
you guys
are you on the apple cider vinegar the
acv
are you on the charcoal um are you on
that
are you on the gut health powders
l-carnitine
glandular supplements whey protein
powder diatomaceous earth particles
um sodium bicarbonate which one
are you guys on rosalie went to the
doctor recently they took 14
vials from me could not stop thinking
about your podcast i wish the doctor had
told me
i wish the doctor had told me
this was going to happen to prepare me
dr jasper here
yeah yeah what we didn't prepare anyone
no we don't prepare you
no no no we don't do that here we just
take all the blood i got a patient here
can you make this quick
yeah i know we just took 140 milliliters
from this patient we didn't prepare her
nope it's like a peer pressure we use a
peer pressure protocol
it's about peer pressure what who
what what happened they hit the ground
after they had the blood drawn what
would happen they took they were walking
and they hit the
ground didn't they have the cookie we
gave them
we gave them a cookie the nurse gives
them a lollipop
yeah yeah the lollipop wasn't enough
they were sugar sensitive they don't eat
candy
so what what do you think what do you
think this is an organic market here at
the doctor's office what are we going to
give them
organic food on their way out
listen we're just here we're drawing the
blood
yeah we know the labs throw out all the
okay i just got to keep working we're
going to take another 140 milliliters
out of this autoimmune patient
who doesn't even have an immune system
because this autoimmune patient doesn't
even have a good immune system but we're
just going to draw the blood out anyway
and throw it all away uh-huh yup yup
medical medium podcast i i've never
heard of it
oh is that that guy that's that guy
where the patients keep on bringing in
the books toward
us doctor's offices yeah yeah we don't
like him
uh-huh he gets in her way okay i gotta
go i gotta go
you know what it's really sad it's
really really sad
um you don't need that much blood you
just don't you just don't need that much
blood
they should only be taking quarter vials
and they shouldn't even be doing that
they only need this much blood and i
told you about this you guys
um this is one of the big traps and they
only need that much blood
right there you can take check this out
right
you can you can take an old pair of
jeans
where someone was murdered like 40 years
ago
and they can take a q-tip a wet
q-tip and they can sit there on the pair
of jeans doing forensics
and they can sit there rubbing that
little piece of dried blood
with a wet q-tip right where you could
barely even see
a stain on the q-tip
they can take that and they can figure
out half
of what's wrong with someone as far as
in our daily blood tests we do today
they can get a nutritional profile from
that a whole nutritional profile
they can check your dna they can check
where your blood sugar is
40 years later a q-tip
dried okay there's a blood scam
going on you guys if you haven't
listened to medical mean podcast at
apple podcast and listen to that one
you know um laura isn't that funny laura
said i can't even
laura ward that's really funny i can't
even i know it's crazy what they do
right you can take a q-tip and get a
little bit of dried blood
and you can get so much information you
can do a psa off of that
you can do an a1c off that cholesterol
you can do a cholesterol off of that
40 years later someone who was who was
murdered
and they found jeans in a mud pit and
they pulled the genes out of a mud pit
and it stayed in the forensic flab for
years right at the police station or
wherever it was going to be and they can
take a q-tip and they can just find this
one
little speck take it and you get the a1c
out of it you can get an anti-nuclear
antigen test out of it you can get
your nutritional profile out of right so
what it is there's a massive blood scam
i really believe it's done on purpose i
do i believe
the blood is not just being thrown away
but i believe the blood hits the black
market
is what i do i believe it hits the black
market for all kinds of sinister things
at this point
because why would they take that much
millions and millions of gallons of
blood you know what it is
it's like it's it's it's a precious
resource but
they've trained us to think it's garbage
they've trained you to believe that your
blood
is worth it's garbage
it's it's a it's not precious it's not
an
important resource it's just trash
you throw it out throw all your blood
out
take too much of it and throw it all out
okay
and it's not easy for your blood your
body to make but they're going to
convince you
that it's easy for your body to make oh
your body will just fix it and i love
this bs this bs right here is my
favorite right
oh your body just rep replaces the
immune cells in three days
your body's bones will replace your
immune cells in three days right
people are already sick with symptoms
their immune systems are already
defunctled you know totally you know
diffused and
hurting and minimized and deficient
right
if they're already low their immune
system they'll make it look like your
immune system will come back in two to
three days
all set perfect don't worry 14 vials 10
vials seven vials
dr fong i just saw you on there we're
live on facebook
in in youtube dr
fun yeah the labs suck blood
right parentheses blood and that's how
it works
it's really really bad you guys so let's
cut let's
let's go into this one truth bombs truth
bombs are critical
they're critical right it's about
protecting the chronic leo it's about
protecting people it's about protecting
people's lives
it's about making sure you don't get
hurt because the system is set up
for you to get hurt every day
in it that's how the system set up is
for you to get hurt that's how it is
the alternative movement is set up for
you to get hurt too and that's what
we're talking about the pitfall
lowers your immune system so the blood
draw
lowers your immune system that's one of
the pitfalls right
okay what's another pitfall hcl
supplements
thinking it's going to help your hcl
meanwhile
scorching your own stomach glands
i've always talked about hcl supplements
being really bad
because they they aren't your natural
gastric juices
you know produced by your own stomach
glands
so when you take the hydrochloric acid
supplements you
burn your stomach you burn your gut you
burn your duodenum
that's not your hcl from a human being
that from your actual glands themselves
dr fun he's not saying don't do blood
tests he says do less but you have to
self
advocate listen to the podcast medical
meeting podcast at apple pod
podcast blood draw uh uh blood draw
which was the name of that podcast oh
and vampirism right blood test blood
drop
vampirism right um and bloodletting
that's the other thing so the bottom
line is
listen to that episode blood droplet
letting vampirism get get to know it's
an important one i'm not against blood
draw i'm not against your
blood test i'm not against you getting a
blood test but this is critical to know
critical to know cindy lou good to see
you this is critical
information to protect you yeah it's
that important right
it's vampirism it's vampirism you know
this day and age let's talk about this i
did the hcl for a couple of seconds
letting you guys know the hcl that they
give you
and say hey take this hydrochloric acid
supplement because alternative medicine
is a bunch of pitfalls too a tremendous
amount of pitfalls so
the hcl supplements i've seen that
damage people over the years
i really have so you got to look out you
don't want to be doing the hcl
supplements because it's damaging
and how is it damaging it scorches your
own stomach glands it scorches your own
stomach
lining scorches your duodenum it's not
the same thing
as your own stomach glands producing
gastric
acid a specific blend i talk about
in medical medium new edition right here
where i talk about the seven
blend gastric acid right so
when they give you hydrochloric acid
supplements that's not the seven
blend of hcl narashini good to see you
um we need to take we need to be vampire
slayers
uh yeah that's really funny lunell hey
what's happening
you called me live i'm glad i caught you
live too i caught you live too it's good
to be here
um so it's important to know that that
hcl
is the bad stuff right the hydrochloric
acid supplements that's a pitfall all on
its own
let's hit more pitfalls what's another
one right there sodium bicarbonate
that's a that's a pitfall all in its own
it is an intestinal liner irritant
it harms all of our good microorganisms
and if we're all about good
microorganisms if we're all about good
bacteria
good microorganic organisms that sodium
bicarbonate
annihilates good bacteria
annihilates important good
microorganisms annihilates
these things a beneficial fungus we need
to survive we have beneficial
fungusiness that's how we stay alive
right
that's how we absorb right well sodium
bicarbonate
holds no bar just goes right in there
holds no quarter
goes in there and it starts to it starts
to
uh injure our good microorganisms not to
mention
total irritant on the lining of the
intestinal tract
small intestinal tract large intestinal
tract that's something right there
never liked one one bit if you guys just
came on making the banana cherry
smoothie i'm talking about all the
pitfalls i'm talking about all the
supplements
all the different stuff that's out there
the trends the trendy traps
karen says so what can we replace sodium
bicarbonate with
uh you're just you just don't need it
there's nothing that you have to replace
sodium bicarbonate with because sodium
bicarbonate isn't something that's
giving you something
internally so it's not providing
anything
for you right so you use it for baking
you know that's what you could do i
guess but it's not if that's what you
wanted to do but i wouldn't recommend
look i wouldn't recommend
using it internally is is the whole
point
so this is about ingesting it
right you know you can bake without it
too you can bake without sodium
bicarbonate but you don't need
sodium bicarbonate so replacing sodium
bicarbonate isn't so
okay so all right it's almost like if
you
well it's almost like arsenic right you
you're not supposed to be drinking
arsenic
so if someone says hey don't drink
arsenic what can you replace it with
i don't know what i mean it's not like
somebody okay something like say
you love whiskey it's like stop drinking
whiskey because it's going to hurt
your liver it's going to hurt you what
do i replace whiskey with
uh vodka no you don't want to replace
you're not trying to replace it you're
not trying to replace it but it's a good
question
so anyway let's move on to another one
too
i'm talking about sodium bicarbonate um
put it this way i've seen people with
crohn's colitis celiac digestive
problems bloating
dump a bunch of sodium bicarbonate in
and literally be in fetal position
and have to go to the emergency room
they're at the er now
and now they're going through the whole
stages of the er
they're waiting there waiting to see a
doctor doctor doesn't understand their
condition anyway
they've already been diagnosed with
crohn's and doctors like well crohn's
will whatever
we'll you know have you you know maybe
we can give you a medication tonight and
send you home with and
this person's suffering and they got and
they did the whole sodium bicarbonate
i've seen this over and over again
let's head to another one iron
supplements gotta be careful with iron
supplements because when people are low
in iron you have to keep this in mind
if the iron supplements aren't really
natural like really
clean like really like derived from a
good source
like with me with iron supplements with
me
is that i like to recommend foods that
are always high in iron right
with the leafy greens right um
the i like some raisins you know i like
wild blueberries i like things that have
the iron in it
which are important right the herbs it's
another thing too the cilantro
parsley i love i love the foods that
have the iron in there right
that's a whole thing too it's it's the
reason why we go
low in iron is because we're also
low-grade viral infections so
we got the viruses right so that's
another thing all in its own
you got the viruses and viruses like
epstein-barr
feed off of iron so that's why the iron
drops
because the viruses feed off of iron so
we have to be cautious right
so you keep if you're if you know if the
doctor is giving you all these iron
supplements and stuff care and churchill
iron supplements help
keep me anemic right helped keep me
anemic
so you got to be cautious with iron
supplements because iron supplements
cause a lot of trouble with a lot of
people what it does is
the symptoms can get worse when you're
dumping in a lot of iron supplements
because
it's fuel for certain varieties of
epstein-barr virus they love to feed off
of iron so then
you're dumping more iron in and then the
virus are eating more and how you're
getting more body aches and pains you're
getting a little bit more fatigue and
the doctor's just like well you're
getting more fatigue because you're
anemic meanwhile the doctor is supposed
to be saying
you're getting more fatigue because of
low-grade viral infections
and and and but they don't say that and
that's the whole thing on it's all on
its own
dolly says i take a tiny bit of sodium
bicarbonate occasionally it eases my
acid burn
i use apples too however i notice less
reflux with iodine as prescribed by dr
brownstein
iodine protocol so what i like to do for
reflux is i like to fix the problem
so that's what i like to do because acid
reflux is
streptococcus bacteria staph bacteria
it's e coli bacteria it's a lot of
bacteria
acid reflux is also a stagnant sluggish
liver
so what i like to do with acid reflux so
that it's not just
coming and going and you're trying to
find some things to kind of soothe it
i like to actually fix it so what i like
to do is lower fats it's something
that helps all on its own because you're
not bombarding the liver you're not
fatting yourself to death because that's
what everybody does
they fat themselves to death they fat
themselves to
death is what they do it's fat let me
have more fat let me have more fat no i
need more fat let me grab more
no grab some more fat here yeah let me
grab
let me grab a chicken i'll grab some
more fat here
let me grab a chicken that's what i'm
going to do here too i want to call a
friend
let me call a friend here
you coming over for chicken yeah i made
a chicken
yeah roasted chicken i roasted it in the
oven uh-huh
you're i you can take the skin off
and just have the white meat yeah the
white meat
that's fine yeah uh-huh
yeah there's no fat in the white meat
there is
there is fat in the white meat oh
okay i didn't know i thought it was just
in the skin
there's plenty of fat in the white meat
okay
the thing is is you gotta you got acid
reflux
so so the chicken fat might be really
hard on what the gallbladder
really i didn't know that the chicken
fat's hard on the gallbladder
think it'll help if i could turn this
phone around yeah
now i hear you better hey hey
yeah okay what happens is that
the gallbladder and the liver whoa
it gets all you get worse when you're
having all that fat
all right well maybe maybe we'll have
something else well maybe we'll have
pizza
is pizza okay tonight the same thing
there's a lot of fat in the pizza
uh all right maybe we'll have a
turkey all right i'm gonna hang up
so what happens is we fat ourselves to
death you guys
we blow out our gallbladders we blow out
our pancreases we blow out our liver
over time we blow out our stomach glands
for the hcl we blow everything out and
then we got the acid reflux
and now you're looking for remedies well
i'll try a little bit of this oh no that
helps to soothe it too a little bit wait
that helps to ease it off a little bit
too
i like fixing it i like fixing it fixing
the liver
lowering the fats bring in some celery
juice right
lower the fats again and try to get the
liver out of that stagnant sluggish
nature do 16 to 30
32 ounces of lemon water in the morning
that's what i like to do i like to try
to fix the liver so
things strengthen hcl strengthens then i
like to knock
bacteria down if it was me and that was
happening i'd be on some golden seal
that's what i would do you you guys do
what the doctor tells you to do you do
whatever your doctor tells you i'm just
saying if it was me
i'd be doing some goldenseal if i had
some acid reflux
i'd be doing that for sure it'd be doing
licorice root
because it's not you're not trying to
remedy
you're trying to fix you're trying to
actually fix right
um and cleanse the heel i have some
other options too with
uh with with um with acid reflux a
protocol
all of it so it's important to do
it's um g colgin says it's a lot of
information to remember took me a long
time to absorb
yeah it's information to actually help
you heal when you take the time to apply
it then you can heal and go all the way
i know everybody wants a magic pill
don't want a magic pill yeah someone
gave me a magic pill
there's a magic pill in here so let me
see what kind of what do i have i got a
magic pill in here
let me uh let me take a magic pill and
that's what they want they want that
magic pill like
oh my god that's it
that's it doctor that's the magic pill
doctor that's the magic pill right there
all i got to do is pop that pill
everything's fixed
everything goes away that's all i need
and that's what everybody wants that's
what everybody wants they don't want to
know
you know what's really going on but i
mean if i had the acid reflux i'd be
doing some goldenseal to knock out the
bacteria
i'd be doing some licorice root knock
out any viral stuff
also it soothes the linings right i'd be
if i
if i had acid reflux um i'd be doing
those for sure these are just a couple
of things i would do
lemon balm if i had acid reflux it's
another one too
be doing some zinc if i add acid reflux
that's what i would be doing right
and i'd be doing celery juice 16 to 32
ounces i'd probably be doing 32 ounces
of celery juice okay if i had acid
reflux that's what i would do
um definitely 32 ounces i'd be doing a
lemon water right
anyway these are the vimergy stuff right
you guys know the vimorji
because that's another thing because i'm
going to go into some other stuff about
how we get trapped on those down those
pitfalls too because if you don't have
the right supplements and there's
alcohol in them
with a really low grade or they got
fillers or they got preservatives
well then we're trying to climb that
cliff i told you about
we're trying to go and there's natural
flavors in there you're trying to climb
that cliff
climbing that cliff i'm getting i'm
trying to get to the top and then
someone smacks you in the head and they
smack in the heads with natural flavors
msg right all right we got we got a lot
to cover
let's keep it going you can find the
right supplements at medicalmedium.com
the directory i have there
it's really helpful i'm not sponsored by
those guys this is my the stuff that i
love my favorite
talk about diatomaceous earth
when i hear people are on diatomaceous
earth
right i i just feel for them
it it gives me like a chill down my
spine
i've heard so many stories but seeing it
in person
too sophie says i got rid of my acid
reflux had problems for 15 years
incredible that's amazing diatomaceous
dr fahn have you seen anything with
diatomaceous earth particles ever
i just see dr fonz there too um
i've witnessed it for years right i
remember this one case
where the person was just ripped the
shreds from it and
it's it's and then i know this other
case where
um this person actually blamed
the end of their life because of it it's
the most saddest story
i've ever ever ever seen i think the
bottom line is what i don't like about
diatomaceous earth is it
clings to the walls of the intestinal
lining and colon
and when you're inflamed it's the last
thing you want it causes so much agony
for a lot of people and if you don't
feel any agony and you feel fine and you
don't
you're good with it and you're taking it
it doesn't mean it's
not creating what i've always known as
this malabsorption where you can't
absorb
properly you can't absorb the same thing
charcoal does the same thing
in many ways right people take the
charcoal we'll get to that too
this diatomaceous earth it's always just
it's always been a problem
sherry says i just received your updated
medical medium book i started your
protocol already feeling better after a
week i have stage four ebv
i'm so excited to be on this healing
journey honored you're here
truly it's the best news best news ever
incredible yeah vanessa says i believe
the iron supplements i took during third
trimester and i developed severe
preeclampsia
i swore it was connected vanessa i'm
going to tell you right now something
that's really interesting
okay is that preeclampsia is low grade
viral
so yeah so if you're taking an iron
supplement
during pregnancy and you're
and there's a virus at hand the virus is
going to get really strong because when
you're pregnant
50 of your immune system when you're
pregnant is watching the baby
so that's important to know so here's
how it works it's like
50 of your um 50 of your immune system
is to take care of the baby
that's what 50 does when you're pregnant
is to take care of the baby your baby
doesn't have an immune system when
you're pregnant
so your 50 goes to the baby
right so now you only have 50
of your immune system for the rest of
your body instead of a hundred percent
so you only have 50 now right now if you
have any kind of low-grade viral issue
you can get pre-eclampsia pretty easily
for a lot of women so we dump a whole
bunch of iron in there then we feed that
virus right
dump a whole bunch of iron in there and
you feed the virus where's my virus
here we are and the virus will start
eating all the iron
and next thing you know what you got
this pre-eclampsia because the virus
multiplies
fast it proliferates when it's feeding
off of the iron
that's how it's done irma forgive me for
my comment
but i thought you were a little wacky
but i was willing to read your
book medical medium you have been like a
miracle
i take celery juice religiously i can
eat
no pain incredible phone's ringing i
think right now that's incredible
um karate
hello hey dr wacky
yeah i made an appointment yeah
i'm coming in tomorrow okay
you guys are gonna draw blood how much
are you gonna take
14 vials but you took that last month
uh-huh i was really dizzy for a week you
gonna take 14 vials again
hey dr wacky hey um
listen you gave me a whole bunch of iron
supplements
i haven't been feeling that great
don't worry okay hey dr wacky
you put me on two tablespoons of apple
cider vinegar
uh-huh and i just been getting the worst
sour stomach now
don't worry about it all right dr wacky
hey dr wacky i've been taking a lot of
fish oil supplements you told me to take
uh-huh yeah dr wacky
fish oil supplements remember you gave
them to me
every time i take them i feel like i
burp up all this fish
i'm burping all the time don't worry
fish oil supplements are good dr wacky
nutritional yeast yeah you told me to do
tons of it
i'm doing tons of it i do a whole box a
day
still keep up with the nutritional yeast
why
isn't yeast bad dr wacky it's not
there's it's nutritional okay all right
thank you dr white i'll be getting my
blood drawn tomorrow
i'm glad i'm glad you i don't take
offense on the comment at all i'm glad
you're here and i'm honored you're here
and um and i'm happy that you're working
with the medical medium information
what's really wacky though and what
what's interesting about that
is the crap that's out there right and
how how many pitfalls and potholes and
death by a thousand cuts
and you know what the doctors
everybody will just say it's
happenstance
it's like you get sicker
oh this happenstance you have more
problems oh it's happenstance
it's happenstance you guys just
happenstance right
it's not from the fish oil it's not from
the diatomaceous earth it's not from all
the blood draws it's not from the hcl
supplements not from nutritional yeast
it's not from the acv
it's not from the charcoal it's not from
the corella it's not from the plant
protein powders
it's not from the whey protein powders
happenstance
it's not from viruses out there and all
the different radiation and all the crap
falling out of the sky and the
chemtrails dumping on us
with mercury constantly and all the
chemicals like i told you on the
chemtrail episode
where the planes are dumping stuff from
all the chemical companies
all around the world or loading that
stuff up into planes and they're dumping
it on us
every single day right now it's
happenstance happenstance
yeah i love that everything's
happenstance
um this is not the gas pump the gasoline
we're breathing in and the air
fresheners and the clones and perfumes
it's not the clones and perfumes know
that poisonous on a daily
daily basis is not the hair sprays it's
not the conventional cleaners that's
happenstance
you know happenstance you know it's not
the fact that
50 of all pharmaceuticals
50 of all pharmaceuticals are recalled
from dangerous side effects fifty
percent
of all the pharmaceuticals in the world
that have ever been minted and printed
and produced and created fifty 50
of all of them have been pulled
because of side effects right no it's
happenstance
everything's everything's happenstance
let's move on
um whey protein powder it's one of my
favorites it's a
viral feeder viruses feed off of it you
want to get sicker
do some whey protein powder you want to
get worse do some whey protein powder
right i always say no way to weigh
that's what i that's what i've always
said all these years is like say no way
to weigh and that's it whey protein
powder plus they'll throw they'll throw
all kinds of stuff in whey protein
powder and boot it up and make it worse
natural flavors
which is msg whey protein powders always
have natural flavors in there if you
find
one that doesn't have a natural
flavoring it's still bad news
yeah david happenstance that's what it
is it's all happenstance
so let's move on to another one whey
protein powder is really really
ear an irritant for people makes mucus
form from feeding bacteria so whey
protein powder
feeds bacteria really easily that's
another thing too you want to grow all
that bad bacteria to keep on doing the
whey protein powder right
so we got that covered we got a lot of
different things
let's go into multivitamins junk junk
junk
junk junk multivitamins
are the junk keep that in mind that's
the multivitamins cheap
low-grade vitamins sitting in vitamin
storage
bins massive lots of vitamin
warehouses filled with vitamin
powders the bad ones garbage
bulk low grade sitting there sometimes
for 10 years
and you know what they don't put in the
the expiration date doesn't start when
they get the bulk stuff
the bulk stuff that sits in these
massive massive warehouses where
the bad cheap vitamins get their stuff
the expiration date starts when it gets
into your
bottle that's when it starts it doesn't
start
it could sit for 10 years
and then you get this moldy vitamin that
has
a little bit of everything a little bit
of calcium a little bit of this a little
bit of that a little bit of selenium a
little bit blah blah blah
a little bit of some enzymes bubble all
this other stuff all the way down a
little vitamin a blah blah blah blah
right your multivitamin the bees
and all that that stuff is so old
even though the date looks great hey
this expires 2022.
this one's fresh dude it's 10 years old
already
so low grade bulk garbage
multivitamins where they rip you off a
little speck of everything
in there it's not even done right that's
just one reason why it's not good
multivitamins will have
a lot of fillers in there a lot of
garbage in there but the big
reason why i also don't like the
multivitamins is because
it's it's the one the big reasons is
this stuff
is like ancient it's not produced and
then goes out the door
right manufacturing doesn't work like
that for the low
grade multi vitamin stuff for
for all that stuff so that's one thing
right there it's really important to go
to another one
that i mean that's just that's just one
thing but i got to move along hair
skin and nail supplements
so hair skin nail supplements right
that's a sham scam on its own
okay because what's in there really
isn't
for your hair skin and nails
right so you'll be told that you'll
think that that's
just bait it's like whoa my nails are
getting chewed up really bad
i need to do something about it let me i
gotta strengthen them
i can't grow my nails they're breaking
all the time
it's like one of those one of those
vanity
uh supplements right it's one of those
vanity supplements i want my skin better
i want my skin to look really good i
want my skin good
let me get that hair skin nail
supplement another scam of a lifetime
going on out there
um same thing though right it's it's
they put a little bit of all these
things in there
that could never move the needle and you
buy it and you spend good money on it
and then there's fillers in there too
that's a whole nother thing all on its
own so
that that i mean just giving you a quick
rundown of why i don't even like that
stuff
um and it's not even for hair skin and
nails you want you want
your skin better you got to do some
stuff for it
you know you've got to do something for
it if you're getting hair loss as a
woman
that's adrenals that have to be
addressed hair skin nail supplements
don't address the adrenals
so it's not even addressing why a
woman's losing her hair like
hair skin hair skin nail supplements
aren't addressing adrenals
they're not since that's important all
on its own um
and then let's keep on going a little
bit more with this right
so when it comes down to
hair skin nail supplements okay keep in
mind that this is how it works right
what's in there is a man-made
concoction of what
someone thinks you will need to get your
skin
better your nails better right
and that's a mistake all on its own in
order to get
nails better you have to fix the liver
but a hair skin nail supplement
isn't going to fix your liver it's not
there to repair your
liver keep that in mind right so
already we're off the mark like boom
down the drain we're already going down
the drain we already have a problem
in order for hair skin nail supplement
to be a hair
skin nail supplement it has has to be
fixing your liver
and it's not fixing your liver in order
to get your nails to way you want them
you've got to fix your liver that's your
vitamin
mineral producer in a way
or storage bin right that's what's
storing all your vitamins and then
converting them
if your liver stagnant and sluggish and
having problems
you're not going to be fixing that liver
with a jamokey
gimmicky hair skin hair skin nail
supplement it's not going to happen
um it has to be something that's geared
towards fixing a stagnant sluggish liver
that's what it needs like that's what
you need and that's a problem all on its
own so that's a big one looking for my
liver right now
um and so keep that in mind really
so that's something there
so the bottom line is that's when it
comes down to nails so when it comes
down to fixing your liver
it comes down to fixing
it comes down to fixing your nails it
comes down to fixing your liver
comes down to fixing your skin you have
to fix your liver
so okay let me go take let me go grab
let me go grab this hair skin and nail
supplement
right okay um i need my skin better
so i'm gonna grab this skin supplement
over here
uh but if the skin supplement doesn't
have anything in there to fix your liver
or to help your liver in any way then
it's not helping you okay same thing
with collagen
you can't take collagen so that's the
next one we'll talk about you can't take
collagen
maybe i'll put the liver in the cherry
smoothie right we'll chop up some liver
or put some liver in the cherry smoothie
just kidding around
you can't take a collagen to
actually help create collagen like you
can't take collagen
you can't eat a sheep's eyeball to fix
your eyeball it doesn't work right you
can't take an
animal's eyeball right you can't take an
animal's eyeball
it's an eyeball right there you see you
guys know if you can see it
can't take an animal's eyeball right
and eat it to fix your eye you can't
take an animal's kidney
and eat it to fix your kidney you can't
take
you can't eat lungs to fix your lungs if
you've got a lung problem you can't eat
lungs to fix your lungs alright
just want to say thank you so michelle
daniel says i just want to say thank you
for all that you do i knew all along
since i got mono and almost died
that it had to be a virus whoa that's
that's amazing that you knew that but no
doctor
supported that i was on the highest
thyroid dose
after lots of doctors making horrible
recommendations hcg hcg is terrifying
the whole hcg thing is just horrible hcg
diet
overworking the adrenals i was crashing
all the time crying every day i've seen
the hcg
hcg diet really hurt a lot of people
over the years you guys i've i can't
tell you how many people i talked to
i was crashing all the time crying every
day 2010
did five to six rounds of hcg then 2014
did a fitness show and changed my diet
to their recommendations
all the wrong stuff after three days of
taking the bad foods
i reduced my t3 by 50
and then by 75 after adding celery juice
i'm now 50 of my t4
i'm now 50 of my t4 and telling everyone
i know about their problems and how to
heal incredible story
incredible story i mean seriously that
is incredible it really is
um so we're going into the cup you go
going into the collagen a little bit
more basically what happens is that
we we think that if we can take
something
right that has that word well my
collagen is bad
uh my skin's getting all fallen apart
it's getting i'm aging fast my skin's
getting saggy i got problems
better get that collagen in me because
isn't it my collagen
and then we and then all the trendy
giants out there right they sell all
that collagen and the man they're
manufacturing and they're making
millions and millions of dollars and
everybody's sucked into it and the
ads go out that's how it works
you guys need to know it's you guys are
just you're
you're part of the ad campaign that's
out there
right it's throw ads at you guys 24
7 throw ads at you guys for collagen
throw ads at you guys for all this other
stuff hair skin dance throw
throw ads at you and that's how they do
it right and then it catches on and
people are taking it and it catches on
because the ads are just going in and
in and in and a million dollars in ads a
month these companies spend
a million dollars in ads a month
to make sure you guys keep on buying
that stuff
right so you know all this information
is really it's precious information
i had a doctor tell me that the other
day beth says what about fish oil let's
go
this oil said there right
fish oil is a bad one i actually have a
fish oil bottle somewhere around here
but before this for this as a prop
fish oil is one of those things where we
get
sold a bill of goods with that one like
we need that omega in the fish oil like
we need
fish oil right we're sold we're
brainwashed into fish oil
okay and the irony is is we don't need
fish oil
so what they do is they take all these
body parts
fish body parts that aren't being used
okay so they take
fish and they flay the fish they take
the fillet
and they put that in the restaurants
right they take the filet they put that
in the grocery stores
they take to the filet they put that in
the seafood market right
they take that filet and they make it
into fish sticks frozen fish right
and then they take the heads the tails
the fins some of the guts
they take all that and the skin and
everything else and all this gnarly
stuff
and they take that and they send that to
the fish oil companies right
fish oil companies got a billion fish
different kinds of fish all mixed up
different fish
parts all messed up mitch mashed right
and then they press it press it press it
to get all that fish oil out of it
okay which is actually the whole thing's
just sick right
then that fish oil has got more mercury
in it than if you were to eat a piece of
fish
so that fish oil's got more mercury in
it than if you were gonna ever eat a
piece of fish
that's what's really interesting about
it okay so
it's got more mercury and if you were
ever to eat the salmon right here
okay so that salmon's got mercury in it
but that salmon has way less mercury in
it
than if you were going to have a fish
oil supplement now fish oil company be
like no no no we remove our mercury
nope we get ours tested we remove the
mercury
when they do that mercury removal right
that centrifuge
and they do that mercury removal they're
creating a homeopathic
nightmare a homeopathic nightmare
when you remove mercury out of fish oil
you leave the essence of that mercury
behind
now we made it hundreds of times
stronger we turned it into a
methyl mercury a mercury that can travel
deeper into the brain
so fish oil supplements take you to also
you want alzheimer's
do you guys want dementia you want to
you don't want to know where your car
keys are ever ever
you don't want to know where your phone
you don't want to remember your phone
number
you don't want to remember your best
friend's phone number um
you want severe debilitating anxiety
depression
uh keep on doing fish oil because it'll
take you there faster
that's the brain killer it's one of the
brain killers
and um so the fish oil thing is the real
scary thing for me
for a lot of people and i'm worried
about a lot of people that are on it
because it's like dude it's time to
reverse whatever damage that has
occurred all these years you've been on
fish oil all these years it's time to do
something about it right
so i'm going to put the salmon away
we're live right now if you guys didn't
know
uh cassandra risley my ferritin is
extremely low
how do i how do i get it to increase
without an iron supplement if they're
bad for you
if you have to go with an iron
supplement go with a plant-based iron
supplement
i mean that's what i would do do what
your doctor tells you because android
your doctor tells you your doctor tells
you to do this or that or take iron or
whatever it is
you listen to your doctor but i'm just
saying that if it was me
and i had low iron what i would do is i
would get it from foods
if you or if if my doctor was telling me
hey
you should do you know iron here's the
iron and be like well let me go find a
good plant-based iron and then ask your
doctor's permission right
um that's something right there but
foods is like where i like to get iron
from my wild blueberries i like to get
iron from
um from barley grass juice powder it's
another thing too so i love to get iron
from that
love to get iron from spirulina because
even small amounts of iron right this is
barley grassy's powder right here even
small amounts of
iron okay um
small amounts of iron right can be more
assimilatable could be more absorbable
could be more
you can have more conversion process
with that with your body and your liver
because you can take gobs of iron
and your body just not do anything with
it right
so then when the doctor draws your blood
like well yeah your iron's up
doesn't mean it's working but your irons
up right
so they draw the blood that's what
happens there um i like knowing i'm
getting
choice iron from places like this is
cherries because i make the banana
cherry smoothie right there there's iron
and cherries
iron wild blueberries iron and grapes
and raisins
it's ironing you know barley grass juice
powder right
so that's that's what i'm talking about
it's about it's about where to get it
quality control okay and then
i like to go after the bugs that are
eating the iron i like to go after the
viruses
that are eating the eye that's what i
would do you do what your doctor tells
you but
i'm just saying that what i would do is
i'd be going after
i'd be going after the bugs that are
going after the iron that i talk about
all the time
regina my ferritin has never been
never been so high since almost three
years of medical medium i'm so grateful
for
uh for you so because you're going after
the viruses you're actually doing it
right
so you're going you're cleaning things
up corella
we're heading to carella now let's go
there
with corella cruella is one of these one
of these
supplements that are out there that i
really don't like
because it's irresponsible it doesn't
remove toxic heavy metals it's caught
this
this talk amongst the health community
that
oh use it for removing heavy metals
that's great because it doesn't work
um it just doesn't it's one thing i
don't like about another thing i don't
like about corella
is that it i've seen batches of it out
there
have bacteria in it that literally
puts people in a state that's not good
vomiting diarrhea vomiting vomiting
fetal position and agony and cramps
vomiting
fetal position in agony cramps emergency
room
back from the emergency room still sick
for weeks
i've seen bad batches of krell for some
reason that has slipped
through the gates over the years you
know the whole thing with krill i'm not
a fan of it
ten different reasons i'm just giving
you two right there it doesn't remove
metals out and if it does it drops them
um talk about caffeine a little bit
caffeine you guys know how much i've
been talking about caffeine medical
being podcasted apple podcasts i talk
about caffeine right
caffeine's a whole nother level right
there of of problems you got the coffee
drinks you got the energy drinks
you got the coffee you got the chocolate
right so you got the matcha tea you got
the teas
right you got the green teas caffeine
that's the ager
of our time right if women want to age
and they want those wrinkles fast and
they want those wrinkles in their early
30s and late
20s they want they want their skin to
sag they want the malaysia they want the
spots if if women want all that stuff
then drink lots of caffeine
drink your coffee drinks drink your your
green tea drink your matcha tea
just give you the rundown it's the ager
it's the women ager
and man ager two but it's the ager
especially women because women have
their adrenals are under different
demands their adrenals go through
different
different things than men's adrenals do
women's adrenals are always in more
fight or flight
and then when you add the caffeine you
put them in super fight or flight
then you burn out the hormones in the
adrenals hormone producers that's
another thing too
but the caffeine burns out the liver it
eats up
it eats up the bones women get
osteopenia from it they get teeth
problems
caffeine will be that's the literally
the
the big a big one for women right there
angel's rising i finally been able to
gain weight
using steamed potatoes veggies thank you
incredible
amazing apple cider vinegar go in there
a little bit
the teeth dissolver you can you can
listen to the apple cider vinegar
podcast
uh medical bean podcast at apple podcast
the apple cider vinegar
the teeth dissolver episode does it
dissolve the teeth
yeah it dissolves the teeth you want
your teeth to fall apart
caffeine does too caffeine does remove
does remove calcium from our teeth
but but apple cider vinegar oh my god
that is like stay with the apple cider
vinegar you you know lose the teeth you
know
so it's like i do a post saying acv is
not good out there
it's like everybody's like what do you
mean what do you mean i'm on acv and i
follow medical medium and i'm on acv i'm
like what
i talk about it every day for the last
how many years right
so um acb that's the teeth dissolver
you don't have to even let it touch your
teeth it is the teeth destroyer
okay let's keep on going cold white
spring good to see you
um so here's the no what else uh
charcoal
charcoal is a bad one so everybody's
like oh no i
i my my naturopath my you know
my chinese medicine doctor said just do
some do some
charcoal so i've been doing charcoal
every day
charcoal is a way to eventually become
super mineral and in vitamin deficient
that's a doorway into
vitamin mineral deficiencies it's like
what's that door
yeah what's that door what is that door
i see let me open that door
don't open that door why now let me open
that door
that's the charcoal door we open that
door okay opening it
okay okay boom you got you got the
mineral deficiencies the vitamin mineral
deficiencies
the nutrient deficiencies the chemical
compound deficiencies the antioxidant
deficiencies
it is a nightmare why and i'll tell you
why
chad says acv did actually almost ruin
my teeth
yeah chad it's it
young women don't know this right
they're all about making sure their
teeth are like super
white like taking care of their teeth
want them all straight
right and they're doing the apple cider
vinegar every single day
and it's like it scares me because i
want what people want if
you want your teeth to be a certain way
i want your teeth to be whatever you
want them to be right if you want to be
whatever you want to be i want to
support that right but then i just watch
this disaster happening it doesn't have
to touch the teeth like i said already
but it's it's i've watched this disaster
happen the apple cider vinegar nightmare
in the 20-something year olds and then i
know that it's like
it's hard when you know this stuff right
it's hard you guys when you know
and you're like okay you just did three
years apple cider vinegar gummies and
shots
and you're 25 years old it's like okay
when you're 35 you're gonna be in the
dentist chair every single day
and there's nothing you can say you know
it's like see we hear i see that topical
charcoal
topical charcoal is is fine if you want
to use charcoal topically for something
yeah i mean if you want uh so
but but internally like diges
ingesting it right but the people i see
with the teeth problems that come years
later it's like yeah you've been doing
the vinegars i don't know what to say
you've been doing it what am i gonna do
i can't stop you from doing it i can't
i can't stop you i don't know what to do
right but the charcoal suffocates
absorption so it's
so fine and it doesn't
come out of your
layer that layer that's on the
inside the gut this layer right
it suffocates and destroys
like your cell
um basically that that transfusion that
occurs right
with cells the absorption process
and as a cell in your intestinal lining
is
is awaiting to absorb anything
the charcoal is so fine it clogs up the
cell it doesn't cleanse the cell
it clogs it up it suffocates so when you
when you do the internal charcoal and
you're taking the supplements
you coat your entire intestinal tract
going all the way down to your colon
with charcoal and it adheres it just
cleans just like diatomaceous earth
particles clings
to the walls and it doesn't let
nutrients
go in it doesn't let the absorption
absorption for you get malabsorption
you're going to be pooping out all of
your nutrients and not bringing them
in it's a nightmare let's head to
another one
um
soul seeker az
um cheryl angela almost everyone i know
in the wellness world pushes cacao and
chocolate is
healing and do all the ceremonies and
it's so hard to witness
um you know the problem is
it could be because they're they're
they're slaves to the caffeine industry
you know
it's the caffeine industry knows if you
can if you can invade the healing
sacred area of wellness right
the caffeine industry knows if you can
hit the yoga mamas
if you can hit the yoga community if you
can hit the spiritual community
if you can saturate these communities
into the sacred belief community right
of sacred
you know things being self-care sacred
self-care sacred medicine sacred
everything
the caffeine industry knows that if you
can you can get in there
they're golden they just have to get in
there and they have they've gotten in
there right
so you get all the cacao ceremonies you
get all the you get all the
you know you get all that going on so
and what happens is
it's basically an enslavement for women
and it's just to basically keep them on
caffeine
for the rest of their lives and to think
that i mean do you think eating
chocolate is a great idea
right you know what that does to
everybody's mood up down
up down up down crash burn crash burn
hi hi hi hi crash crash crash crash
crash hi crash
hi crash a friend's gonna call me any
second too because my my friend's
watching this right now
and yeah my friend's watching this right
now and he's gonna call me
things but you know what's funny about
this whole thing with how it works
it's it's like you're up you're up
you're up and you go down you go down
you go down
you're up you're up you're up you go
down you go down
hello hey hey i'm glad you called just
now
so what you did you did the ceremony
last night
what happened you did a large amount
of straight cacao are you okay
you're jittery today really
so everybody was just they were just
like
totally high yeah
who what someone was talking about the
stars
well that sounds cool you guys were all
talking about like
the universe who said what about
extraterrestrials
really what ceremony was this
it was a it was a really cool like
sacred
shaman plant medicine person was there
she said that you should be drinking
lots of cacao every day
you feel like you can't why you feel
like you're
you're shaky and jittery and your
adrenals like
you're nauseous today why do you think
but yet you want the chocolate really
bad but
you know it's not a good idea why is it
not a good idea
because you know it's you know it's not
a good idea
i gotcha so are you supposed to be on
chocolate every single day
and just be on highs and lows what
happened you crashed really bad
it's awful and then you are feeling good
you feel like you don't even know who
you are now like depersonalization
maybe you just need a chocolate hit like
another cacao hit
and you can kind of find yourself and
normalize
but what happens when it starts wearing
off then you're into this like weird
depression again
all right i'll talk about after the show
we're live right now
no i know i told you to call in i'm
sorry about that but we got to cover the
rest
i got to talk about a little bit more
the problem is with cacao is is that it
blows your adrenals out so you age fast
and so really what's happening is it's
teaching women just to get their babies
also on cacao
everybody on cacao and can continue that
life cycle of cacao right
of the caffeine industry so that the
shareholders can sit back
and they know that the addiction itself
takes care of it and no matter what
you can be in financial ruin but you'll
buy that chocolate
you can be like no job and still buy
that chocolate inflation
can go through the roof and literally
there's there's like
people just can't afford anything and
they'll just be buying the chocolate it
reminds me of a friend of mine right
who had no money no money but made sure
like no money
to actually even like feed their family
right but yet
they made enough meaning they made room
for cigarettes
right they made room for cigarettes they
always had
they bought two packs a day right but
yet
their kids like there's like their kids
it was like no we can't afford that
no we can't afford those apples no
sweetie we can't afford those
those strawberries they're too much per
pint but it was still
two three packs of cigarettes a day
right no i still gotta get my cigarettes
doesn't matter still got to get my
cigarettes it doesn't matter
i'm not shaming anyone but this is what
the industry does to you
the industries want you nicotined out
caffeine out
they want you doing the chocolate and
they want the spiritual community
to take it in and take that that whole
message
of sacred sacred medicine cacao
chocolate yay
rightly want that going down i know i
make no friends
once again because i get it that just
cut out now the cacao community right
now they're just gonna be like he's just
he's terrible right
go right about another bad story about
me i don't care
the point is is like you know a fake one
obviously you know and the whole point
is like yeah
there you go anyway you guys we're we're
i ran through as many as i could right
now
um my books are free at the library you
guys know you can also buy them in
amazon or anywhere else you want right
barnes
barnes noble all that but the free the
library if you don't have any money
um get them free medical media
information is free you guys know that
all of it okay and uh i didn't even
cover i don't know if i covered l
carnitine gut blends
uh nutritional yeast nutritional yeast
i'm gonna cover that right off the
running going into ig in a few minutes
that's gonna do check out my free
podcast medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast
and i didn't make the cherry smoothie
i'm gonna make it on ig
i'm gonna head there and make the cherry
smoothie on ig go in there now
i'm gonna be on instagram and tick tock
live in just a few minutes and i'm going
to be making
the cherry smoothie there i just i
covered so many things right here you
guys that actually couldn't get to it
but guess what
come on to ig with me or tick tock let's
make the cherry smoothie
i'm going to cover some of this stuff
again but i'm going to cover nutritional
yeast
because that one's important i'm going
to even open up with that one
all right i love you guys