did you guys see Angels demons and
spiritual tools because it is ready for
pre-order okay so check it out you could
go to Amazon you could see it there you
could go to Apple see it there and I
just want to say this is that when you
do hear what you're about to hear when
you actually get a hold of the Angels
demons and spiritual tools just know
it's 7 and 1/2 hours 7 and 1/2 hours of
information from above s so lots of
questions I asked lots of questions that
I thought about other people have asked
me and what happens is it turns into the
situation where you're saying okay but
wait a minute how does it work with
demons what happens with demons are
demons even real what is a demon what
does a demon
do what happens to somebody's Soul when
they pass where does it go what happens
with that and the question is just roll
into one question after another after
another you if you don't know what I'm
talking about I'm talking about angels
demons and spiritual tools check it out
on Amazon just type in medical medium
Angels demons and spiritual Tools in
Amazon Apple it's there too uh I think
it's on Spotify I think it's there too
but so what would happen is I'm like
okay Spirit okay what is a demon like
for real though people say this and
people say that and people do this and
people what is what's really what is
what is a
demon and
so it's information that I think you got
to be ready for you have to be ready for
the information I'm going to be honest
and you might want to like keyate it a
little bit you might want to decant it a
little bit you might want to increment
it a little bit if that's even a word if
any of those are words you might want to
just kind of ease into it the seven and
a half hours you might start with a half
an hour you listen to that half an
hour and then you go okay okay okay all
right all right and then you back away
from it because there's so much to
digest because I actually have a
source that understands what Angels what
demons are what kind of spiritual tools
to use and information about yes hell
yes hell and other information too so
when it's real information from above
the game Changes Everything Changes it's
not like oh theories and theorizing and
theologists you know going into some
scripture and you know looking into here
and looking into here but this says this
and this is that and then summary you
know summarizing what they think it
could be when you hear it from s so and
you hear about demons and you hear about
angels and you hear about things like
hell and you hear about and then you
hear what it really is and what's
happening it's something that's a whole
another level of understanding it's a
whole another level of all kinds of
stuff so I'm just saying this because
it's getting closer it's it's coming out
March 18th get you know pre-order it get
a hold of it you can get it for free how
about that you can get it fore for free
if you're subscribed already to all
these different you know things that
people do for audibles and audio stuff
and um it's an original audio and my
publisher I mean God bless them they're
backing me they're backing me 100% on
this God bless them you know and the
thing is is and when they heard it when
the publisher heard this
like oh my God and I'm like yeah you
think people are going to be ready for
it do you think people are going to be
ready for
it I mean I can't really answer that but
anyway look talking about angels demons
and spiritual tools check it out you can
pre-order it now it's coming out March
18th but pre-order it now get a copy get
it like loaded up so that you can start
with it in
start getting into it remember it's
seven and a half hours every single line
I'm the narrator every single line is
it's every single line it's not like
fluff and just and coffee talk and you
know what I mean like right coffee talk
and fluff and stuff like that it's every
single line is like what like what like
what do you mean that's a demon I what
is that what
it's just like every single line so yeah
I just want you guys to know that you're
hearing it here from the horse's
mouth you know get ready you know be
prepared definitely do the lemon balm
tea definitely do the lemon balm tea
when you start listening to that audio
that original audio it's medical medium
Angels demons and spiritual tools spider
empowerment but about important
empowerment because we don't know we
don't know what's really happening in
The Ether we don't know what's really
happening around us
right you got all this adversity and all
this all these different things that are
happening and people's struggles and
freak accidents freak accidents you know
when you ask Spirit of compassion like
so all right so I'm afraid to
ask right I'm afraid to ask Spirit but
can you fill me in a little bit about
freak
accidents how does that work like how is
it possible the craziest crap happens
how's it possible a girl can be sitting
on uh a rocky area in Thailand or
something and you've got the water
coming in the waves are coming in and
the friends are all there and how you
know how is it possible where all of a
sudden just a wave comes and the
person's gone or how's it
possible with the freak accident thing
like what is it is it really coincidence
and I'm just asking Spirit I'm like
Spirit like come on you know is it
really coincidence what's a freak
accident and it takes it all the way
down to freak to begin with the whole
freak word information about this from
Spirit of compassion and when you hear
that you're just like what like oh my
God I'm going to release this I'm going
to release this
information yeah I'm going to release
this
information and it just gives you
tingles up your spine tingles up your
spine anyway Angels demons and spiritual
tools check it out I mean I look I'll
talk about it more as we go along but
that's that's I'm actually like nervous
nervous I mean look I I've done a
trillion lives trillion lives right I
haven't done a trillion lives but I've
been live a lot of times over the years
right and I've done different things but
I'm nervous just talking about the
angels and demons and spiritual tools
just talking about angel Steven
spiritual tools because it's so intense
and it's so jam-packed but it's not just
jam-packed it's not like it's different
than the medical medium books the other
medical medium books it's different than
cleanse to heel it's different than
brain saver it's different than you know
medical medium books because it's the
spiritual end of things and there's
spiritual information in these medical
medium books the spirit of compassion
has given a lot of spiritual about the
soul about lots of things in the medical
medium books but
then if you like is the Grim Reaper real
what is the Grim Reaper how does it work
if there was a grim reaper and then you
hear this information I'm here it from
Spirit of compassion and I'm like okay
all right I will put that in here I will
put that in here what is a grim reaper
is there a grim reaper what is it really
what happens with Souls when they cross
over what ha is the are demons real like
all this information like what is this
and then like I said before freak
accidents and things like that and all
kinds of stuff like what is and when you
really when you guys chip chip away at
this audio when you get it you just do a
half an hour at a time that's what I
mean by chipping away at it you just
don't I probably wouldn't recommend
doing the seven and a half hours all at
once I probably wouldn't recommend that
the Angels
demons and spiritual tools
audio I wouldn't do the seven and 1 half
hours all at once I mean
you know I K around and I do this a lot
like but I'm I'm serious I'm
serious okay all right so couple
announcements anyway I just want to talk
Wellness reset at Cafe Gratitude the
wellness reset okay this is the kick
butt Wellness reset right there you're
looking at it all right there it is
Wellness reset okay talking about
healing the body talking about healing
the liver talking about healing the gut
healing the pancreas healing the lungs
healing everything it's only available
for a limited time it's at Cafe
Gratitude it's a wellness reset it's
Dirt Cheap guess what I'm making on it
do you want to know what I'm making on
it you guys okay guess what I'm making
on this Wellness reset at Cafe Gratitude
where when you go and purchase this you
pre-order it you purchase it and I'm
going to go over what's in here here
right and you can see the celery juice
is in here heavy metal detox smoothie is
in here and you see the the the brain
Soother juice and you see the different
things in here guess what I'm making on
this at Cafe Gratitude a big zero
because I just want people healing I
want people better the price is so low
it is a cleanse it's a celery juice
heavy metal detox smoothie it's the
craving shifter shot it's a spiced
squash soup and I'm going to show you
the recipes it's the brain Soother juice
it's the healing broth soup the dream
shifter shot and you can do add-ons to
this cleanse you can do the Estonian Sue
Sue and you can do the massaged kale
salad that's what's really cool right
there so let me take a look
here so I want to show you what's in
here okay all right let's go first of
all I'm going to go to page I'm going to
start with page 310 I think well look
there's the celery ju that's the brain
sther juice of course there we go nice
the celery juice right there that's in
the cleanse made already for you a
beautiful celery juice boom and you know
what that does cleans up the body cleans
up the liver cleans up the blood helps
get rid of dirty blood
syndrome I mean you name it it does all
these amazing things right you got the
celery juice knocks down pathogens helps
to heal I mean that's celery juice
that's in in the cleanse right that's in
the cleanse let's go to page
264 let's find that right there 264
there it is heavy metal detox smoothie
so what are you doing with the heavy
metal detox smoothie it's in this
cleanse the wellness reset there's
cleanses out there but come on there's
cleanses out there but we're talking
about like something that works
something that heals getting Metals out
of the brain getting Metals out of the
liver get getting Metals out of the
organs the bones the bone
marrow getting Metals out of the bone
marrow how incredible that heavy metal
defect smoothie is in the cleanse so if
you guys just got on here I'm talking
about the wellness reset at Cafe
Gratitude it's really an incredible
cleanse you can pre-order limited time
only let's go into page 210 let's look
for
that so I'm in the shots right here so
in this cleanse you get the Cravings
shifter shot there it is right there
there craving shifter shot right there
okay there it
is craving shifter
shot boom let me see if I can do this
better real Qui for you there you
are okay that's in there too what does
it do not only is it a healing healing
shot it actually rewires the brain so
you're not craving so much so you're not
off B balance with your craving so
you're not trying to you know overeat
tank the food down that's in the cleanse
how cool is that spice squash soup let's
go to page 338 right here it's amazing
is that it boom that's it right
there there it is spice squash
soup right there okay squash is an
incredible fruit for you it's one of the
best fruits you can actually eat is
squash so squash soup butternut squash
onion garlic is in there Ginger hot
pepper cumin coriander Cayenne it's
amazing that's in the wellness reset
cleanse could pre-order this whole
cleanse how sick is that at Cafe
Gratitude you
know um let's take a look brain Soother
juice let's look for that really quick
okay man how cool is this right brain
Soother juice there it is right there I
want to show you by the way I've been
medical medium brain saver protocols
that's where I am okay brain Soother
juice right
there boom brain Soo juice cucumber
celery apple fenel good for the brain
gets all kinds of minerals to the brain
exactly gets a balance of minerals trace
minerals to the brain that's a good one
right there and at the same time you're
cleansing you're cleansing toxins
poisons everything out of you how
incredible is that okay all right page
370 right here I'm looking right now for
the next next thing all right so let's
see is it in here is it in here am mind
in the right book there's so many books
let's
go let's keep on
looking oh yeah I'm looking I'm looking
hold on you
guys there it is page
370 okay healing broth soup right there
boom
there it is healing broth soup sweet
potato carrot onion Taki mushroom
parsley garlic ginger turmeric hot
pepper in the wellness reset cleanse
dream shifter let's hit that right now
okay page 218 we'll get the dream
shifter going there it is right there
dream shifter I know you guys are doing
the dream shifter you guys are doing
some of these I know many of you do the
brain shots it's in the cleanse how
incredible is that when I think about it
boom it's in the cleanse it's make dream
shifter shot Ginger mango Cherry
zucchini mint all made for
you that's what I'm talking about
Estonian stew let's see it's the medical
medium book right
here let's find it right
now all right here it is these are
add-ons so you can get the Estonian stew
it's an add-on to this cleanse here it
is right here okay onion mushroom carrot
cabbage potato po healing broth fresh
dill how incredible is this and that is
part of the cleanse too it's an add-on
you can get in the wellness reset so
when you're doing healing like this in a
cleanse wow it's it's just a whole
another whole another thing people just
don't know when it cleanse that works
counts you know what I mean so in the
massage kale salad we're trying to find
that really
quick see if we can get it there it is
massage kale salad right there the
medical be book all these incredible
healing tools made for you the wellness
reset you can't go wrong it's made for
you right there at Cafe Gratitude only
available for a limited time Cafe
Gratitude in La you can go and just
pre-order it get them working on it
they'll have it ready and fresh for you
and then you're doing your healing and
you don't have to worry about making it
and it's so inexpensive in my opinion
heck yeah there you go and if somebody's
like oh he's doing all this promotion
really cuz I'm not getting paid for it
I'm not I just want a healing cleanse in
an amazing place like Cafe Gratitude so
people can heal and move forward with
their lives and you know with their
lives in the healing process and getting
their lives back quality of their lives
back people asked me to do this forever
they've been asking me put it in put it
in Cafe Gratitude put it in a place put
it you know the whole
bit and that is the wellness reset
medical medium cleanse in Cafe Gratitude
you can get it there order
it that's the wellness reset right there
okay another announcement right here get
ready pizza party are you guys coming
did you get a ticket the medical medium
pizza party at Cafe Gratitude
collaboration between Cafe Gratitude
medical medium I worked on the crust
myself I worked on the crust and then
yeah Chef Drew worked on the
crust and we got a crust that is to die
for or to live for like people say I
like to say to die
for because it's incred that incredible
that incredible so this crust is amazing
the pizzas are amazing and you also are
going to experience here's the thing so
the pizza party right those are dinners
okay March 3rd fourth 5th right coming
right up did you get a ticket are you
going to be there a meet and greet and
maybe we'll do a light blast you never
know but you can get the pizzas there
from there on after so you can get those
medical medium pizzas they're going to
be on the menu at Cafe graat from there
on after so that that's incredible all
on its own it's not just for the party
it's going to be on the menu there also
other incredible things on the menu too
like the Nori rolls and so forth the
sushi
rolls any anyway I hope you guys are
coming who actually got a ticket I'm
going to be there in person I can't wait
to see you it's going to be a meet and
greet it's going to be exciting and
we're all going to be eating pizza like
what pizza medical medium pizzas come on
a Cafe Gratitude medical me and pizzas
at Cafe Gratitude I mean seriously how
cool is
that and guess what it's like coming
around the around the B what is today
Sunday Monday Tuesday
Wednesday yeah I got to get out there
okay I got to get out there I got to get
my crap together and I'm going to be
there going to grab my bag and I'm going
to be there yeah I'm blown away I can't
believe it's coming and it's the medical
mem pizza party oh let's not forget two
cookies are going to be on the menu two
cookies are going to be two medical M
cookies are going to be at the pizza
party and time t on the menu come on
Amazing you got a ticket you're going to
be there all right
so let's let's get down to
it let's get down to
it bird flu think it's stupid no it's
not bird flu think it's funny no it's
not right now something's happening and
people are not aware of it oh but I'm
aware of the bird flu aw have heard
about the bird flu many times different
than any other bird flu it's a bird flu
that's out there on
purpose is that a crappy job that one
right there it's a bird flu that's
actually out there on
purpose and it's out there for reason
and and it's like there's a bad flu out
there now right it's out there for a
reason so that the bird flu and the flu
come together and they produce something
else like a mutation of a bird flu
that's the
goal anyway don't eat chicken is the
name of this episode or you know stay
away from chicken or whatever you want
to call it keep chicken away so let's go
into it a little
bit I got a roasted chicken right here
as you can see I also have some others
chicken too I got some chicken tenders
or whatever you want to call them I
don't know what you call them I got some
Buffalo WIS here as well just going to
place them in front of us right here I
got the white board we're going to talk
about this stick around for this little
talk cuz it's critical it is it's
critical the bird flu was designed and
manufactur it in a lab that's what it
was it's not a natural occurring thing a
bird can't catch a flu a bird doesn't
produce a flu it doesn't work like that
so it's not like a bird just suddenly
came down with the flu the flu the Aven
bird flu the bird
flu the different strains of bird flu
they just don't produce themselves they
don't come out of nowhere they're put
out there they're put out there in the
crops and I'm just hinting to something
but you
know
drones
drones yeah sorry I don't know if you
heard that right
there but I have a bad cough I got the
bird flu just kidding I don't have a bad
cough how did that bird flu get out
there
um so the bird flu is put out there
purposely so Birds catch it wild birds
are catching it right now wild birds are
they're falling out of the sky in droves
geese are falling out of the sky in
droves Just landing on highways right
now people just don't realize this but
it but it's happening geese are falling
out of the
sky ducks are falling out of the sky
Robins are falling out of the sky yes
Robins because the bird flu is designed
to kill the bird it's not designed for
the bird to survive birds don't normally
survive a bird flu not this one now and
not this one here
when the bird catches the bird flu the
bird dies the bird dies not because the
bird's adrenals explode just like other
flu and so forth and like ca right and
the adrenals
explode but bird the birds die from the
bird flu because the bird flu virus goes
after the cells of the bird after the
organ
cells after the muscle
cells after the fat
cells so the virus is designed to go and
eat to go and feast on these cells to
attack the cells on the deepest level
the bird flu is designed that virus is
designed to attack the bird's nervous
system it's designed to attack the
bird's brain and nerves that's why the
birds suddenly get the bird flu and with
an hour the bird just
dies that's what's
happening the reason why they're
executing and killing so many birds
right now so many different p in the
poultry World agricultural the poultry
world
right the reason why they're killing so
many is because they're watching the
birds die that fast and it's scaring the
crap out of everybody it's not like the
birds are sick and you put these birds
over here they're sick maybe these birds
didn't catch the flu yet put them over
here maybe in this you know in this pen
here the birds didn't get it we just
have Birds getting sick in this pen
because they're dropping dead so fast
it's scaring the crap out of people so
they're killing millions and millions
and millions of chickens right now
you're seeing the egg prices go up
you're seeing eggs get scarce and
they're going to get scarcer and
scarcer so the bird flu is interesting
because it is jumping to humans to some
degree but for a bird flu of this
magnitude to do damage in a human in a
human which it does when it does get
into a human it needs another flu
present so it needs two flu right needs
another flu
present so let's see what we got
here so you got one
I don't know if you guys could see this
or
not got another one okay that's one flu
virus that's the human flu virus right
there then you got the bird flu virus
right
there okay so the goal of the evildoers
is to make sure the bird flu enters the
body and has a good chance of being in
the body at the same time time whether
or not at the tail end but at the
beginning of a human flu virus in the
same
body this is the
goal you might not be able to see it too
easily there you go how about
that yep there we
are what happens is they Spar for a
little bit that's right they do a little
bit of sparring
okay they check each other out they size
each other
up they both don't want to
die and they both want to challenge and
trick out the human immune
system so instead of one killing the
other they
transmute they connect they sequence
because they're all about reproducing
because that's what happens if you get
one flu
cell viral cell in
you how does it
work it reproduces
itself to turn into a
thousand to turn into hundreds of
thousands so that when you sneeze you're
spreading
it it's out there right so it's done
but these two
viruses eventually will bond together so
that's what the evildoers want they want
them to bond together and then
sequence what that means is they bond
together and they reproduce a hybrid out
of the human flu and the bird
flu now that hybrid has information in
it to destroy bird flesh
to destroy bird flesh bird cells bird
brain cells bird nerve cells that's the
goal yes of the virus it's been
engineered manufactured and raised in
eggs to do so and then Place into birds
in labs and they see enough Birds die
they see birds die quick they want like
a 90% death rate they want a 90 5% bird
death rate when they see that then they
get it out there they got different
means of getting the bird flu out
there different means of doing
it so the goal is for people to carry a
bird flu maybe without
knowing and then pick up the flu that's
going around
yeah that they put out there
too so they put both of them out
there the goal
is the goal
[Laughter]
is just
laughing the goal is to get these two to
se sequence and get them to cause a
problem so what happens when the
mutation starts we have a new bug that's
the goal the mutation has a really high
rate of killing
people because it's with the human flu
and it's the bird flu put together the
ratio of the death rate will most likely
be at 50% that's the goal so if you look
at what 8 billion people on the planet
or don't quote me on the number of the
people on this Earth but say 8 billion
roughly give or take
four billion die that's the goal I'm not
saying it's going to happen and I'm not
saying it's happening
now and I'm not saying God won't step in
and I'm not saying the Angels won't step
in and derail it and I'm not saying the
light won't come in and derail it but
that's what they're trying to do right
now pretty crazy crap
so I'm not saying don't eat chicken
because I'm a person of vegan nature a
vegan connoisseur plant-based person and
I got all kinds of different propaganda
lined up to try to get you guys to stop
eating chicken you want to eat chicken
eat
chicken but I'm going to go into why we
shouldn't eat chicken so we're going to
head into that okay all
right cooking the chicken doesn't help
cook your chicken chicken cook your
chicken I'll say that 100 times do not
eat raw chicken do not eat raw chicken
cook your chicken whatever you
do Deborah I'm a nurse in hospital are
full of influenza A and B by the
way flu a patients right now so Deborah
says she's a nurse and the hospitals are
filled with influenza A
Yep they're also filled with B they're
also filled with
Co and a few bird
flu they release some bad flu that's why
everybody's sick right now but the
timing is
purposeful they released some bad bird
flow bird
flu so they released you know more than
one it g gives a greater chance for
somebody get to get that bird flu not
just somebody hundreds and hundreds of
people and at the same time getting
hundreds and hundreds of that flu the
human flu the goal is to get those two
to bond and mutate and make a deadly
flu people say I can just eat the
chicken and it will be okay how does
that work does it work that way it's
like this the more chicken you eat
the more chances you're going to keep
the bird
flu
active strong and
Alive because pretty soon a lot of
people are going to have the bird flu
because it's jumping into people you
don't want that chance for it to jump
and then proliferate fast and not be
killed off by your immune
system the more bird flu gets around and
spreads because it's feeding on chicken
inside people's bodies the more chances
it's going to get stronger and stick
around longer to eventually make the
sequence occur between the human flu and
the bird flu cooking the chicken doesn't
stop the problem that has nothing to do
with it this isn't about eating a bad
chicken that happens to have the bird
flu this isn't about
eating a roasted chicken right there
like what's sitting there it's a buffalo
chicken when wings or whatever it's not
about eating those and saying well it
was cooked good enough so the virus is
dead it's not what it is I'm not talking
about eating a chicken that has a virus
that's not it at all the flu virus feeds
on chicken flesh the bird flu virus
feeds off of chicken flesh that's why
the chickens are
dying because it attacks every cell in
the chicken and feeds off of it it eats
it so when we have chicken in our livers
Chicken in our bloodstream chicken in
her guts chicken sitting in her colon
for weeks and weeks and weeks for eating
chicken three times a week twice a week
once a week for eating chicken once a
month if you eat chicken once a month
you still have chicken in you that's it
it it's not going to leave you if you
eat chicken once a month just CU you
went to the bathroom and you think you
saw it on the way out doesn't
mean you don't have chicken in your
cells and inside your liver and chicken
fat inside your body building inside
your body it doesn't work that way so
it's best to be free from chicken for
quite a long time I'm not saying you
can't eat a piece of chicken it's a good
chance sure you'll be fine whatever you
may not get the bird flu but there is
going to be a
mutation it is going to happen at some
point is it going to be a real deadly
deadly one very well could
be is is there a possibility it won't be
a real deadly one God intervenes yeah
it's it's very possible but the chicken
that's in your bloodstream and in your
organs because so many people eat
chicken talking about a
crop that everybody just eats all the
same it's crazy what's for dinner what's
chicken okay well I'm having some
asparagus but chicken I'm having some
broccoli but it's chicken what you have
for lunch Chicken on salad chicken salad
you got chicken on your pizza heads it
Chicken on my
pizza anyway but the point is is that
what people don't realize is everybody
should stop eating chicken right now
every single person should stop it's
critical because a they're not going to
stop no one's going to stop how many
people are going to see this not
probably the whole world isn't going to
see this although the medical meem
podcast reached a lot of people so the
bird flu episode of the medical medum
podcast reached a trrap ton of people
around the world and that is still being
listened to right now every single day
every hour right now that one that one
did really crazy out
there all right so let's just let's just
do a quick little um run through okay
there's a bird flu released by The
evildoers classified medical research
and science they put the bird flu out
there various different ways of
contamination so Birds would get it
birds Don't naturally get the bird flu
it's impossible it's not possible for a
bird to get the bird flu a bird can't
just come down with the flu but for some
reason they figured out ways of putting
it out there drones drones nobody knew
what the drones are
for and they got it out there somehow
whatever it is it's out there birds are
getting it wild birds are dying all the
time right now in massive droves and
crops everywhere from both the crops of
birds and Agland that are happening like
the poultry and so forth the foul all
that turkeys included are all dying out
there but wild birds are dying like
Robins crows and other birds
too pretty soon at this rate the bird
flu is taking over the planet there's a
good chance if God doesn't intervene or
it doesn't stop at some point in 3 to 5
years all birds can be gone yes all
birds can be gone on the
planet all birds
gone evildoers are putting the bird flu
out there because they know it'll jump
to humans they've actually designed it
to have the ability to jump to a human
even though it's not the normal process
in which that virus works but people are
getting that virus evildoers put out the
other flu that's out there now there's a
reason why hospitals are filled with
that flu the timing is actually lined up
perfectly that's what the evildoers did
they put the bird flu out there they put
the regular flu out there the human flu
because there's a fantastic chance
someone with the human flu is going to
get the bird flu here and there and
everywhere including yes men and women
women working at bird
factories chicken
factories egg
factories those people pick it up first
they end up picking up the bird flu from
the birds then they pick up the human
flu and they know that the amount of
chicken factories around the world and
bird factories around the world they
know there's going to be an incredible
chance for that to happen from the
workers working in these places that
they're going to eventually pick up the
human flu
somewhere and they're going to pick up
that human flu and they're going to pick
up the bird flu at the same time and
those are going to be the first people
sending out the mutations it's going to
be the people working in the bird
factories in the chicken factories and
so forth hen houses and everything else
for egg production and everything else
those people are going to go out one
night to a bar whatever they going to do
on Friday night they're going to pick up
the influenza that's actually going
around right now then they're going to
go back to work on Monday and they're
going to pick up the bird flu and
they're going to have both those flu
inside of them and evildoers know this
eventually a mutation is going to be
sprung because both these viruses don't
want to kill themselves they want to
work together so they Spar they learn
about each other and then boom they
sequence when they
sequence that's when the mess happens
they create a virus that a wants to kill
every chicken and bird there is in the
world and now wants to kill humans more
than ever before so now the flu becomes
something different between the bird flu
and that flu put together it becomes a
bug that wants to kill people at
probably a 50% die off
rate that's the goal and that's what
they're doing what I recommend is stop
eating chicken completely stop I think
everyone on the planet should stop
eating turkeys and chickens and quails
and pheasants and Ducks who eats ducks
you always find somebody in a restaurant
fine dining like I'll have the
duck and yes there are some people that
have contracted the bird flu like I said
before already and you just got to line
it up just right what I'm talking about
is the mutation that is coming not the
bird flu that's out there in the moment
but the mutation between the bird flu
and the human flu and that mutation and
what's coming now there's a chance that
not come and there's a chance that it
just might not happen and I would say
for sure that's God's
intervention but it could happen still
all the same the reason why you want to
stop eating chicken or any kind of birds
is because you don't want that inside
your cells you don't want chicken in
your cells yes it doesn't just go in
your mouth and your stomach down your
dadum and your small intestinal tract
your colon and out the other end and
it's
gone it actually sits in your body it
takes months to get get it out months
you should do a cleanse maybe go to Cafe
Gratitude do a wellness reset cleanse
maybe pick up a medical medium book do
one of those cleanses 369 and get the
chicken out of your bloodstream get it
out of your liver get it out of your
cells get it out of your
bones so that you're free from that
being in you and the best thing could
have ever ever happened right now is
eggs being scarce and egg prices going
up unless it's the only food you can eat
for some reason cuz you have a medical
condition and so all you can eat is eggs
Blended in a blender or something like
that but the point is is it's a good
thing eggs are getting
scarcer and it's hard to get
eggs because nobody should be eating
eggs or chicken right now because of
what the plan is and what they're
doing and if you think it sounds crazy
or anything like okay good just think of
it as just a fun story we're just having
fun today that's fine with me
anyway so what I recommend is get rid of
the
chicken so here's how it
works you guys like my art
skills I'm an artist
here's how it works you eat the
chicken
okay some of the chicken fat gets
absorbed through the mouth yeah believe
it or not lots of different chemicals
and hormones in the chicken you don't
eat chicken with hormones but yes you do
every single chicken has hormones in it
every single chicken does hormones get
absorbed into your
mouth from eating the chicken already
you got the hormones what the bird flu
loves is the hormones now actually
occurring hormones in organic chicken
whatever free range chicken it's one
thing that occurs the virus will feed
off those hormones you swallow the
chicken it's in your stomach right
now okay your HCL is breaking it apart
starting to dissolve and break the
proteins down cuz that's what your HCL
does if you got strong HCL if you don't
the proteins just sit there rot in your
gut and then you're fermenting got
fermented putrified chicken carcass in
your gut and that's what's happening
this isn't vegan propag has nothing to
do with that I would if you're somebody
that's eating chick chicken all the time
and you need you you feel like you need
an animal protein to move on to beef
grass-fed beef that flu virus that bird
flu virus doesn't want
beef chicken's in here and it breaks
down it starts breaking down okay and
then it moves down the dadum into the
small intestinal tract and breaks down
even more and then
that chicken part of it Li liquifies
gets into the liver through the paddock
portal Highway goes right up into the
liver right here and it sits in the
liver fat from the chicken is dispersed
by guess what your bile reserves your
bile actually starts to break down the
fats and disperses the fats that goes
all through the body gets into the
liver and then gets through into
everywhere else as well so so when
you're when you're sitting there and you
got chicken now inside your gut and it's
being dissolved by your gastric juices
and dissolved by your
bile it ends up everywhere in your body
your brain your nervous system something
from that chicken ends up somewhere
everywhere your bone marrow your liver
and it takes time to get it
out when the day comes that these two
viruses become one and mutate and we
have a deadly bird
flu you're going to
want you
know I think we have a tech problem with
Tik Tock I think they boot at me
again you're going to want chicken out
of your body you'll have the greatest
chance to push that virus out of your
body the greatest chance and you'll have
a
survival opportunity as
well the evildoers are relying on the
amount of chicken people eat the amount
of chicken people eat we guarantee that
the virus will be even more hungrier and
deadlier and cause more
damage anyway
so
you guys got to watch this from the
beginning definitely have to watch it
from the beginning without a doubt
okay and I think the phone is
ringing um
but anyway about the bird flu and stuff
that's only if the viruses mutate like I
said God's intervention will definitely
kick in and it's probably not going to
happen but I'm just saying that's how it
works with the bird flu talked about it
on the medical beam podcast check it out
when you can
it's actually a really good episode it's
the bird flu episode and it's really
interesting as hell it's got a lot of
great
information we're just having Tech
problems right now you guys so just
beare with us
all right just a recap you
guys check out angel to Demons spiritual
tools you could actually um just go on
Amazon type it in you'll see it check it
out when you get a chance see a lot of
people laughing and okay check out the
wellness reset Cafe Gratitude and are
you going to be there meet and
greet at Cafe Gratitude next week for
the medical me and pizza party another
thing too watch this whole thing from
the beginning so you can hear about all
of that which is really
cool I'm reading your comments right now
too light light light mebe 787 that's
right
that's the thing you
know as far as what people have to you
have to understand something about the
chicken and everything else you keep it
away and that literally right there
gives you a lot of protection and people
don't realize that and that's how great
it
is I'm reading
comments seriously folks this guy is
talking nonsense about viruses eat free
range chicken if you
like and kick fear into touch
oh good advice go
ahead anyway it's not vegan propaganda I
saw somebody saying ah it's vegan
propaganda it's not what it
is I've been told this for decades and
proven right over and over with so much
information so anyway well look let's
hope nothing happens and that's the
whole point there's a good chance it
won't but the goal is to create
problems and I could just keep the
information to
myself but how great would that be I
want to make sure people have that
information you're excited for the new
audio wait till you hear it you're going
to be blown off your seat I was talking
about it earlier you pre-ordered it
amazing I'm excited 7 and 1 half hours
of listening take a little bit at a time
light
blast I hope you're there at cafeic
gratitude hope you got a
ticket me the third fourth and
fifth somebody said please don't so
grateful for you sharing I mean see
they're keeping the information to
myself but I never do I make sure I let
everybody know what's going
on you're late you don't eat chicken
there you go but almost every every body
does it's
crazy what time does it release March
18th I'm just trying to read
some can't wait for Monday yeah I can't
wait
too I got to get my stuff together and I
got to make sure I'm
there um
I got a friend right
here if you're wondering with all the
commotion was I was trying to make sure
my friend
arrived is what I was trying to
do so now what you're looking at right
now is not Dr
nesbet you're looking at Dr nesbit's
cousin um
looking at Dr nzb's husband Charlie
husband's
Charlie huh says get it right I am so I
got to tell you something so the news I
have right now is Dr nesbet has the bird
flow and that's why Charlie's
here he's doing a little better he's
doing a little bit better he's been
drinking a lot it seems to be helping
his bird flu he's been drinking a lot of
vodka
yeah no yeah that's you can say that
it's
okay he's been having some vomiting and
some diarrhea diarrhea that what it is
okay
um what am I doing I'm reading comments
I had didn't get a chance to read any
comments at all Charlie saying that Dr
nezbit is going to make a full recovery
but how's that possible you know during
this show I was talking about how like
when Birds got the bird flew they're all
dying that's
why you're just trying to keep everybody
in good spirits
what okay Dr nesbet is still alive so
you got to just know that and we'll make
sure Dr nesbet recovers is Dr nesbet
doing all the right stuff Dr nesbet
stopped eating
chicken um
when did he stop eating
chicken he stopped eating chicken when
he got the bird
flu why is Dr nesbet eating
chicken Dr nesbit's favorite chicken are
buffalo chicken wings right
here um do you want
one um that's a chicken wing Charlie
doesn't likei chicken um just for the
record not a big chicken
fan so but you're having a little bit
now no you're not okay okay then put it
back
down I'm really sorry that Dr nesbet
isn't here tonight I feel bad that's
what was going on I was trying to see
where Dr nesbet
was Nicholas says I've been following aw
since 2015 and he is always always right
on point he even pre-war us about
covid yeah I know I I I did and I talked
also about a bunch of other stuff
too before Co came who what else so
you're not even allowed to still say
that
word it's
crazy Jess can you explain to us why
they would poison themselves how does
that give them control in the
end you'll receive the answers you will
receive the answers with the angels
demons and spiritual tools just hold on
a second you
guys Charli this this is like getting
really kind of
got a little too
much all
right don't worry Dr nzb's going to make
it it's going to be
fine a little bird flu is not going to
take Dr nesbet out he's a surgeon and
board certified psychiatrist for God's
sake talked about what long flu was
before the covid pandemic I talked about
long flu and how it works you get the
flu and then the flu lowers the immune
system and the immune system
system gets dropped and then it allows
EP bars and all these other things just
you know just constantly just crop
up and so that's long flu anyway so
medical medum
information so yeah Co did the same
thing so yeah medical medum information
is highly Advanced and always ahead of
the
curve Mark says this is scare mongering
prepandemic too [__] and this [__]
now
Mark have you been looking around lately
everybody is like screaming bloody
murder every 5 seconds and shock and awe
and everything else and I'm just talking
about the bird flu and the flu getting
together on a little
dance see Lindsay said this guy is such
an idiot
yeah
uh-huh she doesn't like she doesn't have
a lot of
friends
no Charlie over here says that that
person doesn't have a lot of
friends and has too much time on their
hands what else really they eat that
kind of stuff that person doesn't eat
anything good
either
and sees a therapist twice a week for
what oh dear
God that's not good that's not good for
that
person who else is on
here Charlie you just just scared me
Charlie's just hanging out right now Dr
nesbet is sick with the bird
flu Tiki says wow so stoked about Ang
demons Angels demons and spiritual tools
Ken says you are
hilarious how you says is beis okay um
well that's kind of part of what
happened beis is kind of over there in
the other side of the
kitchen so beus just never came to the
table Yeah and right now the bird flu is
is not a
problem I'm just talking about what the
goal
is
so via says Charlie is a great
co-host Charlie said damn
right what else it's a nice person nice
person probably says you're a nice
person Christine says I have flu now for
weeks
don't eat chicken Charlie
said re says why are you
watching you must be answering that
other person that says I am not a great
person um daffany says we are lucky to
have you aw I'm going to get off my
knees here for a second
here this fulvic asset help detox any of
the viruses no it doesn't far from it
happiness with from from within says I
love your sense of
humor thank you for being on here by the
way really appreciate
you Heather Skinner says thank you so
much awfc you are such a blessing to us
your words are life saving and I have
never been more healthy after following
our teach your teachings I no longer
have to worry about catching the flu
that are running
rampant I mean it's powerful information
you got the flu protocol and everything
and the medical medium books which is
always there you guys it's always
there Jackie B says people get angry
when chicken is involved oh man do they
get angry they get so
angry don't swear
Charlie bleep those people Charlie come
on
don't say anything terrible like that
who you're different than Dr nesbet my
God you got a mouth on you oh my
god bleep those people you want me to
say the word are you kidding I'm not
going to say that on here I'm going to
say
bleep uh let's see D says my family and
I love you thank
you thank you you're a very special
person Christ said what I'm getting
compliments but remember those other two
people
said Terrible Things Chrissy said so I
so thank you for you aw been following
let's see so thankful for you aw been
following for 11 years and healed lime
and other things you are the
best you guys should listen to
the medical me medical Me podcast listen
to to the bird flu episode is what you
should listen
to and check out the audio Mel says are
we having a book as well or just
audio I thought really good
question Sira says I am watching a dude
in a chicken have a conversation what
the f is going on you said what the f is
happening
Sara I'm glad you're on here right
now you like her Charlie says he likes
you Sor Charlie says he likes you you
want to go on a
date Charlie
says you just want to like you want to
give s a tour through a chicken
farm
okay well I'm sure she
heard she can try to contact you after
the
show
mhm wow blueberry bab says book in
series a lot of good stuff coming that's
all I can say but uh
just don't get upset with me you guys
when you hear the audio s and a half
hours of angels demons and spiritual
tools
well the
reborn maybe Chick-fil-A was made for
the bird food
what Colleen says did ha house changed
their minds about publishing the
spiritual
books a house doesn't changed their mind
on anything they're backing Angels
demons and spiritual tools
100% that's what they're
doing for some
reason Charlie this position is really
annoying um
okay
what singing sweetie said I won't get
upset we'll
see we'll see you when you listen hey I
get a
chair it's hard to uh see Charlie it's
hard to actually be down in here while
Holding On To
You Kelly L says can't wait till the
next book any plans for
one Stephie he
says when I float on mattress
Island so
fatigued I can't get out of bed I listen
to your old old podcasts your voice
talks to my
soul it lights my fire and my path and
motivation to
heal Keep On Healing keep on moving
forward Charlie
says send some prayers your way
tonight thank you Charlie Charlie you're
so much better than Dr nesbet Dr nbet
said the most terrible things you just
you just have a different kind of
demeanor Mason says the comments are too
fast gone comments yes they're
fast Jay says Anthony
spill well
listen Charlie says a couple of things
just want to say okay Charlie said that
I didn't give Charlie any chance to talk
at all
um Charlie says that Dr nesbit's goingon
to
call I'm just waiting drth going to call
there's a phone over
here just waiting for Dr n to call right
here Charlie I haven't been able to say
a lot of things that you're saying
because a lot of the things you're
saying are just quite crazy you're
talking about Donnie the donkey and
you're talking talking about Piggy and
you're talking about all the crazy stuff
that happens between Donnie the donkey
and piggy because you hang out with them
and Dr nbut doesn't hang out with them
anymore because he's doing too many
surgeries so I understand that so what
do you want to say about
piggy piggy poos
everywhere even in your your house so
piggy comes and poos right on the floor
and then then
what you have to ask for help to clean
it up okay okay you wanted to tell them
that that's what you really wanted to
say and that's why Dr Nesbit might be a
better fit he has to get better from the
bird flu what else and Donnie the
donkey he overeats really and he threw
up in the car
again Don donkey threw up in the car
again and piggy poops all over the floor
at Charlie's house so Charlie just
wanted that across because Charlie's
hoping to embarrass them to get them
back
okay well I think that was very
productive and um quite useful right
wouldn't you
say trying to save lives here
oh Dr NE it thank you for calling AR
nit oh my God you are sick
like really
sick I just thought Charlie was kind of
[__] with us right now you know
Charlie's been saying all this crazy
terrible stuff you know like pulling her
chain you know what I
mean what okay okay you want to talk to
Charlie okay hold
on Dr nut's on the phone right here
sorry about
that all right so what did you say tell
Charlie to get home and put a pot of
soup on
Charlie came over here to take your spot
yeah I know which you you can you're too
sick to get out of bed Dr neeth says
he's too sick to get what kind of flu do
you really have the bird flu or you just
kidding around with me you really do Dr
nee's a surgeon board certified surgeon
and a board certified
psychiatrist he doesn't fo around he
doesn't joke too
often he's got the bird flu okay you
know that you know all the birds are
dying right just stay out of the poultry
Farms whatever you do do not do a
surgery there yeah stay the hell out of
the poultry Farms Dr nbit because I
swear I swear to God they're just going
to round you up with the rest of the
chickens and kill all you guys yeah they
don't care if you got a little briefcase
and you're your tools in them and you're
a doctor they don't care you're a
chicken to
them
yeah you you know you can get rid of the
bird you're doing the medical meeting
protocol good good
okay did you ask your doctor what's
right for you oh that's right you are a
doctor Dr NES
surgeon okay Charlie's been really kind
of annoying me I wish you didn't send
your
cousin Charlie came on his own he's
supposed to be changing your bed pan
right
now Charlie you got to be changing Dr
nesbit's bed pan you want to say one
more
thing did Charlie okay go
ahead sorry guys sorry about
this okay what did you tell him okay
what Charlie told me that I have to say
it what is
it Charlie
said this is because you ate chicken
last night Dr nesbet why the hell would
you eat chicken you are a chicken you
know that's
cannibalism did you know that it's
cannibalism Dr nbet ate a chicken last
night who was it that you ate somebody
you knew Dr nbet said he didn't know the
chicken he bought the chicken at the
store okay I'm going to let you go I
need you to work on your healing process
Dr Nesbit it's not nonsense Dr
Nesbit do all the things that you need
to do please just get
better and um I'll send Charlie home
okay you guys Charlie is going to go
home oh my God why is everyone asking
about a tsunami in California what did
happen there check out the medical
medium uh microplastics podcast
episode you guys notice something about
the medical Me podcast do you guys
notice something have you have you
learned this yet medical mean podcast is
no advertisers advertising
and no
commercials did you know that that's
something that doesn't exist in today's
podcast World especially if you have a
podcast that a lot of people are
listening to it doesn't
exist medical medum podcast doesn't have
any of that that's right so guess how
much I'm making from the medical medum
podcast
zero z z guess how much money I could
make from the medical medum podcast
Millions
I choose not to to make sure you guys
get free listening so you're not hearing
all the
[__] anyway check out the medical
medum
podcast and what else is going
on Charlie says there's no subscription
fees at the medical medium website
medical medium.com free information and
tons of free information free
information lots of free information
still no subscription fees you don't
have to pay a monthly fee sign up to any
we don't withhold information from you
at Medical medium.com and there was just
recently this doctor guy talking crap
about medical medium out there and he
was like you can pay for my subscription
fees on my website and you'll get more
information from my scientific
information for my subscription fees at
$60 a month then you'd get anything from
medical medium
meanwhile he said something like that
meanwhile meanwhile the stuff he's
talking about is a AI regurg hated [__]
from AI what a ripoff and what a scammer
go to medical.com get free information
and it's not
aied Sarah Hughes says love the no ads
thank you yes that's exactly
right five years ago the medical medium
podcast was approached by ended by the
industries of
Hollywood and they said why don't you
have all the advertisers on there we can
make you Millions each year and you can
be like other podcasters that just do
the whole thing they run ads they make
money from their advertisers they keep
the cycle going so they can climb the
ladder of the podcast world and I said I
don't want to do
that I just want to do things that I
know God
would
appreciate when it's time to leave here
anyway Charlie what
else all right okay guys doesn't mean
someday I
won't got to keep the door open you
never know someday I may have to someday
I may do
it anyway but anyway go to medical.com
get free information go to my telegram I
leave exclusive messages on there
rewatch this stop eating
chicken eat beef if that's what you like
eat fish if that's what you like the
right
kind eat some
sardines or
maybe don't eat any of
that how about
that eat some other things check out
medical medium information check out the
books but yeah it's not a good time to
eat chicken right now maybe next year is
a better time to eat chicken and maybe
two years from now it's a better time to
eat chicken how about that eat chicken 6
months from now I just wouldn't eat it
right now until they get that stuff
under control heel with celery juice
says no ripoff Retreats like some are
pushing these days no Retreats medical
medium doesn't do Retreats doesn't put
ripoff Retreats out there that's right
healed celery juice you get it you get
it it's all free information it's always
been there's no
Retreats and medical medium
events you know are there to help people
too all right you
guys I'm going to go thank you for your
patience we had a tech problem and I was
crawling on the floor looking for
Charlie I was actually ransacking the
house looking for
Dr
Nesbit and Dr nesbit's
wife and so I'm sorry about the delay
where I look like a de any headlights
when I realized I didn't have the right
chicken that's insulting sorry about
that so I don't know if you can see a
difference take a look
at Charlie's
eyes all right you guys