We're talking about how the chemtrails
kill the birds. Ducks flying at 10,000
ft will match a chemtrail plane flying
at 10,000 ft. So, simplifying it a
little bit, birds fly high, chemtrail
planes fly low, birds get caught into
the chemtrails themselves and get
snuffed out and then die. And we're not
just talking about a few birds. We're
talking about thousands of birds. tens
of thousands in just a flock migrating.
We're talking about a massive amount of
birds dying close to death almost at
exactly the same time. And keep in mind,
every batch lot in the plane, every
group of chemicals that they have that
they're dumping, whether it's
geoengineering planes or a chemtrail
plane, can be different at any given
time. So, some concoctions could be
instantly deadly, while some are
intoxicating and dangerous enough to
weaken the birds, causing their flight
pattern to be disturbed, causing them to
weaken and have to drop out of the sky,
disturbing the process of nature,
destroying the very birds we love. So,
how do 10,000 birds die at a clip? How
does it really happen?
[Music]