something critical you have to
understand
and I know this runs through people's
veins
it's blaming yourself
blaming yourself
for any kind of adversity and any kind
of struggle
it's blaming yourself
okay now when it comes down to health
issues if you're struggling with a
symptom depression multiple sclerosis
nausea anxiety seizures whatever it is
we covered a lot of stuff CFS whatever
it is it's not your fault
I can promise you it's not your fault
you have to remember that
this critical and don't forget it it
gets in the way of your healing process
when you believe it's your fault it
interferes
it messes with your mind
that messes with your soul
if you're sick you're sick and it's not
your fault something happened and it's
about discovering why
and how to correct it and move forward
because your body loves you
unconditionally and it wants to heal
your body wants to heal and it loves you
unconditionally and you can't forget
that
you cannot forget that
[Music]
don't forget that
and you're not a bad person you didn't
create your symptoms you didn't create
your doctor bills you didn't create
your compromises from being sick you
didn't create your emotional pain and
you didn't create your losses you have
to remember that and don't forget this
pat yourself on the back have compassion
for yourself critical critical
I know
that it's not your fault that you're
sick or have a chronic illness or a
symptom I know I need you
I know
I know SOC knows but I need you to know
[Music]