now the episode is released
blood draw bloodletting and vampirism
so you've got to listen to the episode
as soon as soon as you can
it's really important i'm going to give
you a couple of tips like run a couple
of things by you
why this episode is so important medical
medium podcast at apple podcast just so
there's no confusion it's not
this episode on the youtube it's the
podcast episode medical meeting podcast
at apple
podcast link is in the description share
it with
anyone everybody you know
just share it with the trees okay share
it with trees all right trees have their
own iphones now
they have their own androids share it
with the trees okay
they need to hear it too listen you guys
well actually they get tapped from maple
syrup they get tapped from maple water
they don't get tapped for blood
listen you guys this episode you can't
you can't you just got oh my god christy
spears
just got finished listening to it
amazing blew my mind
oh my god that's incredible he chota
this podcast was incredible worth the
wait everyone needs to listen yeah
to protect them it's critical to protect
people
this is so important um yeah you guys
have a watermelon right here right
see the watermelon that's one of the
tips in the podcast episode remember
watermelon really important remember
i'll talk about it a little bit
okay also got a brain right here in
front of me
i'm gonna talk about the brain a little
bit why this is critical information
um pam fraser just watched the podcast
in eye opener since i got my blood
tested a couple of weeks ago
and now have weakness in my leg and
vertigo yes
it's what i've been talking about this
is the very thing that
brings people back notches in your
health thank god you got medical medium
information
because you can move forward and get
yourself strong again rebecca one of my
doctors took
39 vials of blood
at once i don't even know what to say
right there
it's just awful i'm so sorry so sorry
about it yeah um
simple simply healing watermelon you saw
his honestly
so you pop up there um 39 vials of blood
this is probably one of the most
important episodes
this should if you guys can help me get
this
episode out there there's no
advertisements there's no commercials
so i'm not making money off of it okay
because podcasters want their podcast
episodes shared so they can make money
right there's that's not happening this
is about working for the chronically ill
that's a free episode i don't
have any advertisers on there paying me
money why people listen
it's there just so people can heal get
their lives back
you can't miss this blood draw
bloodletting and vampirism episode
medical mean podcast apple podcast now
listen if you hear the episode some
other platform
if it's not apple podcast then there's
going to be little pieces missing
i'm just going to give there's a good
chance so apple podcast is where the
uncensored version
is medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast okay
share the podcast episode with everyone
everybody you can
to help them heal i'm going to talk
about the podcast episode a little bit
so i want you guys if you're coming on i
want to be able to
give you the rundown on this okay what
it's about i have my celery juice
going to drink a little bit dr phan will
share i'm honored
truly honored amazing md truly truly
honored
maddie shilling says she's almost done
listening whoa
whoa she got a little fireball next to
there too so
you guys this this episode's really
critical because what happens is the
industry
the industry not the doctors it's not
their fault
it's not the doctor's fault the industry
has trained
has trained the medical communities to
take and take and take too much blood
from us
okay and this leads to a couple
questions that i've seen on social media
that i want to answer too why i'm here
um so yeah if you don't if you don't
have it on
apple you can go to themedicalmedium.com
look look at the podcast there you can
just dial it up right there and make it
happen
no matter what device you're using so
you can learn how to do it um
other people can help you you know share
how that's done too
anyway good to see you guys on here
let's cover this for a couple of minutes
and talk about it so um jerry what's the
podcast about
it's about getting your blood tested
it's about
blood draw getting your blood your blood
drawn
they take too much blood
period that's what they do this is an
episode about
protecting you so when you get your
blood tests when you get your blood
drawn
you can protect your immune system
protect your body because blood draw
sets people back and it keeps a lot of
people sick for the rest of their life
they go to the doctor and their immune
system is removed in their blood draw
and that that blood they take all gets
thrown away
except for a smidgen of it and what
happens is
your white count goes out boom you get
the blood drawn your white count goes
out with it okay your white blood cells
they all go out with it
and what people don't understand is your
immune system is there to protect
protect your heart
okay it's to protect your heart that's
what your immune system is there for
it's to protect your heart and that's
what and what happens is that
your immune system is in your
bloodstream so you don't get an
infection to the heart or an infection
to the brain
really important to know and what they
do is they remove
they remove with negligence
a big hunk of our blood seven vials five
vials full vial seven full vials
nine full vials 10 11 39 vials like
like someone was just talking about
earlier right and they remove it and
your immune system goes out
with it is what happens when it goes out
with it you're susceptible you're
susceptible to
fibromyalgia ms tingles and numbness
aches and pains
ringing in the ears vertigo dizziness
you're susceptible to
pcos more susceptible to endometriosis
susceptible to hpv
so what happens is all these women right
and all these men
they go to get their blood tested men
and women
and they draw the same amount of blood
from a 220 pound male
6 foot 5 220 230 pound male
they draw the same amount of blood that
they would a
hundred pound female they they that's
what they do
and there's so many holes in all of this
so you
you got to learn how to protect yourself
listen to this podcast episode
um it's not this youtube episode right
here i'm in i'm live right now in this
youtube episode
it's not this youtube episode it's the
podcast episode medical meeting podcast
at apple podcast
i just released it okay
so it's it's important okay um you had
no idea blood draw was bad
i'm glad you brought it up courtney said
i'm glad you're here
there's a way to get your blood drawn
there's a way to get your blood tested
and i talk about it in the podcast
episode
because i believe in getting your blood
test i believe in getting your blood
drawn
right but as you get sicker with your
health conditions they draw more blood
they remove your immune system every
time they draw more blood and they
remove your immune system
is what they do you get sicker it keeps
people sick for 20 years
with hashimoto's fibromyalgia chronic
fatigue syndrome
acne aches and pains excess rice it
keeps them sick forever
and medical medium information battles
this
so when you take medical medium
information in your life and you're
healing
we're up against the blood they're
taking you see how it works
so here you are i'm doing the heavy
metal detox smoothie the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie
i'm doing the medical medium celery
juice i'm taking care of myself i'm
doing the spinach soup i'm doing the
healing broth i'm doing the meditations
i'm doing all this stuff to get myself
better and to get myself better i'm
doing the mono eating
i'm doing the different supplement
protocols and what happens is
medical medium information is moving you
forward and then you go get your blood
drawn
and then boom they move you backwards
like that now you're backwards that's
what they do
so jerry don't you make more blood cells
yes and in the episode i talk about what
happens
if you're already sick you're already
got fibro
you already got some kind of condition
you're already dealing with some kind of
symptom
right that's why people just everybody's
got a symptom right chronic sinusitis
utis
whatever people get they're already sick
with things
cystitis aches and pains fatigue their
immune system is already low
they're already struggling they need
their immune cells to be at the top
of the the game their game top of their
game
okay what happens is right they're
already having immune
complications they then draw
all this blood constantly and you get
sicker because of it because your immune
system is being removed
and when your immune immune system is
removed your problems get worse
and then guess what they draw more
blood uh you're sick you're getting
sicker
yeah i just don't feel good it's been a
month now and i'm feeling kind of worse
my symptoms are persisting
um i need to go to a specialist now and
what do they want they want
20 tubes now drawn and you go backwards
this is a bloodletting technique the top
of the industry does
to take people out it is not a good
thing
and you've got to listen to it link is
in the description
you want to hear link is in the
description go to medical medium podcast
at apple podcast to hear
the blood draw bloodletting vampirism
episode margaret hey someone
they went up there i try to read them as
fast as i can
lorraine's there um yeah so
it's look the whole point is this is
good information that could be
life-saving for many people
helpful for you know many people um
margaret said someone tried the link did
it work i hope so the link is in the
description
should take you there so you can hear
the episodes you don't want to miss this
episode
so i talk about this episode this as far
as watermelon be one of the tools to
help you
when you get your blood drawn and it
doesn't mean it's going to save you
because you get too much blood drawn if
we get in trouble but i also give you
tips of what to tell the doctor what to
ask the doctor
okay like there's all kinds of questions
you're gonna have
they should be they'll be answered in
the episode
so that's important we lose electrolytes
that's why the watermelon is important
we lose electrolytes
it's one thing right there um when we
get our blood
drawn and that's so i give you tips on
how to protect yourself
then i talk about blood donating blood
to blood donations
donating blood how to protect yourself
so we can give
life-saving blood for other people that
get into bad car accidents that have
that need a life-saving surgery you know
they need
they need their heart okay valves
replaced and
they might need or people who need blood
transfusions because
they're losing blood for some reason
right i want people to be able to donate
blood but
but blood donating can also be
detrimental
and bring you to a place of a very ill
person
okay and bringing to a place of needing
to
actually get a blood transfusion to
someday taking to a place of a very bad
in a bad way if you're not protecting
yourself i talk about if you're sick
with chronic illness you shouldn't give
blood
but it should be for the people who are
healthy and strong or feel healthy and
strong
and even when they do it there's ways of
protecting themselves
before you give donate blood there's a
way to protect yourself and after you
donate blood because i want people to be
able to donate blood
absolutely but at the same time a lot of
people with a lot of symptoms donate
blood a lot of women
they feel like it's their duty and they
want to donate blood
and because men don't really donate
blood you know it's mostly women
that's who donates blood so the whole
planet is really women that are donating
blood but men aren't
so anyway just you know not as many it's
like you know so we got wit so here's
what's happening we got
with with donating blood we got women
that are struggling
with their health fatigue from low-grade
viruses
epstein-barr they got fibromyalgia
they're the ones donating blood
we got women that are actually
struggling with lyme disease they're
donating blood it's like
it's like something's wrong with the
system because
that's a risky area because now we're
losing our immune system by donating
blood while we're sick
and then i talk about how they take just
as much blood in a donation from
a female as they would a male so you got
a 250-pound male
they'll just take the same pint as
they'll take from a 90-pound woman
they don't even question it like hey
wait a minute she's 92 pounds
she's got fibromyalgia she doesn't feel
good let's just take a whole pint from
her
i mean the whole system's just arranged
i talk about it
i'm not saying you can't donate i want
people to donate blood i'm all
supportive of it
but but the system's not protecting
women that are sick when it comes down
to donating blood they don't say for a
whole week you should know
how to take your care of yourself and
get yourself ready for the blood
donation
and then after the blood blood donation
how to protect yourself
after the blood donation see so much
information in this episode i think you
guys
you guys have to see it so and then
you're gonna get there's a question i
hear out there a couple questions well
women bleed they have their cycle so you
mean to tell me what's going on with
that well that's a natural process of
life okay
that's a process of life that your
immune system
as a woman is ready for because 80
of your immune system goes to the
reproductive system during menstruation
the reason for that when you bleed
having a period
it's not even a fraction of the blood
they take or
draw with big blood draws that's a whole
nother thing all on its own
it's a smaller amount of blood with
tissue
shedding of the uterus lining
so it's not and then when a woman is in
in this serious condition where they're
bleeding too much with their periods
where they're
hemorrhaging it's devastating and
life-threatening
exactly that's why we have to worry
about blood draws that's why we have to
worry about taking so much blood from
women and some men too
well of course not with the menstruation
thing but you know with everything else
men don't go through that but for women
with the menstruation cycle
and the natural process that they go
through it
it's it's if they're hemorrhaging and
and too much bleeding
yes that's a major concern a lot of
women they get in trouble with that
but that's what i'm trying to say but no
one's saying when we take 39
vials from a woman like you know we take
39 vials from 104
pound um woman or 110 or 120 pound take
39 vials 35 vials 22 28 vials no one's
talking about that
that's different than a cycle it's
different than a natural cycle
or a normal cycle where there's a little
bit of blood
and then some lining some shedding of
the lining it's so it's really the whole
system is
all not where it should be it's the
information in this is mind-blowing
truly
um yeah one donation can save up to
three lives
with each each whole blood donation
absolutely regina and i believe in blood
donating
of course but look who's looking out for
the people donating blood
are they asking them questions are they
asking them the questions they
should ask them there's so many
variables are they looking to see if
they're
110 pounds and maybe
there should be a different way of
handling it are they looking at their
health history
really looking at it symptoms and
different things they're going through
are they looking at other exposures
they're having are they having stress in
their life
are they looking at that because i've
seen a lot of people donate blood
and get a lot sicker and sicker and then
they're bedridden because
they had conditions and symptoms they
weren't the same weight as a 250 pound
male who's six
foot five they were 125 pounds with a
little bit of fibromyalgia
some acne and some some psoriasis and
what happened was
they donated their pint and then they
were set backwards for months in their
healing and sometimes
actually in their healing throughout
their whole life so
you know dealing with their conditions
but i but yes
we want to get healthy and donate blood
but we want to protect ourselves
no one's saying when you donate blood
why don't we get your electrolytes
really strong because we're about to
take a pint of blood from you
so let's get your electrolyte strong
let's make sure
you're doing melon every day celery
juice cucumber juice before you go in
and deliver a pint of life-saving blood
for somebody else
they're not doing that and besides that
okay and and so i'm giving you tips in
this
episode so you can you can donate blood
if that's where your heart's at
the point is is you gotta listen to it
it's link is in the description
okay educating myself the magnitude of
info he
he processes is mind-blowing um i'm
blown away okay
because the information in this episode
just like the other
17 episodes the medical meet podcast is
jammed
packed jam-packed i can't even tell you
guys
um
that's not true you can't even donate
blood if you that's not true
women go in there women go in there all
the time i hear it all the time i've
doctors telling me women go in there
they leave with a pint of blood and
they're under 100 pounds
that's not true that's exactly that's
exactly one of the holes in the system
yeah that might be a
one place there are thousands of women
going into all kinds of blood donation
clinics
they walk in at 101 pounds they walk in
at 99 pounds they walk in
at 98.5 pounds and they leave blood
no one's watching no one's properly
keeping an
eye on them that's misinformation right
there sorry
misinformation debunked you know you
gotta get
if you if you know a lot you don't think
i've talked to dozens of nurses
you don't think i've actually done the
work myself
out there you don't think i've talked to
hundreds of doctors and hundreds of
doctors you don't think i know how blood
donations work
so yeah no one's no one's keeping an
eye on them no one's watching their
weight specifically
okay they're no one's watching all of
that their symptoms what they've gone
through
and look most importantly
this is also about your routine blood
tests
five aisles seven vials ten vials
can set you back greatly and it's not
it's not
being cared for you're not being cared
for
you're not being taught how to protect
yourself it's one of the most important
areas
and what happens with medical medium
information gets all these people better
and then they're all just getting blood
drained out of them every which way
and it's going against their healing
they're getting 14 vials drawn
seven vials drawn you guys got to hear
the episode
okay i got about 40 vials taken from me
oh it's going up i gotta take a look at
that let me see if i can get it back
down here
michaela i got about 40 vials taken from
me within a four to five month period
while being chronically ill
would i still be having issues from this
without knowing
i've been i have been following your
protocols for a month and a half yes you
could be
easily having issues i talked about it
in the episode you could be set back for
months in your healing three to six
months
just to get your 40 vials to get your
red blood cells back it could take three
to six months
to get them back to where they need to
be to get your white count back it could
be three to six months
to get him back and that's the problem
it's criminal it's actually criminal
that's what it is
and that's the industry it's modern day
bloodletting without looking after the
person
wait till you hear the episode if you
can share
this episode with anybody and everybody
you know and ask them to share it
because you're going to save somebody
from getting chronically ill you're
going to save somebody from getting
worse
and you're going to get somebody better
faster once they're able to protect
themselves
you can still get blood work you can
still get blood tests because i believe
in it
i support it i want you to get your
blood tested because you got your
doctors i want you to get your blood
tested but i'm just going to let you
know
there's a way to do it to protect
yourself and stand up for yourself
and get your blood tested right lorraine
yep share share share
it really matters uh roshini
says has anybody heard the episode hey i
love your comments by the way
um you you left a comment that was
really really gracious
it was very nice it was on the last
youtube was on yesterday's youtube i'm
honored
um anyway because you understand that i
am fighting for the chronic leo that i
am fighting for the people who are sick
and
i'm i'm blown away by your comment on
youtube
that you left uh i don't know if it was
today or yesterday anyway you guys
watermelon is in my hand it's one of the
tips that's in there
um and and but you want to
hear this episode medical beam podcast
at apple podcast that's the uncensored
version
link is in the description share with
everybody you can okay
and it talks about how we lose our
immune systems in this modern day
vampirism and they throw out all the
blood
and you can ask for half files i talk
about all the information's in there
okay um yeah
really important to know the
information's in there you love
watermelon tj
me too i do do all right it's a really
really really good
um really good
tool for healing okay you guys i'm
heading over to um
ig i'm heading over to tick tock that's
where i'm going
okay i might crack the watermelon open
on ig and tic toc
i love you guys and mean podcast at
apple podcast check it out