[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now
and the high blood pressure shows where
we are today low low blood pressure high
blood pressure and the secrets about
what that is about the answers to the
mystery blood pressure issues because
really it's mystery unless there's a
blockage that's actually seen by the by
by your you know cardiologist or by the
doctor or or through testing and and in
a scope getting a scope put up into the
heart whatever whether it's a blockage
or it's you know someone who really has
a heart problem
unless it's unless it's something unless
there's a real reason and and listen
even those are pretty much mysteries of
why people get a lot of heart problems
all that's mystery out there for the
most part heart disease itself I mean we
got some Clues and we got some good
ideas why people get heart disease but a
lot lot of times it's mystery out there
in the medical Arenas so but high blood
pressure low blood pressure with no real
evidence of heart
disease arterial sclerosis or some kind
of you know artery disease no real
evidence of cardiovascular
disease but yet having low blood
pressure high blood pressure it's a
mystery mystery mystery listen you don't
think a lot of people have blood
pressure problems everybody gets them
someday everybody gets them whether
they're eating way too much fat for a 50
years and then then finally it catches
up or they think you know they're eating
pretty good and all is good and then
there's just this mystery blood pressure
problem either way almost everyone has
to hear about it some way in their life
whether they younger or older in one way
or another so is this important yes it's
a big one it's a big show I love it I
love this one because this is an
important show and I I really want to
get people better get them feeling
better so who has 10 years to wait to
get answers let's do it now that's the
whole point listen this is the only show
where the information is not repackaged
or recycled Theory that's what happens
out there that's revolving the revolver
the the the musical chairs of recycled
repackaged information out there of
theory it that's not what this show is
the information here doesn't come from
the medical interest groups that are
contaminated in all the information out
of their medical funding with strings
attached botch research that's a thumb
on the scale that's the whole thing paid
and bought paid and bought and
grandfathered in laws because of
investors investing in money in botch
research you know uh funky sign out
there that everybody thinks is real but
it's not lobbyists internal Kickbacks
persuaded belief systems in the
alternative and and and conventional
medical Arenas private panels of
influencers with money going underneath
the table so the information is
contaminated and then it gets cited and
then peerreview studies and it goes into
book after book and it doesn't get
people better because it's contaminated
or trendy traps yes I have to say that
because guess what it's so important to
know that it's important to know that
the information in the show is the only
this is the only show where the
information is pure untampered with
clean and that's the you know what you
know let me tell you something if I had
the op if I didn't have this gift if I
didn't get this gift when I was age four
of knowing what's going on in hearing
spirit and having the information that
was Advanced and ahead of decades ahead
of that what's out there now with
information and help hundreds of
thousands of people over my whole
lifetime if I didn't have that gift and
I was just somebody out there looking
for answers and I I just and i' I've
been and I was burned left and right
with reading different things and going
different places and spending tons and
tons of thousands of dollars and having
a mystery illness or diagnosed Illness
but who knows what was going on up and
down wrong or right and I had a chance
to hear information that wasn't attached
to any of that stuff any of that junk
science that was paid for out there
attached to any of that contamination
that I just mentioned if I had a chance
to hear free information meaning free
and clear from contamination
that had truth in it and it was real if
I had that chance I'd be like I'd be on
it and be like okay no I'm listening to
this because I understand I've been
around the block I know what's going on
I've suffered enough I know that I want
to hear this instead of the garbage
that's out there that's over and over
again in the experts books of today that
are unbelievable just recycled junk over
and over again belief systems and so
forth I would I would definitely want to
hear so that's just me maybe you maybe
you who tuned in the radio show you're
not interested but I'd be interested
100% And I'd be interested to know about
blood pressure cuz that's where we're
going now so here we are let's get
started with this how do we get high
blood pressure let's talk about that
first because you know that that's just
that's important to know how do we get
high blood pressure bad lifestyle we
don't exercise so we don't exercise we
have a bad lifestyle or something or not
a healthy lifestyle we're eating too
much processed food right and we start
getting high blood pressure doctor says
look you got to you got to be careful
here you got to reduce your red meat I
don't know if doctors are saying that
anymore they're probably all pro pro red
meat eat more red meat that's where they
are now I think that's where it's
shifting it's shifting now where all the
medical doctors are like no matter what
they are whether they're functional or
regular conventional they're like no you
got to eat more meat you just got to get
rid of all fruit you know like fruit is
the cause of high blood pressure like
fruit like
fruit like fruit is the cause of high
blood pressure yeah okay I I'll buy that
one you know but just like doctors are
like you know at least they had
something right a few years back I think
it was about 10 years ago I think it was
about 10 years ago um 10 12 15 years ago
doctors like you know when people were
having when they were having coming in
with heart problems and or or high blood
pressure and they were coming into the
doctor's office they'd be like you got
to lower your red meat and this was
coming from conventional doctors I
remember that day when it was happening
and I was like finally something is
going right in the industries
finally something is going right and
guess what now you don't hear that it's
now it's just like no you need to eat
more red meat but grass-fed that's all
and you need to get rid of all your
sugar so don't eat any
fruit listen the whole the whole thing
that happens with blood pressure to
begin with comes from an organ in the
body and it's not the heart it comes
from it it deres es from an organ the
problem can you guess what that organ is
you know what that organ is you know
what it is are you thinking are you
thinking brain is that what you're
thinking about what you're thinking
pancreas maybe you're thinking colon
maybe you're thinking gut maybe you're
thinking kidneys you know and well
kidneys has a little something to do
with it if you have kidney problems you
can get blood pressure problems but
there's a reason why you would get
kidney problems to begin with and what's
that organ what is it you guys remember
I might have talked about this before in
an old show or something like that it's
the liver the liver the liver that's the
organ interesting right
interesting the liver is responsible
it's responsible for all mystery high
blood
pressure and mystery low blood
pressure mystery high blood pressure
mystery low blood pressure
so in the high blood pressure Department
how does this work what even happens
what goes on first of all your heart
your heart it gets its blood from where
where does your heart get its blood from
uh just the blood
system from where does it get the blood
from you know when you think about it
it's like I don't know like where does
it it gets it from your liver that's
where your heart gets its blood
from your liver has these hepatic portal
highways hepatic portal highways that's
what it is got the hepatic portal vein
comes from your colon drives up all
those nutrients so when you're eating
food your food breaks down miraculously
mysteriously inside your intestinal
tract and then nutrients along with
blood also
like up amazing nutrients a little bit
of oxygen all go up through these
capillaries and blood vessels and find
their way up the her hepatic
vein hepatic vein in the portal system
these are all the veins attached to your
colon and intestinal tract and
Elum all these veins and these veins
where do they lead into a highway a
massive Highway a massive Highway going
into your liver
your
liver and so these veins are drawn
blood's being sucked up sucked up these
veins that's right that's right your
heart's pumping and creating
suction so your heart's pumping and
creating suction so you see what I'm you
see where I'm going here so it's as it's
as it's creating suction it's drawing
blood up these veins up the portal
hepatic portal Highway the veins heading
into the
liver so you with me and those veins
heading up to the liver they're all
filled with
blood blood that the heart's pumping and
drawing and creating
suction and what's that blood filled
with I know I told you a little bit a
couple minutes ago I just want to make
sure you're on this with me filled with
lots and lots of nutrients
phytochemicals vitamins minerals trace
minerals
oxygen and water and water water so all
that's being drawn up in that Highway of
blood goes into your
liver and a healthy liver is all happy
and it's taking all this healthy blood
in and a healthy liver is all happy it's
taking all this healthy blood in and
it's taking all this healthy blood in
and then and then it releases that blood
actually after it filters it it filters
it and it's dispersing all the nutrients
and everything they're going in all the
right places in the liver and the liver
is taking care of everything and the
blood then exits it exits the liver and
guess where it goes It goes to your
heart it goes to your
heart
interesting
interesting it's all packaged ready and
happy going to the
heart but guess what goes wrong guess
what goes wrong guess what I didn't
mention is in that blood and the hepatic
in the hepatic veins heading from the
colon to the liver to begin with
remember I'll go back a little ways
let's go back a couple of minutes
remember what how I said there's water
in that blood there's nutrients there's
phytochemicals there's minerals there's
trace minerals there's vitamins and
oxygen all coming in guess what else is
in that blood poison poison toxic
poisons fat also fat cells from putrid
fat from eating too much too much too
much red meat lots of toxins and
poisons heavy metals solvents for
Malahide okay
everything everything
chlorine all right from Water Systems
everything's going in
there I mean it's a Flor
all of it is just going in that Highway
up to the liver lots and lots of Gunk
and poison toxins and
debris so even though that blood is
filled with all this good stuff liquid
is filled with too all this bad stuff
and guess what the liver has to collect
it filter it collect it filter it
collect it filter it collect it and
filter it and if we're not eating right
and we're not taking care of ourselves
and we're not doing the right things or
the liver's already burdened and already
held back from poisons and toxins it
inherited from birth and Beyond where
you it's inherited all the toxins the
old DDT you know the unforgiving for who
has life-changing Foods who has
life-changing Foods my book
life-changing foods do you guys have it
if anyone said I don't have
it if anyone says I don't have it I'll
just smack myself in the head or I'll
bang my head on my desk right now let me
just do that let me just hit my head or
bang it against the wall
because you're missing out I didn't I
didn't kill
myself to take all the information from
Spirit and put it in life-changing food
so you so you wouldn't get the book
because in that book has the unforgiving
four because in that Highway of
nastiness the blood toxicity along with
all that good I mentioned that's heading
up to the liver up the hepatic portal
highway coming from the colon heading
all the way up to the liver all that
toxic and poisonous stuff is the
unforgiving for it's old DDT that was
inside the liver to begin with it's
pesticides and herbicides that are
actually now in our all in our you know
way now that we deal with every day
going up the blood oh going right in the
bloodstream there's all of that there's
also bacteria viral issues issues viral
byproduct all that stuff and even a
little radiation all that is going up
the hepatic portal
Highway and it gets into the liver if
the liver doesn't already have it in
there already to begin with and as this
goes into the liver and it saturates the
liver and saturates the liver the liver
starts getting doggish and the Heart
relying on clean blood clean mean
machine
blood the heart relying on
it is pumping harder and
harder because the filter is getting
thicker dirtier stagnant more sluggish
more doggish and when that and when that
livers get getting filled with more and
more of that stuff and we're not eating
right and and
instead instead we you know we we head
off to a high trendy high fat diet of
the day the flavor of the day that you
see on say a doctor show or you see out
there and you see some fancy new diet
fancy new book or something and we head
to that direction and we quit the
processed foods we start exercising we
may help the liver a little
bit but a little bit isn't enough
it isn't enough because it'll sneak up
on you and it'll bite you in the butt
later it'll sneak up on you and bite you
in the butt and you'll get that high
blood pressure down the road or you'll
get that low blood pressure or you'll
get a blood pressure problem one way or
another down the
road down the
road and you'll get that well that will
happen even on you know a fancy cute
diet because it's not addressing the
real problem
and the the liver still getting dirty
along the way and still getting flooded
with poisons and still get it FL getting
flooded with
toxins so we're going to cover all that
a little bit about what foods to do for
high blood pressure what we can eat what
we can do to knock high blood pressure
down and what we can do to stabilize
blood pressure this is this is exciting
this is an exciting one so what happens
is when that liver gets filled and toxic
and stagnant and sluggish and doggish
and filled with poisons what happen
happens you guys is the heart has to
pump harder and harder and harder and
the
blood the blood isn't easy to come out
of the liver it's not easy it's not free
flowing out of the liver so easy so
there's pressure the suction occurs more
suction has to happen it's like sipping
through a straw instead of sipping water
through a straw you're
sipping something else through a straw
you're sipping like a
milkshake thick
milkshake or then you're then you're
sipping Jello-O through a
straw how about that one trying to sip
sip Jello-O through a straw and so
that's what
occurs and what happens is your liver
gets it gets dirty it's gets sluggish it
gets sick and then your blood gets dirty
and gets thick and your blood becomes
dirty and thick and then you're eating
more High fats more High fats whatever
diet you believe in whatever belief
system you've been sucked into you're
eating a higher fat diet without
realizing it even if you're doing
plant-based high fat even if you're
doing Paleo High fat or some autoimmune
high fat whatever you choose you're
doing you think it's high protein but
it's all high fat and you're doing more
high fat and what's happening is your
blood's getting more dehydrated thicker
and thicker and thicker unless you
unless you're doing things to offset the
high fat diet a lot more juicing a
little a little less red meat and then
you know it won't get so thick but if
you're not it's still going to get thick
in the end it's still going to get thick
in the end like I said like I said 10 15
years ago and I think it was probably 15
years ago now time's Flying Too Fast
remember the doctors being like no keep
that red meat down you got to watch that
high blood pressure keep the red meat
down it was
brilliant brilliant absolutely brilliant
but those days are gone that smartness
smartness
that that goodness and smartness was
only there for a hot second and then
it's gone now every single doctor on the
planet's like no no no animal protein no
sugar animal protein no
sugar I'm not saying I have anything
against animal protein I'm just saying
if you're dealing with high blood
pressure or something you might want to
switch up your game for a little while
in your life and not have to be so stuck
into a belief system
because belief systems will break you
down not break you down they'll get you
in the end because the belief system
itself won't be looking out for you and
you'll get cheated shorted and you'll
get the the the bad end of this the
whole bad end of it all because belief
systems don't believe in
you belief systems don't protect you and
don't care about you in the end
and belief systems just can't they just
don't
so so what happens how do we get that
high blood pressure without having heart
disease or cardiovascular disease or
anything like that how do we get it the
liver starts getting Mucky dirty
sluggish doggish
stagnant The Blood starts getting
thicker and thicker and thicker and then
the heart's working harder to pump blood
through a straw thick milkshake blood
through a straw
and that's what happens and if you're
vegetarian hey I don't eat red meat I'm
a
vegetarian and that look I that's cool
you're vegetarian but if you're eating
cheese clogging up that liver thickening
up the
blood and the heart has to pump through
a straw like that that that thick
milkshake through a straw versus water
through a straw it has to pull blood
through those
veins thick heavy blood fill the cheese
mucus mucus cheese Dairy
butter the butter thing out of control
is it Butter's good for us oh dear Lord
oh my God Trend fat fads and
Trends you got to laugh a little bit you
can't get too upset about it all even
though people's lives are always you
know involved and at risk and you know
people sufferings involved but you can't
you can't you can't these Trends you
can't let these Trends make you too
crazy you have to kind of laugh about it
a little bit the butter thing so so when
you're thinking about putting butter in
your in your drink in the morning in
your hot drink in the morning or you're
thinking about you know whatever
thinking it's healthy just think again
because your liver doesn't like it and
your heart's not going to like it and if
you're young and you don't have high
blood pressure and you want to have
butter and you want to live in the
moment okay but you know what remember
the show 20 years from
now remember the show 20 years from now
when you're
40 remember the show 20 years from now
when you're 50 okay so here's the
deal it's not just about cleaning up the
liver or anything like that it's about
getting the diet right so the heart
doesn't have to pump so hard look if you
don't have high blood pressure or if you
don't have a blood pressure problem at
all then don't even D just okay fine you
don't have to worry just move on but you
should listen to it and you should learn
cuz it's important it is important so
you can look out for a loved one or look
out for yourself in the
future so when that blood gets thick and
pasty and
dehydrated and the heart has to work
harder it strains the heart it strains
it and it causes veins to have such a
suction to it that the veins they
tighten up they tighten up they don't
collapse in but they they
constrict they constrict because of the
suction the pole so the veins constrict
makes it even more
difficult and less oxygen even gets to
the liver which in turn less oxygen gets
to the heart gets to the
heart something to be cons something to
understand something to consider
something to know the heart wants free
and clear fresh clean blood
hydrated the right water content
content the right minerals the right
nutrients it wants blood that's like a
waterfall in the Amazon that you would
that you would dream of you know you
would dream of of being in that water
while the water's coming down even
though there's serpents in that water
like some dangerous snakes down there
and out there in the Amazon like the
fertil an snake the fertil an thing F
you you're
dead man you just you know people they
go on these trips and they go into the
Amazon and they go to South America or
they go in other places around the world
and and you know in different different
different areas of the world and they
want to be playing in that nice little
swimming hole with that water coming
down and all those Vines going around
you get bit by a ferti an snake man it
happens all the
time yeah I know I'm a downer I'm a
downer
but I'm all about looking out for you
I'm all about looking out for you okay
so the heart wants us clean blood
because it has to work harder when it
works harder you get a elevated blood
pressure doctor looks at you there's no
cardiovascular disease diagnoses you
with hypertension so you get diagnosed
as you know
hypertension if you ask the doctor why
is it the doctor says well I don't know
your diet's not so bad I don't see any
cardiovascular problems maybe you just
need to exercise get your diet a little
bit better maybe do a little bit more
high protein which is wrong
but maybe do a little high protein knock
out the sugar well yeah knock out the
sugar is right not the fruit not the
sweet potatoes not the yams not the
winter squash not the regular potatoes
you don't knock any of that out that's
just blatant stupidity in the world of
Trends right now trendy junk science
trendy junk science someone said to me
and said wait a minute here your books
are filled with science
I said ' huh and somebody said your
books are filled with science all your
books it's just it's all
science I go it's all from Spirit it's
undiscovered science and they go okay
wait a minute but it's not it's not like
peer-reviewed science I go why would I
want that that's junk science I don't
want my books filled with junk science
no one would have gotten better or maybe
a handful got better and then I would
have to heral Herald them as as the the
poster the poster people
because you know what it's there's a
difference when you get tens of
thousands of people better and healed
and better from your books than just
getting a few and then trying to exalt
that and and use that as your poster
board I said you know yeah no it's not
fill the junk I don't want junk science
in there it's from
Spirit yeah there's a big difference big
difference so what happens is when
you're told that you need more high
protein and to avoid fruit and avoid
fruit and sweet potato Poes and avoid
yams and avoid regular potatoes and
avoid other things like this and avoid
raw honey when you're told to avoid all
those
things because of junk science it is
junk science you see how it works I mean
because you're not supposed to avoid
apples you're not supposed to avoid all
the different good fruits you're not
supposed to avoid bananas no you're not
it's the greatest food to keep your
blood clean it's the greatest food for
the heart guess what your heart is do
you know what your heart is
your heart is a muscle it's a muscle
guess what a muscle needs a carbohydrate
you know what happens if we starve a
muscle of sugar it dies it atrophies if
you starve a muscle of sugar it
atrophies did you know I have seen
people over the years go on a no sugar
diet completely no sugar at all nothing
at all no sugar at all these were a lot
of bad trendy diets that were no sugar
at all not even a berry put in there not
even an apple Apple put in there not
even a green apple did you know their
hearts atrophied because they're on
animal protein only and a few assorted
vegetables and they didn't get enough
carbohydrate to their heart and their
brain their heart though being a muscle
atrophied so they atrophied their hearts
they atrophied their hearts on the
trendy trendy high protein no sugar diet
their hearts atrophied because their
hearts are a muscle and they require a
lot of carbohydrate a tremendous amount
of carbohydrate in
Sugar you take a carbohydrate away from
a marathon runner put a marathon runner
on high protein in a few vegetables and
never give them one single gram of sugar
put a put a marathon runner on that
we'll see how good his game goes or her
game goes be a
disaster but what happens is protein
bars are filled with sugar no one
realizes that they're filled with sugar
so when you're eating protein bars
you're getting sugar so at least you can
run your Marathon because you got sugar
going in you even if you're told to stay
off of all sugar it's just
bizarre your heart has to have a
carbohydrate every cell in the heart a
sugar has to enter it in order to keep
it alive thriving and non-
atrophying you have to remember that
that's how critical it is your liers
filled the glucose it stores the
glycogen to keep you safe and keep your
adrenal safe if you don't eat the right
fruits and the right sweet potatoes and
if you want to be a raw dude if you want
to be a raw dude then you just do all
raw fruits raw fruits and lots of leafy
greens and vegetables and the whole bit
and you can do some nuts and seeds and
you can do things like that and all of
it you got to be careful you don't
overdo the nuts and seeds you want to be
vegetarian you got to do lots of fruits
you know I tell
vegetarians I tell vegetarians why don't
you you're already there why don't you
go
plant-based and and you know when I tell
animal I tell paleo people and high
animal protein people people there I say
look you're already now bringing in a
green juice for the first time you
because of because the trendy diet is
Shifting now because they the trendy
diets right now are stealing from the
alternative model it's hilarious to see
it from standing away from it you guys
might not see it because it you know I I
could stand away from it and see it
because I don't hold the belief system
and a lot of people they hold the belief
system and what happens is the belief
system blinds them so they can't stand
away from it I can stand away and see
that the conventional movement in the
diet world all the experts now they
robbed and theft it and
stole alternative things that were
critical to Healing people so
alternative movement healed a lot of
people over the years too I mean there's
a lot of people that healed a lot of
great alternative stuff and one of the
reasons why what healed them was a lot
of the juicing a lot of the vegetables a
lot of leafy greens and fruits and stuff
like that and that you know a lot of the
plant-based
movement that did a lot for people
people so what happened was the animal
protein people in The Last 5 Years the
experts putting out their books now they
they're robbing and thefting those green
juices they're incorporating them into
their their trendy high-fat diets and
they're noticing people are getting a
little bit better so what I tell is that
you know I tell the Paleo crowd the high
protein crowd you're already there you
got now the green juice in there Bravo
you got the green juice in there now and
you got more leafy greens in there now
just lower the animal protein a little
bit more for your liver and your heart
you can still keep your animal proteins
in there if you really want but just
lower them down a little bit and I tell
the vegetarians look you're already
there get rid of the cheese you're
already you're almost plant-based get
rid of the cheese you don't eat red meat
get rid of the cheese and get rid of the
eggs and they're like I don't know
they're like no you know Mr William I
don't know I I don't know if I could do
that I go what do you mean you're all
you're already
there why are you going to Gunk Gunk up
your liver and Gunk up your heart with
all that cheese and all that milk and
all those eggs you're already there you
should be going plant-based if that's
where you want to go and the high
protein people look you're already there
the high protein paleo people you
already got in you're already getting in
the juices you're already getting in
more leafy greens and and and more
berries and more berries in a green
apple why don't you bring in a little
bit more of that and just lower your
animal protein a little bit do it once a
day so you can save your liver and your
heart when you step back and you don't
have a belief system you know what you
can do for people and you know what's
right because you know when you don't
have that belief system you can you can
navigate you can
navigate and that's the gift Spirit gave
me you know Spirit told me when I was
younger Spirit was like you're going to
be able to navigate I'm going to give
you the information you're going to be
able to
navigate and I love that so all right so
here's the deal the heart's a muscle it
needs a carbohydrate you got to be
cautious you can't high fat your blood
with so much fat that means if you're
plant-based you can't be doing nutcakes
and nut pies 247 you got to be doing
lots of fruit plant-based and lots of
leafy greens when you're plant-based you
could still have some hem seeds and some
walnuts and you can still do what you
want to do there you have some avocado
of course you can but you got to keep
your fats low like I said with the VAR
vegetarians just get rid of the eggs and
dairy like I said with the high high
protein people limit it to one protein
or something and go every other day with
an animal protein in this way you can
get your blood less fatty your heart
works less hard your liver works less
hard your blood gets cleaner it gets
more hydrated it gets a better quality
of blood going in there oxygen rises in
the blood when the blood's rushing to
the liver through the hepatic portal
vein it's alive it's got less poisons
and toxins in it it's got more water
molecules and it has more of everything
oxygen included it goes to the liver the
liver starts to heal the heart works
less and all the fruits you're adding
into your diet and the sweet potatoes
and the winter squash and even the
regular potatoes you're adding into your
diet with your leafy greens and
everything else you're doing gets your
heart to get that precious glycogen
storage the glucose I mean glucose into
the cells of the heart the liver has the
glycogen storage the heart gets cells
gets sugar right directly into every
cell and the Heart Won't atrophy and it
stays strong so when it has to work hard
and pump thick nasty blood it doesn't
weaken it stays strong too that's
another thing and then you start you
you'll see the blood pressure go down
the doctor be like I don't know why your
blood your blood pressure went down
let's take you off the medication well
you you need less blood pressure
medication and less or don't even use
the blood pressure medication let's just
see where we're going it's getting
better and better and
better what's going on Mr Jones are you
exercising and and eating more red meat
no what I'm doing is cleaning up my
blood getting my liver a little better
and giving my heart a
break and you get better and that's the
mystery of high blood
pressure that's the mystery high blood
pressure celery juice is a miracle for
blood pressure I know that there's a lot
of people that are worried about ah my
blood pressure is too low I can't drink
celery juice my blood pressure is too
low can't drink it I can't drink it not
true Did You Know that celery juice
balances blood pressure balances no one
knows this once again because of trendy
Miss information or recycled theories
going around out there no one has it
right is why I read the that's why I
read the beginning of the show like I do
and I say what I do I probably drives
you crazy when I do that in front of
every show there's a reason cuz no one
has it right it's
painful it's pain
painful to see it celery juice is a
blood stabilizer balancer it's
adaptogenic for the body what happens is
if your blood pressure is low celery
juice can raise it if your blood
pressure is high celery juice can lower
it see just just just walk this walk
through this with me I know because a
lot of people who have low blood
pressure they're they're totally
paranoid about the
celery and then you know what they'll go
and eat something
ridiculous they'll eat
eggs me they'll eat eggs I see it all
the time I mean I even see it on social
media I see it all the time out there
it's like no no I can't do celery juice
I got low BL low blood pressure and they
got they eat two eggs that
[Laughter]
day
seriously all right so anyway so I got
to walk through it with you again the
celery juice raises blood pressure when
it's low it it St it's a
stabilizer because what happens with low
blood pressure people they have a
different problem with their liver they
have a whole entire different problem if
they don't have a leak somewhere if they
don't have a valve leak if they don't
have a ventricle leak if they don't have
something like that going on and a
doctor I mean we're talking about low
blood pressure I'm talking about low
blood pressure and a doctor that ran
every test in the book can't find a
physical physical aspect to why they
have low blood pressure so they have to
come up with all these autoimmune
theories or the body's just confused or
you're it's genetic you know maybe
somebody in your ancestry had low blood
pressure they have to come up with all
that crap that junk science feeds
doctors so doctors have some kind of
answer and so all that
involved all that
involved and then you know what happens
there massive confusion and so when
someone someone has this kind of low
blood pressure they don't know where to
go what is it what really does this
what's happening what they have going on
is a whole different problem they got a
viral issue that's a viral issue low
blood pressure people have a viral issue
that's what they do and they have a
little bit of an adrenal dysfunction
along with it even if they don't have
the fat fatigue they have a little bit
of an adrenal
function issue and they're they're and
they have a viral issue too that's what
low blood pressure people have and it's
a
virus and that that's what happens there
so this is what happens when you have a
low-grade virus a lot of people have
different varieties of lowgrade viruses
and there's nothing wrong with that
perfectly fine perfectly fine there's
nothing wrong with that but a few things
occur as the virus releases certain
types of poisons and certain types of
poisons are recognized by the
body the
heart does something a little different
because the heart doesn't want to be
pumping lots and lots of poison really
hard and fast throughout the body so the
brain gets saturated with
it so the body's communicating with self
the brain's communicating with the heart
the liver's communicating with the heart
the brain's communicating with the liver
they're all communicating together and
even the thyroids communicating with all
that so with all that together
communicating low blood pressure occurs
because of a toxic load a toxic load
that the body's being systematically
cautious
about that means that if the if if if
the heart for instance somebody with low
blood pressure if they exercise the
people with low blood pressure usually
have other symptoms develop or they had
symptoms before their low blood blood
low blood pressure and they're dealing
with lowgrade problems low grade
symptoms fatigue a little bit of fatigue
they're dealing with things where they
they if they exercise they're they're
like wasted for a few days they don't
feel good all these kinds of different
things happen with people at low blood
pressure then they get diagnosed with
all these different things they can get
diagnosed with dis with dis aonia dis
aonia you and that's a whole thing that
can happen too they can get diagnosed
with different varieties of that you
know pots whatever they can get they the
whole thing with blood pressure but it's
viral it's 100% viral and sometimes
adrenals get underactive because of the
viral issue sometimes the virus is
sitting in the liver that's usually
where it sits it doesn't mean the liver
is so clogged or so toxic where the
heart has to work harder it's just that
there's communication within the body
the brain the heart liver thyroid the
adrenals just communication going on
through the whole body and is the
low-grade virus you get the low this is
the same thing with people that get real
low temperatures they got a low grade
virus
so you gets people that are like oh my
God I'm actually
95.9 de I'm not 86 I am not
88.6 88.6 I'm not 98.6 sorry about that
you
[Laughter]
guys I'm not 98.6 degrees I'm
96.4
degrees how is that possible that's what
people that people they all freak out
when they get their when they finally
take their temperatures or they the
doctor takes their temperature and the
doctor's like doctor's office like
you're 96.7 de you're supposed to be
98.6 first of all not everybody's
supposed to be
98.6 a lot of people are supposed to be
97 in the 97s I'm just telling you right
now but there's people that they're
literally in the
96s and because of that that's a low
that's a low grade viral infection
there's no fever but that's a low- grade
viral infection that's what that that is
inside the liver and inside the body
it's the same thing with the low blood
pressure the mystery low blood pressure
I'm not talking about an actual real
physical condition discovered by the
doctors talking about mystery low blood
pressure there there's a low-grade virus
causing that too it's very similar most
people with the mystery low blood
pressure have a very low temperature
especially in the
morning in the morning and even at night
even at night too or in the middle of
the day you can do I've seen it in the
middle of the day people's temperatures
drop seen it in the morning right when
they get up their temperature drop
seeing it even at the end of the day or
the evening which usually is when it
goes up for the most part but it's
usually I guess morning and and
afternoon and there's a lowgrade viral
thing going on in the system and there's
a communication going on with the whole
body because what happens is if if that
if that Blood starts rushing with
because the body's on alert it's on
alert if the blood starts rushing it you
know it the body's concerned about
poisons and toxins going into certain
places like the brain the liver is
concerned it's going to go to the BL
brain organs have communicate first of
all have to know this organs communicate
they communicate with each other and
they have high intelligence level
extremely high intelligence level
intelligence we can't even think about
or understand or know about science of
research has no idea how the liver
communicates with the brain how the
brain communicates with the liver how it
works how the heart communicates there's
communication going on all the time it's
not just the brain's giving orders
through nerves and making nerve function
happen and making organs do with their
that's not it at all it's way more than
that if we think it's not more than that
then we're just ridiculous because it's
way more than that we're in just Deni if
we don't if we don't know
that and so that's another that's
another thing that happens plus you can
have somebody with different kinds of um
low-grade viral issues and they'll have
their adrenals will be really
underactive they'll have underactive
adrenals that that itself will cause low
blood pressure underactive
adrenals that itself so when you have
underactive adrenals you have a viral
situation in the body you can you can
get the low blood
pressure so that that all that that's
these are just some of the reasons for
low blood
pressure also there's a lot of people
that are supposed to have lower blood
pressure there's there's a lot of people
out there that are supposed to have
lower low not super low not super low
but they're supposed to be their blood
pressure is supposed to be
lower it's who they are it's just it's
it's natural and guess what it's not a
bad thing it's just when you go past the
limitations of low and you're in another
another level of low that's when there's
this low-grade viral infection you can
be in a normal low blood pressure where
it's actually healthy and good and and
and but yet a little extra
low and and there's nothing wrong with
that also another thing to understand
someone with low blood pressure in the
super low Zone With lowgrade viral stuff
it doesn't hurt the heart it doesn't
hurt the heart
and and and really it honestly when you
work on cleaning up the viral stuff and
you work on cleaning up the liver and
you work on cleaning up your body and
healing you
know people with low low low low blood
PR blood pressure have the Epstein bar
virus they have the Epstein bar virus
but they have they it's a certain
variety of Epstein
bar and so that's that's a big part of
that but once you heal and move forward
that that that blood pressure will come
up and it'll come up and you'll get it a
little better and a little better a
little better you can't be afraid of
celery juice CU you got low blood
pressure low celery juice will help lift
it
up will help lift it up so that's just a
massive confusion right there so what do
we do let's just go with the m first of
all let's talk about the we'll talk
about the mystery the mystery high blood
pressure got to lower your fats and you
got to ease the burden off your liver so
that's one thing got to lower your fats
and ease the burden off your liver so
that's really important it's stopping
your blood from being so thick not
letting your blood get so thick and and
dirty and that's what you have to do so
you already know the diet whole thing
with the diet with you know with a diet
with the uh if you want to be animal
protein you got to bring it down to one
you know one serving a day or every
other day you can still be an animal
protein person just bring in more of all
the other things I talked about more of
the fruits the vegetables can't be
afraid of all the different fruits
they're all there for a reason don't
walk past the fruit section because
you're being told somewhere that it's
not it's not good for you you can you
can eat some oranges there's no reason
why you can't get an orange I mean it's
longevity food that's what it is you're
passing the longevity section of the
market when you go past the produce
aisle you're P meaning you're passing
the fruit section then that means you're
passing the longevity section that's
that's literally a decision you're
making because of trendy Mis you know
Mis Mis guided information so you're
you're walking past that aisle you just
you don't want to just grab a pint of
berries you want to go into that aisle
and you want to grab your oranges you
want to grab a bunch of apples you want
to grab a few pears you better believe
it you want to grab um a melon you want
to see if they can have some
mangoes you want to make grab some kiwis
grab some kiwis you want to make sure
hey if you love pineapple get a
pineapple but you want want to get into
that aisle and you want to start
learning about it more and grabbing
those foods and then you can go to the
the vegetable aisle and you grab the you
got the celery going because you got to
get the celery juices for high blood
pressure it's great for the it's it's
honestly it's like a liver cure that's
the celery juice is and so you want to
go you want to go get the celery juice
pick up some cucumbers for cucumber
juice too you can do that you know you
can that would be amazing grab your
spinach in the aisle why not grab more
spinach CU you can do spinach salads get
a couple of avocados absolutely get a
couple of
avocados definitely have a big spinach
salad throw an avocado in it that would
be better than a salad with two eggs in
it hard-boiled eggs in it I promise you
that having that avocado in that salad
would be a th million times better than
having two eggs in there two heart
killing eggs to I you know I love where
it's like all of a sudden you know an
egg is a perfect food and it's it's got
all these Omega-3s and it's heart
healthy I I've never seen anything so
demented in my life because it's not
it's not don't get fooled by that unless
it's the only food you got yes there's
some nutrients and eggs yeah there's
some vitamins and eggs yeah there's
there's in some eggs there's an omega-3
in there yeah in the healthier eggs of
course but that's nothing that's nothing
compared to what an avocado has and it's
nothing compared to juicing celery juice
has nothing compared to sweet potatoes
have I mean they haven't even tapped
into what's in a sweet potato yet
because no one wants to spend the money
research and science doesn't want to
know what's in a sweet potato cuz it's
going to make people buy more of
them and then you know what they're
going to see doctors less and women are
going to see doctors less because
they're eating their sweet potatoes said
they don't want the research of science
doesn't want you eating sweet potatoes
no
way why why why would they want you to
do that so you know it's about lowering
your fats though at the same time so
that means you could still do some
healthy fats like the avocado some hem
seeds some some walnuts and stuff like
throw walnuts in a salad absolutely you
can still do these have a little bit of
olive oil if you really
want but just don't overdo it don't
overdo it and get more of the fresh
fruits and vegetables and you're you'll
see your high blood pressure come down
you'll see it come down you really will
get on some magnesium I think that would
be great for you get on some magnesium
without a doubt I like the Magnesium
glycinate I feel like it works really
good I know it works Spirit tells me it
works I've given it to people over the
years I like magnesium glycinate that
that one works natural Cal is okay you
know that's all right just make sure you
pour hot water into the cup when you put
a teaspoon of natural c in there or two
teaspoons of natural C make sure you
pour you know really like you were going
to make a hot cup of tea you pour the
water in there because by doing that it
uh it it it really activates it the
right way makes it better so if you
really need to do something like that
you can so that's great now that's great
nettle Leaf is a great one circumin is
great for for for taking care of CoQ10 I
like that one too circumin is a great
one lots of turmeric that's a great one
tumeric Ginger shots are great for
lowering blood pressure and turmeric
ginger shots are great for raising blood
pressure for people with low blood
pressure because they're number one
they're antiviral number two they help
they help with the adrenals too A lot of
people with the low blood pressure that
are that are viral the really low blood
pressure and they're viral they they
they all have a adrenal issues and
adrenal dysfunction adrenal adrenal
issues those people with low blood
pressure you might want to consider
doing ashwagandha that would be really
good you might even want to consider
doing licorice I think licorice would be
fantastic for the people with low blood
pressure I mean talk to your doctor talk
to your practitioner about it but I
would do licorice root you could do
licorice tea every single day or go to
my directory at Medical medium.com and
get the right licorice
tincture the one without
alcohol which is a bon IED mess that
alcohols in tinctures that's that's just
that's terrible that's terrible it's
travesty all on its own so make sure
that you you know you get the licorish
root you can do licorice root tea people
with low blood pressure licorice root
tea you can do that all right that's
great nettle leaf tea that's also pretty
good but the licorice root is great so
consider that and and then the
ashwaganda get your adrenal see the
licorish and the ashwaganda are going to
help somebody with low blood pressure
with the adrenal problems causing part
of the low pressure being so low it's
also going to help with the viruses too
licorice help with the virus will help
with the viruses somebody with low blood
pressure and then get your diet's right
no cheese no Dairy no milk no butter no
eggs be
cautious keep your animal proteins low
if you're an anal protein lover if
you're a vegan keep the keep all the nut
pies a little lower keep them lower
bring in more fresh fruits and leafy
greens more celery juice and you'll get
the blood pressure up you'll get the
blood pressure up people who worry about
the blood pressure going down from
celery juice no you go get it up but you
you can't just do a celery juice and not
eat that day or that morning you can't
you have to eat too people with low
blood pressure have to eat every hour
and a half you have to eat something
every hour and a half you have to snack
and graze whether it's celery sticks and
apple slices whether it's apple slices
and dates whether it's you know a piece
of fruit and some and you know whatever
whether it's Apples by themselves you
have to to snack whether it's a handful
of nuts whether it's a handful of hem
seeds and an apple you have to snack and
graze if you have low blood pressure you
can't just go hours without food because
you know what's going to happen your
blood pressure is going to drop lower
and lower and lower and then when you
drink your celery juice and it's the
only thing you had that day you're going
to be like I I told you it would drop my
my blow it would make my lip blood
pressure lower I I knew it I knew I
should have drank this celery juice no
it's not how it works the celery juice
is there to balance it and bring it up
but you got to eat and I noticed low
blood pressure people they don't eat
much at all they eat like birds even
though birds eat a lot they eat like
birds and and and you know that's what
I've noticed like literally like like a
little handful of food throughout the
day and they're at their practitioner's
office and their practitioner like well
I think you got sibo no I think you will
you know got this I got that and we're
going to have to get you just done
chicken you'll be on chicken twice a day
only eat twice a day and just eat
chicken and and this little tiny thing
of collared
greens yeah it's terrible you got to get
lots of fruits lots of vegetables lots
of other leafy greens in you you got to
do that kind of thing potatoes are
really good for somebody with low blood
pressure and they're also good with
somebody with high blood pressure too
remember that so these are all the
techniques and tricks you can do tricks
tricks to heal this
situation high blood pressure like I
said the Magnesium everybody knows that
magnesium for high blood pressure I'm
not giving you anything new on that but
make sure you know the the Magnesium
glycin Ator really like but but like I
said before make sure you're doing the
cumin the coenzyme Q10 the turmeric even
the ginger shots that's great for high
blood pressure and great for low blood
pressure make sure that's all in there
nettle Leaf that's great licorice root
ashwaganda for low blood pressure people
talk to your doctor if you're on a bunch
of medications okay if you're on a bunch
of medications you're on 5 10
medications whatever it is talk to your
doctor tell them about these things and
see what they want to
do that's what I would do
and then um but you got a you got a good
idea of how it works and what's going on
high blood pressure is a cinch to get
rid of a cinch change your diet around
just make make make your blood cleaner
get it more oxygen hydrate lots of lemon
water lemon water for the high blood
pressure people lemon water just boom
lemon water every single day celery
juice every single day do the foods I
was talking about and your your high
blood pressure will be coming down it'll
be coming down and if you exercise take
walks or whatever you do all that's
great so honestly it's pretty simplistic
pretty simplistic thanks for being on
the show with me this time I thought
hope you guys had a good time I try my
best I try my best to deliver the
information and also deliver it in a
happy way so that you guys stay happy
too take one day at a time pat yourself
on the back be easy on yourself don't be
so down on every don't be on down on
yourself a lot of people when they get
sick and they have struggles they
they're so hard on themselves it's so
sad to see that pat yourself you're a
good person remember that never forget
that I stand behind you I believe in you
I love you guys God bless you all right
take care