body pain back pain
you know the thing is with the back a
lot of people have sciatica they've got
the sciatic nerve pain
they're in pain all the time they're
walking around aching and everything and
the problem is with backs
is that
it's not just about seeing a
chiropractor which is fine you can see a
chiropractor if somebody wants they can
get massage if somebody wants
they can get back surgery if somebody
wants right not that they always want
back surgery but a lot of people get
pushed into it the key is
why is it inflamed right is is it a
degenerative disc issue
right but here's the thing
a lot of people walk around and their
backs are shot
they got bulging discs degenerative disc
issues right spinal stenosis they get
all these kinds of issues going on with
their back
but they're not in any pain whatsoever
so they're not in any pain good to see
you guys coming on here they walk around
and they're fine and that's what's
confusing
probably to a lot of doctors out there
and a lot of chiropractors and a lot of
natural doctors holistic doctors
functional medicine doctors where
they're like why isn't something
happening here if they ever take a look
at somebody's lumbar somebody's lower
spine and they're like well they've got
a two bulging discs right and the
person's not hurting
and how does this happen
one reason is it takes more than a
pinched nerve to have pain and so many
people have pain
in their back right and that's just one
area in their back they have pain in
other places too good to see you guys
coming on talking about back problems
and body pain right specifically back
problems for a lot of people sciatic
acidic nerve pain
so
the thing is with nerve pain
inflammation
can take back problems to a whole other
level so its inflammatory issues can
take your back problem to a whole other
place
someone with a bulging disc if they're
not inflamed they won't have a problem
somebody
with a bulging disc that's inflamed will
have a problem and that's a big big
thing so many people get they get into
back surgery
so they have back surgery done
and it doesn't fix the problem and
they're confused like this it was
supposed to go away this was supposed to
no i was not supposed to have this
problem the doctor would be like well
you know we did your back surgery you
should be walking in three days you
should be all better and there they are
they're not better and they have these
back problems and it goes on for like a
year and two years and three years and
four years and it just keeps on going on
even after back surgery a lot of people
get repeated back surgery too so why is
this important because a lot of people
without realizing it right
have this nerve inflammation so the
nerves are inflamed in their back
and that's what they don't know so i
want to bring this over for a second too
okay
good to see you guys coming on here
we're talking about sciatic nerve pain
or back pain a lot of people have it
and you know a lot of people suffer from
it and the whole bit and it's something
that i don't talk about too often
because there's so many other problems
people have and so many other conditions
like brain conditions and everything
else right that we talk about but when
it comes down to back problems and
here if you're if you feel young if
you're young and you feel indestructible
you haven't had anything hit you yet you
just get a massage once in a while right
it's like who cares about your back and
then you pull out your back in a sense
like a back muscle if you work out too
hard or something like that you know and
then and a lot of people do that well
they'll just they'll pull a muscle out
i'm talking about when back problems
become this chronic illness problem this
chronic issue and that chronic issue
just doesn't go away and it stays there
forever and that's what we're we're on
right now so
it takes
inflammation of that nerve to really
make a back problem happen unless you
get a fracture or you get a break or you
got degenerative disease where the the
disc just crumbles and falls apart
completely falls apart and then now
you've got pressure on all the nerves
and that's a different situation but
most people out there right
they have nerve pain
okay and that nerve pain isn't because
of a bulging disc that nerve pain isn't
because of something else and that's
important to like degenerative disc
problems there's people out there their
backs are chewed up their backs are shot
their their vertebrae is is damaged in
so many ways but they're out there and
they're living their life they're like
doing this they're doing that they're
taking walks they're running on
treadmills they're living their life and
their backs are shot
but it's that one moment where
all you need
is that viral inflammation and the
minute you get that viral inflammation
you've got a lifetime of sciatica
sciatic nerve pain got a lifetime of
lower back problems and other places too
can happen in other areas as well in the
back okay we're live on facebook youtube
rumble telegram tick tock twitch and
getter so we're live on all those
platforms right now which i'm excited
about i haven't seen you guys in a while
it's good to see you guys
a dot m dot says aw amazon easter basket
was great today love the goodies of the
basket thank you for being there guys
check out that amazon live
i did with the easter baskets i put all
these easter baskets together and i made
some potato deviled potato bites which
were really good and the whole day
you know i got high on maple syrup you
know like the whole bit cotton candy i
had cotton candy in there it was really
great
it was fun you guys so check it out when
you get a chance and then you'll see the
link in the description
so
here we are talking about back problems
people have so what can we do about it
getting the inflammation down is
critical you guys if you want a good
back
and i mean that it's not just about
massage it's not just about you know
chiropractor adjustments it's not just
about any of that okay when you're when
your back's inflamed and i've seen this
a lot of times when your back is
inflamed because of inflammation caused
by a pathogen
everything changes everything changes
that's when you got chronic back
problems you can get massages once twice
a week you keep your chiropractor
adjustments right
you can try all these devices and you're
still dealing with sciatic nerve pains
attica you're dealing with problems in
the back problems in the lumbar so this
is important right now so what i what i
tell people friends and family
that have a back problem
okay they go to their doctor the doctor
checks out their back right they're like
well you got you've got a little bit of
a bulge in one disc or you're a little
degenerative at another disc right
where everything looks fine we don't
know why your back hurts and that's
another thing too
a lot of people everything checks fine
checks out fine in their back
everything checks out okay
but they don't know why they're in pain
they just don't know why their leg is
numb they don't know why their foot
hurts they don't know why they have pain
in the calf
they don't have any of that so that's
important to know
a lot of people
right will have pain in their knee
they'll have pain in their ankle pain
somewhere in their foot
and they'll get a diagnosis of like
plantar fasciitis they'll get some other
type of diagnosis right but really
what's happening the pain is coming from
their lower back and that's where it's
coming from so you can get pain in your
legs you can get numbness you can get
tingling in the legs you can get
problems in the legs and feet which can
lead to a different diagnosis meanwhile
the problem is inflammation with the
sciatic nerve in inflammation with the
tibial nerve inflammation with the lower
lumbar right the lumbar it could be
inflammation in you know l5 l4 l3 l2 l1
could be inflammation in all of those
and that's people will deal with that's
what they do they deal with this chronic
problem
any advice on degenerative discs so the
whole thing is what i'm trying to say is
that when you get your inflammation
down something changes
something changes i'm going to talk
about degenerative discs and bone
problems too with all that when you get
your inflammation down
i've seen even the worst backs
recover and get better debbie evans says
hello the celery juice took away my back
pain that's incredible because the
inflammation went down from the celery
juice alone i have r.a
and i used to have so many aching places
in my body you're on facebook debbie
evans amazing
well that's what happens is like celery
juice is one of the medical medium tools
right and it has an ability to change
people's lives even if they're just
doing that a lot of people they may need
more than that and there's a lot of
medical medium tools but the celery
juice is helping because it's knocking
down
viral inflammation so that's what it's
doing it's knocking down viral
inflammation now if celery juice doesn't
do the trick for a lot of people then
that's when a lot of other things have
to be thought about like one is
when you're dealing with back problems
you're dealing with nerves right
so that's when b12 is critical so that's
a big piece of how we keep our nerves
good it's through b12 that's another
example right there okay magnesium is a
good thing for for nerves and it's good
thing for problems like that but guess
what
when it's viral inflammation
then you're looking at things that are
anti-viral right where you're looking at
like lysine and you're looking at stuff
like that these things make a difference
p there's a lot of people with stubborn
back problems they just don't go away
and the stubborn back problems are
because they're dealing with viral
inflammation
a pathogen so it's critical to have the
right type of stuff the right kind of
stuff right and so
this is the vimergy stuff right here i'm
not sponsored but this is the vimergy
stuff that's the microc that's the
lysine because when you're dealing with
inflammation you're dealing with pain in
the body
and it's mysterious
then there's something going on immune
system problems along with pathogen
issues along with viral issues and you
know so we have to realize you got
immune system is low
uh pathogens are increasing so what's
the number one pathogen that gets in the
way when it comes to back problems the
number one pathogen that gets in the way
with the back problem you guys
is the shingles virus
that's the number one and you don't have
to have
shingles
to have that back pain okay
you don't have to see the shingles like
you don't have to see the pustules of
the shingles stripped across your chest
you're stripped across your back or
on your leg or on your butt or on your
thigh you don't even need to see the
shingles for it to cause problems the
shingles virus sits in everybody and it
can cause a problem one way or another
as time goes on so what happens is we're
living our life our immune system gets
knocked down it gets knocked down by
different things different problems that
we're up against our immune system gets
knocked down right
like betrayal and hardship and loss can
break down our immune system okay
foods that aren't good for us can break
down our immune system over time
and
these different things break down immune
system and then viruses like the
shingles can creep up and creep up but
when that virus creeps up it loves a
couple of different areas it loves the
trigeminal nerve it loves to be up here
in this area okay and it can cause
things like bell's palsy it can cause
things like trigeminal nerve pain that's
one thing shingles and another thing it
does
it can
actually more commonly too
it gets into the nerves in the lower
back so shingles can get into the nerves
and lower back another thing too
it's the big body pain causer for so
many people of course you can mess up
your back of course you can have pinched
nerves of course you can have a
vertebrae problem but guess what
if a viral issue is combined with that
vertebrae vertebrae problem if a viral
issue is combined with that pinched
nerve
if a viral issue like shingles is
combined with
that inflame that sorry that sciatic
nerve or tibial nerve when that virus is
involved it takes it
and it explodes it the impact is so much
more so now you've got sciatic problems
forever you've got problems with your
back forever it's like not a good day my
back's not doing good you know i'm gonna
go see somebody else from my back and
you have these problems that could be
long-lasting so what happens is if
someone has like neurological lyme or if
they have something like multiple
sclerosis or if they got lupus or they
got fibromyalgia it usually comes with
back pain too because you're dealing
with pathogens and when those pathogens
are up
they tend to cling onto nerves and the
lumbar is a place where the shingles
likes to cling on to that's a big area
that the shingles likes to cling on to
likes to cling onto the lumbar so one of
the things that i tell my family
and i teach doctors is you got to get
the immune system strong right you got
to get the immune system strong there's
some olive leaf right
licorice is another thing
these are antiviral you know you got the
licorice you got the
got the olive leaf you got the cat's
claw okay that's one way of doing it you
can be somebody where you just do celery
juice and you start with celery juice
and that's what you use and celery's
used as anti-pathogenic so what soda
just does is it reduces pathogen levels
in the body
that's what celery juice does so that's
why a lot of people are like i'm
drinking celery juice
like debbie said i'm drinking celery
juice for a certain amount of time and
all of a sudden now things are getting
better my back pain is getting better my
problems are getting better but there's
a lot of people
they're really viral they have a lot of
viral inflammation they'll have two or
three epstein bars they'll have a
shingles they'll have two shingles
viruses and don't even know it
and they get into that lower back that's
what they do and especially the shingles
virus the problem there is then we have
pew dental nerve problems where we have
bladder problems and we have nerve pain
in our groin and nerve pain pain in our
lower abdomen and nerve pain in our
pudendal nerve down there in the bladder
and that will happen too
and
the shingles virus tends to cause all of
this while it's also clinging on to the
lumbar nerves and clinging on to getting
in between the vertebrae and inflaming a
nerve and here's one of the reasons why
it does that if a nerve does get pinched
right
root hairs
fray off of that nerve and when root
hairs fray off of that nerve
a signal happens inside the body it's
like a homing signal for a pathogen and
that's when the shingles virus will go
looking for
and i've talked about this in the
medical media books it'll go looking for
that damaged nerve that injured nerve
and that's what it does
so you'll end up with
you guys if you just came on here and
talked about sciatic nerve pain body
pain joint pain we're just talking about
back problems this is an important lie
for anybody who's struggling with back
issues and stuff like that it's really
good information um
which can be really helpful
so as nerve hairs get frayed you guys
nerves like the sciatic nerve or typical
nerve or any of these nerves coming off
the spine when they get frayed
because these root hairs come off the
nerve
kind of like yarn i don't know if you
guys ever seen a strip strip of yarn
where you got all these little hairs on
that yarn all popping up all over the
place well guess what when that happens
and it happens to a lot of people's
nerves
viruses like the shingles look for that
and that virus goes and it clings on to
the nerve is what it does when it clings
onto the nerve
the nerve swells
so now the nerve swells so now
somebody's sciatic level sciatic pain
level is even more and now somebody's
static nerve pains even more and that
leads us into this vicious cycle
the more pain we're in with our lower
back the more chances we're going to
jolt it or hurt it and that's what
happens people walk around they hurt
their back
you know other things happen marla says
totally i've had back issues seeing a
cairo for years amazing now following
medical medium protocols i'm finally
healing oh that's incredible doing the
medical media protocols for the back
issues the chiropractor says it's like
adjusting
a different body that's amazing marla
you know that's that's amazing so i see
a question on tick tock says how do you
get the shingles so
here's the thing with shingles shingles
is easy to get you can catch the
shingles in just a public restroom just
off the toilet seat
very easy just off the toilet seat i
often talk about
how you got to look out when you're
going to bathroom in a public restroom
you got to flush the toilet first
before you sit down to eliminate because
when you sit down to eliminate as you're
dropping that torpedo into the toilet
yeah talked about this so many times a
splash can happen and that splash has
other things in the toilet bowl i've
talked about all these different
pathogens in there and you can have
shingles could be just floating on top
of the water and it just splashes back
up could be on toilet seats restaurants
eating out restaurants is probably one
of the biggest ways to actually catch
the shingles
um there's there's so much shingle
contamination just in that in that alone
so yeah so what happens if people don't
realize that we we would we in
restaurants were eating off of forks the
forks weren't sterilized there's a lot
of stuff i've talked about about that
with the forks
where forks aren't sterilized so when
you go to a dentist
and the dentist sticks a drill in your
mouth or sticks a probe like the metal
probe have any of you guys what been to
a dentist where the dentist takes a
metal probe
and they're poking around and they're
they're jamming it into your teeth right
okay
well
that's that's basically you go to a
restaurant and they're not sticking that
in a you know like a um you know a
sanitizer they're not doing that they
put those tools in these little and
these little bug killer machines right
that's what they do or they they open up
brand new tools for people they just
open them up and they poke in their
mouth to the brand new tool that's never
touched another person's mouth when you
go into a restaurant they don't take the
forks and the spoons and they don't put
it into like
literally like a ten thousand dollar
unit to actually kill everything on them
instead they just run through a crappy
dishwasher if you're lucky they do that
in the restaurants busy restaurants if
you're lucky you can do that now you got
a fork that's been in 20 people's mouth
that mounts that day you know 10
people's mouths a day or that week or
whatever and then you're using that fork
and you're jamming it in your gums and
you're hitting your tongue with it and
that's how we get the shingles
that's one reason right there so that so
this information is could be helpful for
you guys like i'm not eating out anymore
relationships is another way to get
shingles
it's it's relationships is how everybody
transfer bugs that's how everybody's
transferring bugs they're transferring
the upsy bar they're transferring the
shingles or transferring these bugs back
and forth and in relationships that's
another big way it's done all the time
so people just all everybody has at
least one variety of shingles in them
and eventually they'll have like a
sciatic nerve pain problem and here's
how it works
someone if their shingles hasn't come
out of dormancy
they can have some damaged back
right damaged vertebrae they could have
pinched nerves but they're not in pain
a lot of people walk around they're not
in pain
they have like you know bulging discs
they have problems with with their back
and they're not in pain but then you get
somebody right
who has hardly anything wrong with their
back or nothing wrong with their back at
all that can be seen with the eye
through x-rays or anything else or
through an mri or an x-ray or anything
at the chiropractor's office and they
can't even see there's nothing there and
then they still have all this mysterious
back pain
right all that mysterious back pain
that's because the shingles virus can
cause this even if you don't have
a back injury or or a sciatic nerve
that's being compressed or any kind of
nerve that's being pinched or any nerves
off the lumbar that's being pinched
right the whole bit so all that's
important to know
what i do is what i tell doctors all the
time is if you want to get back problems
better the first thing you got to do
instead of jumping into surgery and back
surgery because a lot of people jump
into back surgery
and then as they come out of back
surgery man it's not getting better and
now what the heck they're on painkillers
now they're on opioids now they're on a
lot of painkillers and now they're
addicted to painkillers and they still
have the back problem and it's
post-surgery and they're suffering right
and i tell doctors
whenever doctors reach out and doctors
have known for years i tell them what
you have to do is you have to make sure
you try to get that inflammation down
first that's a big thing it's getting
that inflammation down
first if you're even going to do a back
surgery you have to work on getting
inflammation down first unless it's a
crisis
where there's just such a crisis in the
back because of a severe injury or
something that just happened you know
sometimes people can't avoid that but
overall
it's really important to know that
there's measure there's you can take
you can take precautions in so many ways
and avoid back surgeries i've had so
many people avoid back surgeries so a
couple of things let's talk about a
couple of tips to do okay first of all
if you're somebody that's really acidic
and really toxic you're doing your
caffeine right you guys on tick-tock
you're doing your caffeine products i
know you guys on tick-tock
i know a lot of you guys are jacked up
on caffeine and there's no judge i'm not
judging anyone here same thing with you
guys and
and you know in other places too on
facebook wherever else it's i get it
everybody's on caffeine all that but
caffeine
really makes an acidic body and the more
acidic we are the more room we're gonna
have for eventually pathogen issues
another thing is dairy products a lot of
people are doing a lot of dairy products
okay that's another thing that could
make our body right environment really
acidic okay vinegar that's another one
right there too i know everybody's on
vinegar every other day it's in
condiments it's in your refrigerator
these you know everybody's mainlining
all that vinegar right so
and what we're doing is when we're doing
all that
we're starting to lose all our calcium
so we're weakening all of our bones so
we've got to remember that that's one
thing right there so in order to
preserve your lumbar preserve your
vertebrae
preserve your spine and your bones and
your skull
is to get that acidity under control so
you're not using
your calcium to neutralize all the other
stuff you're doing like the dairy
products and
and and the caffeine and the vinegar so
we have to keep that in mind right a lot
of us are just really acidic and that
doesn't help but the acidity can lower
the immune system allowing pathogens to
creep up like shingles and then when
pathogens like shingles creeps up we
inflame the nerves and then that
pathogen inflames all the different
nerves and that's important to know and
so we end up hurting ourselves we hurt
our back
and we got
we got a real acidic environment in our
body right
we're totally acidic our immune system
is already struggling a little bit and
then all it takes is that and then boom
the shingles virus comes out and when it
comes out
when it comes ripping out
you don't need a rash you don't need
pustules you don't have to have any
punctuals you don't have any rashes you
don't need any of that to have shingles
the shingles virus
does things on its own without
showcasing that pustule or that rash and
it goes into the lumbar into the nerves
attaches itself to the sciatic nerve
attaches itself to nerves coming off of
l1 lt l3 l4 l5 it attaches itself to
those lumbar nerves coming out okay
out of the spine and it attacks it it
attaches itself to the tibial nerves
and attach itself to the pudendal nerve
in the front so a lot of people okay a
lot of people
right in the front the pudendal nerve
okay
that shingles virus will attach into the
pudendal nerve and then they have the
overactive bladder then they have the
bladder pain then they have the bladder
problems then they have all that weird
the terrible itching in their lower
abdomen that they can't like get any
kind of just you know any kind of relief
from all these problems can happen from
the shingles virus getting into the
lower part of the body so i guess the
bottom line is one of the things i'm
trying to tell you guys is the shingles
virus can get into the lower part of our
body and wreak a lot of havoc
and what it does it gets into the spine
the lower spine and that's where it
causes a lot of turmoil the shingles
virus there so some of the basic steps
and i tell doctors to tell their
patients is celery juice is a great
place to start there's no question if
you're doing 16 ounces a day empty
stomach every single morning don't add
anything to it that right there is
something you can start with because
that at least starts to bring the
inflammation down by getting toxins and
poisons that the viruses create to flush
out of the body okay
here's where back problems get really
bad
right
you got the shingles virus your nerves
are inflamed
your sciatic nerves are inflamed your
lumbar is inflamed okay
and then
you also have an epstein bar
right at the same time that's out
a lot of people they struggle because
they'll have the fibromyalgia diagnosis
with the neurological dia lyme diagnosis
with the back problem diagnosis from the
chiropractor with some other diagnosis
and they'll be into like four or five
diagnoses they'll have the epstein bars
with the shingles they'll have an
inflamed back and body pain everywhere
so it's confusing so let's go into that
now a lot of people will have two
viruses
they'll have the shingles causing
sciatic pain and body pain and joint
pain in the back and in the hips and
then they'll have the epstein bar
causing nerve pain everywhere shoulders
arms hands in other places in the body
neck right they'll have the epstein bar
with this shingle so they'll have a
combination of both and people walk
around with all these low-grade viral
infections and they're highly inflamed
and they don't know what they can do
about it one of the things i recommend i
recommend any family members i tell
doctors is too is to make sure you're
doing the cold packs on the lower spine
when you've got sciatic nerve pain make
sure you're doing that every day you can
do some heat on it in the morning that's
something you can offer heat on it in
the morning is fine right cold packs too
you know on your lower back that's a
great thing you do
right and movement's important too
okay so movement is important michelle l
says shingles has caused so much pain it
causes a lot of pain with a lot of
people
movement's good too but you got to take
it slow movement really slow depending
on how you're inflamed i've seen a lot
of people get pushed into
heavy exercise with their trainers while
they're inflamed from viral inflammation
they don't know about in their lower
back and then it takes them to another
level where now they're really hurting
really bad and then up for then they're
eligible for a back surgery which could
be avoided which could have been avoided
so anyway some of the other things do is
is to take the viral load down it's like
dropping down the inflammation and
that's the next thing you can do and
that's why i talk about in the medical
medium book so
if you're somebody who just got on here
i've got cleanse the heel book right
here
okay so this has the multiple cleanses
but has the symptoms and conditions in
here and the dosages in case you're new
to medical medium information this is
the cleanse the heel book get it free at
the library
right or get it get it on amazon.com and
it talks about the shingles in here in
the shingles section like the sciatic
nerve pain the frozen shoulder
bell's palsy other problems that the
shingles caused claudia says i've had
bad shingle pain for years it's starting
to get better on your protocols i'm
thrilled claudia on facebook thank you
for being here
protocols are in here
you know so
so according ema says i do everything
you recommend for movement that's
fantastic
so
good to see you guys coming on here
when it comes down to getting viral
information now claudia says so which
protocol to use if you have ebv versus
shingles with the neurological issues
so you check out check out the books
when you get a chance you what i always
say
is what kind of symptom does somebody
have what kind of condition does
somebody have right all right so ebv
plus shingles i say so what kind of
symptom that you have i always say try
to find your symptoms in the books
that's one way of doing it right is find
your symptoms in your book and it'll
lead you to being able to start battling
that epstein-barr battling that shingles
take the book to your doctor too so your
doctor you know
can take a look
how to get inflammation down
using antiviral approaches gets the
inflammation down with the back really
important to know right anti-viral
approaches
so i got some golden seal right here
okay and i would start with the symptom
that causes you the most trouble if it's
your back it's sciatic pain or anything
that and that's the symptom that causes
the most trouble you start with that
in the cleanse the heel book amazon.com
us it's only 69 16.99 so it's 51 off 16
dollars get it free at the library you
can learn about the protocols
so when you when you're building up your
immune system and knocking down
inflammation
some of the things that i teach doctors
all the time is goldenseal is a good one
right there cat's claws is another good
one ask your doctors that's your
doctor's what's right for you
licorice is another great one when it
comes down to shingles and back pain and
back problems right that's another one
that's really important olive leaf's
another one that's really important
which is vitamin c
right
you know the buffered vitamin c not the
scorpic acid right that's the micro see
right there
and um and you can go to the library get
the book for free at the library you
know if you're somebody that's like look
i don't have the 16
get the book learn about why i have the
problem so you can actually do some
things through some foods and some other
and some cleanses right and supplement
quality matters too just not every
vitamin c is the same ascorbic acid can
be hard on people's stomachs
that's why i'm always recommending
vimergy this stuff is so easy on the
system
so yeah totally um
you guys i'm heading off to ig i'm going
to turn tick tock back on i'm going to
pop tick tock back on we're going to
instagram
and
i can't wait i'm looking forward to it
i'll have telegram back on too
i'll see you guys then and we'll cover
more there about lumbar back nerves
all that stuff