medium healing broth i'm really excited
i got my pot right here going everything
else
this is in the new revised and expanded
new edition
of medical medium book one and then on
tik tok and instagram you guys
i'm gonna make the sweet potato tortilla
soup so i'm gonna make the healing broth
now
with you guys on facebook and youtube
and i'm making the sweet potato
okay tortilla soup on
tick tock and instagram all right let's
get that straight so here we go i'm
excited to be here okay
that's medical medium book one but
really it's the new edition
a whole book added to it powerful book
i'm really excited about it
excited for you guys to get your hands
on this i can't wait
so let's do it um you saw michelle l
come on
and everybody's coming on there miranda
healing broth
awesome so you guys i'm gonna start with
some carrots i'm gonna get this healing
broth going
so let's do some carrots here four
carrots look and you know you guys can
do what you want you can do if you have
you may not have four carrots you might
have two you just do the best you can
when you guys are making your broth
sometimes you know when you go into the
fridge you're like do i have everything
so what i'm doing is i'm chopping up
some carrots right now i'm gonna um
looking at
everybody coming on and
so the healing broth recipe is in the
new edition medical medium book one
new addition revised and expand it
so this is a really powerful
medical medium healing tool the healing
broth has helped a lot of people
throughout the years heal in many
different ways
such an important really important
tool that's what i've always called it
i'm throwing some carrots in here
elena says so happy to be here i'm happy
you're here i'm excited
lots to talk about you guys you might
want to fasten your seat belts
because i got some stuff to say
i got some serious stuff to say today
so i'm just kind of like warming you up
a little bit
is what i'm doing you know i'm getting
some carrots in here
but really what i gotta say is i'm
probably gonna piss off a few people
and at the same time some of you guys
might be like whoa wait a minute that's
actually pretty interesting but
you gotta fasten your seat belts for
today
because i don't think i'm holding back
yay truth randomly says hey true yeah i
know i know i'm gonna
i'm gonna say some pretty intense things
today
you guys know i've been talking about
caffeine you guys know i've been talking
about chocolate
you look if you eat chocolate caffeine
fine i've been talking about fragrances
about the damage it does the scented
candles been talking about all those
different things
but i'm going to talk about a few other
things today
so um it's going to be fun i just want
to get some carrots in here um
yeah people don't a lot of people don't
like to hear truth though
you know a lot of people don't like to
hear truth let's do some celery in here
we'll do two stalks
i'm gonna put three stalks because
get some celery going if you guys just
came out of making the medical medium
healing broth and then
i hope everybody here comes with me on
either ig
or tick tock okay and you might want to
come on the tick tock live
really because i think you get a better
view than the view on ig
just letting you know so and i'm gonna
make the sweet potato soup
and i'm using the medical medium healing
broth
as a base for the sweet potato um
tortilla soup
so i got some celery in here i got some
carrots in here you you can put
optional instead of carrots you could
put one sweet potato in here that's the
option for this recipe for a healing
broth letting you know let's do some
onion
let's get that going here so this is
exciting
i'm going to do two onions right
i'm gonna do two onions here
i've been following your practice of
sarah says i've been following your
practice
on foods and struggle with excess weight
from hormone imbalance do you have any
additional tips for someone struggling
with hormone weight
as i do not have an idea what's going on
as i do not like the idea
of going on pharmaceuticals that's
that's liver issues so that's what that
is
it's not hormones like weight coming on
isn't hormones
so that's that's how misinformation
works you guys
check this out okay so when medical
medium booked
the medical medium first book came out
right
this is the new edition right here when
when the first book came out
i used a word i used a word in the
health scene
that no one else used at the time
the word was misinformation that was a
medical medium word of course i didn't
create the word so before anybody starts
talking crap
and smack and say oh now the medical
medium is claiming he created the word
misinformation
but i didn't create the word but what
happened
was i used the word and i used it a lot
when no one in the health scene
used the word because the medical
the medical establishment science and
research
medical science research had a
tremendous amount of misinformation
still due to this day right and so when
i broke out on the scene with the book
and i've been in the scene
for over 30 years but when the first
book came out
um trish says not true hormones later in
life and women cause weight gain
trish that's not true but just stay on
because i want to help you out with that
one so you know
what happens trish is your liver gets
stagnant and sluggish later on in your
lifetime
because it gets full of stuff full of
crap
all kinds of bad things in there toxic
heavy metals
pesticides herbicides fungicides ddt
yeah is inside your liver absolutely
everybody has it in there even asbestos
gets inside people's livers how do you
like that one
okay it's blowing on the highways all
day long
still till this day gasoline fumes
petrochemicals plastics your liver gets
filled up with plastics
pharmaceuticals have you had a
pharmaceutical in your life
it it it fills into the liver and here's
what happens
you could be young and your liver can
fill up and then the weight starts
coming on
and guess what you can be older and your
and and
and your liver fills up and the weight
comes on
everybody's a little different on their
timeline of when that filter
gets clogged up really important to know
so guys i'm putting in some um
onions here i got carrots i got celery
i'm making the medical medium healing
broth
see the hormone blame is just to trick
out women
and it's bad if you fall for it because
yes hormones become imbalanced
absolutely and yes
i believe in in hormones being
imbalanced of course and i believe in
every aspect of that
but what women have been tricked with is
they're blamed for all their problems as
being hormonal
that was a man's trick to women so
medical research and science
all men at the time came up with the
biggest scam of a century
which is everything wrong with you trish
and any other woman
it's your hormones it's your hormones
it's your hormones because you're a
woman
you're a woman it's your hormones you're
going to be emotional too you're going
to be an emotional mess you're a woman
you're going to be incapable of of being
normal because you're a woman your
hormones are going to run everything
they're going to run your emotions
they're going to run
everything they're going to make you
psycho they're going to make you totally
crazy
that was what it was all these years
when women were depressed anxiety
aches and pains oh you're crazy it's
your hormones
and your nuts lady that's what they said
in the doctor's office
every day for decade after decade after
decade
you're freaking crazy that's what they
said every woman came into the doctor's
office
and the medical establishment came up
with the biggest scam
biggest scam in that ever did ever be
and it's your hormones because they
didn't know what was wrong with women so
hormones hormones hormones you come in
the door oh you need hrt you're coming
the door
or it's just it's you're you're going
into menopause you're coming to the door
oh you're going you must be having some
kind of your cycle must be making you
crazy
oh you come in the door it's your
hormones that's why you're that's why
you're sick
you got fatigue oh it's your hormones
you're sick that
was the game bottom line
just letting you know why did they do it
one they didn't know what was wrong with
anybody they didn't know why you're
gaining
weight two they needed to sell the
out of hormones
that's what it was became a trillion
dollar industry and they needed to sell
the crap
out of hormone therapies back in the day
and they needed and they needed a
scapegoat
they needed to put women in their place
men needed to put women in their place
shut them up
sit down it's your hormones that was the
medical industry back
in the day and it really was i've talked
to doctors back in the 90s that were
80 years old that were having they were
in the heyday in the 1950s and 60s
i've heard it all i know what the scene
was
so i'm cooking cooking some healing
broth
so what happened was though they don't
let that go
that is still here today it's in
alternative medicine
full throttle it's in conventional
medicine full throttle
and and weight gain just like many other
things
is blamed on hormones
yes your hormones can be imbalanced yes
it can i told you guys
get out of my way today because i got a
lot of other stuff to talk about
so you might want to hang in there for
this
um a sluggish stagnant liver causes your
weight gain
and it can happen when you're young and
it can happen when you're older
it just happens that's what creates the
weight gain okay
so i'm gonna put a i'm gonna put some
shiitakes in here i'm gonna put some
mushrooms let's get them in here so
get about a cup in here i'll do like
a few of these caps
you guys what you'll notice right here
when i'm cutting you notice i'm not
doing it this way
i want to show you something okay you
know i'm not doing it this way you see
this right here
see see what i'm doing right here see
this
right you notice on that the reason why
i'm not cutting like that when i'm with
you guys
and i'm cutting and i'm cutting kind of
stupid on here
where i'm doing it like this where i'm
like oop almost going to cut my thumb
off whoa whoa right the reason why i'm
doing that
is because the way this is all set up
and the way the board's rigged
is it's not meant right here in in my
little kitchen studio right here to do
it that way
i have to basically clear everything off
set the cutting board up differently
pull
the stuff in and start really chopping
fast but we're casually
doing this casually chopping so really
kind of
you know i can just basically just
gently chop up stuff but you won't see
me do the
the pro stuff going on which you could
easily do i mean in the sense where just
like you guys do
where you know you you're cutting
everything a certain way
but so if you'll notice i'm doing it
this way it's only because we're cash
and i'm doing it real slow methodical
talking at the same time
so the way coming on
is nita says preaching to sell his books
that's funny because you can go into the
library and get them for free i've been
saying that for years
i probably sent millions over the years
into the library to actually get them
for free and it made me not a penny
and i'm the only author that's ever done
that
where i want everybody to go in the
library and get it for free that's
number one
number two is i can sell i can sell
courses for thousands of dollars classes
for thousands of dollars
i can sell products for thousands of
dollars i could be a billionaire
tomorrow
with the amount of people that know
about medical medium which is probably
about 500 million people in the world
know about medical medium
and literally i could bank like nobody
can bank
and you're worried about me trying to
preach about selling a book or something
it's interesting you know kind of get
your head kind of get your head together
and really know the facts about that
stuff
um and okay so let me not get
get you a book that has information
that's saving lives how about that
how about if i don't write books anymore
okay so what about the people's lives
that have been saved here because of the
medical medium books and they got off at
couch island and mattress island and
they're
able to work for the first time in life
should i have not sold them a book
should i have not written a book so they
can buy spend 16
on a book and save their life or do you
would you rather have them
buy all kinds of stuff out there
millions of dollars and millions of
dollars of
crap sold to people out there and them
not getting better how about that
and just for the record you guys anita
i've been asked to write the books for
years decades
anthony write a book write a book write
a book write a book
but i understand what you're saying i
understand
all right you guys going to get a few
more things in here so this is i'm going
to actually add some water in this
too right now so i'm going to do
and get this going so i'm making the
healing broth i got two tomatoes that
are gonna go in here
so i'm gonna chop up some tomatoes
that's going to go in the healing broth
so here's what causes weight gain
years and years of coffee chocolate
caffeine
a green tea any kind of caffeine energy
drinks you burn your liver out you burn
your adrenals out and the liver gets
burnt out from
caffeine from adrenaline highs and then
after your 20 years of burning your
liver out and adrenals out
okay after you do that you end up with
the weight gain
and it's going to be blamed on your
hormones how about that one here's
another thing that causes the weight
gain
the high fat diets see when you're
younger
and your liver is working pretty good
you can do the high fat diet every
single day you're taught to eat the high
fat diet every day you're taught to eat
lots chicken
eggs has nothing to do about whether i
like animal products or not or
i i support animal protein diets i
support plant-based
diets but every single day you're on a
high fat diet how many times did you eat
bacon
well the liver is going to pay the price
later on and your weight is going to
come on down the road maybe when you're
40 maybe when you're 50.
um you know how many nuts and seeds have
you eaten nut butters peanut butter how
many oils have you had
and then this and then the liver gets
sluggish and stagnant it gets beaten
down down the road
and then your weight gain comes on it
might come on when you're 30 and you
can't keep it off it might come out when
you're 40.
all those eggs all the chicken all the
fish
all the fat right you know it just
oatmeal
is high in fat just so you know
a cup of oatmeal is a minimum of five
grams of fat in a cup of oatmeal
so it's like not also not only doing
bacon and eggs and you're doing chicken
you're doing oils
and then you're doing you're doing your
cheese you're doing your butter and
you're doing your chocolate which is
high in fat
and then on top of that you think you're
eating healthy for five seconds eating
your oatmeal and then that's high in fat
it's like it's like you just it you
can't keep it in check so then the liver
gets beaten down over the years and then
20 years later boom the weight comes on
then
the liver has been beaten up by all that
caffeine all those years and then what
about pharmaceuticals too
what about any kind of pharmaceuticals
that's another thing too
trisha marie's here she's here today
you guys are uh lots of thought i
haven't even started
i haven't even started what i have to
talk about today
um okay let's see what we got here got
the tomatoes in i'm gonna put
i'm gonna put a bulb of garlic
almost a bulb of garlic in the healing
broth if you guys just came on
let's just cover this real quick that's
the healing broth
that's in the medical medium new edition
book right and this is the healing broth
i'm making this with you guys and then
if you guys come with me to instagram
and tiktok you can pick either
platform i'll be on both just like i'm
on facebook and youtube right now
together
after we leave here if you guys come
with me
i'm going to be doing the sweet potato
tortilla soup and i'm going to be using
the healing broth as the base for the
sweet potato tortilla soup
and that's in medical medium new
addition revised and expanded
all right so i got the soup going here
let's get the bulbs of garlic the garlic
in here you could do about
eight cloves you could do a little less
if that's something you want to do
start getting these going here
so here's what's going on
when the medical medium you know and
what happens the same thing with
weight gain with children it's the liver
and the liver getting maxed out early
with toxic heavy metals which children
have
lots of toxic heavy metals so
they're passed down from their their
parents too
so i'm gonna get some cloves of garlic
in here i'm throwing that in here
here's the thing about misinformation i
used the word
misinformation when the first book came
out and i used it in lectures
shortly before the first book came out
years ago
no one was using that word on the
internet it was all about
health and everybody thought there was
no misinformation
but what i did was i exposed areas of
where the misinformation was and i spent
a great deal of time it's about smoky
mountain paradise i think i just saw
um
but what happened is that word i used in
all my articles i used it on the blog
i used it everywhere in lectures and
everything about how much misinformation
was in the alternative health field
including the mess up with candida
including the mess up with the mthfrg
mutation including the mess up with so
many different
uh things and trends and everything so
misinformation was a big word i use
now everybody's using against me right
now
i put out one truth and they'll say
misinformation misinformation they're
actually using my word
now everybody that's what you see on the
internet 24 7.
no one used it before i was the only one
using it spell showing
showing showcasing where everybody was
messing up
including like coffee enemas how bad
they were including things in
alternative movement and then including
things like shingles right
medical the medical industry tricks you
out and says that
shingles is the chickenpox virus so what
i did was
that's misinformation the chicken box
virus
is separate that's a different variety
of virus herpetic family
the shingles is an entirely different
virus than the chickenpox
but they got everybody snowed so i put
out the truth and said there's
misinformation
all right so we got the garlic in there
that's great
uh one inch of freshly cut ginger let's
do that let me
got some ginger right here making the
medical medium healing broth if you just
guys got on here fasten your seatbelts
because i'm going to be talking some
stuff in a little bit
you can peel it back a little i'm
peeling it back a little you don't have
to in a healing broth
you can keep the skin on i've done that
a whole bunch of times
do that mostly really
popping a little ginger in here gonna
slice that up in this healing broth and
throw it in
okay and uh see what else i need i got
that i got the water in here
so i think i got my ingredients in there
i just didn't put my
put a little chili powder don't put too
much chili powder i actually
many times i've made it really hot so
i'm going to put a little pop in here
that's it a bit of chili pepper in there
or red bell pepper flakes really i just
put the hot stuff too that's something
you can do if you want
pepper flakes let me grab some pepper
flakes
put some pepper flakes in here if you
don't like the heat you don't have to do
a lot of them
i tend to spike it a little too much and
the next thing you know i got something
really hot going on where it's too hot
i also have a pepper over here i think i
might pop that in i think i lost my
hot pepper i think i lost it
all right let me put the lid on
oh let me get some parsley and that's
the last thing here i forgot my parsley
see you guys
so now what happens is anything i say
you'll get a whole bunch of people i'd
be like
well science hasn't backed it up
misinformation
so i want to talk about that a little
bit about science and research but
before i go in there
it reminds me about genes
did you guys know that everybody's being
diagnosed
as having gene issues
um amina says bell's palsy
is shingles but i had it from 2007 is it
it is improved but have uh
oh yeah so you still have an issue with
that now but
still recovering is all healing in your
book for me
is the same for shingles sorry guys i
got so much
bright lights in my eyes sometimes a
reflection on a computer screen is not
easy to read a comment
so i'll try it try it better um
no one knew shingles was bell's palsy
just for anybody else who's listening
there
that was medical medium information
so now doctors are actually diagnosing
people with bell's palsy and they're
saying well it could be the shingles
virus that originates from
millions of medical medium books getting
out there
this book right here changed the rules
on bell's palsy
so and that's the shingles virus so
that's how it works there
goes palsy is a non-rashing shingles
virus
gonna have shingles and years later it
show up differently
but but it but it'll happen when you
don't even have shingles you don't even
have a rash but the virus is there and
it'll cause the bell's palsy
so i just put uh parsley in here let
this get ready to cook
cook up nice so i'm making a healing
broth
i want to get this pumping away and i'll
show you guys the healing broth in a
little bit
if you guys just got on here after i do
the healing broth it's going to be the
base
for the sweet potato tortilla soup that
i'm making on ig and tick tock
so everybody
um so everybody like believe
that first of all the shingles was um
the chickenpox virus and that's not true
it's a different bug altogether but that
just shows you how much misinformation
is in the medical
world it's really sad there's
non-rashing shingles varieties and
there's rashing varieties
there's over 30 varieties of shingles
out there and them info and i brought
that to light for people
sciatic nerve pain okay whether you have
a back issue or not that sciatic
nerve pain gets really inflamed from the
shingles virus
that's one thing right there trigeminal
neuralgia that's the shingles bell's
palsy that's the shingles
so these are things that that medical
medium brought to light
but you guys i want to talk about jeans
for a little bit and head into there
so fasten your seatbelts a little bit
because really the
the gene blame game and
the gene scam that's upon people right
now it's
it's really sad and where it's going
it's
they've weaponized the gene terminology
it weaponized it against everybody so
it's purposely
being used against you i want you to
know this
you might want to get an herbal tea or
something lemon balm tea before you hear
this stuff
but medical system
is trying to
and they're doing a great job convince
all of you
that your genes are going bad
there's a reason for it and
they want you to believe that not only
are your genes going bad but your
children's genes are bad
and that your children aren't perfect
and they're all genetically tore up
they're all genetically mutated it's
really evil
actually because the medical system
wants you
to think your child's genes are all
messed up
that's their game that's the direction
they have to go
and there's a reason why they're going
this direction
because hey dr fans here even
even the alternative doctors are saying
the genes are bad yes
exactly and so there's a reason because
a
they don't know what's causing chronic
illness so that's the thing there too
because they don't know what's causing
chronic illness they need to blame
you you're the to blame it's you
you're the problem so your daughter
your son their genes are bad
they get one condition colitis crohn's
celiac eczema psoriasis
anything anything any kind of condition
that
your daughter your son might get or your
kids or your grandkids may get
their genes are bad so it's it's it's
beyond
evil and twisted it's way beyond that
um and so what happens is this is that
you're led to believe now every time you
have a problem
that your genes are mutated they want
you
to believe that you you are the cause
of your children's mutated genes
you hear that that's what they want
that's
exactly what they want that's their
think tank
that's their agenda they need you to
believe
that your children are faulty
they're not perfect no they're not
they're not special no their genes are
all
bad they want you to know that's what
they want you to believe
they need you to believe this okay
and then they need you to believe that
your children's children's genes are
going to be
worse and they're going to be bad
they need you to believe that too and so
what happens is you get older
you're and you get older and your
children get older
and your children have children it's
going to be way worse than this you're
going to see it
more and more and more and more you guys
are all
genetically ruined you're all
genetically
faulty that's where it's going
that's where they need it to go and the
alternative movement
is following suit now here's something
to understand the alternative movements
not the alternate movement anymore
they're in bed with the conventional
movement
get that information in here let it sink
in
okay lorraine lorraine lawson
thank goodness for you and soc thank
goodness you're here
and so the goal is okay
for you not to only think your genes are
bad not to only think that
your children's genes are bad you know
they need you to consciously absorb this
like
it to become part of your soul part of
your consciousness and guess what
the most spiritual people out there all
believe it how do you like that
they all believe it oh all those
affirmations everybody wants people to
do and all the meditations and all the
affirmations
and all of all of the you know promoting
the intuition
but yet they all believe gene just your
genes are bad
the genes are why they're sick genes are
why their family members get sick genes
are why
everybody's get sick say genes are why
people have all this cancer and that's
how it's getting rigged up
so you could be a real spiritual person
totally into everything tend to yoga you
tune everything like namaste you're all
the way
you're like you know you're you're like
essential oils incense
you're just spiritual you're seeing
things you're hearing things
you're hanging out with friends at night
talking about the stars
meanwhile you believe your genes are bad
and you're gonna just
you're just gonna oh my alternative
doctor is saying it's genetic i got a
gene mutation my child's got a gene
mutation
and you're just gonna believe it it
destroys it destroys the
the center of your consciousness without
you even knowing it
it is poison
poison in your veins but it's poison in
your
soul on a deep deep dark
level and it's set up that way purposely
so it's not the viruses the epstein bars
and the shingles virus hhv-6 hhv7
simplex other viruses too sedimental
virus it's not the
viruses that are causing any problems no
it's not the toxic heavy metals the
mercury inside your brain
giving you anxiety depression ocd the
mercury inside your brain that's giving
you
all kinds of conditions severe
depression depersonalization
bipolar mania schizophrenia it's not
that metal causing any problems no it's
not
at all it's not the pesticides
herbicides fungicides you breathe in
every single day out there
that's on your neighbor's lawn around
everybody's apartment buildings and on
the sides of the highway as you've got
your windows rolled down
it's not those toxic chemicals it's not
the petrochemicals you breathe in at the
gas station every single
time you're there filling your tank it's
not the plastic that's filling into your
body every single day
it's none of this it's not the radiation
that's falling out of the sky
since hiroshima and fukushima
it's not it's not like that radiation
that's raining down
on us it's not you know
it's not any of the chemical warfare
that's being dropped on us out there on
planes
it's not the pharmaceuticals that have
been in her system with all that
titanium in it
and all those metals and it's not any of
those pharmaceuticals no
it's none of that it's not the ddt that
we still breathe in every day because
guess what they didn't ban
ddt it's still being used every day out
there and it's floating around
everywhere you go outside you're like
you breathe it right in
it's not any of this all over the world
the ddt is just floating around
everywhere and
and it's not it's not the travel on the
planes and all the radiation on plane
flights that are longer than an hour
it's not that it's not the oil spills
in the in the oceans it's not all the
crap in the oceans
that you actually get on your skin when
you're doing like a swim
it's none of that it's none of that it's
your genes
that's what it is how does it feel
right how does it feel it's your body
you're
faulty you're no good i thought we were
like spiritually evolved i thought
alternative doctors were spiritually
evolved but don't mean they're
spiritually evolved
you can be an alternative doctor but it
don't mean crap
about spiritual growth and spiritual
evolvement
and you can be a conventional doctor
don't mean you're
spiritually growing you know and
every time i throw the truth out there
and that's what i've been doing all
these years all
you hear is smack about me and
everything because of it because
no one likes to hear it they don't want
if you actually have been doing
something your whole life or believing
in something
you think you want to be proved wrong
when you invested all this time and
energy in it
when you invested time and energy in it
you think you want the truth to stand in
your way when you
already told everybody what you believed
in did
everything you believe in what your work
is and then it just people try to defend
it with their life they
they push away the truth to defend
whatever they've been doing because what
they've been doing is basically
fraudulent
and that's what happens when you put
truth out there so when you put truth
out there about the genes
and about how literally they want your
children to believe their genes are
messed up you know what children do
children teenagers though i hear this
from moms i hear this from doctors
that tell me that their their mom
patients
their kids 15 16 17 years old are
on the computer after their diagnosis
from the doctor's office and they're
being
in the computer on the internet it says
you got a gene
problem you know it's genetic and you
got like people
i hear it all the time from doctors that
don't believe in the whole gene thing
thank god there's some out there and
they see the damage being done there's
it's a technique it's a weaponization
to make sure we believe
we're not only faulty as human beings
physically
physically but we're destroying
the planet in a way where we're making
our offspring
is is broken
they want you to believe as a mom well i
don't know if i should have a baby
because
if i have a baby and the baby's gonna
have all these genetic
all these genetic issues what am i going
to do this is not good and then
and then it's only getting worse it's a
sick
sick evil plot that's just part of it
i'm not even going into the rest of it
there's lots of there's lots of reasons
why it's a sick evil plot
um ruthie says i followed the medical
medium thyroid healing for a nodule when
i went back to the endocrinologist for
ultrasound follow-up he said it shrank
and looked at me in awe and said what
did you do
i told a medical medium ruthie amazing
amazing incredible so
um look so when it comes down to genes
and genes being weaponized that's what's
happening right now
and now they're weaponizing science so
let's talk about that a little bit
you know you guys if you just came on
here before i talk about the whole
weaponizing science
which you guys might want to hear right
here um
i'm making the healing broth it's
cooking
right here so i'll show you what it
looks like a little bit
this is the healing broth um
so i got carrots in there i got celery i
got onions this is the medical meme
healing broth that's helped so many
people
uh in this time of year depending on
where you are in the world it's a great
time for this
so
and what i'm going to be doing is on ig
and tiktok i'm going to be on that those
platforms at the same time i'm going to
make the sweet potato soup so you might
want to go from here to
there and the healing bra is going to be
the base for it so
we'll talk about weaponizing science
they want the young people to believe
that science is everything that science
is all knowing that science is not
flawed on any level
that's what they need young people
growing up
right now they need them to believe that
science
is flawless that
science doesn't have anything wrong with
it at all
and there's a technique for that there's
a reason why they're doing this this why
you'll see all over the internet you'll
see all these people and all these
trolls and clones that call them and
they'll just be out there
and they'll just be like where's where's
the science what about this science
study what about that
and there's a lot of issues around this
that i got to tell you that's really
important to know like to begin with
science studies hasn't fixed anyone with
chronic illness so a science study can't
fix you
you can read all the science studies you
want but it's not going to get somebody
better that's really struggling or on
mattress island or couch island so
that's number one
so kind of like put that put that in the
database
it's important to know and what they
want everybody to do is they want
people to believe that there's a
scientific study
waiting to heal them or waiting to
cure them the word that they all use out
there
right and they believe that there's just
gonna be this miracle scientific study
that's
just around the corner it's right around
the corner you guys
and they want you to be a dog waiting
for a bone
they want us all like dogs okay that's
what they want us to be like
so we're just dogs waiting for a bone
we're like where's my bone where's my
bone
oh wait a minute two years later another
scientific study can come out is it
going to save my life
is another scientific study going to
come out i mean there's people been sick
30 40 years with chronic fatigue and no
scientific studies come out has ever
helped them
there's people with hashimoto's
thyroiditis the worst eczema psoriasis
no scientific study
is going to take care of them there's
people with multiple sclerosis no
scientific studies going to help them
there's people with all these different
conditions and they're waiting
tingles and numbness aches and pains
burning skin ringing in the ears there's
no time
science to scientific study that's going
to go and save somebody with any of that
and you know what's funny is is that
so we're we have to sit there waiting
for
these scientific studies as if
they're like frosting at the mouth as if
this scientific study
is gonna be the saving grace somewhere
and
here's the thing
everybody's always saying where's your
scientific proof where's your study
where's your peer review study well
or oh i'm gonna or i'm gonna link this
study here
go check out this study that's not gonna
fix anybody
you can link and check out every study
you want to check out out there every
scientific study out there
and it's not going to fix anybody with
psoriasis or eczema
it's not going to fix somebody with
lupus it's not going to fix somebody
with any kind of condition
so that's something to know right there
but they want you
to believe and they want the younger
generation to believe
wholeheartedly etched in their soul
their mind their consciousness their
whole being
they want them to believe that science
is a religion science is a god
science is above god science is even
bigger than that
you can't mess with science and so that
leads me to the next part i want to talk
to you about with this okay
so here's okay perfect
g says um i think the comment i want to
say
we wouldn't have cell phones okay
and physics right so here's the thing
science and chronic illness is not that
science
just so you know you that's the ploy
that's the trick out and that's the next
part i was going into
you look at your cell phone i got mine
over here
whoa science is going really amazing
look at this
i could text somebody from around the
world wait hello oh my god science is
incredible i can hear somebody at the
end of this phone
because science is ingenious you can't
mess with that
wait i could send emails through my
phone whoa emails
emails that's science right that kind of
technology isn't what i'm talking about
okay that kind of technology is not
science and chronic illness
all right okay how about this science do
you like this science how about this
okay
all right in the 1940s the 1950s
the 1960s the 1970s
if you were a girl and you had a little
bit of anxiety and you were 20
if you were 18 19 if you were 15 if you
were 28
young women 28 25 if you
had a little bit of anxiety you were
eligible
for a lobotomy and guess what hundreds
and hundreds and hundreds of thousands
of
young women had a probe stuck up their
nose
and the front of their brain tore off
and
taken out of through their nasal cavity
just to see if it will treat their
science
their start treat their anxiety or any
other kind of emotional
problem they were having that was
science at its
best then it was indisputable because it
was science
okay it was indisputable because it was
science how would you like to be
there in 1965 and have the front of your
brain removed
and now you don't even know your name
and you just sit in a rocking chair for
the rest of your life
for no reason and that was science how
about that
because science knew all and science
never gets slapped it never gets smacked
it never gets
punished it's ruined millions of lives
millions of lives millions of girls
lives okay
that's one example let's go into lyme
disease so science is so
great in the 1980s in the late 1970s and
1980s
and 1990s and 2000s
hundreds of thousands of women have
not only lost their lives in different
ways
including died from antibiotic overuse
from being diagnosed with lyme disease
and being treated wrong
lives destroyed awake you guys
don't even know or realize but wait a
minute
um couldn't have uh couldn't have a good
cell connection
couldn't have a good tv connection
couldn't be watching all different
all the different tv shows you can watch
or anything you want to do
i get it your car is totally decked out
you got wi-fi in your car
but that's the trick out the trick out
is that the young people they see all
this technology
and they think science has got them
covered all the way
without a doubt science is everything i
have nothing against science i believe
in science
but when it comes down to chronic
illness
no science is let out of the gate that
really can
fix people and that's done on purpose
see look around you do you think there's
anything bad going on around there
around the world do you think there's
anything bad going on do you think
there's bad going on with the pollution
what's your fight what's your
what's your thought out there what are
you thinking out there like what's going
bad in the world to you
okay where is it is it
you know people's rights are you worried
about people having rights
are you worried about racism are you
worried about rights issues
are you worried about oil spilled in the
in
in in the oceans are you worried about
what like what's your fight like what is
it
that you're that you're fighting for
because
we know the world is corrupt we know the
world is messed up
we know that there's all these bad
things happening in the world right
we know that there's all kinds of things
going wrong you're worried about 5g
right you know when i talk to people
every day it's like i'm always like what
are you worried about and then someone
told me i'm worried about 5g and then
someone will tell me why i'm worried
about
you know i'm worried about racism
another person will say
i'm worried about um i'm worried about
chemicals in our ocean
another person is like i'm worried about
the great garbage patch out in the
pacific ocean
where it's the size of texas and it's
eating up wildlife and all these birds
are swallowing all this plastic
and that's what i'm worried about i
talked to somebody else and they're
worried about all these little plastic
straws
and bottles in the ocean and then i
talked to somebody else they're worried
about a polluted lake
and then we're you know like everybody's
like worried about something right
and so we know the world's messed up
you know the world's messed up right and
then
but science isn't oh wait wait a minute
science isn't you mean to tell me that
there's no bad people in science
i you mean to tell me wait a minute
there's no bad anything in science
i'm confused that's a head scratcher for
me all right like
so there's angels
so everybody in science they're angels
uh
right they're holy angels is that who's
in science
so every single man in science is a holy
angel
that could do no wrong is that what it
is
like okay so i'm because i'm scratching
my head so
all the scientists there's not one bad
person at a lot so all the millions of
scientists around the world
they're all telling the truth there's
not one that lies oh wait
there's not one scientist that's a bad
person that doesn't beat their wife when
they come home
um there's no there's not one scientist
that hasn't
there's not one science scientist that
hasn't like
done something bad no they're all
perfect every single person is perfect
in science wait a minute the scientific
community is perfect
flawless they could not do no wrong
um interesting wait a minute um
the people that pay and hire scientists
and the people that pay for science to
be done
oh they can't do no wrong either so the
funders of science
can't do no wrong so you mean to tell me
there's not one
bad lot out there there's not one
bad funder of science the biggest
industries out there that are paying for
all the scientific studies
you mean to tell me that every one of
those big industries that are paying for
scientific studies
haven't done one thing wrong at all
i didn't know it's all perfect out there
science is perfect
the people who pay for scientific
studies are perfect the medical
industry is perfect everything's perfect
out there
and there's no agendas at all and
there's no interests involved
i didn't know because i don't know what
world
everybody's living in about thinking
that all you got to say is the word
science
hey uh yeah um is there any science with
that because
all i got to do is we'll use that word
science hey pal um
that's science word and then we're all
clear whoa he said science whoa
wait wait a study whoa wait what study
because that can't be wrong
that scientific study can't be wrong
there can't be anything wrong with
it um
science says asbestos was
fine and safe and then we got like
millions of people around the world
dying from asbestos cancer in their
lungs
science said cigarettes were fine for us
they were actually great for us
science says that that mesh they stuck
in for hernias
was perfectly fine they did all the math
they did all the science they made this
really nice mesh that you can put in
your abdomen and there's a billion
lawsuits
science said those lobotomies for all
those girls ruined
millions of lives actually around the
planet they lay a girl on a table
they knock her out and they stick a
probe up her nose
and they pull the front of her brain off
that i don't think that didn't happen
and science said that the lyme disease
treatments
for all those women that literally has
killed so many of them and you can't
talk about it
you talk about it anywhere and everybody
gets silenced because you can't go
against science because science is god
and they need every single person
to be science brainwashed like it's it's
more than
kool-aid it's like here's the kool-aid
the science kool-aid
once you drink that science kool-aid
like whoa and what they do is
they're teaching the youth that boy
science is amazing like
all the technology you got going on you
know
it's incredible science has become
weaponized
so that's what's happening there it's
become weaponized
and that's what's going on with science
it's
the beyond a new religion it's
beyond all of that it's
it's actually like a training a
conditioning
that's happening so
you actually believe that science
in medicine is above
board can't do no wrong
nothing can happen and it's free of
corruption
you know there's corruption everywhere
else right i just told you all those
different things like what's your fight
what's your worry what's your concern
because that's where this you know you
know
about all this corruption out there you
guys are out there you see it you guys
are on the internet you see different
things that you know about you guys
look into things you guys know
corruption but there's no corruption in
science no whoa
whoa all those paid for studies
paid and funded no thumb on the scale
right
you know what i know a lot of scientists
because
the years of the work that i've done and
bringing so much information out there
to others so i know
a lot of scientists and guess what they
can't feed their families
if they don't produce an outcome if you
don't produce an
outcome to the funder that's actually
hiring you
and that outcome doesn't suit the funder
then guess what you never work again
and you never get hired by another
funder another company won't hire you
so guess what that's the last job you
work you're going to be working
somewhere else
a scientist friend of mine said it was
either working at mcdonald's
or you better come up with something
whether you got to pull it out of your
ass you better come up with something
because when you're getting funded and
that's a corporation that's funding you
and you're like oh crap i gotta come up
with something on this table
let me get the chemistry out let me get
my theories going here because i better
come up with something
and if you botch it up you get a bad
recommendation
that corporation doesn't want to refer
you as a scientist anymore to another
corporation to keep you going so you
could feed your family
and now now you're working for like a
car service and you're driving people
around and they're in the back seat of
your car
when you were the scientist before
even though that's it's all good i mean
whatever you do is great you guys know i
talk about
medical medium book what
i did growing up and you guys should
read the origins of medical medium
when i was 14 and 15 i used to pump gas
medical science doesn't
get called out so it never gets called
out it makes mistake after mistake after
mistake
it's your genes it's the biggest mistake
ever but it doesn't matter it'll never
get called out you'll buy it you'll buy
into it
you know anything that has the word
science now
and forget it it's platinum gold you
can't
you can't go near it it's diamonds and
they'll tell your body's attacking
itself so when you got hashimoto's and
you got
ra and you got multiple sclerosis and
you got fibromyalgia you got cfs and
you've got
all kinds of other problems they're
going to tell you your body's attacking
itself because science wants to blame
your body
it's body shaming so they want your
children body shamed
thinking their genes are bad and faulty
that's a real
hard pill to swallow right there they
want
you and your children to believe that
your body's attacking itself
they want you to believe that you have
all these gene mutations and that's why
you're sick
and they want you if you're a woman they
want you to believe it's your hormones a
hundred percent
yeah our hormones are imbalanced and you
you should get a really good doctor
a really good doctor and have them do
some hormone testing absolutely
and they can offer something natural
that can really help
but but they blame science wants
everything blamed on hormones everything
blamed on hormones
and that's what they want science
doesn't want you to know that it's a
toxic heavy metal against the viruses
and the shingles virus and the
epstein-barr
and all the different varieties in the
streptococcus and they want
they don't want you knowing the real
problems of why your hormones are
imbalanced they don't want to look for
the real issues
science doesn't want to do that medical
science you know
doesn't care about you medical science
looks out for medical science
that's how it works i mean it's
something to keep keep an eye on
you might not believe that now but if
you're somebody that was sick for 25
years already you know that
that's the way it goes the best science
doesn't get people out of bed it doesn't
get people off of mattress island when
it comes
down to chronic illness you know
and the best science and then there's
this you ready for this you guys
okay here's how it works we need
scientists
we need science but the best science out
there that has
truth will never be revealed
it will never get a spotlight it will
get squashed
and crushed so if you fund some
scientists to actually discover the real
cause of something
there's going to be literally men in
black
suits busting down those doors and
shutting that down
you can't you can't fund real science in
health
and wellness you can fund science and
technology like i was telling you before
and it and it it going good you can fund
as good as it can you can fund
technology can fund other things
but you can't fund science to fix
problems to really
know to really discover what's wrong
because that stuff will be shut down
fast
totally shut down because the minute the
word gets out
there of why people are really sick it
leads a trail back to where it came from
like the epstein-barr virus it leads a
trail where these viruses really come
from it leads a trail where these toxic
heavy metals come from
and that they can't expose that they
don't want scientists
learning how to heal people either
scientists are not allowed
to find answers and to work in medical
science and research
to actually heal people to actually heal
people
because if they do that it defies what
medical research and science is trying
to do
they like creating equipment they like
creating things
they like to make things
and um you know they like to make things
and stuff
so science loves to do that where they
they can put nuts and bolts together
you know they can help you get more
comfortable with like if you have a leg
problem a knee problem they can create
knee braces science works in those areas
right
mechanical and other things like that
they work with some pharmaceuticals that
can be helpful
because they sell that's the thing it's
all part of that they want to sell all
that stuff but they don't want
the real reasons why you're sick and how
to head that off at the pass
and how to heal that they don't want
that happening so really good
good science doesn't get its day
it gets crushed every time it wants to
peek its head out
so hey wait a minute toxic heavy metals
are responsible for these diseases
boom it gets crushed wait a minute this
you you can't go
there that's how it works and then
then there's the fight of two sciences
right you get people
where's your science what science are
you talking about because conventional
science doesn't believe in alternative
science
they don't believe food has any science
involved there's nothing even involved
with food
they don't believe in anything so what
signs are even talking about whose
science are you even on or even talking
about that's a whole other thing too
and studies are always being trumped on
studies
like that study is an old study that
studies useless
and then the new study comes out and
crushes it and then the bias
the bias in studies is a whole other
game
um so yeah yeah yeah susan says forget
about science right now
okay well you know what there's millions
and millions and millions of kids
that believe science knows everything
about their health
and that their genes are faulty and
their bodies are attacking themselves
and when hey when mom is driving home
from a doctor's appointment
and she's got her 15 year old son and
he's looking on the computer
and he's finding out his hashimoto's is
his body destroying his thyroid
it's devastating devastating
because science doesn't have her son's
back
or her back so i mean the traps are set
for you guys
bottom line celery juice works yeah it
does um
so anyway if i don't talk about this
then you guys will fall into traps
that's how the system's set up and i let
you know as what's to come
anyway i'm making you guys healing broth
right here
heading over to tick tock and ig the
healing broth is done
just letting you know and the healing
broth the base to the healing broth is
going into the sweet potato tortilla
soup that i haven't made yet
so are you guys coming over with me or
what
so i made the healing broth this is this
right here
and that's in the medical medium new
edition check it out
and sweet potato tortilla soup is what
i'm making next i'm making this i'll be
live on tik tok at the same time as i'm
on ig
there's been some glitches with ig
lately some so you might
you might want to be on tiktok or try
either one see how it goes
so head there now you guys
um this is fun i'm gonna make the sweet
potato soup coming up i hope to see you
guys