we're doing a live meditation I'm
excited about this
Soul light infusion meditation so I
don't know if you guys heard the
meditation
the medical meeting podcast at Apple
podcast the soul light infusion
meditation right out of here
out of the protocols book
so
I thought it'd be really
I just thought it would be really nice
to just really go over this it's kind of
this is raw you know this is a
meditation live right now
if anybody gets on here and it's in the
middle of the meditation or you can
always listen to the video afterwards
but we're live right now which is this
is really fun
so the soul light meditation
is a special one
it's really powerful
and it came from SOC
but I want to also just address a few
things because I feel like it's my
responsibility
to make sure and I was talking to a
doctor friend he was telling me how he's
seeing more patients with the flu
flu season coming on we're going to go
into the holidays
immune systems get compromised
and so I was talking to Dr Freddie he
was like have you been telling your
people as I haven't had a chance I can
work you know working on the brain
challenge the brain shot challenge right
the brain shot therapies and all of that
and he said well just kind of remind
everybody I go I'm on it I'm on it
because it's true you know and I'm
starting to see a little bit of that too
out there so what I'm doing for myself
is I'm taking my zinc that's what I'm
doing
I'm taking my
um my propolis that's what I'm doing
taking my vitamin C
which I'm getting low on
so it's going down
so
and the thing is is that and you know if
you guys just came on here right now
we're about to do a live meditation so
I'm really excited about this so what
you could do is you can just relax you
can lay down you can just listen you
don't even have to look this way or
anything
so we we can do it this way which is
really cool never done it this way like
live right here right now
so I'm excited so I was talking about
the immune system though I've been
telling
I've been telling uh
um another friend of mine too who was
getting sick so it was like look
the zinc the whole bit the propolis
great for the immune system so I just
wanted to remind everybody about that
now these are the bemerjee products here
I fully endorsed this company because of
the four reasons
which are mind blowing like mind-blowing
for reasons you don't see anywhere else
in my opinion I have not seen it
anywhere else so the first reason is
that label requirements allow supplement
companies
to put ingredients inside their products
that they don't disclose
and bemerjee
they say no way we're never going to do
that If energy does not put in small
percentages of ingredients
hidden in their supplements
they will not do that that right there
blows me away because I cannot get a
supplement company to say that out there
I have not been able to find a
supplement company to say that
and save energy refuses to put a small
percentage of hidden ingredients
that they don't disclose
that right there
is unbelievable to me so label
requirements legally out there they make
it so supplement companies can put a
small percentage and hide it
and not disclose it in the products okay
so think about that
that's one thing right there if you guys
just got on here I'm talking about
immune system talking about the flu
coming we're going into the holidays the
other thing is Bemidji products are
third-party independently tested
third party
independently tested here's another
thing too remember the four reasons and
just going because people always asking
me about supplements and haven't had a
chance to even utter the word
supplements or something because things
have been so crazy but that right there
is mind-blowing okay and you'll see on
my directory at medicalmedium.com you'll
see how supplements kind of come and go
because they have free will and I can't
have them like do the right things so
that's why
they actually go in and out like that
and then use you won't see them on my
directory you won't see them because
people in supplement companies have
their own free will so going back to the
four big things about like why I fully
endorse themergy to the tilt
to the Tilt so one is the label
requirements well label label
requirements out there make it so
supplement companies don't have to
disclose hidden ingredients how insane
is that
the energy promises not to do that
that's incredible
another thing is vermigree products are
third party independently tested another
thing let's go to the third one
which is incredibly ready this one's
mind-blowing
and I can't find this for many companies
out there ready
femergy products
contain no alcohol
no soy
no gluten no citric acid and you see
citric acid and everything out there no
maltodextrin which is practically in
everything no magnesium steroid
no vinegar no caffeine yeah
no natural flavors
I can't even tell you how bad that is
no artificial flavors no titanium
dioxide
drop the mic if I could drop this mic
because I don't want to break it
this is a nice mic I don't want to break
it's a really nice mic drop the mic
the uh the fourth thing
I'm just letting everybody know the
fourth thing you won't find this
anywhere else I'm just telling you from
what I've ever seen the fourth thing
is that supplement companies to save
money
because it's about the bottom line
and the profit margin supplement
companies pick the lower quality tiers
when they're putting together their
supplements
they can still call it high quality
they're allowed to but they pick the
lower high quality
vemergy picks the highest to the degree
where they even have to have stuff like
grown for them
the highest
they don't care about the profit margin
highest
it goes down on record as being like the
best company in my opinion and so I
fully endorsed the best company I have
ever seen anywhere in supplementations
that's why I fully endorsement 100
billion percent so when I think about
those four things drop the mic mind
blown
and when it comes down to Healing mind
blown quality matters when it comes down
to that I've seen the Energy Products
move the needle so
from my friends my family my doctor
friends all of that so anyway you guys
with flu season coming into town
I I do the micro c i do the zinc I do
the propolis
you know when I don't have the flu or
anything I just do it that's the vitamin
D that's in my opinion the purest form
out there hands down I know people like
vitamin D I know they take vitamin D
so anyway
um
and the propolis
the the whole thing with the propolis is
it's it's the it's the metaphysical part
which is incredible it's no no alcohol
in this
which is unbelievable and the way they
do it with the beekeepers with this
specific one of energy actually gets
anyway
the spiritual connection with this
purpose is utterly insane like I'm all
about because Spirit of compassion in my
whole life you know helping people I'm
all about that connection if you guys
just came on here we're going to do a
live
meditation out of the book Soul light
infusion meditation
Dr Sherry green an amazing doctor by the
way Dr Sherry green beverage equality is
just beyond then using supplements in my
practice for 29 years that's a seasoned
doctor by the way never seen results
like these products the reason why Dr
Sherry green and you know why those four
tears
you'll never see supplement companies
out there say those four tiers
there's four points
you'll never see him out there saying
those four points Olivia let's let's
says vimorgy is so far beyond the best
it's incredible
and that's that's amazing
so what I do is for the meditation
so anytime I do the meditations right
well I'll do is the lemon balm that's
what I do every time so I find the lemon
balm is incredible because of the
relaxation it gives me and
I'm going to do some lemon balm before I
do the live meditation with you guys
because I'm going to be reading
the meditation someone to take
a couple of dropper folds here
so if you guys just came on here these
are the vimergy products that I talked
about if you just came on here watch the
video from the beginning
we're going to do live meditation but
I'm talking about
the four
like I say unbelievable points of why G
hands down is the best and companies
will not say those four points out there
they just won't people are always asking
me about what supplements I recommend I
can't say it every minute I got too much
work to do but I have to let you guys
know once in a while because people are
asking me asking me and the other thing
is
flu season Dr Sherry green do you know
that Dr Fawn MD you know that flu
season's coming into town it's gonna
come holidays
so anyway I'm going to take some lemon
balm before we start this live
meditation
bartender give me another
that's in a meditative way of saying it
versus when we're doing the brain
Challenge and I yell bartender give me
another one
so I take that for my nervous system
I take that
to just relax the nerves I've been going
since five o'clock this morning I'm
still going I had meetings today I've
been working all day
it's I'm not winding down yet
I took some lemon balm
clairvik says you did did light
meditation today incredible
incredible
that's amazing
yeah Michelle all says laugh out loud aw
in meditative mode in meditative mode
bartender give me another in meditative
mode
right
all right you guys so let's do the
meditation let's get into it a little
bit if you just got here watch this from
the beginning there's good information
in here
yep I'm excited so let's get into this a
little bit why not
so what I recommend is maybe just
chilling out relaxing why we do this
live meditation right here you can kick
back you can just listen you can sit on
the couch the whole bit
you can just like kick back all of it
let's get into it
this mic's very strong it picks up every
single
thing every noise so I can talk a little
lower okay
Soul light
infusion meditation right here
this is a powerful Soul healing
meditation
to mend fractures in the soul that have
collected throughout the years
as you experienced hardships
losses betrayal
broken trust in times of being
misunderstood
or if you fought battles against
Injustice in your life and lost
or if you feel you have lost a piece of
your soul and you're searching to get it
back
now let's begin the meditation
find yourself a safe comfortable place
to lie down
so find yourself a safe comfortable
place to lie down
if you need to do this meditation while
sitting up
that will work fine
once you are in a relaxing position
close your eyes
now take a deep breath in
and release
on the count of three
take another deep breath
one
two
three
deep breath in
and release
envision
tall staircase in the distance
you start heading in the direction of
the staircase
a misty fog starts to roll in
do you see the fog
you still see the staircase in the
distance
you keep walking in that direction
it's getting closer
you are almost there
just a few more steps
you are now at the bottom of the
staircase looking up
now take a deep breath in
and release
there are 21 steps
to the top of the staircase
do you see them
we are going to count each step together
as you climb the staircase
place your foot
on the first step
that is one
now place your other foot
on the Step Above This step
that is two
As You Are Climbing the staircase
in the fog
do any of these numbers have meaning for
you
now let's climb the rest of the steps
together
three
four
five
six
seven
eight
nine
you are now at the top of the staircase
a door opens
and appears
it is a portal
now take a deep breath in
and release
now grab the doorknob
and open the door to this portal
you enter into a dark
wide open space
there is no floor underneath you
you are floating
can you feel yourself floating
when you look up and around
you see glittering stars in the far
distance
look straight ahead
there is a ball of light heading your
way
do you see this light
get ready and put your hand out
you are going to catch the Light
here it comes
three
two
one grab onto it
you are now holding this light
now bring the light up to your forehead
and push it in
and let it enter your soul
another light in the distance is heading
your way
the light is coming closer to you
get ready to catch it with your hand
three
two
one
grab onto it
you are now holding this light
how does it feel to hold on to this
light
bring the light up to your forehead
and push it in and let it enter your
soul
foreign
there is another light in the distance
heading your way
do you see it
this light is brighter and larger
you need to catch this light
with both hands
the light is getting closer and closer
to you
get ready to catch it
three
two one grab onto it with both hands
do you see how beautiful this light is
in your hands
it is warm
soothing
comforting light
part of you is in this light
this part of you is pure untouched
uninjured
and has been kept safe
now bring the light up to your forehead
and push it in
and let it into your soul
do you feel the light inside your soul
now take a deep breath in
and release
on the count of three
take another deep breath
one
two
three
deep breath in
and release
now it's time to leave this space and
head back to the portal doorway
the door is still open
foreign
are you there yet
Are you standing at the top of the
staircase
grab the doorknob and close the door
behind you
the portal is now closed
it's time to descend back down the
staircase
one step at a time
let's count together with each step you
take get ready
three
two
one
take a deep breath in
and release
you can open your eyes
you have now completed the soul light
infusion meditation
any fractures within your soul are now
in the process of mending
as fractures mend your soul is healing
your soul is complete now and not
missing precious lost pieces that may
have been pushed away from you in times
of struggle
loss and hardship
your spiritual Force as a light being in
this world has elevated
Old Wounds from the past will not have a
grip upon your soul as they once did
no one owns your soul but you
and you have every right to heal your
soul
feel free to repeat this powerful
meditation daily or as many times as
needed to bring peace and healing to
your soul
that was the soul
the soul light infusion meditation live
right now
and the lemon balm really really felt
good I gotta say incredible it's out of
the brain saver books right here
that's a brain saver protocol book and
that's the brain saver book right there
that I'd show you guys
on Instagram I have been taking B12 for
a while the doctor always said you are
low on B12 when I discovered mm started
on vimergy B12 just two weeks ago did
blood work doctor told me B12 was
perfect it matters with B12
November gb12 being the quality is
critical and
there's no soy alcohol gluten citric
acid hidden things maltodextrin steroid
vinegar or whatever caffeine nothing in
there
uh SOG Lily says vimergy feels right in
the body
well it's that it's the whole thing
about the four things that I talk about
it's critical
Mark says I had no idea companies were
allowed to not disclose ingredients
that is exactly how it is companies are
able to hide ingredients up to a certain
percentage the law allows it
so label requirements allow companies to
not have to disclose all the little
hidden stuff in small percentages
beverages says they're not going to do
that
that alone is like drop the mic
I don't want to drop this one
it's really nice Mike
Brenda says vimergy supplements has made
a huge difference in my healing
difference in my healing and that's what
that's what's critical is having that
happen in your life Marissa spiritual
hey Marissa I truly notice a difference
in my health and healing when I was
without propolis for weeks I felt so
much once I was able to so much better
once I was able to have it again
it's in my state it's my staple in my
life all the time like regardless of
what I'm doing I'm always using the
memory probe was
Robin says I never took a vitamin I
could feel working like Imaging
and thousands feel that way it's that
important to have that it really is
all these things matter they just do and
if you guys I mean
seriously it's just it's crazy if you
don't know what it is it's V as in
Victor I am as in Mary e r g y so V as
in Victor i m is in Mary e r g y.com
themergy.com I fully endorse them
the highest degree I could ever endorse
any company
and and I'm proud to do that because I
want this stuff to be here I want the
stuff to stick around because we have to
have options that actually matter
it's no joke Claudia says I love the
meditation thank you so much I'm kind of
dizzy you're a little bit dizzy from the
meditation I would just sit that kick
back and relax
and uh Clement bomb just totally chilled
me out and that's what it does I take it
when I want to just I just want to
actually smooth out
see Leo Miller says since I started to
read the ingredients on the label
there's almost nothing to buy at the
stores it's insane how poisonous
everything on the product shelves are
what what I find is there's natural
flavors and everything which you guys
heard my natural flavors show probably
on medical medium podcast setup a
podcast natural flavors and all this
other stuff that's in their citric acid
and all this other junk and the image
you won't do that
and so they they had they adhere to a
standard that I can't find anywhere
it's it's on all levels though with them
it's just incredible
um Catherine Blake what is the list of
Energy Products and where do you get
your vitamin C so
that's of energy product right there if
energy has a lot of products
all of them are at the highest quality
with that four the four things I keep on
telling you guys so critical
Elena says aw how much problems you take
you could take what's on that stuff is
so incredible you could take what's just
right on the bottle
it's amazing that's the micro C right
there I'm running low
had that bottle for a while
Denise said vimergy is the best memory G
is the best been on these supplements
for 15 months
incredible
and I'm so proud of you too because you
know when you stay with something and
keep it in your routine
so yeah it's just it's just amazing so I
wanted to tell you guys about that so
with the flu and everything coming and
all that if you watch this from the
beginning I talked about that so I was
talking to a doctor friend he was like
aren't you supposed to be telling your
people because it's it's happening
is very much he so here's a comment is
memory better than an injection for
vitamin B12 if you read the medical
medium books you can learn a lot about
that so
you can take a look at the medical mean
books and learn a lot about that Patty
says meditation brought tears to my eyes
I feel a high level of Soul healing
going on excited for future meditations
I want to offer everything I can offer
that comes from above so you have these
tools
Kelly Burke says I didn't notice a
difference with my body pain until I
started taking beverages propolis
Nature's answer didn't even touch it now
I'm not going to mention any other
company names or anything like that I'm
just saying that
that I'll tell you right now the memory
propolis is unlike anything there is and
there's a reason though there's a reason
number one
there's no alcohol
but companies still can have alcohol in
their propolis
regardless and remember she doesn't have
that's number one just so you know
number two is
the propolis that they actually
Harvest that's harvested for it I'm just
saying that nothing nothing's like it
out there I mean I don't even know
there's no words actually
see a pregrino says I have reversed all
of my symptoms from your information
I mean that's everything
when you have symptoms and you're
struggling and all that that's
incredible
I'm proud of you truly proud of you
so
you know I just want you guys to know
how it works out there I think that's
what has happened over the years is I've
always told you guys how things work out
there like all the hidden secrets all
that stuff that happens out there and
that's one of the things I've been able
to tell you guys and teach you guys
through the books and the information
Marissa spiritual said this was amazing
Anthony my husband joined me for the
meditation so special that's incredible
God bless you guys that's amazing really
Rose Jackson says doing that meditation
collectively just then with the
community was very heartwarming oh it is
really heartwarming it truly is
it really is Carrie Llewellyn says thank
you so much Anthony such a beautiful
meditation I feel totally relaxed and
sleepy again I feel relaxed because I
got my lemon
balmergillon bomb which is a whole other
thing by the way it's really potent too
which is incredible
the potency is just off the charts which
is what I really love
which is incredible and I don't have to
worry I don't have to be in fear knowing
that companies or this company is hiding
a certain percentage of ingredients
because they're allowed to do that
right companies are allowed to hide a
certain small percentage of ingredients
that are hidden in here that I don't
even know what they are I don't have to
have fear
I don't have to think well what is that
is it MSG is it something else like
what's hid I don't have to think that
like it gives me peace and the one thing
I can tell you right now and why I fully
endorse Bemidji is because I I want to
have peace in my heart and my soul and I
want to be able to feel that energy and
have peace that I'm not being tricked or
something isn't not disclosed in the
supplement like I don't I don't I have a
hard enough life like you guys you know
like all that you know you go through in
life
you don't need that you know
have you been joining me on the medical
media brain shot therapy challenge
tomorrow is day nine the nerve shifter
it's a brain shot therapy the nerve
shifter you can catch the replays on
medicalme.com for free free free
download your free pdf so you can know
your grocery shopping lists we can do it
tomorrow how incredible is that
day nines tomorrow
Michelle L right isn't that true it's
awful right I know
so Kerry says memory curcumin helps my
burning skin tremendously
I mean
that matters
it just does
Elena says with Bemidji you can notice a
difference right away it matters it all
does samima says I am
converting converting everyone in my
extended family one at a time to
remember G Subs the products are
unmatched for sure
they just are
it's it's like this okay
if another company comes along and can
top themergy
then guess what you'll be seeing that
those products if it can top it I
haven't seen it yet there is no company
in my opinion that can top it and I'm
waiting and I haven't seen anything
so this is the best it gets and it's
incredible in my opinion absolutely
incredible Michelle L propolis really
helps with shingles after shingles
flares after emotional hits of
adrenaline
um Penta says High ew
this is uh Margarita I am doing all the
10-day brain shots
incredible and feel very good thank you
for all that you do and thank you SOC
thank you for being here you're on
Facebook that's awesome thank you for
being on there tonight I don't know how
you found your way here because
sometimes it's hard to find the lives
and thank you for being here that's
incredible on Facebook Jackie yes it is
awesome doing it live
I just wanted to try to do this
meditation live because why not why not
I'm winding down at the end of the day
and it feels good because I'm doing the
meditation with you even though I'm
reading it I'm still doing it with you
Michelle Wallace's first meditation I
ever tried love it amazing on Facebook
incredible
I love this meditation it's powerful and
there's other meditations in the brain
saver books when you guys see him you'll
see them I mean how incredible Allison
says I've I'm zoned out
that's awesome
Cold Light spring says I can't believe
you did this meditation now
it may it was it was really special
when do I do that when do I do that
Babylon says vemergy is literally the
only brand I'll take you can feel its
energy instantly in your body made with
love
there's a reason why it's because when
they choose the highest tier instead of
the lower high qualities here there's a
high high quality tier companies don't
choose those High tiers because it costs
too much and so they they but vimorigi
doesn't care about the bottom line
profit margin they just want to make
sure they get the highest quality there
is that's why part of why you feel it
another thing is there's no there's no
you know hidden undisclosed gradients
and stuff like that all kinds of stuff
Carrie Llewellyn says vimergy microc is
the only vitamin C I can take that does
not irritate my stomach that's the whole
point I'm going to tell you right now
that it's the only buffered one like
buffered it's not ascorbic acid and
that's critical
that's critical I have a lot of doctor
friends that are using the micro C now
because it's they're learning that when
they give their patients ascorbic acid
like straight ascorbic acid
they get the funny tummy and so I have a
lot of doctor friends that are actually
like learning about using the
non-ascorbic acid
I mean all this stuff matters who does
this like who does this well companies
do this
it's insane
Darcy Lee Womack says my daughter is
using the vimergy products and your
protocol for acne she had a meeting with
her teacher and she said she was so much
calmer
amazing
said she was so much calmer and much
less nervous she said that not only is
the acne healing but other things is
healing too and changing oh my God so
happy for your information awsoc and
you're on Facebook incredible
that's amazing
well incredible you guys
I know may you said I can't believe you
did the meditation now it's funny
amazing
incredible you guys so if you just got
in here watch this video from the
beginning you can find it on my website
find the video on my website
medicalme.com by the way you guys I'm
I'm totally totally vamping up the
website like we're we're doing all kinds
of stuff there like
so you have free access to tremendous
amounts of information like you always
have but up totally upgrading and
upgrading and enhancing so the place is
just a great home to be in
medicalmedium.com
and uh and guess what there's no paywall
anywhere
if you go on medicalme.com
there's no paywall anywhere
and I'll do a free meditation just like
this with you guys right from my own
book number one New York Times look I'm
going to prop myself up okay since I'm
always like acting like I'm just you
know whatever
number one New York Times best-selling
author
the number one
selling Health author in the world for
eight years running
and I'm sitting here with you guys
because guess what you guys
are like everything
and you're incredible and you better
believe I'm gonna be sitting here and
doing this meditation with you guys I'll
do it any day
by the way uh so medical medium Candace
it's uh excellent customer service at
Bemidji they got the best customer
service
it's ridiculous
it's ridiculous it's the best customer
service
Nancy carmeli says I've never been able
to take supplements until I tried memory
because
they know about sensitive people they
care about sensitive people
they know
that sense of people need to take
supplements and they need to actually it
needs to work it needs to feel good
incredible
Austin Celia says I love the new topic
PDFs on the new website they look
amazing and then the information is very
clear and digestible and credible
incredible
I'm proud of you guys truly
so you guys I can't wait for tomorrow is
day nine the medical meme brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge
and I'm pumped up
hopefully everything's right with this
mic and it's got a good sound
and everything
this fancy mic I have in front of me all
right you guys I love you dearly God
bless God bless you guys keep a light
heart always remember that keep a light
heart
storms will pass
okay love you guys