out the brain and short circuiting
you know it's crazy when I think about
things you guys
brain saver I'm going to read out of it
I'm also going to make a detox bitters
juice which is really cool helping to
detox various chemicals out of the brain
which is needed now you don't believe me
you don't believe people have chemicals
inside their brain and everything else
check this out a friend of mine was at a
college football game recently
and there was like 80 000 students
in the stands right out there watching
it and he was telling me that he thought
about it and so he asked me some
questions he said
how many students are on Adderall
how many
and so I was like oh well let me just
kind of try to figure that out talk to
Spirit of compassion a little bit
it's a lot
huge amounts so bottles of Adderall and
purses bottles of Adderall in people's
cars bottles in their pockets pills in
their pockets pills and their purses
pills in their wallets
pills in their bloodstream
you got 80 000 students
almost all of them not all of them
almost all of them are on Adderall
and why and then their parents are
taking them to the doctor's office right
and so you got all those doctors think
about that
thousands and thousands of doctors
because all those 80 000 students aren't
all going to the same doctor so you have
thousands of doctors
handing out Adderall
so the students
can actually have some clarity to get
out of their focus and concentration
problems
and at the same time those thousands and
thousands of doctors don't know why the
students are having
focus and concentration problems think
about how insane this all is this is
think about that it's utterly insane
so and that's just one thing right and
then out of the 80 000 students watching
a big football game
how many students are on antidepressants
and anti-anti-anxiety meds and that's
something SOC told me so well you're
forgetting about aw you're forgetting
about the anti-anxiety meds and the
antidepressants so you got out of the 80
000 students watching a football game
the majority
think about this so SOC told me the
majority of the 80 000 students watching
the football game are also on an
antidepressant or an anti-anxiety Med
think about that one
at the same time the majority are on
Adderall
at that same time at the same time not
one doctor out of tens of thousands of
Physicians knows why
all those students can't focus and
concentrate without drugs
now you think science research has it
all
bagged up you think they got it all down
you think they have all the answers
signs of research doesn't know why
those 80 000 students can't focus and
concentrate and need drugs to focus in
concentrate all those doctors who are
so-called under Sciences whatever don't
know why the kids have anxiety
depression can't focus can't concentrate
ADHD and everything else and they have
to be on Adderall and antidepressants
and anti-anxiety meds
so you have medical research and science
has no idea
you got all the doctors that have no
idea and all the kids
are going to the doctors because Mom and
Dad are bringing all the students to the
doctors
thinking that science and research has
it all sewed up
and so they're bringing their children
into the doctor's office and the doctors
is just like oh you can't focus and
concentrate you can't do your school
studies you can't keep up with your
schedule here's another bottle of
Adderall
oh you're depressed you got anxiety
here's another bottle of anti-anxiety
meds when you think about it it's
totally insane
just think about that
so what none of them know
none of the moms and dads none of the
doctors none of the research and science
people behind it all they don't know
what causes all those problems they have
no idea so think about
what an insane world we live in
now how come I have to be this messenger
getting information from above
that's way ahead of science and research
it's way ahead of the doctors handing
out all the Adderall how come I have to
be this Messenger to why
those 80 000 students
in an arena like that watching a game
are loaded with drugs getting filled up
with drugs now it is possible that
medical research decides never wants to
know the answer because that's a lot of
drugs so when you think about how much
Adderall was in their purses their
pockets
their wallets their cars in their
bloodstream how many antidepressants and
anti-anxiety meds were in their
bloodstream their purses their pockets
their wallets their cars
and and their apartments on campus
how many of those drugs
are in there and if you added all those
up with the majority of 80 000 students
if you added all those drugs up
it would make a mountain a small
mountain of prescription bottles
not to mention the black market drugs
too for focusing concentration right
it would pile up
a massive pile of drugs
that all the students are on
but yet medical research and science nor
do the doctors nor do the parents have
any idea why their students their
children and their patients have to be
on all those drugs to get by and focused
and concentrate and try to do school
studies
and whatever and keep up with their
partying or whatever that they're doing
and be able to do that it's incredible
right
when medical research and science has no
idea about
there are answers
of why
people are dealing with that that's just
something to think about when I think
about it and might be something to think
about when you guys think about because
oh my God anyway I'm going to be reading
some killer information something called
melting down in the brain say rebook I'm
also making a recipe just so you know
making the brain detox bitters recipe
right there
which is really fun because
I couldn't wait to make this one you see
some apples right there you see some
spinach right here look at this really
nice you see some dandelions these are
wild
actually dandelions
you see some kale right there
Dinosaur Kale
so I'm gonna make that bitters so it's a
brain detox bitters drink which is
really good have you guys tried it from
the brain saver protocols book
it's really cool I'm excited Deanna says
I have seen ads on TV for lawyers asking
if you have kids with autism and did you
feed them baby food and they say that
those foods have been found to be
contaminated with heavy metals
interesting
well Deanna
science research nor any lawyers or
anything
knows or knew that toxic heavy metals
are responsible for kids with autism
having autism or ADHD that is original
medical medium information going all the
way back
so that's poaching with no science
behind it
so that's really interesting lawyers
aren't going to be finding any people to
find any science behind that at all it's
not going to even happen that they can
link that and that was only considered
being a possible link to it through
medical medium information
that I've been teaching for years not to
mention the published material
so this broke that out to the world
millions and millions and millions of
copies of the cause true cause of ADHD
and autism including lectures and other
work that I've done prior and during so
that's the only reason why you can even
see that notice go out there and add
running saying that Metals could be
linked to autism because it's all
original medical medium information and
those are poachers
and that's whatever so
here's the sad part with the lawyers or
whoever are poachers involved in that ad
or whatever that campaign is
they will not cite back where they got
the original medical medium information
so
the kids
and the babies can get the toxic heavy
metals out
of their brain
those kids will never get the medals out
of their brain ever
to help with autism or ADHD unless it
was cited to a source where there are
actual books information
and so many people who have gotten the
metals out of the brain and recovered
from so many different conditions so
that's what's really sad about that and
that's the disgusting part of what you
saw in that ad they're not saying
but we have answers to help all those
kids that somehow got contaminated with
toxic heavy metals because the answers
came originally from medical medium so
let's figure out how to get rid of those
Metals but they'll never do that and
that's how like grotesque all of it
really is guys I'm excited about this
and this is fun stuff we're talking
about too at the same time
so I just want to say a couple things
right here
one is
that's the recipe I'm making
okay I'm excited I got everything here
that I need
and I am going to even get my little
foot stand out here so I want to read a
little bit here
now to get give everybody a 4-1-1 we're
about to make a juice which I'm excited
about
to detox bitters but I'm going to talk
about different chemicals and things
like that how the brain works and all
that with just a little bit of the
information from brain saver which I'm
excited about
and you guys Black Friday was yesterday
people are asking me left and right like
what's the best this what's the best
that I'm going to be using the mm1500 25
off
check it out right there link is in the
description in the profile but it's 25
off you can get a free cleanse the heel
book with it
and the mm-1500 is insanely awesome I'll
go into that a little bit too if you got
suckered into another juicer I feel bad
because this I don't know if you know
saves money
and the other juicer companies I noticed
and the influencers that are pushing
those other juicers think everybody's
rich
and you can just throw away produce when
you juice it's really sad I'll talk
about that more later it's interesting
you guys I'm excited let's go
I'm reading something called melting
down right here
page 30
in brain saver
when our brains get hot and there's
metal involved
this is a big deal the toxic heavy metal
particles break down
so first of all
that is so Advanced that information
right there I'm just reading one line
out of brain saver
and it's mind-blowing just that one line
so when our brains get hot and there's
metal involved
the toxic heavy metal particles break
down the metals melt
besides research doesn't know that
I'll talk about why it's so important to
know this
and yeah
toxic heavy metals in the brain get wear
and tear when electrical currents are
entering them
so you got all this electricity right
here electricity is running through the
brain
running through the neurons
and as electricity is hitting tiny tiny
the active particles tiny tiny
septoparticles hitting these tiny metal
particles this Nano metal
it starts to melt down
foreign piece of information right there
when electrical currents are entering
them they start to change
so the metal in everybody's branding
remember I opened this up talking about
Adderall I was opening up talking about
the drugs all the students are on all
the kids are on I talked about all of
that if you guys just got on here I just
did a whole talk about that
well with the ADHD all the different
focusing concentration problems we're
dealing with a metal
Alicia says can't decide which juicer to
get 1500 900 I can just only say this
from my experience
is that
um the 1500 does other things so it's
incredible not only does it have that
high compression where you can actually
squeeze out so much juice and save money
the other thing it does is it makes it
makes like hummus and it makes salsa and
it makes
ice cream and it makes like you know
what I mean it's incredible what it does
nut Butters and nut milks it's insane
really
all right so I'm in rice Melton says
what that chapter is I'm on page 30. I'm
on alloy bringing
right and it's blowing your mind
incredible
Cornelius says every line of brain saver
is amazing every line it really is it's
actually blows my mind every time
so
as the electrical electrical currents
are entering
the metal
they start to change
their shapes change
she got all these people that are
dealing with anxiety depression OCD
depersonalization bipolar
right
and they're dealing with all these
different issues focus and concentration
this is just some I'm only mentioning a
couple of different conditions
and as they're dealing with that they're
dealing with electrical currents
entering into these tiny little reactive
particles these tiny little
nanoparticles of metal and then changing
the metal inside their brain
so the shapes of the metal start to
change
corrosion then occurs
the smaller the particles the more
easily they melt under the heat of the
brain
and here's the thing if metals are in
the brain getting people more emotional
speaking for people when people don't
want that the metals are actually
controlling people and that's what the
industries love
one thing the industries do know is they
know Metals will mess your head up
and then you'll require lots of
pharmaceuticals see how it works lots of
metal inside your brain will mess you up
so that you're in the need for lots of
drugs that's how the game works
so these Metals this shape changes
corrosion can occur the smaller the
particles the more easily they melt
under the heat of the brain and here's
where I'm going back to this so when
metals get us really depressed and then
we're really upset because their
depression is torturing us
more heat is generated
if metals are giving us anxiety and
we're suffering from anxiety and
struggling from anxiety
it's more heat on the brain more heat on
the metal particles
if someone's bipolar and they're really
up and down and they're manic they're in
Mania and they're just ore in this anger
this this unbelievable anger occurrence
for things that they shouldn't be angry
about because they're suffering and
they're struggling mentally emotionally
it's more heat generating
which actually puts more heat into the
particles of metal that are inside their
brain
when toxic heavy metals that reside in
the brain melt they transform into a
liquid gas chemical composition
but guys is like
seriously when I got that piece of
information
of compassion my mind was blown
the thing is is research and science
doesn't know any of this
unless they poach this
piece of information which probably will
someone will poach it
so when toxic heavy metals that reside
in the brain melt
they transform into a liquid gas
chemical composition that is the metals
change from a solid to a liquid gas
and can spread and cover more ground
inside the brain more easily
so our electricity is melting these tiny
ectochemicals size chemicals
these tiny septal chemicals these tiny
nanochemicals or brain electricities
melting them they're then turning into a
liquid gas and then they're traveling
through the brain more easily and that's
why someone's condition gets worse as
years go by or months go by next thing
you know it Adderall is not cutting it
for their focus and concentration next
thing you know they're antidepressant is
making them feel worse next thing you
note their anti their anti-anxiety meds
are making them feel worse next thing
you know they're getting worse overall
and they're having more struggles and
more problems because those metals are
turning into liquid gas and then
spreading
through the brain
a little mm school today you guys know I
was going to come out and do some mm
School
too funny I'm reading right out of brain
saver if you guys just got here 40 it's
even 41 off I think 42 off
something like that amazon.com get them
for presents and stuff if you're out
there looking for deals and stuff these
are Bibles they're thick they're filled
with information
over 40 off
it's insane the price you can get them
at amazon.com us it's actually insane
it's
I feel like it's an Angelic blessing to
make it affordable for people that's
really a special thing
this means that as toxic heavy metals in
the brain heat up and melt you guys they
move
and they can slowly travel to adjacent
brain tissue over the years they melt
they turn into liquid gas and they move
and they travel so that mercury moves
and travels slowly as the years go by
melting toxic heavy metals in the brain
are one reason why so many conditions
and symptoms Alzheimer's is just one
example that's just one
for example worsens with time the gas
alone can worsen any any mental physical
or emotional condition
any physical emotional mental condition
worsens from that moving metal that
turned into gas transformed into gas
from electrical heat that's occurring
another reason brain conditions worsen
with time is that more toxic heavy
metals continue to collect in certain
areas of the brain
the brain's electromagnetic field draws
metal in
nobody knows that
there's no Neuroscience guy there's no
Neuroscience doctor there's no
Neuroscience lady there's no
Neuroscience anybody it's just
unbelievable when this information came
through
I was just like are you just as like
unbelievable are you kidding
so another reason brain conditions worse
than with time is that more toxic heavy
metals continue to collect in certain
areas of the brain the brain's
electromagnetic electromagnetic field
draws Metals in nobody knows that the
brain has an electromagnetic field
nobody knows that it draws Metals in
that's just incredible creating in a
an accumulation effect
that makes large deposits of toxic heavy
metals keep growing so what that means
you guys is pockets of metals that
reside inside the brain
grow
they grow because of an electromagnetic
effect that the brain has as more toxic
heavy metals enter to your Bot into your
body whether it's Pharmaceuticals
and that's the other crazy thing
you got all these students on
Pharmaceuticals so they can focus and
concentrate
and at the same time the metals in these
Pharmaceuticals
are actually accumulating they're going
into pockets in areas of the brain and
building up Bigger Pockets in areas of
the brain
the larger the deposit the greater it's
electromagnetic pull
meaning that it will keep attracting
toxic heavy metals into it making the
deposit larger and larger over time
so what this is saying
is that the more metals that are being
electromagnetically brought in
attracting to the deposits that are
already there that exist more metals
that go into those deposits
make it so the deposits grow but the
electromagnetic field gets stronger in
those deposits attracting even more
metal as time goes on
well the brain's electromagnetic field
is drawing toxic heavy metals into other
areas of the brain too the metals tend
to accumulate where the field is
stronger due to these nuggets
of toxic heavy metals we got Nuggets in
our heads
so if you got 80 000 students watching a
college football game in the stands and
the majority are on all of these drugs
to manage
their mental emotional physical problems
they have with their brain
nuggets are being created inside their
head
nuggets of electromagnetic pull
occurring
where
they're 18 right now they're 19 years
old they're 20 they're 21 they're 22 but
when they're 41 42 43 44 and they got
these nuggets inside their head that
have been there way too long and their
conditions have worsened over the years
no one's done anything for them doesn't
they don't even understand how they even
got there to that position they're still
on drugs most of them probably if not
even more
it's really sad when you think about it
when I'm reading out of brain saver
mind-blowing information brain saver and
I got brain saver protocols right here
you guys I'm excited I'm on page 31 of
brain saver I got brain saver protocols
we're going to be making brand detox
bitters
because it's really helpful for our
brains in so many different ways these
are the greatest books of all time
since nobody challenges me
on any debates or anything
since nobody says hey let's actually
have that guy debate a neuroscience guy
they won't do it
because they really can't talk about
anything they don't really know anything
they'll give you the five best reasons
why maybe you can get a better sleep at
night they'll tell you make sure you
make your bed all nice
it'll tell you make sure you get off
your phone
they'll say that five best tips of how
that's that's what that's what
Neuroscience has now that's all you got
articles five best tips to how to sleep
better make sure you're off your devices
before bed
that's like f you man how stupid
they have no answers whatsoever
on any level about why anybody's brains
are all funked and having problems and
symptoms and conditions and at the same
time they'll give you like the best they
can do right now is the newest article
out there is how to sleep better by
neuroscientist blah blah blah make sure
you shut your devices off before bed
everybody make sure you make your bed
before you go to bed make sure you just
do a little meditation before bed okay
great tell that person who's suffering
with the worst panic attacks the worst
the worst anxiety the worst depression
the worst bipolar the worst OCD the
worst anything yeah that'll fix them and
get answers that'll really work
when it comes to Mercury did I really
say F you that's just terrible when it
comes to Mercury deposits
they're not just formed through
electromagnetic pool Mercury doesn't
need this electromagnetic field to
accumulate in the brain even though it
uses the electromagnetic field Mercury
finds Mercury on its own that's another
thing research and science says now
Mercury inside the brain causing autism
and ADHD nocd and Alzheimer's and
Dementia or anything else anxiety
depression Mercury that's inside our
brain
actually Builds on itself Mercury
attracts Mercury that's one of the
metals that actually attracts itself
when it's inside our brain especially
so Mercury doesn't need this
electromagnetic field to accumulate in
the brain Mercury finds Mercury on its
own with Mercury deposits forming in the
brain both from electromagnet magnetic
fields and from Mercury's tendency to
find Mercury Mercury finds itself
Mercury deposits are that much more of a
hindrance this is why Mercury really
sucks
and people are filled with it inside
their brains
and so when you think about the 80 000
students that are watching a college
football game
are screaming and yelling and cheering
but they're all drugged up
almost all of them
one way or another
when you think about that
and you got to realize how much mercury
is in all of their brains and how that
works
that's just unbelievable
if we're experiencing a lot of friction
and stress in our lives electricity
travels through our brain at a higher
intensity and velocity
so if you're up against some friction
if you're up against some stress
electricity is flying through your brain
we're talking about a whole nother
velocity going on there
because adrenaline both increases heart
rate and enters the brain raising the
brain's heat levels
if you're under stress you've got
adrenaline Brewing now if you're under
stress you got adrenaline cooking that's
what you have right that's just how life
Works Beverly says wish I knew this 40
years ago
first person that came to see me when I
opened my office 40 years ago almost
the first person that's came to see me
and found answers
said I wish I knew this 40 years ago
and that was almost 40 years ago
I was just reading an Amazon review
of someone saying that the brain saver
books are incredible
and then saying I worked with Anthony
William personally many many years ago
don't quote me on exact the exact
wording but many many years ago
and he saved my life
and then they wrote this Amazon review
it's really cool it was really cool it
was cool to see when you've helped out
people so many years ago long before the
books came out and you helped out people
and you saved their lives it's just it's
such a blessing that's why I just love
being here doing this that's why when
people don't cite the medical meme
information they make others lose out on
so much precious material and time and
precious things and many times decades
later they might find mm then but they
lost two decades or a decade of like
time
again the more toxic heavy metals in the
brain the hotter it runs if you have
more it's like a vicious cycle check
this out
the more Metals you have in your brain
the more problems we have emotionally
mentally and physically
but the more problems we have
emotionally mentally and physically we
feel more stress and get upset
so therefore we get suspicious cycle we
get upset or stressed out
and then that's cranking up the heat
melting more metal
and moving more metal around in our
brain
we don't know why we're sick we don't
know why we're mentally emotionally
physically sick or struggling the metals
are actually doing it in our brain
the more upset we get the more the
metals move
and we can't do anything about it
because we don't understand it so we're
caught in this Catch-22 this vicious
cycle
so the more toxic heavy metals in the
brain the hotter it runs and again
Metals retain the heat that's a whole
other problem medical research and
science don't realize this metal is
inside your brain those yactoseized
Metals in the brain they retain heat
causing an additional healing up inside
your brain
it can become a vicious cycle
for instance someone who's perpetually
angry about anything and everything
or who has frequent spells of anger may
have higher levels of toxic heavy metals
in the brain in the first place that are
aggravating that anger you guys I'm
reading out of brain saver amazon.com us
over 40 off like 42 off or something
like it's incredible right now
amazon.com us you want both books I
promise you this you want both of them
because they were one book you want both
and we're gonna be making this I have
the juicer out you see some spinach here
some kale here some dandelion green some
wild dandelion greens and you see some
apples
it's gonna be fun
all right
as he is generated for any reason
the metals change shape and form those
anger spells will then generate more
heat as anger raises the electrical
field creating an electrical storm
which in turn melts more metal so that
it spreads and has the potential to
interfere with even more electrical
signals in the brain making us mental
making us emotional
making us mental emotional and
physically
struggling
those melting toxic heavy metals
spreading their liquid gas can hinder
bodily functions and communication
because I just read
a half a page less than half a page from
here to here I've read a little bit off
of page 30 and I read
um just a little bit of a half of a
section in page 31 just now brain saver
that alone what you have to know this
that's why these are the greatest books
of all time
hands down I could say that I can judge
these books just like anybody else can
and and that's what I do when Spirit of
compassion is giving me the information
from above I can be I can have my own
opinion
and they are the greatest books of all
time and I'm going to tell you what's so
incredible about this I only read a
little tidbit inside
the brain saver book
but even that little tidbit beats out
any kind of Neuroscience theories that
are out there now in anywhere it beats
out any information known in clinics
about what's wrong with people with
these symptoms and conditions
it supersedes medical research and
Science by light years actually
that's what it does and I just read a
little bit that's why these are the
greatest books of all time
but that's just one little thing you got
the brain shot therapies that give us
instant relief in these books if you you
guys are trying the brain shot therapies
right
we did the brain shot therapy challenge
that alone is just unbelievable and
there's so much more in these books I
just wanted everybody to know
take advantage of the sale right now
that's happening in the books of answers
to what to do not just information that
blows your mind but answer is on what to
do and it's got the heavy metal detox
cleanses seven
medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanses that work
that's the difference there too that
actually work
and that's the difference all on its own
right there it's mind-blowing
let's make some juice
let's make some juice you guys I'm
pumped up about that
all right so this is a detox bitters
juice Spirit of compassion gave me this
recipe
I put it in the book
which I'm excited about
I got my I did I tell you what I was
doing you guys with my tea now
Brittany Lee says what is the best for
getting rid of depression anxiety and
depersonalization do you have the books
they are so packed with that information
there's chapters in here on depression
and anxiety like you can't go wrong when
you see what's in here the like the
chapters are absolutely incredible
and the book covers will even say
it might say anxiety in that book cover
right there it does anxiety right there
and it says depression too right on the
cover
so check it out when you get a chance so
worth it really
Kim Miller the nerve gut acid stabilizer
is healing my vagus nerve and digestion
like no other and it that's what I love
to hear I love to know that you have
this option you actually have this
so it's here for you and that's what
it's all about you guys have been doing
this right you know like the MRG
beverages got a sale right now Black
Friday take advantage of it people ask
me about supplements all the time
it's what they do all the time
and uh
I'm putting two dropper fulls right
there
you know I fully endorsed imagery I'm
not going to go into all the details
because I always do I sit here and I
just go into all the details all the
time but I gotta make a juice but I
endorse them anyway what I did was I put
the lemon balm their incredible lemon
balm right there what I'm finding is I
used you know I used to always recommend
like the traditional medicinals teas and
stuff and and other teas that I like too
that are actually really good but I like
something more potent more powerful so
what I've been doing and because that's
the best lemon balm right there you can
get anywhere right and lemon balm is a
commentative it's for the nerves and
it's a commentative right and
so what I'm doing now is I got rid of
tea altogether not all together some
teas I like but I got rid of some for
sure because this is way better so what
I do is I take the hot water like that
and I put
the purest form the best form that I
could ever find ever because this is the
material the medicinal version of it
right and I put it right there and
that's what I do now for lemon balm tea
hmm
so good
I love that it's the biggest sale of the
year at themergy.com these invictor I am
is Mary ergy.com take advantage of it
it's the biggest sale of the year right
now so I'm just letting you know get on
vimorgies newsletter that's important
too so you can know what they offer
which is a big deal anyway you guys
let's make some juice I'm excited
let's get the stuff ready
Marcy said what about hibiscus and
raspberry leaf tea you can get those two
out there it's incredible Jackie B says
Bemidji is more potent than the actual
tea I've noticed well that's the whole
point that's why I've actually just it's
a massive upgrade
so that's what I do Jackie B is it's
it's a whole other game and that's all
that matters always it's always about
getting the best you can get Phyllis
said there's not enough words or emotion
to describe how fortunate I feel to be
part of this community the medical
medium Community I'm at your service too
here and the thing is though what's
incredible about the medical medium
Community is people who have been
through hell and back they've actually
been scammed out there over and over
again they left the Colts out there the
big alternative medicine cult out there
which is all saying the same thing like
they're all saying the same thing that's
when you know it's a cult right anyway
the point is they left those Cults out
there
and they found a place where you got
your free will your freedom you can you
can actually
um customize your healing process
through the medical beam information
it's not man-made so none of the
information is man-made it comes from
above so it gives us freedom and it's
such a great community and most
importantly
um most importantly too I wanted to
mention a couple other things the
incredible thing about the medical
medium Community is people who actually
really do care
they actually have compassion for like
others because I see like I say I'm at
your service but you know what I see
people in the medical meme Community
they actually are at other people's
service too they care
they're actually like always trying to
help it's an incredible community and
it's really special it really is so you
guys there's cold and flu protocols and
brain saver just so you know so in the
brain saver books brain saver protocols
cold and flu protocols in here including
for children keep that in mind as well
which is incredible too
all right so I'm gonna make some juice
the bidders detox
so get this thing running right here
three to five apples
I'm gonna push some apples in there okay
now we're gonna do three to five apples
we're gonna do some kale we're gonna do
some spinach we're gonna do some
dandelion greens
I like this detox bitters because it
tastes good too which is incredible and
what it does
for the brain so I'm gonna chop up some
apples if you guys don't mind right
so three to five apples
so I'm gonna get my apples going
get another Apple too let me run some
through
now remember with this juicer it's not
only a cold pressed juicer right and it
doesn't have metal touching metal it's
which is incredible about this juicer
but it's got that compression
so it has that celery attachment that
compression going on there so what that
does is it makes it so you're saving
money
so this juicer paid for itself over and
over again and I was talking about like
the other juices out there the juicer
sharks I call them that that enter into
the medical medium community and they
try to rip people off what happens is
that they know their juicer doesn't do
this
they know that it doesn't save people
money
but they push it anyway and they noticed
that some of the influencers that are
well known out there they're like
well-known influencers that stand behind
those juicers right
they're involved in those juicers
they have plenty of money
they don't know what it's like to be
wondering like am I going to be able to
buy food this week and if I want to heal
myself I need to be able to save money
somehow they don't they don't care about
that
so what I like about this and the reason
why I stand behind the mm 1500 900 and
I've worked with the mega is because we
all cared about that see the difference
so we're like how are we gonna do this
where we can get like people to save
money while healing so the juicer pays
for itself
that's what it was about and it wasn't
about instead selling them a fancy fancy
juicer that pay a lot of money for and
they can just throw away produce
now
food prices are rising Spirit of
compassion's holy food prices were gonna
rise
years ago
and
that's why I wanted to make sure
that if you're gonna be like making
medicine with your juicer you not only
have a cold pressed juicer to do so but
you have a juicer that's saving you
money and it's squeezing more out of
your food that you're putting through it
you see how it works
Now the recipe we're doing is on page
right here it's on 304 of the protocols
book it is called brain detox bitters
that's the recipe we're making right now
you guys excited about this
so I'm putting a couple of apples in
here
I think that's good
maybe I'll put one more
so it's three to five apples in the
recipe I just did two apples
now here's how it works
with this juicer
the pulp comes out extremely dry so it's
in the process of extracting as much as
it possibly can out of your produce
that's the difference
so the reason why the mm-1500 and the
mm-900 came about was because it was
about making medicine for people to heal
like it's doing their celery juice every
single day
doing their juices every single day
and saving money at the same time
and then not having Metal Gears touch
each other like this touch itself the
metal gears
wearing and tearing on itself you know
what that means when Metal's doing this
you know what happens right
yep you want to choose so that doesn't
just rip up the juice in a few seconds
spit it out throw out a lot of the juice
and also
heat up everything so this is a cold
pressed masticating juicer so it's not
heating up everything people don't
realize those other juicers with the
basket and everything the heating that
occurs it's ripping it up spitting it
out and then what happens is sure it
might be fun for a second but at the
same time you're spilling out all this
money out of your wallet to buy more
produce to feed that machine it becomes
like a monster you can't give it enough
produce to get you enough juice you have
to do so much more and that's why you'll
even see when the influencers use them
that are behind them they're jumping in
so much produce to get their thing of
juice but so much is going through there
it's like oh yeah sure everybody's Rich
they can do what you're doing there
because apparently you're not worried
about anything so you must have a lot of
money to just be throwing it out and
down the drain like that and the funny
thing is is that it's like I know I'm
being sarcastic but I'm saying this
because they know there's a juicer that
does save you money and they're not like
you know what there's people who are
chronically sick
and you know let's you know there's
people that are chronically sick so
let's get them what they need and stuff
like that it's just it's really
ridiculous how it works I'm gonna drop
some kale in here next actually
so the thing is about
um
now what you're watching right now is
the Kale's coming through
you're watching pulp that's really
really dry that's what you're seeing
it's almost Dusty dry that's how like
dry it gets there's not going to be any
liquid inside that container right there
so I'm dropping some kale into this
because it's part of the recipe it's two
cups of loosely packed kale
I'm gauging it to what I'm used to doing
to get us too cuffs
so I'm running this um
dinosaur Tail in
now you would need with other juicers so
much more pimp now what you're seeing
right here is dry
so that's dry
so people wonder about like my integrity
and stuff they'll be like oh the medical
media whatever it's like oh yeah well
what that does is it saves people who
have chronic illness money
it's people who have chronic illness
don't have a lot of money unless they
were Rich to begin with and then they
got sick
but people with chronic illness most
everybody they don't have a lot of money
because they're spending it on doctors
doctor appointments they're spending it
in so many different ways like that
and they're not working a lot of people
who are chronically sick don't work
because they can't it's not that they
don't want to work they want to work
and so that's that's something too these
were all the things I thought about that
went into the mm-1500 and the mm-900
it's not like just so oh the guy's got a
juicer he's gonna do some celery There's
real like meaning and thought about it
and that's what people don't realize
they just don't know that
so that's the kale that's in there so
what I have right here
it's really dry pulp
it's like Dusty dry I don't know if you
guys have an mm-1500 many of you do I
mean when I'm holding that pulp it's
unbelievable we have there
so
that alone is incredible
kale tends to foam up so what I'm doing
is I'm just
moving some of that through the screen
right there
now there's different ways to do it you
can use the screen they give you I use
another screen with my mm-900
all right so let's knock in a few other
things we're going to put some spinach
down in here too
which is great
okay what you're looking at right here
is Trace mineral salts lots of Trace
mineral salts
I call these I call these mm 1500s and
900s the medicine makers the medicine
machines
25 off right now
so I'm dropping some spinach down in
here right now this is really incredible
so when you really know why things are
done you'll be like wait a minute that's
different than some Juicer Company
and some influencers pushing out a
juicer because they want to take
advantage of the juicing business that
exploded because medical medium and
celery juice right they want to take
advantage of that
and but they have their reasons it's not
to save people money it's not to juice
it and extract to have like an
extraction from that high pressure and
it's not that you know it's not that's
not what they're in it for they're not
in it for that
so I got my spinach down in there now
I'm gonna put some dandelions in there
too so I got these wild dandelions and
if you guys know this these are the real
bitter
some are more bitter than others
there we go
now I'm not trying to rush it too
because I'm talking
so
what's incredible about this brain saver
bitters
is how potent it is but it's the
combination Spirit of compassion
you know told me about which is so
important so I want to show you this
poll
now what you're seeing
you're seeing dry Dusty pulp just pop
out of here like this can you guys see
that
that's where the savings come from so
you have a juicer that pays for itself
so you're saving because food cost
prices are up so it's like healing while
you're saving money but it's not even
just that it's the extraction process of
a cold pressed masticating juicer too
without having all that metal rubbing
each other too which is really important
grinding into each other right so that's
the dry
pulp which is so incredible
so what I'm doing is I'm just moving
so you have some foam left over when you
do anything with greens you'll have foam
one is anything with greens so I'm just
moving the juice in to finish that up
Christine says where can I get the brain
saver book on sale amazon.com us it's
probably on sale in other places too and
maybe some bookstores possibly
but it's definitely on sale on
amazon.com us
so there's no question there
check it out and the sale is incredible
for that book for those both those books
that's really amazing
cool
so I have the juice right there
let me move the pulp over 42 percent off
and 41 off
which is absolutely incredible
all right so what I'm going to do is
drop this in here
I'm gonna mix it up a little bit
I can't even tell you the wastage
with the other juicers it's just insane
talks bitters
right out of brand saver right there
now what I love about this
right
this special recipe helps remove various
toxic chemicals toxic chemicals from the
brain that cloud the mind so we're
talking about heavy metals but we're
there are thousands of toxic chemicals
getting into people's brains and we have
the heavy metal cleanses and detoxes we
have all that in the books but we also
need something for all the other
chemicals that make it even worse and
worse and worse April says where do I
purchase the juicer you have so link is
in the description link is in the
profile it's Omega juicers.com but check
out the link to find it this is the
mm-1500 so make sure you actually get
the right one because you might
accidentally get the wrong one at Omega
and then that one doesn't do what these
do it doesn't do with the 900 and the
1500 do so that's important to know
but this is the 1500 the 1500 you're
looking at dry
you're looking at dry pulp
it's the difference is unbelievable I
saw someone do an insta story with the
fancy fancy juicers that are going
around right now that they you know
busted into they're like the Sharks
busting into the medical meme community
and they had so much wet pulp
that if that it was it was insane and it
was a pile of Pulp
and it was ridiculous right and it's
like yeah if you're rich fine juice like
that but buy all those like fruits and
vegetables buy the truckloads because
you're gonna feed that Beast if you want
to juice every day
that juicer is going to cost you so much
money so the difference is the reason
why
people like wonder why I stand by things
you guys know why I stand by what I
stand by
but this was a legendary decision
meaning legendary product right it's
like the 1500 and 900 how do you save
people who are struggling
because they're struggling financially
they don't have a lot of money they have
to heal you got to get better and heal
so this was all about the person
struggling that's what the juicer was
about because if it wasn't
then I could have done juicers 20 years
ago I could have been the juicer guy for
the last 30 years
there's no there's no meaning behind
that you have to have something you have
to have something behind there that's
just mind-blowing like what's the
meaning like what's the mind-blowing
nature of it because I could have done
juicers and done juicer companies and
stuff for 30 years like and been the
juicer guy like whatever but
the reason for this was how can we make
something like work where it gives you
that extraction where you save money and
it pays for itself and you heal at the
same time and that's when boom and
that's why I have anything to do with
users
them
and so that's the 1500 900. I never told
that story because I you know it's like
today's like a different chill day it's
a different day plus it's they they have
the Black Friday sale and it's like you
know what if someone wants to take
advantage of that take advantage of it
now and know why the whole reason was
behind it
and MV Doom says over on YouTube so
grateful for this info
I'm honored to feel that way truly
well that's what it was about I'm just
telling you guys so um
a second about the vermergy products you
guys know why I stand behind those guys
I've talked about that many times
recently right that's the letter bomb I
do the limb mom tea just check out their
sales too I'm just letting you know that
this is the time if you're actually
trying to get things the sales are
insane take advantage of the Black Black
Friday sales
go to vimergy.com
right check out the juicer when you can
that's the link is in the profile it's
the mm1500 check that out
right check out the books make sure you
have the book so you have this powerful
healing information so make sure that is
and
and you guys also with Wyman's you guys
know I stand behind Wyman's right
check out their sale they have which is
insane too all on its own so check this
out right
if you buy their juice
which is also on sale right now because
they're Black Friday you can get a
coupon to go into the store and get two
free three pound bags of Frozen wild
blueberries and that's their Black
Friday thing so you got to get the juice
and then you get the coupon right but
that that's insane see that's what I'm
talking about it's like it's the
integrity
it's the Integrity it's the caring it's
about like how do we help anyone and get
what they need and that's the key all on
its own you know like the beverages
stuff's just off the chart what they do
to get people what they need right but
and this is stuff that matters to me it
matters to me so I could have done
juicers like 30 years ago I could have
done juicers all these years and just
been like the juicer guy
and whatever but
that's not gonna really move the needle
I need something to help people move the
needle so this was kind of a project of
love where
these guys were like yeah
let's try to help people there's a
difference and that's the difference
right there so that's why this to me is
like a miracle every time I see it and
I'm always buying less produce and I
think about everybody else who's buying
less produce and check out the cold and
this is the free cold and flu tool kit
at medicalmedium.com download this for
free which is really cool okay then I
got a new podcast coming out check that
out too medical meme podcast Apple
podcast make sure you sign up to the
medical medium newsletter
so you know when the podcast comes out
so you know all the information and when
you know the neck will actually win the
first the first light blast announcement
will come out
where we're going to be doing that live
light blast that's going to be a whole
nother thing make sure that you're on
the newsletter so you can even get the
invite to actually sign up to that light
blast
I don't know if you guys know about the
medical medium light blast
but it's not me it's Spirit of
compassion and spirit of compassion told
me
recently it was like I don't know it was
a few months ago
um through the compassion said
we can do this and I was like are you
serious
and super compassion was like we can do
this
if you get the people together
live
we can get the light down upon them
I said let's do it let's work on it so
the medical medium team started working
on this and this is costing me thousands
of dollars to arrange the light blast
that tens of thousands of dollars you
guys out of my pocket and guess what it
costs to join sign up
and be there live for for the light
blast guess what it cost does it cost
300 does it cost 500 does it cost a
thousand dollars
it costs zero it cost me tens of
thousands of dollars to create the light
blasts for everybody
out of my pocket
but it cost everybody nothing it's free
and we're going to be doing that light
blast
it's gonna be incredible but it's a
limited amount of people
it's only 20 000 people allowed Spirit
of compassion
told me 20 000 people
so my team is
creating this creating the whole thing
where it's 20 000 people
free live and you get the light blast
but it's only 20 000 people so if you
don't sign up to medicalme.com you
should tell everybody you guys should
tell everybody they should be signing up
medical medium.com newsletter so that
you don't miss out on this
so yes
indeed
anything I can do as the messenger from
above
which is all
fine and dandy I want to anyway you guys
I'm gonna have a little sip of this if
you guys don't mind I'm excited
hmm
amazing
incredible
I got guys I love you thank you for
being here I will see you next time I
don't know when the next time is going
to be
but I got a podcast episode coming out I
hope you guys enjoy it I got some other
stuff happening too
but I just want to do more and more and
check this out too if you guys are still
here which I know you guys are
I'm gonna be doing exclusive stuff on
Twitter
it's gonna be pretty cool
exclusive stuff on Twitter let's go to
my Twitter page
make sure your notification works on the
Twitter page
because my notifications all don't work
on Twitter
from the past
so all my hundred thousand followers on
Twitter never get notified
if you know why over these years
but anyway go to my Twitter page
sign up because I'm going to be putting
out tweets that I don't put out anywhere
else information on and videos too an
exclusive audio message messages by the
way are on telegrams that's cool so I'm
always doing that
so yeah and me we as well let's not
forget about miwi
so anyway you guys incredible check out
the Black Friday sales we talked about
take advantage Now's the Time
I want you guys to have every
opportunity possible you guys know I
love you and I will see you again soon