we're live right now
brain fog
how many people walk around with brain
fog right
headaches migraines it's another thing
people walk around with all the time
eczema it's another one right there how
many people have skin problems vertigo
balance issues dizziness right or
vertigo or episodes of vertigo
throughout their life we're talking
about all those we'll talk about some
other stuff too we're in cleanse the
heel
what we're doing right now
is we're
demonstrating really demonstrating
hey how to work with supplements and
protocols because people get lost they
don't know how to heal and then they're
just stuck
and if they're just stuck
then we're in trouble right there
because so many people just get stuck
and that's sad right and then we got the
dabblers nothing wrong with the dabbler
it's good to see you guys coming on
nothing wrong with the dabblers
that's okay
medical medium dabbling is all right
everybody's accepted here absolutely i
want you look if you want to try one
thing
one thing
and that's it hey i'm doing some celery
juice hey i tried a little zinc hey i'm
doing some wild blueberry juice hey i'm
trying this or i'm trying that i'm
keeping eggs out that's perfectly fine
dabbling is accepted i love dabblers
there's nothing wrong with that all just
don't dabble for two or three years
get sick
because of something happening or
something you're doing or too many blood
draws you're getting the blood taken out
every minute and your doctor's killing
you you don't know it
i'm not saying you know that's what all
doctors do some great doctors out there
but and then your doctor's killing you
and then all of a sudden you're getting
sick
and all you were doing was dabbling and
then you say mm didn't work
mm just didn't work so you guys were
talking about brain fog vertigo
migraines eczema that's what we're doing
okay and uh i got cleansed the heel
right here good to see you guys coming
on
i want everybody to know you can go as
far as you need to go you can go as far
as you need to go
we're live right now on telegram
live
on rumble
live on tick tock live on facebook live
on youtube youtube which is really cool
and give me a thumbs up if you guys like
the video
cleansing heal is an amazing book and
i'll tell you why because the record
the record of that many people healing
and getting their lives back around the
world it's insane it's almost insane at
this point
people oh my god i lost 20 pounds doing
your cleanses oh my god i lost 30 pounds
oh my god i lost 50 pounds got rid of my
high blood pressure oh my god i got rid
of my vertigo oh i got rid of my
migraines got rid of my endometriosis my
my fibroids like it's unbelievable
extraordinary really when you think
about how many people are getting their
lives back when they go in here they
dive into here i hear it all the time
you know
i got the book
and i was just doing one thing out of
the book but then you know i can't
believe how much is in here because then
i could do this and then i can go this
far to heal and this far to heal
it's really incredible so we're going to
talk about supplements dosages
for these conditions and anything else
that could come up too so that's what
i'm excited about i'm glad you guys are
here got got the i got the props out too
because we might do a little demo
a little bit of demo and i want to give
you guys a little news flash
okay 6 30
eastern 3 30 pacific i'm gonna be on
rumble exclusively for a little talk
i'm excited about that
so i can't wait to see you guys there
all right let's get into it
so right now i'm in the knowing the
cause and the protocol
knowing the cause and the protocol
you know what happens a friend of mine
he goes out and gets all the health
books out there he's looking at all the
health books out there he gets this one
he gets this one by some doctor
so-and-so or he gets this health book
out here and he says how come
they don't have specific dosages
specific protocols and i always say
because they don't know the protocols
they don't know why people are sick
and how come they don't talk about why
someone's really sick why do they have
eczema
and he grabs all the different health
books out there for fun and he reads and
he goes i can't find one health book
that explains why someone actually has
eczema and then a protocol on how to
heal
because there is none
there is none
this is the first that's ever been done
and that's why i was the first to be
censored years ago censored in 2017 i
was censored when the first book medical
medium came out
i was censored we had a fight our way
through it you have to fight your way
through the darkness right when the
darkness comes and wants to stomp out
the light
you gotta fight your way through it to
make sure people heal
right so when the darkness comes and
wants to stomp that light out be like
you can't heal anybody
you're not allowed to heal anybody
you're not allowed to break the rules
and teach them why they're sick the true
causes
we want everybody is sick the darkness
just wants to keep everybody sick going
to your pharmacies you see that now see
everybody going to the pharmacies
they're lined up in pharmacy some place
in the u.s that and also around the
world some place in the u.s some places
the pharmacies can't keep up
with how many drugs they have to delve
out everybody's waiting in line for a
drug everybody's waiting in line for a
drug
exactly that's what's happening out
there and you're not allowed to get
people better in large numbers and
change your life so we're going to
censor
and we're going to talk crap about him
we're going to talk crap about him and
that's how it works
right
you guys be on the lookout by the way
another topic all right be on the
lookout i'm making an announcement about
something
oddly exciting
this weekend okay i'm gonna be doing
something
different
than i've done okay something different
than i've done in any platform
keep a lookout all right keep a lookout
for any kind of announcements anything
like that because i'm gonna be making an
announcement of something i've never
done before
and
it's gonna it could be fun it could be
fun
it
could be who knows what it could be but
yeah so i'm excited so we're knowing the
cause and the protocol we're in cleanse
the heel
just a reminder get it free at the
library
library for free
f-r-e-e
right or amazon.com us 1699 51
off
keep in mind do you have it do you have
this set of tools
so
i'm starting on page 476 but i'm i'm
over here and what you need to know
about supplements right here okay
right i just want to give everybody a
reminder one thing
in the moment if you are on supplements
that are not medical medium recommended
which people do all the time because
dabblers do that they'll be on a little
bit of this a little bit of that they'll
be on a little bit of this right that's
what they'll be on for instance whey
protein powder prime example right there
if you're on whey protein powder if
you're on some type of plant protein
powder
packed with msg and you don't even know
it right
fish oil if you're on some kind of fish
oil okay
maybe you're on some kind of fish oil
epic disaster for your health you want
alzheimer's do you want alzheimer's down
the road
that will get you there fish oil you
want the alzheimer's you want the
dementia guys want to lose your memory
more and more
keep the fish oil going you want to get
sicker keep the fish oil going that's
all
that's all right
fish oil there's another one right there
hair nail and skin supplements right
trickery of those unbelievable they put
a little bit of this in there and a
little bit of that in there and you get
ripped off
in a bunch of junk and garbage right
chlorella details matter details matter
chlorella
chlorella is
epically harmful for people and they
don't even know it and still to this day
you see some influencers out there i'm
taking my chlorella tablets i'm doing my
chlorella powder i'm getting rid of
metals
even though medical medium taught the
world about toxic heavy metals and how
to get rid of them all of a sudden i
heard from another expert about metals
who learned from medical medium or
something
yeah and
i'm doing chlorella now mixing this in
there yeah
terrifying doesn't remove metals and
chlorella drops stuff if it picks up a
toxin it moves it drops it in a volatile
area
nice way to mess up your blood brain
berry and everything else i'll tell you
is another one these are just some
glandular supplements right there that's
a tricky one too right glandular sub acv
vinegar lose your teeth
lose your teeth i may not be the
prettiest
guy you ever seen okay
i may not be you know the most handsome
guy in the world but i got all my teeth
yeah all my teeth right
and there's nothing wrong with them and
there's a reason i stayed away from
vinegar i stayed away from acv
stayed away
just an acv and vinegar and acv tablets
and everything else and boom or the
gummies whatever it is down the road you
lose all your teeth
and it happens quick they all start
crumbling in before you know it before
you know it
diatomaceous earth particles stay away
from that bentonite clay stay away from
that activated charcoal stay away from
the activated charcoal i'll tell you why
when you consume the activated charcoal
it suffocates the intestinal lining not
allowing nutrients and enzymes and
everything that needs an amino acids and
all these fantastic things it doesn't
allow anything to come through very
rarely can it come through so it has to
come through in different moments of
time you get nutrient deficiency totally
nutrient deficiencies
big time with activated charcoal right
so keep that in mind right there these
are just a few things i'm just going to
run down a few things okay so what
you're learning with the medical medium
information
is
priceless
because your health
means everything you can't put a price
on your health you cannot put a price
it's not measurable your soul
you cannot
put a price on your soul
it cannot happen
your soul is beyond priceless there is
no price
we take our soul
and it goes and leaves here this planet
after we're gone right
and there's no way there's no way to
measure that value of a human soul right
so that's
and that soul sits inside our physical
body our physical health is critical
it's precious
all these things matter so when we're
talking about getting our health back
and our lives back and you guys just
came on here we're talking about brain
fog we're talking about headaches and
migraines protocols and supplements
eczema talk about vertigo protocols and
supplements right
your health matters
so taking the wrong things like they all
throw at us okay your bentonite clay
rips your intestinal tract apart
destroys your lining in your intestinal
tract you don't do clays
remember that
okay so very important to know all of
this so let's move on a little bit so i
just want to kind of kind of cover that
area
right
and
here's an interesting part here to run
by because we're talking about
supplements and protocols so if you guys
got a second all right
before we go on though
just telling you i'll be on rumble
exclusively to talk about a talk that's
different than anything today that i'm
doing on these lives right it's a 6 30
eastern 3 30
specific just letting you know
and i'm making an announcement pretty
soon about something i've never done
before it could be it could go really
bad it could go really good i don't know
what
but you guys might want to listen out
for that something haven't done
could be exciting
all right you'll notice that almost
every one of the items
that's recommended supplementation
in this book in the protocols so if you
go to eczema you go to brain fog you go
to an area inside this book you'll
notice
almost all of the recommendations of
supplements in there are mostly singles
singles say you take a lemon balm what
does it say it says lemon balm
it's not a blend of 50 herbs it's not a
blend of 50 nutrients
that's how they take you
yeah that's rip off land and that's why
people don't get better i mean people
who get sick don't get better people who
are waiting back and forth are not so
sick and sick they're just elevating
back and forth and things are keeping
afloat and keeping a float when you go
down and you go really sick and you're
really sick
you got to know the protocols and you
have to know
why singles
are critical
singles
i call this singles for a reason right
here so you'll notice that almost every
one of the items to come
in this section a single herb
right what you won't find here are
bottles and bottles of supplements you
guys this is so important
with dozens and dozens of ingredients
herbs dozens of vitamins a dozen amino
acids and more you won't find that in
the recommended supplements here
because you don't get better you don't
go to the finish line details matter
details matter details matter
they matter
there's a reason for this when you fill
a capsule with anywhere from 10 to 40
items 10 to 40 nutrients
10 to 40 nutrients of herbs and whatever
else and minerals and amino acids or
whatever it's going to be it's only
going to contain a spec of each one so
it's only going to contain a spec of
each one keep that in mind
and that spec won't it won't even be of
the quality that you need
this is why
junk supplements or supplements that are
even of quality of some sort don't get
people better after all these years this
is you guys
maybe
many of you guys know the history in the
last 10 20 30 years in your life you're
seasoned
you've been there you tried all these
piles of supplements you've been to
another lime doctor and tried a bunch
more pile supplements and you went to a
functional medicine doctor and you tried
this and the specialist who tried this
you're taking all the supplements and
then a year goes by you're still sick
and they all sit and up in the cat
cupboard and then you get a whole bunch
more because you go see another doctor
right and all these supplements are
saturated with lots and lots and lots of
bits and spark pieces of tidbits of
nutrients like i said and that's why
people don't get better this is so
important if you guys just came on we're
about to run into brain fog
headaches and migraines eczema vertigo
right
this is a practice that the industry
does they put together junk supps and
they put specs and specs and specs and
tidbits in of each little thing that's
how they make their money when you do a
spec of an amino acid then a speck of
this is speck of spirulina and then a
speck of this and then a speck of
bladder rack and then a speck of an herb
whatever it is you just spec spec spec
specs back
you got a capsule now with a bunch of
specks that will never move the needle
you can't move the needle with a speck
here you are sick for real reasons we're
going to talk about cover and cleanse
the heel and you can't move the needle
with a speck
this
schooling or whatever this learning or
this information is so critical here
there's a reason why i'm here making
shorts for free making sure i'm not
turning this into some kind of course
making sure i'm not making you guys pay
for all this information this is
precious information
so
alina says i am migraine free
and i had daily migraines for two years
nothing helped with medical medium means
alina you were doing the protocols you
were doing you're seeing
what works and you're experiencing it
and you're feeling it
yeah cindy lou says it's so hard to hear
about friends taking junk supplements
right
i wasted so much money
so let's go into it a little bit let's
head into an area now let's talk about
brain fog
you can have brain fog
and this person can have brain fog
on this other person over here can have
brain fog
and everybody can have brain fog
but nobody will know
why they have brain fog you can guess
everybody can guess you can go to
another practitioner another doctor and
we can guess while we have brain fog
and we can guess and we can guess and we
can guess to the cows come home we can
guess until the cows come home
but won't know why we have brain fog
lots of guesses
the true cause of brain fog is low-grade
chronic viral infections
most commonly caused by one of the over
60 varieties of epstein-barr virus
and toxic heavy metals such as mercury
aluminum and copper or both of viral and
a viral load and toxic heavy metals in
combination so viral load and toxic
heavy metals in combination right
copper toxic heavy metal right there
right it's copper
big thing of copper right here okay
toxic heavy metal in our system
right
virus
virus inner system
virus and metals
makes
brain fog
how
because the virus feeds off of metal
releases a metal neurotoxin
that neurotoxin
heads up to the brain
enters
the brain
lands on neurons and you got the brain
fog
let's go into the brain a little bit for
a couple of seconds
everybody's got metal inside their head
everybody does
it's ignored by the industries
it's frowned upon to even think about
how that's even possible
the industries they'd still be well they
still are they're still putting mercury
amalgams in people what am i saying
i was wrong just got corrected by spirit
of compassion just now
i mean i hate being corrected by
spiritual compassion but i have to eat
it when i gotta eat it
when i've been wrong
and
what i was thinking for a second was no
they don't put mercury amalgams in
anybody anymore it's been outlawed or
something they don't do it in spirit
compassion corrected me and said no
they're doing it still they still put
put mercury amalgams in people here in
the u.s and around the world i was stand
corrected so i have to eat that one
but regardless okay
there's so much mercury out there that's
to be had in many ways
it's in the fish you eat every time i
hear no i had sushi i'm eating healthy i
had my sushi
i'm eating healthy
right
having my sushi
okay every time i hear that i just i
just
kind of like
cower a little bit like
bone it down like what
really
because you just get more mercury so
when you have your brain fog or you're
going to feed your brain fog more and
more and more
our brains get mercury
our brains get a lot of toxic heavy
metals inside of them okay
those metals start to rust and corrode
and
bleed those metals start to
decay
is what they do
just like your mercury filling did in
your tooth they break up they discharge
they decay and the same thing happens
with all the metal particles inside of
our brain
and those toxic heavy metals once they
start coming apart
outgassing
rusting
decaying
right popping apart all those different
molecules of toxic heavy metals
they start to age
and then it spreads to adjacent tissue
and neurons and then your electrical
field starts hitting more and more metal
and more and more places and now you've
got the brain fog and the brain fog's
bad and the brain fog is worse and the
brain fogs back and that's what happens
right there
and we get in trouble
then
if you got a viral issue too you've got
a viral issue got the shingles
epstein-barr
hhv-6 set of megalovirs all the viruses
that everybody walks around with the
viruses
the real virus is the ones that have
been keeping everybody chronically ill
the ones that trigger up
when they get a bad flu or the plague
and then boom they triggered up i don't
know why i got the hearing problems now
after the plague normally i have the
tinnitus and the vertigo after playing
that those are viral issues that's
reactivated shingles reactivated
epstein-barr reactivate viruses when you
have the viruses
you don't even need the plague you got
the viruses
right the viruses are feeding off those
metals inside the body
then they release neurotoxins and then
we're even worse off with a brain fog
you could have the worst brain fog your
brain fog could get so bad you don't
even know who you are sometimes that's
how bad brain fog can get it could get
really crazy
so i'm in the brain fog section now i
covered a little bit about the cause of
brain fog something that
you can't hear from a doctor something
something that you can't hear from a
practitioner unless they use medical
medium info or they mutated medical
medium info and added their own
blend of something in there
right so what's in here we got a fresh
celery juice work up to 32 ounces every
morning if that's all you can do
just the fresh celery juice
about you
i never shame anybody i never shame
anybody
when it comes down to healing i know
it's not easy we take one step at a time
i'm not here
to make things harder than they already
are for so many sick people and
chronically ill people
i'm not
i mean you can just get celery juice
down i'm fine but you know what's gonna
happen though right
yeah that medical medium guy
he's telling everybody they could be
cured one shot would sell a glass of
celery juice and they're cured medical
medium is going to be clear every
medical medium
give it out a glass of celery juice
everybody's cured one shot that's what
they're saying let's write a let's write
another media
another media slander story
right you guys know how it rolls it
moves the needle for many people when
you first take a few sips
right but it's also a powerful healing
tool coupled with a lot of medical
medium tools
combined with other medical medium tools
to move the needle in some serious
chronic illness brain fog or anything
like that
yeah i've seen people down celery juice
for a week and boom their brain fog
lifts i've also seen them need way more
than that
way more than this this is fresh celery
juice so you might be somebody that
needs a little bit more than celery
juice so here you go here's cleanse the
heel a minute
and now it says celery force right by
the way i took some before i came on
and it's kicking in it's kicking in
right celery force that's the vimergy
celery force says that in there
i took four capsules before coming on to
this live just now
so then there's
5mthf right so i see 5mthf
in here so it says one capsule daily of
5mthf right the methylfolate one capsule
daily
actually says one capsule twice a day
ashwagandha
says ashwagandha
right here one dropper full twice a day
for brain fog ashwagandha so i'm doing
one dropper full right there
in the shot glass
so what i like to do is i like to put up
in the shot glass and i like to put a
little bit of water and then then i'm
good okay
so we got that barley grass juice powder
the barley grass cheese powder
the supplements i use for my friends and
family and for me that i recommend
anything
anytime a friend contacts me and says
what do i take for this
i'll be like make sure it's it's it you
get that and they're like well what
brand i'm like vimorji i'm not sponsored
by these guys but the stuff is that good
right that's the barley grass juice
powder
right
it says cat's claw here it's interesting
so it says cat's claw okay
so
there's a cat's glove
now why would we need cats claw for
brain fog
because someone might have a really
difficult case of brain fog where it's
viral for sure not just metals maybe
it's a lot of viral going on maybe they
got the epstein barr and they got the
shingles and they got some other ones
and they're creating a lot of poison in
their system and you want to do some
viral killing
some epstein-barr killing you want to do
some shingles slaying so that's where
you got the cat's cost so it's in the
brain fog section right here cat's claw
right there
so what does it say for a dosage it says
one drop or full twice a day
one dropper full twice a day so let's
put some cat's claw
in there okay
lemon balm
lemon balm is anti-viral
it's also
healing for the nerves lemon balm is
really soothing on the central nervous
system incredible for panic attacks
anytime i've had a family member a
friend or anything say they have some
anxiety or some panic attack or anytime
i talk to a doctor that wants advice
from me i'll be like make sure you do
make sure you have your patients do the
lemon bomb for panic attacks you can you
can do a lot of lemon balm
so important so important one dropper
full twice a day it says for brain fog
so i'm going to put a dropper full of
lemon balm in there
if you guys don't mind right
see that
got a drop on the book
so let's see what else we got going on
the chaga mushroom
we you know beverage has a chaga
mushroom i didn't put it out just now
the limit licorice root
so why would we use licorice root for
brain fog
why
antiviral licorice root is anti
epstein-barr the very thing behind one
of the very things next to metals is the
epson bar right the very thing behind
brain fog so you see licorice roots here
one dropper full
that in there
all right nettle leaf it's interesting
spirit of compassion wants a metal leaf
in here one dropper full twice a day of
the nettle leaf so you got the metal
leaf now look you could be somebody i
don't want anybody overwhelmed you can
be somebody that just does one thing
you can be somebody that just does a
couple of things here because the b12 is
coming up so it says b12 all right
so
that's the dolls let's see where's the
b12 the b12 so that's a liquid b12
you can be somebody that's it's just the
b12 one dropper full twice a day b12
maybe you're still going to get just the
b12 that's all you do
right and maybe you're somebody that
just does the b12 and sync and if you
read in this section you'll see the best
you know few supplements to start with
if you're somebody that should only do
one thing hey i can only do one thing aw
you know i can only do two things what
should i do well you can do the zinc you
could do the b12 read the section in the
book if you guys just came on here
making a couple of announcements
one is
i'm going to be on rumble at 6 30
eastern 3 30 pacific
today after a bunch of lives i'm gonna
do right so i'm gonna be there okay and
i'm gonna be covering a topic that i'm
not covering here and then one other
thing look out for a special
announcement of something i'm gonna be
doing different than i've ever done
and i'm hoping i get you guys a support
you know i hope i get your support on it
because i think it's going to be fun
kind of hilarious
different fun i don't know
we'll see
helpful i'm hoping it's helpful
all right
so we went through some of the
supplements right here for brain fog
and if you take the book
and you learn how to use the
supplementation in the protocols for
your brain fog and then you pick a
cleanse in here maybe you want to try
the mono cleanse for two weeks to get
rid of your brain fog maybe you want to
do 369
right
maybe you want to do the 369 or you know
original 369 advanced maybe you want to
do the heavy metal detox
right the heavy metal detox
maybe you want to do that but you have
so many options in here i'm showing you
supplements and protocols right here
okay and what we're doing now
you can use it says wild blueberry
powder in here is as as a as an option
it's one tablespoon of wild blueberry
powder can use
the weinman wild blueberry juice if you
want and that's what i'll do crack this
open
and
now you guys know i work with this
company though right i'm letting you
guys know okay
i actually work with these guys because
i'm trying to keep this
out there in the world because it's it's
there's nothing like it
they take the wild blueberry out of the
field
they press it
they press it with this incredible press
right
and and literally bottle it
in this glass
and and the antioxidants are
insane like really insane like every
time
anytime friends and family's like well i
got a friend that's
dealing with any kind of alzheimer's i
got a friend who's like whoa are they
doing the wild blueberry juice
so anyway it's an incredible medical
medium tool right there
alice says i would like to purchase the
book where can i get it if you want to
purchase it amazon.com us 51 percent off
cleanse the heal right
book depository if you're somewhere else
in the world you can try that and try
your local bookstores okay target i
think you try target
maybe you can try barnes and nobles has
it
okay
or go to the library and try to get it
for free
maybe you can get it for free at the
library
so
let's move into the next one
if you guys just came on here we're
covering symptoms and conditions
how to use a healing protocol
how to get started how to get going in
this right so let's head to the next one
you guys and i'm look i'm looking in
here and i'm seeing the bloating section
i'm bloating how many of you guys are
bloating and you don't know why you're
bloating right
brittle ridge nails there's a protocol
in here for brittle ridge any of you
guys have the ridge nails like the
ridges are insane and the nails are the
ridges are like really
just out of control
right you get the ridges and you get the
brittle nails or they're just breaking
everywhere just chipping apart and
breaking right
and hair skin nail supplements do not
fix nails
i mean i the decades they've been
getting people they've been getting
women with that one for decades and
decades buy her hair skin nail
supplement now we have collagen in our
hair skin nail supplement meaning like
it's endless right it's endless i mean
well you know meanwhile no their nails
are still their nails don't get better
from that those hairs get nail
supplements
i mean you have to do in the hair skin
nail supplement and then you have to
change your entire everything everything
including get your diet better in some
way to see anything but it's like right
here there's a protocol
so it tells you bridge ridge nails
a true cause stagnant sluggish liver
filled with toxins leading to zinc
deficiencies
leading to zinc deficiencies so what's
in the protocol well
right there zinc
so i was just like stumbling across this
just now and i'm like you know i know so
many people with nail problems out there
one dropper full of zinc doing a little
protocol for there right there right
okay
someone's dealing with hashimoto's i
know some of you guys have
hyperthyroidism hypothyroidism
hashimoto's thyroiditis
cysts nodules i know so many of you guys
have so many thyroid problems the
protocols are in cleanse to heal so just
like i'm doing the protocols here
they're in there vision problems the
protocols are in cleansing heal for
vision problems i'm just letting you
know so there's that too
so when we're in bridge brittle
ridged nails okay
so i was just showing you some zinc in
there that's one thing right there
vitamin c
there's the micro c right there's the
vimergy micro seed
incredible product incredible product so
there's that it tells you the dosage
divine light say i had terrible nails
and hair
and after doing the medical medium
protocols i now have the most beautiful
nails and hair they have miraculously
healed and are growing so beautifully
incredible divine light it's the best
news i ever heard it's amazing it's
wonderful it's wonderful so let's go and
i'm just i'm just kind of cutting
through the book right there there's
cataracts
right chemical and food sensitivities
canker sores
so what about fibromyalgia linda
fibromyalgia is in the medical medium
books okay um you can i mean you really
people need both of these books because
they're so incredible right but you got
you got the medical medium book one with
the fibromyalgia fibromyalgia in this
book too
right here
okay and cleanse the heel protocol
dosages so i'm just kind of cutting
through this a little bit what else the
cold and flu
right
that's in here too
so
i mean there's so much
so much
what about mystery hunger and overeating
how many of you guys have mystery hunger
you guys trying to eat in the middle of
the night so i'm including you and i'm
just running across so many protocols
are you guys eating in the middle of the
night do you wake up in the middle of
night i'm like okay i'm gonna go in the
fridge here and i gotta go in the fridge
and let me you open up the fridge right
you guys guys doing the middle of the
night mystery hunger overreading all the
time i'm just kind of curious if that's
kind of
kind of happening for some of you guys
constipation how many how many of you
guys are constipated have had
constipation issues are you guys all on
all those on all those different you
know
anti-constipation drugs and stuff right
macy said i did the 369 original 16
times
in a row last year
incredible changed my life now i do 32
ounces of celery juice tinctures
whoa so you know the protocols in here
right now capsules and i continue to see
improvement so whoa think ew and your
work
okay wait a minute so macy really what
you're saying is you took one of the
cleanses and you did that cleanse over
and over again and move the needle right
and then you always then you went to the
tinctures and some of the supplements
and then you're moving the needle boom
boom boom incredible incredible darlene
says no constipation here maria says
your info saved my gallbladder
that's incredible
it really is so i'm happy to hear that
truly
i'm looking there's a look depression
a lot of people suffer from depression
that's just no joke right diabetes
i got that in here i mean it's just it's
loaded i'm just i'm not trying to buy
you guys down so many different options
in here but i'm just saying there's that
much
eczema let's go into that let's head to
eczema we're in cleanse to heal we're in
supplements and protocols that's what
we're doing right now i'm just going to
take a shot of the wild blueberry juice
yep
take a little sip off of that
now while blueberry juice just like for
me i just feel a rush
now it's incredible it's just no
caffeine in it
right
it's and i hear that all the time like
didn't my wild blueberry juice just
started feeling better right but
for my for for me i just feel this rush
and then i you know i feel better i
think better i all that it's just it's
really cool
so
you guys we're just on
we're live on telegram we're live on
youtube we're live on rumble we're live
on tick tock okay and facebook turned
off earlier just letting you guys know
so facebook just
it went down for some reason
all right we're on eczema
how many of you guys know somebody that
has eczema
psoriasis
lupus style rashes what about lupus
style rashes
age spots any of you guys got age spots
cooking right
liver spots they age spots
lichen sclerosis scleroderma vitiligo
seborrheia dermatitis classic dermatitis
something i call classic dermatitis a
tin of keratosis cellulitis all these
different liver issues right
so
we're talking about eczema right now so
how many people are dealing with eczema
let's go into that so i'm in the
protocol for eczema and let's go into
the true causes of eczema right now
let's go into that a little bit
so i'm going to move the book over a
touch
okay
somehow
some way
in somebody's life
something moved into the liver
something what is it what moved into
their liver
somewhere maybe they drank
water that went through copper pipes
maybe
they had
copper
from some other water contamination in a
restaurant when they got their coffee
maybe
their family members had ddt already
inside of them which is high in copper
ddt
and that ddt passed down from generation
to generation
maybe
someone had pharmaceuticals
that were high in copper because all
pharmaceuticals are high in toxic heavy
metals and somehow that copper found its
way inside their liver
right
and then that copper sat there it was
fine that that copper sat there that was
okay
so right if the copper sat there right
let the copper sit in somebody's liver
that's fine
that's fine but then one day
one day
that person
whoever that is
ended up
contracting an epstein-barr virus
the epstein barr
and maybe that epstein barr was passed
down
from their parents generation to
generation in the womb as a child
maybe the epstein barr
was passed around in college
maybe it was that first person that you
know someone became intimate with and
that partner in life or anybody and that
was passed along maybe they drank out of
a glass at a restaurant an epstein-barr
was on that glass stuck in somebody's
lipstick or stuck in some guy's saliva
that wasn't washed off the glass good
enough at the restaurant
maybe they'd have seen bar was on a
toilet seat somewhere
and someone's
put their butt right down on the toilet
seat and picked up that epstein bar
and found its way inside of them
but they got the epstein-barr virus an
epstein-barr
has
a really good relationship with copper
the copper was in the liver and the
epstein bar is now in the liver and that
epstein bar feeds off of copper inside
the liver
you see
and as that epson bar is eating all that
copper particles that were trapped
inside that liver and somebody that i've
seen bar got so full and so fat and
happy and so stuffed as if it was
thanksgiving
that the epstein bar burped
and pooped
out that copper
and that copper poop
in that copper burp
outgassed a copper neurotoxin but that's
okay
that copper neurotoxin sat inside the
liver for the first six months of that
person's time with all this and then
that copper neurotoxin that the virus
pooped out
and excreted out
stayed inside the liver for longer and
longer and then that liver finally got
so
tired of holding on to all that copper
dermatoxin
that it puffed out of the liver
and that copper dermatoxin puffed and
puffed out of the liver and then it
started heading to the outer regions of
the skin in the derma
and that person got their eczema and
their psoriasis
and that's the cause of eczema psoriasis
story time i thought i would do a story
time on the cause of eczema and
psoriasis
so what do we do about it fine
fine
someone might say you convinced me
what do we do about it we got to get one
or two one or the other out of the liver
we got to get the virus out of liver the
epstein-barr virus or we have to get the
copper out which one would you like
which one do you want to get out i don't
care which one
you want to get out the viral issue get
out the virus you want to get out the
copper and get out the copper because in
this book cleanse the heel you can do
the heavy metal detox cleanse
you can do the heavy metal detox
smoothie you can have like you know the
vimergy spirulina or demergy barley
grass
and that's what you put in the heavy
metal detox smoothie you can have the
dolls right
there's the dolls liquid
okay you can put that in there
but you can get the copper out
there's a way to get it out and when you
get the copper out if that's the route
you want to go you want to go with
getting the metal out
hey you can get rid of your eczema
you can get rid of it
and if you want to go the route of
getting the epstein bar out you can do
that too then you go with the anti
epstein-barr
anti-epstein bar option
and you can get
the viral issue out
of your liver
so that's
eczema okay
one or more of the 60 varieties of fcmr
virus living inside the liver feeding
on an abundance of the toxic heavy metal
copper releasing a copper-infused
dermatoxin that circulates throughout
the body and can't detoxify properly due
to a high fat high protein diet whether
it's plant-based or animal-based there's
no there's no uh being biased against
one or the other
you can do a high-protein plant-based
diet a high-fat plant-based
plant-based diet you can do a high-fat
high-protein animal-based diet doesn't
matter
and other food choices that are
unproductive to the condition when these
dermatoxins float to the surface of the
skin they cause the source and rashing
of eczema psoriasis
with vitiligo
it's an aluminum-based dermatoxin it's
an aluminum-based dermatoxin different
pathogen toxin brews are are behind
different varieties of these skin
conditions so that's right there so what
do we do
what do we do about eczema
right so let's go to page 509 where it
is that's where xm is i just lost the
page okay
here we are
and it says fresh celery juice
fresh celery juice if that's all you can
do let's do that
and that's all you can do
let's do it let's do it why not it also
has five mta five five mthf here because
i like that for helping the skin
but you'll see in here there's cat's
claw you'll see in here lemon balm
licorice fruit l-lysine
l-lysine for the epstein bar right and
i'll say the dosage for 500 milligram
capsules twice a day if you can only do
one capsule once a day that's where you
start talk to your doctor see what's
right for you maybe you're somebody
that's sensitive you just want to do one
little thing because you've tried so
many bad things and things that were not
good that you just you got burned too
many times and now you're scared you say
okay well i'll do one thing
and then it says mullin leaf it says
nettle leaf it says spirulina it says
the b12 the zinc the c right
so it shows in here an anti epstein-barr
protocol
but it also shows the spirulina
right and the barley grass juice powder
because you're doing an anti-copper
based metal protocol
it's like hey someone wants to get
better
there are answers out there there are
answers out there
is adults tincture better than flakes
you could do either or
either or adults tincture or the flags
like right if you got the flakes use the
flakes so if you got the flakes use the
flakes
right this is just so easy for me
because a lot of times i can't find the
flakes i can't find adults i run out all
the time so this is just this is so easy
for me and what i like about the dulce
the dulce liquid right is all of it's
there to grab onto the metal and i know
because
all of the chemical compounds are there
to grab onto metal and pull metal out so
i just i just love it
atlantic dolls tincture that's the
vimergy if you don't know the company
i'm not sponsored by the guys but it's
vimergy v is in victor i am as
amerigy.com
ray so we're talking about eczema let's
hit vertigo really quick let's look for
vertigo
so i'm going there now
i think it's on 550.
so a lot of conditions a lot of symptoms
in here so let's try to let's try to get
there we'll find that
here it is so we got vertigo
okay so vertigo is the vagus nerve
everybody needs to know that april taft
says can you explain how eczema heals
does it constantly
how it
here's how it works right the minute you
start cleaning up your liver
you start cleaning that up if that liver
is filled up with a lot of dermatoxin
from the virus or a lot of copper right
it gets sludgy it gets packed in there
so as you're trying to heal your liver
is going to be puffing out a lot of that
old copper a lot of that old dermatox
and a lot of that old viral byproduct
right it's going to be puffing it out so
you you get your healing it's not
unusual to have moments where it's up
and down i always say three steps up two
steps back three sips up two steps back
so you're going up right eventually once
your liver clears up with enough of that
now you're home free it's less and less
less and less less and less and then
it's gone so many people you've seen how
many people got worse got rid of the
worst skin conditions and medical medium
information by the way that's never
happened before in chronic illness
anywhere in history
and that's what's incredible about it
someone might have a more aggressive
viral condition that takes a little bit
more of a makes a little bit more work
well that's why the protocols are here
you can take it as far as you need to go
to keep on getting a more aggressive bug
out
right or if you got a lot of copper in
there
it takes a little time to get the copper
out but one is going to get one is going
to give it's going to be either the
viral issue is going to give give and
boom or it's going to be the copper is
going to get and boom and then you're
home free so many people have
riddled with eczema
and
and just and it's gone right so let's
talk about vertigo a little bit
vertigo is the vagus nerves
the vagus
nerves
that's what vertigo is right
so keep in mind so the vertigo
also when someone has vertigo i mean
they can have tightness of the chest
they can have tightness of the throat
they can feel not just dizzy and have
the balance issues somebody with vertigo
can have even more than that so not just
dizziness and and the balance issues
it's you can have tightness to the chest
you get crippling anxiety when you when
your vagus nerves are inflamed crippling
anxiety panic attacks a lot of people
have panic attack where they're just
panic attacks all the time their heart's
going they're panic attacking everywhere
they're nervous they're scared you know
because they're so ptsd from their panic
attacks that's another thing you get the
post-traumatic stress syndrome from
having so much anxiety right and that's
really difficult for so many and the
vagus nerves are inflamed so when the
vagus nerves come out of the brain stem
and they come out of that brain stem
right so when the vagus nerves come out
of there okay and there's then now
they're traveling and they're going in a
couple of different directions hitting
every single almost every single nerve
an intestinal tract hitting nerves in
the heart right when those vagus nerves
get inflamed
that's when anything could go wrong with
the vertigo at any moment because the
brain stem
vagus nerves coming out of the brain
stem get inflamed up there by the brain
stem
and then boom you're in vertigo boom
you're in vertigo
that's where you are
and now you're getting the bed spins the
room's spinning you're getting the spins
you close your eyes and everything's
moving this way you know and going like
this over and over again where you close
your eyes and then you're literally you
you have to sit so still as you're
spinning and then you you turn over and
you you vomit on the floor you know so
many people just vomit they can't help
it they're spinning so much that they
have a bedpan where they vomit in the
bedpan some people can't walk they're so
dizzy and it starts hitting them or they
go down where they're walking and all
they're walking along and all of a
sudden they start going down like they
feel like they're going down even though
they're standing upright they feel like
they're going down that's the kind of
vertigo they have
okay so they have all these different
renditions so many people have this
where the vertigo is just out of control
and what that is is that's the vagus
nerves being
inflamed but what are they inflamed with
medical medium information teaches
people why they're inflamed
okay and so when you look at that you're
like why are they inflamed like what's
going on true cause epstein-barr virus
epstein-barr virus neurotoxins wreak a
lot of havoc
they create fibromyalgia they create
vertigo they create tinnitus there's
over 60 varieties of epsom bar
and different epstein bars do different
things some aggravate
aggravate aggravate um vagus nerves like
no other virus does
and if you're high in toxic heavy metals
then there's even more chances of having
a vertigo that sticks around and keeps
the brain stem area and the vagus nerves
and everything inflamed this is all
original medical medium information
which leads to that whole thing where
you know everybody takes a nugget they
go out there somewhere and drop the
nugget off somewhere nobody knows where
it came from and they'll never know how
to really heal
so veneers
is
made up
so we have to know that so meniere's
disease
where you have crystals in your ear
is a theory
just critical to know
all
vertigo
that's mysterious
because meniere's is
just mysterious because they're just
theorizing saying maybe it's these
crystals in somebody's ear well
that was
a funny theory when you're 60 years old
because that's what happened back back
30 years ago back 30 40 40 years ago if
you were 60 years old 50 years old you
got your first bout of vertigo
because young people didn't get vertigo
by the way
rare
rare a 20 year old a 19 year old a 17
year old ever got vertigo it was only 60
year olds 70 year olds 80 year olds
50 year olds back 40 years ago it was
only 50 year olds it was rare was ever a
40 year old that got vertigo yeah you'd
get that occasional 30 38 year old or
something a 35 year old but it was rare
vertigo mysterious vertigo was always
for people that were in their 60s or 70s
or 80s back 40 50 years ago remember
talking to doctors a long time ago
they'd be like oh yeah it's vertigo
cases are people that are in their 70s
you know in my practice another doctor
like people in their 80s and other
people be like yeah i had a few that are
in their 50s but that's years ago right
now you're 20 you're 19 years old you're
21 years old you're 25 years old and
everybody's got vertigo now so what
happened did the crystals change did the
crystals pick a different age bracket
i'm kind of curious on that because i
scratch my head all the time they always
said when you're 80 years old you got
meniere's that's what your vertigo is
it's crystals in your ear
because you know you've got crystals in
your okay well that it's only for older
people because young people don't have
crystals crystals don't exist in young
people's ears okay i'm scratching my
head on that one because everybody in
their 20s now has vertigo they're all
getting sick with vertigo and they don't
have crystals so i'm kind of confused
there did the crystals all of a sudden
change their job
because i'd like to know that
did the so-called crystals these this
theory of crystals from the medical
establishment did they change their age
bracket of what they're targeting
are they like are they like some kind of
like
demographic social media demographic
crystals all get together around a round
table i think to all these crystals get
together
and they're all talking to each other
like hey by the way let's go start uh
causing vertigo in a 20 year old for the
first time in history
no the crystals didn't change their
demographic they didn't change their age
bracket they didn't change anything the
crystals weren't the reason why anybody
had vertigo was always viral it's
because the vagus nerves get inflamed
here's the problem people in their 20s
now are all getting inflamed vagus
nerves people in their 20s people in
their 30s people in their teens are all
getting inflamed vagus nerves and that's
why they end up getting the vertigo it's
the epstein-barr
causing
it's the epidemic of the epstein barr
the different varieties the fact that it
went rampant the fact that it's been
passed around over and over again all
around the world the fact that everybody
has epstein-barr
yeah
chester says this guy is too legit to
quit
i wish i read that better would have
been cooler
thanks chester appreciate it
appreciate it
so we're in here we got a protocol in
here for this you know and what you'll
see in here is antivirals to get the
virus down it causes the inflamed vagus
nerves and that's what that is right
there which is really cool
so
so you'll see the different
supplements and dosages right check with
your doctor what's right for you take a
medical medium cleanse a heal to your
doctor
ask your doctor what supplement or
dosage is right for you or or whatever
your doctor thinks right
and the information's here check out the
book when you can right you guys so
just want to make this final
announcement
i'm announcing something that i've never
done before
probably pretty soon whether it's
tomorrow whether it's day after tomorrow
but i'm announcing it soon
okay and i hope you guys support me
i really i love your support okay it
could be interesting i think it's kind
of funny i don't know and and that's why
i want to do it it's just you know shake
things up help people out in a different
way i can't wait to talk about it too
but also exclusively by the way i'm
going to be on
uh rumble later 6 30 eastern 3 30
pacific i'll see you guys soon
okay