podcast pharmaceutical
exposures everyone is on bleep everyone
is on
bleep everyone is on bleep even if they
don't know what even if they think hey
I'm not on any bleeps no way I'm not on
any bleeps but they are but they don't
realize it pharmaceutical exposure you
see pharmaceutical exposure when your
own free will isn't in the mix on it
Like It's Just Happening any any way
you're getting it in you no matter what
even if you're like oh no I'm not on
Pharmaceuticals I don't take any
prescriptions I'm doing good I'm like I
don't need any of that you're on it
anyway you're on it anyway anyway check
out medical Me podcast at Apple podcast
pharmaceutical exposures everyone's
on everyone's on it so anyway okay we're
talking about some symptoms conditions
today so I'm excited about this by the
way have you got on to the newsletter
going to be making an announcement
pretty soon about me being somewhere to
do a book signing so you don't want to
miss that too okay so it's first
official book signing ever in all the
years I've been doing this and it's
exciting because I'm going to be there
just bring your books whatever whatever
book you have if you have more than one
just bring them and I'll just sign it
the whole bit so make sure you're on the
newsletter so you actually know when
that's happening so you can look out for
that let's go into this let's get going
let's move into it now ADHD do you guys
want to talk about that a little bit CU
I think it's way worth talking about so
many people have it more than ever how
many people are on
amphetamines how many people are on
amphetamines prescribed every day they
can't function they wake up in the
morning they have to take it it's like
their day exists like that they wake up
in the morning they can't think and they
just have to pop a pel infames they have
to go on it right A lot of people people
a lot of adults are on it and they're
putting children on it too so that's
what's happening there let's go into
ADHD a little bit okay here's what ADHD
isn't it's not genetic and it's not
guess what gut related now if that
pisses you off anything hang around so I
can talk about it a little bit okay but
ADHD is not gut related it's not coming
from the gut it's in the brain that's
where the problem is and there's people
with Messy gut guts and they don't have
ADHD messy guts their guts are filled
with all kinds of different toxins and
fungus and everything in mold and
garbage and processed food that's caked
on the side of their intestinal tract
forever no real good bacteria lots of
bad bacteria and they don't have ADHD
keep that in mind there's a whole ton of
those people out there and they don't
have ADHD but they have guts that are
sloppy messy crudded up fill all kinds
of nasty fungus nasty yeast nasty mold
nasty bacteria all kinds of different
stuff dehydrated stuck feces that have
been there for 30 years lining their
intestinal tract and colon and they're
they don't have
ADHD ADHD is not a gut problem it is a
brain problem yeah you better believe it
your gut better at least be ready to
take on some good foods and to take on
some good protocols and good things that
your gut needs to get it to the brain
but your gut isn't the problem that's
not where it's stemming from ADHD is in
the brain let's go into the little bit
okay so ADHD isn't genetic it's not gut
rated neither of these popular
explanations I got ADHD yeah it's
genetic it's in my family line everybody
in my family's got it it's genetic right
I got ADHD it's gut related I went to
the doctor he said it's a gut problem I
had a health coach tell me it's gut
related that's my
ADHD it's not none of these popular
explanations addresses the true
underlying cause of attentional focus
hyperactivity impulsivity or even
executive function or selfregulation
issues someone I think I just saw it
there what book are you reading out a
brains saver Incredible Book check it
out when you get a chance it's
Amazon all right what really causes ADHD
is guess what
Mercury
Mercury and
aluminum Mercury and aluminum medical
medium information original medical
medium information settling in the brain
cerebral midline
Canal right there right there right in
the middle smack in the middle right
there
metal in an early age settling in the
midline canal and then and then as you
get older it squeezes it squeezes closed
okay so when you're young your midline
canals
open it's open more it's like this when
you're a child and then as you're
getting older and your brain is
developing it starts to close up just
like this see and as it's closing up
it's squeezing and holding all that
mercury and aluminum that's settled in
the midline canal so the goal is to get
that out that's critical if you want to
get rid of ADHD you have to get the
metals out right in the medical medium
heavy metal detox is the most popular in
the world getting Metals out of people's
brains there's a lot of competition now
these days you guys trying to get their
own metal stuff and hey try my metal
thing try my metal REM mover and try I
know what it's going on don't do that
one don't do the one that's been working
on everybody all these years and
actually changing their lives and saving
their lives anyway if you see that going
on anyway the heavy metal detox the
medical medium heavy metal detox gets
the metals out of the midline canal so
that ADHD and other problems are getting
better for people okay are getting
better for people very important so many
people got their lives back because of
it all right let's go into a little bit
Mercury and
aluminum and check this out this is
interesting here's some aluminum right
there aluminum foil anyone aluminum
foil I know you don't eat aluminum foil
you don't think you do and there's a lot
of aluminum in so many different ways
that's just one out of a 100 ways you
can get aluminum in your system passes
down from generation Mercury passes down
from generation to generation to
generation
mm
info mm
info okay what really causes ADHD right
is the Mercury and aluminum but check
this out you guys settling in the
midline canal which divides the brain's
left hemisphere from the right along
with some additional metal sprinkled
about like a Christmas tree lighting
like Christmas tree lights sprinkled
about throughout the brain just a little
bit here a little bit there but the
midline canal is the big boy right there
that's the problem for so many people
the same causes
autism important to know so very
important to know same cause as autism
the ratio is a little more aluminum and
a little less Mercury when it comes down
to ADHD saw another person asked what
book it is it is the brainsaver book
check it out okay let's go into this
when these Metals take up residents in
the midline canal when they live live in
here when the Mercury and aluminum live
in here right there the midline canal do
you guys see that they block internal
Communications within the brains keep
keep in mind what happens is when you
have industrialized
metal that's in the midline
canal it's blocking Communications of
the right hemisphere to the left
hemisphere Communications that are
critical all right so there's so much
science and research doesn't know about
the brain yet and about how the
communication goes the electrical grid
the supernatural grid is actually
unknown to medical research in science
communication that the brain has okay
meaning like neurons talking to neurons
and then the s Supernatural forces
involved with neurons talking to neurons
and then the energy fields and then the
energy exchange the frequencies the
vibrations everything that is in here
along with the the soul because that's a
whole another aspect of it the soul
lives in here and when the soul lives in
here you have that so you have the soul
and then you have the physical brain but
when metals get involved and they're all
jammed up in that midline Canal
communication between the right
Hemisphere and the left hemisphere can
go backwards in so many ways all
right Communications within the brain as
a result the brain must adapt so our
brains do adapt and you see it with
people if you've paid attention enough
to other people and what they're going
through and what they're suffering with
you can see how they adapt throughout
the years if you know somebody long
enough or maybe it's a family member and
you know them for the rest of your life
right okay the brain must adapt and
electrical impulses find new avenues so
let's talk about that for a second
electrical impulses find new avenues
important to know all
right okay let's hit
it all right an electrical impulse let's
do a little electrical grid here all
right do a little bit of electrical
grid there we
go okay electrical grid inside your
brain right
there when you get metal which is all
in the midline
canal and you get it sprinkled about in
different places Mercury
aluminum
okay what happens is electrical
impulses
electricity hits the metal and when it
hits the metal it has to derail and go
somewhere else and when it goes
somewhere else it ends up hitting
neurons that wasn't supposed to travel
through different Avenues it wasn't
supposed to travel to so as these
electrical impulses this electricity
this electrical grid is moving it's
hitting into metal right there when it
hits into metal it then moves away from
the metal it travels a different
direction so every time an electrical
impulse is cruising here it goes right
into the metal grid right there boom
into the metal grid ricochets sometimes
it goes off to a different avenue it has
to find different places to go and
that's the adapting people do children
do right adults do they adapt some of
them have to fight their way through it
but they adapt but the electrical
impulses end up hitting metal which is
the red mark right there and then
travels into a different area you see
and that's this whole thing where it's
it's like that basically when we're
suffering with any kind of condition or
symptoms whether it's brain f focus and
concentration issues however it is it's
it's we have to fight through it our
brain is fighting through it for us
those electrical impulses are going in
different places you know so we can
actually adapt and somehow survive it
and we do we do adapt and we do survive
it Aon over there on YouTube I'm doing
the obsessive thoughts brain shot as you
speak it's so helpful and I am really
grateful oh that's incredible brain
shots right there oh in the book right
here
too
woohoo okay let's go into this a little
bit
more all
right um and here's the thing what
people don't realize when we're dealing
with these symptoms and conditions is
that there are real reasons why we're
dealing with it and we tend to start
beating ourselves up so I've seen people
with
ADHD just beat the crap out of
themselves because they're not
performing they feel like they're not
performing the way they need to they
feel they're not they're not doing what
they need to do they're judging
themselves people are judging them that
live with them or that know them and it
gets really hard and we get so
disconnected to realizing there's
actually a real problem and it's not my
fault that we end up just beating the
crap out of ourselves I've seen that
happen for so many people for so many
years so you know and if the medication
they're taking the amphetamines aren't
doing good enough for them then they're
really hard on themselves and they just
walk around like my ADHD is really
acting up my ADHD is really I got ADHD
and that's they tell themselves over and
over again but really what they have is
I got a metal deposit I got Metals in
the mid midline canals what they should
be knowing I got metal sprinkled about
in my brain and I got to get these
Metals out because these metals are
causing this but people take it on like
themselves where they don't know it's
the metals they don't know it's
something else so then it's them it's
them they're the ones so a lot of people
are hard on themselves because they're
the problem that's what they believe I
got ADHD I'm struggling I suck I totally
suck and that's what people believe they
feel that way they they they push
through they push through they take
their amphetamines they prescribed
amphetamines and they push through and
they try to function they try to live
their life but they always have this
thing kind of hanging over them like I'm
just I I'm hard to talk to I get it I
got ADHD or I'm having a moment with the
ADHD and then they're hard on themselves
because they're not focused on what a
with the real problem is they weren't
enlightened into the real problem they
weren't educated on the real problem
instead they're educated with you got
ADHD that's your problem boy that's your
problem and you got to live with it you
can try to take some medication if you
can you can try to get rid of processed
food and try to eat better and maybe
it'll improve a little but either way
you end up thinking that you're just you
got this problem and people when you
move that over to like the real problem
that's when life changes instantly
already it's like wait a minute this
isn't me I'm not the ADHD
person this isn't me um that's not my
identity I'm struggling with toxic heavy
metals I need to get that out so then
when you're doing the medical medium
heavy metal detox and your ADHD is is
leaving it's like a rebirth it's like
what the heck is going on so many people
then they're like reborn it's a
religious experience when you can get
rid of something like your ADHD and you
can get rid of it and it's just
religious experience it's like what
because you're actually like you're
actually hunkering down you're getting
disciplined you're doing the heavy metal
detox and you're getting better and
you're putting it behind you so many
people got rid of their ADHD it's not
even in their vocabulary anymore they
don't even talk about it they moved on
with their life there it was way put in
the past that's the medical medium
information it's just it's just
incredible Trish HR says on Facebook so
you disagree what science says about it
relating to a dopamine deficiency
correct
I do because the dopamine dopamine
deficiency was um was a theory they
don't have any way to prove it I mean
look if science can prove it if they can
show you all that a dopamine deficiency
is really happening in somebody's brain
like could if they could really show you
and then somehow show you that that
dopamine deficiency is causing the ADHD
but they can't right they can't do any
of that they can't do anything they can
just write a paper and that's what they
do so Trish they just write a paper and
a paper with a theory on it saying you
know dopamine deficiency they don't have
a way to test they don't have a way to
test that that's the
ADHD and then that's it there's nothing
there it's like sand through your hands
right but if they had a way to actually
show that or prove it or be able to show
someone somehow that that was it and
they can present that then yeah I'd be
open to it I'd be like all right but
they've never done that doesn't it
because just like all you know know what
science is doing for Alzheimer's now
they're taking medical medium info about
um Mercury toxic heavy metals being
responsible for Alzheimer's so now
they're talking about that now um a
decade or more later after I've already
been talking about it teaching about it
and Publishing information about it so
now science is like oh we think it could
be Metals really and they still haven't
found the metals in the person's brain
to line it up to actually be Alzheimer's
keep that in mind it's not like they cut
somebody's brain open and they found a
metal deposit and they said hey that's
the Alzheimer's we have a metal deposit
in somebody's brain they they're not
doing that they're just like hearing
about it because of the books you know
millions of copies around the world and
and talking about you know like metals
and metals and causing Alzheimer's and
Dementia and then they're hearing about
it and then they're writing papers
saying you know we think there might be
Metals in evolved but they haven't cut
open somebody's brain they haven't
discovered a deposit of metal and then
they haven't lined it up to alzheimer's
see so yeah that's pretty much where
we're at so the evolving domestic
chemical situation you guys that people
are breathing in every single day from
treatments on their lawns to fabric
softeners to detergents to fragrances to
the scented candles right now you hear
it all the time right scented candles
say it's like yep sended candles to all
the different fragrances perfumes and
colog those do domestic Invaders Harbor
more metals they also lower the immune
system they also have their own toxic
agents inside of them but what happens
is those contribute to more Metals
they're vaporized Metals so fragrances
are vaporized Metals toxic conventional
fragrances I'm not talking about like a
really pure lemon
oil okay from the Rind of the lemon and
that's what you're smelling that has
heavy metals in there I'm not going
there I'm talking about like the
fragrances that are just in everyday's
everyday people's lives the air
fresheners to the car air fresheners the
fabric softeners perfumes cologn the
scented candles to the fungicides
everything that's thrown on People's
Clothing all of it combined is filled
with vaporized metal and so you're
breathing it in and what happens is with
children when they have ADHD they
already have the metals in the midline
canal they're already struggling they're
already dealing with Metals right the
aluminum the Mercury and other metals
and then on top of that you get all the
domestic Invaders those exposures and
breathing in all of those exposures and
all that metal and then yeah it just
compiles and worsens and worsens worsens
things but if somebody wants an answer
how do I get rid of my ADHD got to get
the medals out have to it's critical got
to get them out heavy metal
detox very important heavy metal detox
if you want the metals out it's that
critical and one that is that has a
track record that has worked for so many
people that's what matters not new ones
people put together because they want to
hop on the bandwagon the train they want
to make money sell products that's all
great and all but use a heavy metal
detox that is known to work for years
and years and years Dr fwn also don't
buy the
neurodiversity um
celebration it's meant to normalize the
fact that everyone is having
neurological problems and Dr Fawn by the
way is an expert in um in autism expert
in ADHD expert in so many different
neuro and brain condition
so Dr F thank you for being here amazing
so let's uh let's head to
another little spot here where are we
brain fog
yep brain fog is always worth talking
about because so many people suffer from
it to a degree that they feel like
they've lost their mind and they're
getting diagnosis now of early early
Alzheimer's Alzheimer's early dementia
they're getting diagnosis of early
diseases and anybody who's asking about
autism read the uh medical medium
Secrets right read that book if you can
the new edition I have it somewhere I
was looking through it the other day I
will get it voila magically it appears
and I have it right here okay so if you
want to know more about autism check out
medical medium New
Edition if you like problem is with
brain fog is is that it's not like it
was years ago I used to see like severe
brain fog cases years ago I used to see
there's there was a decent amount of
people with it but for the majority of
people with brain fog years ago it was
more mild conditions not as many serious
now we're in an epic state of emergency
when it comes down to brain fog there
are so many people coming down with it
every single day they get the worst
brain fog conditions after right see
after the flu after some kind of you
know condition like some kind of like
bug that's going around or stomach flu
or you neuro virus or something and then
they have the worst brain fog afterwards
there's a lot of people triggered into
it but there's a lot of people that just
it just happens they wake up in the
morning and one morning and it's not
working something is not right
something's not kind of clicking in and
then it goes away by 10: in the morning
or it comes in at 10: in the morning and
then it goes away at around 1 and then
it comes in bad at 3: and then they're
like intermittent brain fog and they're
in this this state of intermittent brain
fog and then it's all day every day all
day every day sometimes really bad
sometimes not so bad scale one to 10
well my brain fog is out of three today
next day my brain fog is out of seven
the next day my brain fog is out of five
next day my brain fog is out 11 where I
can't even focus I can't think I can't
work I can't do anything so many people
really suffer from brain fog and they
really do all right so let's go into a
little bit severe cases of brain fog can
be
devastating indeed
devastating making people feel like
they've lost their Minds I'm in brains
saver guys just reading right out of
brains saver I'm on page 329 I saw
somebody asked what page
329 so yeah all
right so I want to show you the
um other
[Music]
books very interesting all right let's
keep on going even mild brain fog is
very challenging on the person's mental
and emotional state I find brain fog
being one of the most challenging for a
lot of people and
um you know it's really really difficult
for a lot of people can I put this right
here you guys there we go kind of in in
every every place
there heavy metal
detox can't say it enough get
better work on it
heal move past it there is life after
chronic illness there is okay there is
life after chronic illness keep that in
mind never forget that there truly
is okay even mild brain fog is very
challenging on the person's mental and
emotional state one major factor behind
brain fog is a liver that's saturated
with a lot of toxic
metals and
garbage so there we go got the liver
again don't lose that
liver okay livers that get filled up
with all kinds of junk all kinds of
different stuff toxic heavy metals are a
big one right there yep scented candles
air fresheners fragrances pesticides
herbicides other toxins providing fuel
now here's the thing with brain fog
okay brain fog is a little different
sometimes where someone is viral and
toxic viruses in the liver that's the
liver virus in the liver yes the liver
Harbors so many viruses Epstein bar cyto
virus hhv6 hhv7 herpes simplex one HSV 2
okay undiscovered herpes viruses
shingles sit inside our liver that's
where they sit and what they do is they
eat and feed on the the metals so they
eat and feed on the metals inside the
liver and then they release a neurotoxin
and that neurotoxin goes into the
bloodstream and floats
around and gets all through the body and
then it hits the brain and then we short
circuit and then we got brain
fog all right the epin bar virus feeds
on these poisons the neurotoxins it
releases explode through the bloodstream
and spinal fluid and from there they can
cross get ready the blood brain
barrier due to their unique infiltration
quality they can trojen horse it into
your brain they can cross the blood
brain barrier they can trojen horse it
in there that's what they do okay they
enter into the brain they shortcircuit
neurons when once again we're in that
place where the neurons are all short
circuiting Rooney Lee says I'm noticing
more of my friends getting brain fog
after a sickness yes it lasts for them
it lasts for them long after they're
sick yes Rooney totally and and I see
that all the time let me explain why
okay so all right you catch the
flu you get it you're sick with a fever
you're dealing with the flu you got
congestion your body is overrun by flu
viruses they are proliferating and
exploding your immune system has to
battle those flu viruses that's your
immune cells right there's the flu
viruses a war
ensues okay many of your white blood
cells your immune cells and killer cells
get destroyed in the process many of
them are lost in the battle and as
they're battling the flu virus it's
that's happening right there the immune
cell dies and you lost another immune
cell and then many of the immune cells
are actually killing the flu virus see
and eating the flu virus until it's gone
and then die themselves your immune
cells die
themselves because the flu made you lose
half your immune system or
more something decided to rise
up something rose
up it was another virus that was sitting
inside the
liver percolating and living in there
having a good time whether it was
dormant or just a little bit post
dorment and then after the flu when you
losing your half of your immune system
battling the flu viruses and your immune
cells
died the virus rose up and that virus
Epstein
bar most of the time Epstein
bar is having its day and then it's
feeding on things it likes to feed on
poisons toxins toxic heavy metals eggs
as
well
eggs and when it feeds on those eggs
because you're having eggs I don't want
to drop that
egg what happens is that it's releasing
more poisons and toxins those toxins and
poisons go to the
brain and we end up short
circuiting and where we end up sicker
than we were before I was talking about
this long before the
2019 20 long before the 2020
pandemic I've been talking about this
long before that so it's long flu and
that's what it is you get the flu or you
get the neuro
virus you get some kind of bug it knocks
your immune system down a war ensues
your immune cells die and when they die
because they're trying to save your life
and they're beating down viruses then a
different virus that's been hidden in
you set aega virus Epstein bar hhv6
hhv7 shingles Rises up most of the time
Epstein bar virus that's the one that's
the opportunist in the situation Rises
up and now you're sicker with other
problems long after your flu long after
all that so yeah very
interesting
okay over there on YouTube I own a Gaba
and celery Force help my brain fog so
much they do I recommend it to friends
all the time I do I do I do okay
okay MTO cery Force for brain
fog
yep I agree all right let's get into
this because we got some stuff to cover
okay when upar feeds on these poisons
the neurotoxins it releases explode
through the bloodstream spinal fluid
cross the bloodb brain barrier you have
now brain
fog and then short circuiting of the
neurons happens and then damaged
neurotransmitter occur these neurotoxins
have the ability to diminish
neurotransmitter activity and
neurotransmitter chemicals themselves
basically your neur neurotransmitter
chemicals start to diminish and then
you're in worse
shape Kate Courtney says I got brain fog
and you were the only one who saved me a
blessing led me to your first book right
as it was released and I knew I found
the truth thank you he here's my first
book
it's a new edition that's
it all
right the electrical impulse was
carrying messages and thoughts and
information so let's cover that really
quick all right
so yep
all
right so your brain right
here okay electrical impulses are
carrying information so all that
electricity going through your
brain all that electricity going through
your
brain is carrying
information I was just thinking you know
right when it snows
outside how pretty it is the snowflakes
are coming down do you ever see like the
big snowflakes they're coming down and
the temperatur is somewhere around 32
33 and the big snowflakes are just
floating down and they look like they're
about to
melt and when they land on your hand
they're half
melted and it feels cold but yet it's
not that cold
outside and the air smells so fresh and
clean right okay all
right electricity is carrying
information throughout your brain
electricity is carrying information
throughout your
brain so
I I love the winter
and like I really like the snow
um you know like when when it's get gets
cold outside and the snowflakes when
they're they're bigger do you ever see
them like
melt like I talked to somebody recently
and that's what they said to me and I
knew they meant everything that I just
said and they couldn't get it out their
brain fog was so bad the electricity was
hitting metal and toxins everywhere they
had so many neurotoxins in their brain
and they were trying to tell
me
that what they really wanted to say
because I sat there and I talked to them
and I talked to them for like 45 minutes
for like an hour and I talked all about
I said take your time tell me what you
mean tell me what you want to say and
the person who used to talk perfectly
fine talked great articulate anything
actually really smart person a genius
could not
explain properly how they felt
emotionally how they felt about the air
being so crisp and clean how they felt
about the snowflakes how they just start
to melt how the temperature was about 33
degrees really highly intelligent person
that wanted to talk about temperatures
fluctuations of temperatures and
different weather patterns and the
snowflakes into different sizes and
shapes right all that and they couldn't
even get it out and they literally were
in tears and said aw that's why I need
to know like I there somebody I haven't
talked to in years that I knew 20 years
ago and they reached out to me and
they're like I can't even tell you what
I'm going through right now and I'm like
I know what you're going through I I
know I understand yes I'm not in your
shoes and I'm not living with that but
but I know I do know the spirit of
compassion just allows me to know I I I
since I was a child so and this person
this person couldn't even get that out
and the brain fog was taking over and
taking over they had a rest that's it
after that 45 minutes of talking they
were in bed and they were done for the
day that was it the brain fog was so bad
and this was post having a really bad
flu like a month ago six weeks ago
whatever it was terrible terrible so
electrical impulses electricity is going
through the brain carrying information
so it's carrying that snowflake
information or what do you want to talk
about do you want to talk about
something that you saw you want to talk
about some birds you identified and you
want to you want to tell somebody about
which birds you like are your favorite
birds and you want to talk about that so
you have Birds right you have birds in
that information what else do you want
to talk about grocery shopping you were
at the store you saw some really
incredible apples right so you're
looking at these amazing apples so you
got apples on in your mind right on that
electrical impulse in that electrical
impulse going through the neuron you got
apples information about that the ones
that you like you like the red apples
you like whatever Apple that you like
the Fuji apples the bray burs the Gallas
all that and what happens is when your
brain fog is really really bad you won't
be able to really kind of come across to
somebody about the gala versus the bray
bur versus the Fuji versus the honey
crisp right versus the the Macintosh
versus the red delicious versus the you
know the the all the different ones and
the Granny Smith the green apple and you
won't even be able to kind of like work
with that with somebody else like talk
like you want to talk and that's it
people go through they suffer with
severe brain fog where they have to kind
of shut it down and shut it off where
they're not going to be able to talk
about apples they're not going to be
able to talk about their store trip so
much what they see or what they saw at
the Farmers Market Market or how the
weather is and what they whatever what
the trip they took they can't go into
detail and on that electrical you know
grid right here is all that information
trapped on it about the birds they saw
all the information about the food they
were eating or the food they like and
they whatever and it's on that grid and
then that grid short circuits right
there from neurotoxins it's short
circuits from all the Epstein bar
neurotoxins from other metals in the
brain and as it short circuiting
they're starting to run their adrenals
it's not their fault but their adrenals
start to crank up okay here they here
they are lost
them and they start to sweat people with
a lot of brain fog
sweat when they're talking to someone or
trying to convey something or articulate
something or get something across
especially if it's emotional if it's
emotional they start to get wrenched
their armpits get
filled
because adrenaline is actually kicking
in adrenaline's kicking in because
there's a problem in the brain there's
something wrong in the brain there's a
short circuit so really bad brain fog a
short circuit
happens and when that short circuit
happens because metals and neurotoxins
are interfering with electrical impulses
electrical activity and when that's
happening they're short circuiting and
it's making them nervous
and they're struggling and then their
adrenals start to release
adrenaline and that adrenaline is
rushing through their body because they
have to convey a message and they're
upset and they're
emotional and then they get wet their
armpits fill with water they start to
sweat happens all the
time
Tekk says oh my God on YouTube oh my God
aw that's me when I try to communicate
with others it's difficult to get my
words out thank you for all you
do all
right I'm really sorry you go through
that by the way I really am sorry all
right over there you're speaking you're
speaking to me a w I would struggle to
find words to speak
wasn't even able to find things in my
own house it was that bad only and only
medical medium info helps me when I
suffered to death it's
awful I'm so glad that the information
is helping it's moving you forward thank
God anelia says this is me I can't
recount anything I don't sweat but it's
so hard and I feel frustrated ated
because I remember the feeling of what
happened but not
details I understand I
do yeah we're in brain fog a little bit
more and then we're going to move
on all right these neurotoxins have the
ability to diminish neuro
neurotransmitter activity and
neurotransmitter chemicals themselves
meaning that when an electrical impulse
electrical impulse tries to run down a
neuron the electrical impulse can
misfire and it's approaching any kind of
contamination so it misfires in short
circuits that's what
happens another factor in brain fog is a
high toxic heavy metal
load yes within the brain itself that's
a brain loaded with Metals that's
another form of brain fog you can have
both you can have
both keep that in mind you better
believe it okay here's a metal deposit
right there here's a metal deposit right
there aluminum Mercury lead cadmium
arsenic right metal
deposits you can have a bad case of
brain fog or you can have metal
sprinkled about like this Christmas tree
types of of metal sprinkled
about you can have different Metals all
sprinkled about in the brain there you
go
okay toxic heavy
metals
metals that can get us in trouble big
time let's move
on
okay celery
juice I got some celery
juice by the way a little grapefruit
juice today
needed a little glucose right
there to
um get me pumped up all right let's
go focus and concentration
issues let's hit that a little bit one
source of focus and concentration issues
is along the lines of what you read
about in the ADHD section heavy metals
such as mercury and aluminum in the
cerebral midline Canal sprinkle
throughout the brain as well or both
when metals reside in the brain they
often dampen dampen electrical activity
causing the brain to try to adapt by
increasing electrical output which
brings on temporary bouts of
clarity that results in overheating so
then the brain must go into extreme
cooling so we're going to talk about
overheating cooling the whole bit so I'm
in this book right here brain
saver brain
saver
okay which ends up reducing electricity
act activity leading someone to
flip-flop back to moments of poor
concentration so cooling heating cooling
heating cooling
heating this is interesting right here
about focusing concentration okay our
brains get hot and then they quickly
cool then they get hot again then they
quickly cool that's what they
do
our brain gets
hot
right okay that's what happens and
sometimes our brain gets hot certain
area just here our brain gets hot in
this area right
here heats up heats
up then starts to cool
down
see this
fluctuating you're
focused you're focused you're getting
focused
again heats up heats up heats
up you're losing concentration you can't
focus anymore cooling down cooling down
cooling down cooling
down okay
right you're getting focused you're
getting focused it's coming into Clarity
you can think you can actually talk
think you're hanging in there heating up
heating up heating up got a problem
though got a problem cooling down
cooling down cooling down can't focus
losing concentration losing
concentration okay trying to give an
example of kind of how it
works because having toxic heavy metals
in the brain could could cause a lot of
different things to happen one is
Extreme heating extreme cooling
fluctuations of heating cooling heating
cooling and then we're all over the map
we are all over the map emotional we're
like we're focused we're there and then
we're we lost our focus our
concentration we're somewhere else we're
somewhere else now or we're now really
emotional or we're less emotional we can
be everywhere in any where Right Heating
and Cooling happens inside the brain
because metals and the electrical Grid
in some people this whole Supernatural
thing happens physically and right not
physically and it happens spiritually
and physically and it's a mesh a whole
mesh of emotions of physical information
in the
neurons information that's in the
soul there's a lot of heating there's a
lot of emotional output and then there's
a lot of cooling and and it's up and
down all of
it
okay when metals reside in the brain
they often dampen Electric electrical
activity causing the brain to try to
adapt by increasing electrical output
which brings in bouts of clarity Heating
and then boom cooling which ends up
reducing electrical activity leading
someone to flip-flop back to moments of
poor concentration where you're
flip-flopping like I got Clarity I lost
it I had Clarity an hour ago I lost it
now now I'm struggling I had Clarity
this morning before my coffee I drank
all my coffee had you know had Clarity
boom and then after my coffee later on
when everything just kind of like I
don't know when my caffeine ran out no
Clarity anymore no Focus no
concentration no focus and concentration
issues can also come from a chronic
viral in
infection okay chronic viral
infection viruses love to eat they love
to eat this delicious cheddar cheese I
have right here they love cheddar
cheese so when people eat cheddar cheese
the viruses will love to feed on it
sometimes it takes years and then
finally boom it's just they fed on
cheese every now and then when you're
eating it and fed on more cheese every
now and then when you eat it and then
the virus is proliferated they
multiplied they came out of dormy they
got hungrier and
hungrier and so cheese and dairy
products will feed
viruses they will they will over time
butter will feed viruses over
time
see Western says over there on YouTube I
almost never have coffee but when I do
my brain lights up and I can talk so
easily had my coffee Cofe but a day
later I'm depressed and tired oh man I'm
depressed I'm
tired yep I understand all right let's
go let's move let's move move move let's
keep it going
um there a lot of a lot of good comments
coming up okay why does that
happen you had your coffee and your
adrenaline acted as an amphetamine
guess what an amphetamine does okay CU
your coffee is like a daily
amphetamine every day people have their
amphetamine through their caffeine
right and then then there's people that
are taking
amphetamines okay I won't list them all
but there's a bunch of them when they
take their amphetamines guess what it
does it ignites
happiness out of your adrenals it
ignites
adrenaline so the reason why we take the
amphetamine is so our adrenals can go
boom and then we're focused we're
feeling better we're feeling like we can
think we're rising out of our brain fog
rising out of our
ADHD rising out of our focus and
concentration
problems and then when the amphetamine
wears off coffee
chocolate right caffeine Mach tea green
tea or prescribed amphetamine that your
doctor gives you when the amphetamine
wears off and the adrenaline comes
down we're
depressed we're sad we're
depressed we're
crying
we're
miserable many people are just in a dark
place and then we get back on our coffee
or caffeine or matcha our chocolate we
get back on our amphetamines which is
caffeine and then we or we go and we
take another
amphetamine dosage from our doctor's
amphetamine prescription and we're back
on top again for a little bit we're
having a pretty good day we're back on
top and then adrenaline flooding
adrenaline's flowing it's flowing and
then it all comes crashing down and
we're depressed and down in the
dumps Max von says over there on YouTube
when I quit coffee there was a period of
time when I didn't know if I'd ever feel
happy
again it's a struggle it's a struggle
not
easy Von says I gave up coffee amazing
okay all right chronic viral infections
where viruses such as Epstein bar can
feed off of toxic heavy metals such as
mercury and aluminum like we're talking
about before releasing neurotoxins that
float around the bloodstream saturating
neurotransmitter chemicals dampening
everything when this occurs electrical
impulses running across neurons short
circuit because they become polluted
polluted what's next now occurring is a
new wave of dangerous chemicals being
produced every day by the chemical
industry I'm trying to make it sound as
interesting as possible because when you
talk about the chemical IND industry it
just doesn't sound interesting yeah the
chemical
industry
y they're doing some bad stuff out there
chemical industry is creating a bunch of
bad
chemicals and those bad chemicals are
hurting our children children hurting
us but what's now occurring is a new
wave of these dangerous chemicals the
chemical industry is pumping this [__]
everywhere into the environment and our
children and our pets are ingesting it
and we inhale it these toxic chemical
substances are adding to the viral fuel
keeping us sick because it's like
breathing in more dosages of
unauthorized toxic heavy metals that are
floating through the air and getting
into our bloodstream in and our
body glad you guys love to hang around
for some of this you know we're going
into this it's either this or just like
what everybody loves which is five ways
for
longevity five best tips for longevity
CU only everybody has the attention span
right now of a flea did you notice that
you guys that everybody has the
attention span of a flea out there so
all they like is like quick bioh hacks
like five five top foods for longevity
five best ways to stay alive to live to
200 years old I like okay I could watch
that for about 5 seconds or 5
minutes all right sometimes focus and
concentration seems to improve randomly
on its own and sometimes they get worse
one theory is that the gut has
everything to do with the brain that's a
theory out there and so cleaning up the
gut automatically improves mental
Clarity yeah that's it this Theory is
misleading the real reason that someone
can focus more easily when they start
eating better is that they're removing
unhealthy
foods like viral Foods they're low
lowering the viral consumption of the
toxic viral food so what they're doing
so when they're getting away from
processed foods that have a lot of bad
cheese and all the other garbage and
everything else when they're starting to
push that
away and they're pushing away the gluten
because gluten feeds viruses all of a
sudden there's a little bit of an
improvement okay let's go in just a
little
bit okay all
right it's not all about cleaning up the
intestinal tract and restoring bacterial
balance to the gut this is why so many
unhealthy people with very messy
intestinal tracts filled with
unproductive yeast and mold and fungus
never had a focus and concentration
problem ever
ever there people with strep sitting
right there on the outside of their anus
every single day strep like three kinds
of strep if they took a Q-tip and stuck
it in their rectum and try to actually
grow something in a Petri dish right
okay get a culture going they would see
some Fierce
strep grow from just swabbing the
Rus and at the same time those people
don't have Focus concentration issues
they're just living their life going to
work doing their job whatever they're
doing being productive and they have all
kinds of crap inside their guts and all
kinds of stuff bacteria and everything
else in fungus and yeast and mold
unproductive fungus yeast and mold or
really bad stuff right SEI and all kinds
of garbage in there and it's feasting on
everything and it's just a mess in there
and they don't want focus and
concentration you can talk to them and
they'll just like they'll talk circles
around
somebody all right let's move on to the
next one
I see lime disease right there we'll
have to talk about that another day oh
lupus right there you guys have this
book do you have this
book all right CFS me CFS or
CFS also known as neurological
fatigue medical medium information
chronic fatigue syndrome that was no
that's not my info right there CFS the
term CFS chronic fatigue syndrome is not
mine it's not MediCal medium I can't
take that credit neurological fatigue
though is medical medium and it's also
known as some other things too sometimes
fatigue is easy to explain if someone
has been running themselves
down exercising too much playing too
much traveling too much vacationing too
much working too hard maybe they're just
stuck working too hard maybe they're
being emotionally beaten down maybe
they're getting PE PTSD from their jobs
from their careers maybe they're getting
PTSD from their relationships maybe they
have a a very difficult relationship
maybe they're they're breaking up in the
Rel you like their relationships and
friendships are breaking up and they're
having problems and struggles and
there's no resolve and it's weighing
down on their brain and weighing
weighing down on their head and brain
stem and they're just thinking about all
their different problems they have while
they're trying to work while they're
trying to live their life while they're
trying to support themselves everything
all in the above and they get tired and
burnt out and now they got tiredness
fatigued the whole
bit
okay all right
oh I got some celery Force right here
and I'm going to take some
myself so I have not taken any and what
I noticed about celery
Force for me and noticed for a lot of
people kicks in in like 12 for me it's
12 minutes kicks in in 12 minutes I've
seen people where it kicks in in 8
minutes there's no celery in there it's
called celery Force right celery force
is an incredible incredible
supplement that I swear to
God I get I will get on my
knees and swear to
God okay
like I'll say
God if I am not telling you the fact
that this happens to me if I'm not
telling you what I've seen this do for
people okay then I'll take my punishment
whatever that is because if for me it's
12 minutes right so I'm going to pop
some in if you don't
mind did you ever see me swallow a pill
capsule
so what happens is like in like 12
minutes after I send those down the
celery
force all of a sudden things just wake
up and I don't sleep that much because
I'm working really hard so some nights
I'll get like when I'm writing the books
it's really bad it's like 2 hours a
night 3 hours a night sleep and when the
deadline comes up it's like 1
hour and right now you know I'm only
doing like 5 hours of sleep at night
right now so I'm I'm juggling a lot of
stuff and so one when I take that celery
force and I'm not like timing it right
now I don't know I got to look for a
time whatever the
clock but right around 12 minutes is
when it just like slam something starts
happening and it's the craziest Clarity
like it's Clarity right it's so crazy
anyway you you do celer Force too s says
oh my God I took celery Force before
celery juice yesterday and forgot but I
had to Mo I had the most functional
morning like I took like you took
amphetamines
amazing seriously know do you know any
anything about like that like it's crazy
what it does when he says oh yeah celery
force is amazing my best friend lately
yeah and the thing is like every time
like I don't take it like if I just like
forget about it or something and I'm
just like I'm busy and I'm doing stuff
whatever and I don't take it and then
all of a sudden I'm like wait a minute
wait a minute I got to take it it's like
you just feel it hit like smack MTO says
SEL Force helped me immediately with
brain fog thanks beloved yeah no it it's
it's great it's like so great so I'm
still I got like six minutes ago before
it hits me is it like six more minutes
too cold white says are you writing a
book I I want to answer
that believe me
all
right
okay so some people it's not about
fatigue where they're tired because
they're all busy like I said and I
explained all that extreme fatigue
that's not from lack of sleep on the
other hand has an air of mystery about
it it's that fatigue people get where
it's a mystery I'm like four minutes
away 10 more minutes ago wait a minute
when was that comment left cuz I I think
I'm like four am I four minutes away or
5 minutes
away while it can last for a shorter
time extreme fatigue is often
long-term chronic
fatigue syndrome brutal
longterm your legs can feel like you got
rocks tied to them bags of cement on
your arms you feel like you can't lift
your
arms right you feel like you're dragging
you're just dragging along you know that
feeling you're just dragging
along and worse in that you feel like
everything's shutting down on you I
don't know if you guys have ever
experienced it where it's severe CFS
where you're shutting down you have to
nap and you're not even sleeping you're
just shutting down you're still awake
but you're just shutting down you guys
know I endorse these guys fery guys know
I endorse them it's a the best stuff on
the market hands down I don't care what
anybody says out there about their supp
liit being the best sure right no BS
this is the best stuff there is and
there's reasons why it is it's
unbelievable the only company that does
things like doesn't put all the
anti-caking agents in there and all that
stuff that no one tells you about that's
in all those other supplements I could
go on forever but I know that that's not
what this is
today so you know when it comes down to
CFS and chronic fatigue syndrome what I
don't like when I don't like anybody
suffering or struggling with it at all
right kicking in by the way I'm just
starting to feel
it it's kicking in right now what I
don't like is when someone gets more
than the fatigue more than the like the
lead feel like the lead legs and the
lead arms they're feeling the fatigue
where they're shutting
down they're laying on mattress Island
not because they're tired yeah they're
tired but they can't sleep they're
laying on mattress Island awake but shut
down like in this place where they can't
like function they can't talk they're
just they're just shutting down and they
have to do that they have to rest their
nerves for a little while and and then
they come out of it and they're able to
function for a little bit and that's
back to square one again it's such
serious neurological fatigue it's
brutal yep
mhm how fast does celery Force work with
you guys by the
way like seriously like how fast is it 8
minutes 12 minutes 14 minutes 20
minutes I mean it's always it's always
for what I've talked to people and for
me that's between 5 minutes and 20
minutes it's like between five and 20
right somewhere in that
pocket it's insane and it usually hits
the person at the same timeline too like
if they're an eight minutter then like
it hits eight minutes so it's in eight
minutes if they're a 10-min it's like in
10 minutes it's always around 10 minutes
crazy how that
works yeah someday I'll talk about it
more too all right so chronic fatigue
syndrome big part of it is viral
infections Epstein bar CYO Aben bar is
the big one
shingles all the viral loads that bring
people
down but Epstein bar is the big shining
star though that's the big one for
CFS and then what comes along with
Epstein bar is strap so strap and
Epstein bar their the big ticket winners
for
CFS and then if you got chronic fatigue
syndrome that's really really bad and
you're dealing with the viral issue and
the bacterial
issue and your immune system is dogging
it your immune cells are dogging it they
can't keep up with the bacteria the
strep they can't keep up with the virus
they can't keep up and then as that's
happening you might also have metals and
when you got metals like aluminum and
Mercury that's just some aluminum foil
right there couped with all that in your
body and then the domestic Invaders like
all the fragrances giving you more stuff
challenges for the immune system we end
up with severe severe CR chronic fatigue
syndrome and yeah Rachel says sorry
Force makes me
tired okay but do after that are you one
of those where it makes you tired like
the rare one it makes you a little tired
and then you're more more Sparky later
it's actually feeding the brain helping
it to strengthen and then you're more
Sparky later and have a better day ahead
of you or a better day the next day
because it's restoring
that's really awesome all right or or is
it something else or is it something
else that happens you guys incredible so
we covered a lot of different topics I
just want to run across a few things by
let's go to um muscle pain joint and
muscle pain let's look for
it yeah we're going to find
it there it is Joy muscle
pain if someone Falls on a knee or twist
their ankle we know why they're
hurting if somebody falls on a
knee and the
knee healed but the knee is still
hurting we don't know why they're
hurting someone twist your
ankle their ankle
better but their foot still hurts an
ankle still hurts mysteriously we don't
know why they're hurting then they get a
planter
fasciitis diagnosis we still don't know
why they're
hurting if someone didn't fall on their
ankle didn't whatever fall on their foot
fall on their face if someone didn't
break their arm if someone didn't bang
their head if someone didn't bump into
something if someone didn't twist their
leg but yet they got joint and muscle
pain we don't know why they're
hurting we only know why they're hurting
if they twist their
ankle and it
heals and the pain goes away and they
get a clean bill of health from their
doctor Medical
Professional and pain is gone no joint
pain no ankle pain no muscle pain around
the ankle it's gone we know why they
were hurting we know why they were
hurting they were hurting cuz they
twisted their ankle they sprained their
ankle they bang their foot we know why
they were hurting they bang their knee
it healed clean bill of health pain
gone it's because they banged their
knee
they wake up one morning they didn't
bang anything their knee starts hurting
ankle starts feeling like it's sprained
foot
hurts we don't know
why we
don't or like I said if they twist their
ankle and the ankle heals
completely sprain ankle's gone but
they're still hurting for a year
later we don't know why
medical meme information knows why and
the books know
why if someone falls on a knee or
twisted ankle and experiences aute pain
it is usually
straightforward
straightforward some pain comes from
injuries accidents or incidents and
there's no mystery
involved what's very different is if
someone experiences chronic fatigue
sorry chronic pain in the joints or
muscles with no discernable Source
magically happens Magic Ally
appears yeah even if a doctor diagnoses
someone with ra lupus Lyme disease
fibromyalgia it's still a mystery joints
and muscle
pain someone gives somebody a lupus
diagnosis or a fibro diagnosis it's
still a mystery it's mystery joint
shoulder elbow joint pain muscle pain
shoulder pain neck neck pain still a
mystery the real cause of this chronic
pain chronic mystery pain is viral
infection sometimes acute although most
long-term infections of a virus or
viruses sitting in the liver feeding on
its favorite
foods eggs are its favorite
food yep
eggs years down the road you guys all
you're going to hear about how how eggs
cause viral
problems mm info it's all you're going
to hear down the
road I mean it could be 3 years from now
four years from now maybe a little
further down the road but it's all
you're going to hear everybody's going
to be running from eggs everybody's
going to be talking about you know don't
don't eat eggs everybody's going to try
to do shock and all like influencers are
going to be like you should stay away
from eggs science now says eggs are bad
for you and everybody's going to go no
no no don't take my eggs away no you're
a jerk I'm I'm not following you anymore
I'm unfollowing you it's going to happen
like every day down the
[Music]
road meanwhile I've been crucified for
it nailed to the
cross the real cause of this chronic
fatigue and chronic pain and all that
muscle pain and aches acute pain that's
not from banging into a wall or the
corner of a door jam and you bang into
it is viral infections ly says it just
took my accelery force it helps me get
sharp and on my aame at
work is it 8 minutes 12 minutes 10
minutes when does it kick in for
you okay viruses sit in the
liver they actually released
neurotoxins viruses also spread through
throughout the body they get into areas
on
nerves and so let's do a little thing on
that really
quick all right give me a quick second
here
okay so got a Vegas nerves some Vegas
nerves here coming out of the brain
stem
got a little bit of a Vegas nerve here
okay viruses feed off of foods like
eggs that's what they do all
right wherever that bug went I will grab
it right here feeds off of eggs when we
eat eggs so we eat them they go into our
body they become fuel the undeveloped
proteins feed bugs viruses specifically
they love them bacteria too okay
so when the virus releases the
egg in a neurotoxin base okay virus
releases an egg in a neurotoxin base the
neurotoxins so let's make a little virus
here so we got a virus in the body right
there
another virus in the body Epstein bar
Epstein bar is a big one for muscles and
Joints epine bar
baby
yep all these Epstein bar
viruses it's a lot of different epor
viruses people collect a lot of them now
they don't realize
it all right so when those viruses eat
the
egg because you ate the
egg a poison comes
out of the virus that poison see it come
out of the viruses here that
poison is
in highly allergenic poison that hits
the Vagas nerve when it hits the Vagas
nerve different areas we can feel pain
in the strangest places
now if it hits the frenic
nerves some frenic nerves in our body
right in the Fric nerves frenic nerves
right here okay
right hits those frenic nerves right
here we can have pain anywhere
shoulders crazy
places we can have pain
everywhere tibial nerve do a little
tibial nerve down
here that's
right we can have pain in the craziest
places right the virus feeds on the food
it likes this little egg right here
releases
neurotoxins they hit nerves all through
the body nerves that go to joints and so
forth connected tissue around the joints
and now we're in pain mysteriously in
pain
regardless of your diagnosis ongoing
joint and muscle pain is viral that's a
strong bold statement from Spirit of
compassion these are not my words in the
books
okay s so's words in the
book and if someone doesn't like that
well 10 years down the road when all
their bioh hacks didn't work for them
and they were and their scale finally
tipped
and
they're having real problems with their
health and no influencer can kind of
like doctor it
up yeah the books are here for you and
it
matters if you could swallow your pride
and get over it the books are here for
you over here how can we get rid of
these viruses like epen bar protocols in
the books there are protocols in the
medical medium books to get rid of the
viruses right here protocols at work
that's gotten rid of viruses in people
for years and years who have moved
themselves forward there is life after
chronic illness there is life after
sickness there is life after sickness
okay
incredible see on telegram later today
I'm going to drop a telegram
message and you know exclusive audios on
exclusive audios on Telegram and also on
the medical medium IG broadcast channel
you know the one that's mm inside scoop
I'm going to leave a message there too
make sure you go there so you know the
broadcast channel on IG you guys check
it out like try to get on there going to
give you some inside scoop messages and
then telegram going to do a really good
message on that later get on the medical
medium newsletter so you know where I'm
going to be you guys I'm finally izing
the details right now I'm working on it
finalizing the details I am going to be
somewhere I'm letting you know and it's
going to be in
June it's going to be in June that's the
month it's going to be in June I think
it's going to be around June
15th and I'm going to be doing a book
signing yeah in LA Los Angeles
California Los Angeles
California in June around June 15th I'm
going to be doing a book signing I'm
just working out the details figuring it
all out I'll have more information get
on my email list the newsletter list I
can let you know June and La it is
that's where it is tell everybody about
it okay I'm going to be there if you can
if you can deal with
me since I'm so
obnoxious
if you guys can deal with me all right
going to sign books cuz what I'm going
to do I'm going to sign this one right
here I'm going to sign this brains saer
book right here to the medical
medium let me see I'm going to sign it
somewhere
here to the medical
medium
Community I freaking
adore
you that's
right I signed my first
book right here to the medical medium
Community I freaking adore
you I do anyway it's going to be in June
in La I'm going to be physically there
God
willing and um I'll have more
information about it soon location so so
forth and all that and exact day I think
it's going to be June 15th I think and
um all
right love you
guys I'm not going to be in Europe
signing books right now nope this is
where it's going to be it's my first
official and only book signing I've ever
done I don't know if I'm going to do
another one I don't know if I might do
another event of some kind this is a
book signing so I don't know if I'm ever
going to do another book sliding it's
the first one
ever all right love you