tomorrow morning the brain meditation
third episode of the medical medium
podcast
so you can find that you subscribe to
apple podcast to listen to it okay
that's where it is that's the official
platform for the medical medium podcast
but the brain meditation is next it's
the
third episode so you heard the first
episode right chemtrails the sky is
falling
which is really that's a mind blower
it's not for the faint of heart i've
said this before okay
and if you listen to that episode hear
it again because you probably missed
information it's so
packed a line for a line second episode
was fruit fear
okay they lied to you really important
one got to listen to that one again if
you haven't already share it with others
if you can
but the third episode tomorrow morning
make sure you
subscribe to apple podcast so you get
notified first
so of the episode now if you don't have
an apple device
go to medicalmedium.com so if you have
an android
go to medicalmedium.com and you can
actually just upload
the episode right there listen to it you
can listen to it on any device
but the brain meditation is next and
i have to give you a forewarning though
on this okay with the brain meditation
this is really intense in a good way
but it's really intense because once you
do it something's going to
change so when you do the brain
meditation
something is going to change because
it's about
ridding fear out of the soul so what
happens when we go through life
we get broken relationships broken
friendships
we get you know betrayal happens in our
life people
cheat on us they friendships you know
uh they they fall apart things happen we
go through emotional struggles emotional
hardships we get broken trust over it
we feel guilt and shame we get fearful
we get anxiety over depression all these
different things depersonalization
and what happens is this builds up in
our soul
and builds up in our soul and builds up
in our soul over time
and a lot of fear builds up the brain
meditation
and this is from spirit of compassion
this brain meditation is a powerful
powerful way to rid
that fear but here's how it works though
this is not a man-made meditation so
that's one thing right there
that's so important it's not man-made it
it's a meditation i haven't shared with
you guys yet because i've shared
meditations with you guys before right
you know the medical medium books
there's meditations in there and
and what i've done you know lectures
years ago i would share meditations
there too
from medical you know medical media
meditations it was from spirit of
compassion but this one
i haven't shared yet so this is a
special surprise so
um but prepare yourself find a quiet
spot
and settle in with a quiet spot it's a
short meditation so it's not super
long but it's powerful
very powerful it's it's a chiller
actually so it's a chiller so i'm
preparing you on that level because in
order
to rid fear from the soul something
actually has to happen and
because meditations meditations you have
to kind of like keep on doing them over
and over and over again in hopes that
you can get some relief and feel good
from them
and all this this is different this is
about actually
fixing something so this is actually
about
moving something forward and
accomplishing and fixing something
within this brain meditation
so i'll just give you a little run down
about how this works so tomorrow morning
the episode's going to be released okay
subscribe to apple podcast
so you get notified right away okay if
you
listen to medical medium uh old radio
shows or something from the old radio
show
that's censored and that's on different
platforms but
that's censored you have to know the
reason why this is on apple podcast
and that's why that's the official
platform for it is because it's
uncensored these are uncensored episodes
and this is an uncensored podcast
medical medium podcast the first
official uncensored medical meeting
podcast so
that's the official place now if you
listen to the podcast in other places
and you're like well i listened to it on
this platform and i'm telling my friend
to listen to it on that platform well
you're you're hearing censored versions
and where clips are out of it and you
don't know it and you're not
getting the episode it looks the same
seems like it's the same but it's not or
it's not going to upload right
i'm getting dms i'm getting notification
i mean people are notifying me they're
they're giving me dms you're contacting
me and they're telling me that
it's not loading right the episodes
aren't that's because it's not on apple
podcast and i keep on saying that over
and over again for a reason
i'm trying to tell you guys the medical
medium
podcast right now is uncensored and it's
on
apple podcast for a reason that's where
it is uncensored on
so i know you guys want to share with
other people where you're hearing it
hearing one here or hearing there from
another platform but
please know you're sending them to a
platform where they're not even going to
hear
the uncensored version so even if you
think you're you are you're not so sp
apple podcast letting you know so if you
have an android go to medicalmedium.com
and you can just upload the link to
radio show to the
podcast and you can hear it so okay so
um you're excited to listen this brain
meditation i want to talk about it just
for a minute with you guys so you know
what you're up against yeah michelle
michelle l says i have an android and
can listen to apple podcasts on my
browser
amazing michelle tell people that
incredible let them know
so they get the uncensored version
because if they go to the
to the usual places or the other
platforms that they think they've heard
like the old radio shows and stuff on
they're missing
they're potentially missing a lot of
stuff in there and
because those are censored that's why i
keep on telling people this really
important
and remember i'm not sponsored there's
no advertisements
um i'm not going to have an infomercial
in the middle of these episodes
just just you know it's not like that
the guys this
is a free resource not sponsored not
anything
so so yeah so charlotte
charlotte all the platforms out there
they're they're that's why
i'm making sure it's on apple podcast
that's the official launch
place for medical media podcast because
the other ones yes they're they're
censored in different ways in different
ways
um so how do you listen on your android
if you have an android or device
michelle just
she she has an android she said michelle
you can you can find her in the comments
and she said how she does it
okay you can go to medicalmedium.com uh
upload the uh the episode link and you
can listen right on your
your your android uh and michelle
michelle just follow the link and
and we'll open it thank you michelle for
helping her you're awesome
um and i really appreciate all that
you're doing and helping people and
telling people and everything michelle i
really appreciate that
you don't even know how much so and so
this brain meditation here's what
happens
we start getting out of body with ptsd
experiences we have in our life we start
disconnecting
so our soul because we all have a soul
all unique
so that's what makes us different right
there our souls right
what happens is it gets kind of tattered
along the way it gets kind of beaten
along the way
kind of kind of a little beat up and tat
and worn and tattered
by all these experiences we go through
life
divorces breakups friendships that go
wrong
um you know betrayal you know all these
different things that happen in our life
with relationships with other people
with you know with uh careers anything
that could
happen any kind of struggles losses oh
my god
terrible losses people people suffer
from ptsd because of it
and what happens is our soul starts to
kind of
kind of separate because separate from
our physical brain from our physical
body because it's just too much because
it's trying to get protected because
it's getting
injured it could get fractured by all
these experiences along the way and i've
talked about this over the years but
this is a meditation that spirit of
compassion taught me when i was younger
and i've um and i've shared it with
family i've shared it with
friends throughout the years to help
them rid fear
so that a connection is made again and
we don't know we get this disconnection
you guys we don't know
that we get this disconnection and you
will experience
when you do this brain meditation
something that i'm just preparing you
it's a chiller and i'm saying that
because it is because when you
start making that connection and fear is
leaving you as your soul is connecting
to your brain your physical brain and
body
you feel it it something changes you're
changed afterwards and then if you keep
on doing this i saw june has a comment
hey june i can't thank you in spirit
enough for these
mind-blowing and in information pack
podcasts aren't they in
i mean that chemtrail episode oh my god
and i listen to that episode i listen to
the episode
share it with people june i'm sure
you're sharing it i'm sure you are
and and everybody else share these
episodes with people please
the chemtrail one it's not for the faint
of heart though share it with people you
think got a skin
because it's really really intense and
the in the fruit fear one
june did you like the fruit fear one and
um
so and you have all the wonderful books
too bless it bless you
thank you for for for having the books i
got one behind me right here where is it
right there it's
cleansed the heel um so
the brain meditation you can do repeat
it over and over again
and it's a quick meditation really
powerful you could do it first thing in
the morning
mid-morning now when you get notified
apple podcast you subscribe to apple
podcast
yeah you'll hear it um so dominique
android users chrome medicalmedium.com
podcast dot uh plus listen to apple
podcast
click play okay there's the directions
right there go to medicalmedium.com for
android users
thank you thank you incredible
incredible because then
it will be uncensored because because
that's why i'm telling you guys
go to that's why it's the official
platform the apple podcast
and someone's like well what are you
getting sponsored no i'm not getting
sponsored by anybody there's no
advertisements there's no sponsorships
and there's no infomercials
and it's information to help you heal
but
i'm really excited about the brain
meditation being released tomorrow
morning
it's the third episode of the medical
medium podcast that's being released
and um i got a smile on my face on this
one because
this one's really close to me like dear
to me this brain meditation
a spirit of compassion has taught me
since i was a child and
and you can have anyone do this and
there was a question
earlier that came my way was can
children do it absolutely of course they
can do this meditation
and and but it's it's
really really healing on a soul
level of ridding fear is what it does
it's a little bit of a chiller though
i'm just being
frankly i'm just being straight out
about that so pre
so get you know get in a comfy spot
prepare yourself and get ready
because when you make that
soul connection back to the physical
body all the way
when you do this and fear just leaves
it's an experience
it really is so i just wanna i just
wanna
let you guys know um
so yeah so this is really important to
this is really important
information so i want to know i want to
i want you guys to know the chemtrail
episode
okay um share it with anybody you can
it's good for them to know if they can
protect themselves
you know i i don't like not knowing
things do you guys like
you don't like not knowing things in
your life you want to know everything
that's going on around just you could be
more protective so you can protect
yourself
so you know to drink your lemon balm tea
right here you know so you know to drink
in your lemon balm tea and take care of
yourself it's all these things matter
so um yeah and
uh simone says thank you anthony you're
the real deal
uh love you thank you so much uh honored
and you're the real deal too i'm sure of
it
and amy says cannot wait it's
really exciting uh as powerful as your
information is i can't imagine how
powerful this meditation is going to be
blessed to have you in our lives uh this
meditation
is not just the next level i can't even
use that term this meditation is
um it's not just groundbreaking
but it will take you to a new level with
getting rid of fear because there's so
much fear that's inside people and so
many
fear fear of getting a new relationship
fear of starting a new friendship fear
of trying to do something different in
your life fear of
anything with just so much that's going
on out there you love the podcast
greta you love the podcast incredible so
you love the chemtrail podcast
and you love the uh fruit for your
podcast share them with other people
please share them with other people um
but once again about
i just i can only guarantee that
on apple podcast with this with this
podcast the medical medium podcast that
it's uncensored there
i can't guarantee that with the other
platforms as i was saying before please
share
please share what you love about these
podcasts so i can re-post
you know in a whole bit so i want to
please share so i can you know so i can
the whole bit
um and leave a review on apple podcast
if you can
okay that would be amazing um so candy
says oh good
wonderful i started meditating uh well
if you just started meditating
this is this is gonna be this is gonna
be
yeah this is gonna be really special
when you
when you anybody who's even meditated
for 30 years
will be mind-blown when they do this
brain meditation
doesn't matter how long they meditated
all these years different whatever kinds
this is a whole different thing and i'm
kind of i'm giddy about it
i'm excited about it because i know what
you guys are going to experience
so i just like i am so excited tomorrow
morning because i'm going to be like oh
my god
they're experiencing what i've been
keeping
like just just showcase it showing to
family and showing your friends for
years
and and it's time it's time that you
guys
get to experience this meditation
as chad says i was blown away by the
chemtrail episode
the fruit one was really great as well
thank you so much
it's they're they're mind-blowing share
it with someone please
share these episodes with people please
because
it's only going to help people it has to
these episodes have to get around share
and tell them to listen on apple podcast
um can't wait to hear the brain
meditation lisa i'm really excited about
this
okay because what happens is when we go
through life
we we get hurt along the way even on a
little little levels and it creates
little
little specks of fear inside our soul
because then we're like wait a minute i
don't trust that
wait a minute i don't trust this wait a
minute
i don't know if i should do this or make
this decision this decision in life
i don't know if i should do this and so
fear can start to just
dominate and dominate in our lives and
over time
and what happens with this meditation
this brain meditation is
is it reconnects
the the soul and the physical brain
because they start
to separate which is that out of body
thing that goes on that we just start
like because life is so hard
and it reconnects and then fear just
starts to leave and it's really powerful
i can't wait for you guys to try this
and tell other people tell every people
tell people
you know on on your on your platforms
let everybody know you guys and when
you're doing it just no
it's not like you're doing it because oh
you know anthony has so much to gain i
don't have sponsorships with these
these episodes with with this medical
mean podcast i don't have
purposely don't have them i purposely
don't have them i have people
talking in my ear telling me you need
sponsorships you're
number one new york times best selling
author six books and
and and everybody around the world knows
who you are
and you yield millions of people and i'm
like well i don't want the sponsorships
i don't want the advertisers
i don't want all that in my podcasts
and so i want you guys to share these
and know that the intention is there to
just get
people better so please do that please
do that
leave a review if you can on apple
podcast if you feel up to it if you
really enjoyed it
leave a leave a review chrissy you can't
wait really need this
chrissy i can't wait until you try this
brain meditation
repeating it is just as powerful
so if you repeat it once a day i
recommend
i recommend this brain meditation twice
a day
it's a short one i recommend it twice a
day or
once a day every single day um i
meditated for four decades marina i met
meditated for four decades and i'm
excited about this meditation
marina unless i'm just wrong
you're gonna be blown blown away like
this this brain meditation
you're gonna be blown away by this brain
meditation i wasn't wrong about
chemtrails
people's minds are just blown you know
this this brain meditation
what it's going to do is reconnect the
soul to the physical brain
it's that connection that goes apart
over time from every war wound we
have like relationship problems all
these other things and it just happens
and happens christina said how could we
get access to the meditations
okay apple podcast so you want to
look for the medical medium podcast at
apple podcast okay there's a link
in the profile there's a link pinned i
mean there's a link in the
pinned so you can actually see that um
and then you can
you can find it that way now if you
don't have an apple device and you have
an android
uh michelle was earlier michelle just
said
that you can you can still get
medicalmedium.com and you can
find the episode at medicalmedium.com
the link and just upload it and you can
listen to it on any device
okay so it's important but in the
description the link is in the
description here so make sure you look
for it
it's a really good question because i
want people to be able to hear it
and um
i aspire to be like you anthony you're
so generous and loving
uh hannah that you're you're amazing
like
you know you know to know that you feel
that way about me
is really it just makes me feel good
because we're in it together to just
try to get people better and better and
better you know how it's always been
um maura says where is it i want to
watch
so you go to apple podcast so there's an
app apple podcast app you know and if
you have an apple device you go there
and you subscribe to the medical medium
um podcast on apple podcast so you get
notified
and when you get notified you'll get
notified of the brain meditation
tomorrow morning
it's coming tomorrow morning and
yeah i'm really happy about this because
this brain meditation is unlike anything
that's ever been out there anything that
anybody's ever experienced
and um i'm just like i'm thrilled
and but a little forewarn little
forewarning
it's a chiller it's a little bit of a
chiller you know
the hair might go up on the back of your
neck
as you're healing and getting rid of the
fear
and you do it over and over you do it
once a day you do it once a day you do
it twice a day
you can't go wrong with it it's that
powerful and it's that easy to do
um so yeah so yeah
can we start it now stuart said stuart
it's going to be tomorrow morning
and depending on where you are in the
world but it's tomorrow morning
so you go you can go to
medicalmedium.com
and you can you can if you have an
android or some other device and you
don't have apple and you can't
get apple podcast then go to
medicalmedium.com
upload it there okay and you'll see
podcasts in the menu at
medicalmedium.com you'll see podcast in
the menu at medicalmedium.com
so you can get the episodes and then you
can get the brain meditation episode
tomorrow morning
heather says heather angus said just
subscribed and looking forward to
tomorrow
and thanks for being you love this thank
you for subscribing so you can get
the episode i am so excited about this
i am i am um so
have you listened to the chemtrail
episode have you listened to the fruit
for your episode
okay preparing you chemtrail episode
it's a shocker
oh my god it's a shocker fruit fear two
so letting you know
uh no no noelle shepard hey noelle hey
so looking forward to this i can't wait
for you to try this noelle i can't wait
for you to
try this um tell dick i said hi and
uh he's an amazing man so i you know
it's
it's just it's just it's incredible june
i am so excited for the brain meditation
podcast
i know this is going to be amazing and
life-changing june it is
this is this this episode
is life-changing it really is um
please do a podcast on animals too in
the future so important to include our
pets god bless
i have pets i love pets i will have to
do that there's no doubt pets are so
important they are so important
they mean they mean so much you mean
everything michelle says i feel this is
going to be a game changer for me
always feel disconnected from the
traumas and emotions michelle
really really good good point
for me to talk about for a minute that's
so important thank you for
thank you for saying that because what
happens is we have that we have the
broken friendships and relationships and
the betrayal and the hardships and the
losses and all kind even
on the most mildest way to even extreme
then what happens is we kind of get out
of body we get disconnected no one knows
what that is and what that is is the
soul
getting disconnected to the physical
brain the neurons in the brain
and this meditation brings things back
it makes the connection that's why this
is so powerful
share it with others that you think are
hurt or just any
even if they're not they don't seem like
they're hurt they still have fear in
there deep inside
ashley says subscribe to his newsletter
for the links
yep yep correct correct
um yeah
so christine says will will the
meditation work for everyone
yes it does it works for everyone
it's that powerful and that healing
now i have meditations in medical medium
books i've
talked about medical media meditations
over the years this one i've been saving
for a long time
and now it's time to actually release
this
repeat this meditation and it compiles
it makes it even stronger and stronger
as time goes on you heal more
you rid more fear and you heal the soul
more and more so you read more fear
and you heal the soul more and more so
you do
every day do this the kids can do this
meditation i have
i have friends they have their whole
families doing i have friends their
whole families are doing it their kids
are doing
it's yes you can do that um
love you so much you're the best you're
the best you just subscribe mira says
just subscribe christina thanks i'm
honored i'm so proud of all you guys
uh meera said just subscribe incredible
to apple podcast
amazing so you get the notification
subscribe to apple podcast the medical
medium podcast that apple podcast that's
the official platform
and you know and i have people like well
why is it apple podcasts why can't i
listen to just any word because i can't
guarantee
that it's not censored in all those
other places this is uncensored that's
why i keep on saying
it's the uncensored medical medium
podcast for reasons you might be used to
hearing the podcast
on another platform and like where the
old radio shows were and you're telling
other people about that but that's not
help
being much for them because they're not
going to possibly hear the whole podcast
it's just
this is where i can guarantee that's
happening and if you got an android like
i said go to medicalmedium.com
upload link you know you'll you'll yep
the browser you look at the browser you
see podcast and you figure it out
um okay people are asking how long the
meditation is cara
it's a short one it's a short one so
um but powerful you can repeat it
twice a day i recommend twice a day
and that's what i recommend to my family
and friends that have gone through shock
or trauma
and they've gone through hardships ups
and downs even if it's just
a relationship breakup you've had five
years ago
or seven years ago or something else
happened in your life like a loved one
passed away or anything i recommend the
brain meditation
twice a day it's a short one you can do
in the morning you do it at night you
can do it other other places too um
repeat it for sure link is pinned in the
link
for the podcast is pinned in the
comments
and the description
god bless you guys too um
i'm really really okay rosanna
so it's hard for me to meditate mind
wanders all over the place
yes it's meditations out there are hard
they're man-made
and man-made meditations are different
than this this is not a man-made
meditation
this is a meditation that's easy to do
but more powerful
than man-made meditations this
meditation comes from above
since i was child i was taught this
meditation from from
spirit of compassion and it's easy
to do but mind-blowing
and mind-healing it's a chiller
i say that because it is it's a chiller
really important to know
connie says i didn't see the chemtrail
will it be on again
you can listen to the chemtrail episode
at apple podcast
it's a medical medium podcast at apple
podcast so medical medium podcast
at apple podcast look for the link uh
it's in it's pinned so look for the link
it's pinned and you'll hear the chemical
episode
i ask you guys share these episodes with
everybody you can
please share them with everybody you can
um whoever you think can listen just
share to as many people
tell them to share it if you share it
with someone tell them to share it
that and and just you know so
have you know share it with someone else
tell them to please share it because
what it does is it helps
everybody it makes a difference um
that's what i'm all about it's about
getting people the information and i ask
you guys if you can do that
i'm all about free information free free
free free free free
and if you can share it that's my wish
danielle good question will the
meditation heal in layers
the more that we do yes the first time
you do it
powerful you keep on doing it powerful
you keep on doing it powerful and more
powerful
and it literally becomes a part of your
soul
to get rid of the fear and it becomes
this anchor so that your soul
stays with your physical brain and body
because when we get hurt
when someone cheats on us boom our soul
just gets knocked out of us for a moment
we're out of body
when we lose a loved one boom our soul
gets knocked out of us for a little
while we're out of body
when we get hurt by someone boom
when we have a divorce boom when we have
a uh
some kind of confrontation boom our soul
goes out of body and it kind of hovers
around us a little bit
and we start getting disconnected and
and
when you do the meditation you're
bringing your soul closer
to your to your neurons you're
connecting the physical part of your
body with your soul everybody has a soul
that's that's what that's what we are
we're a soul inside a physical body
and so it's connecting it and healing it
it's ridding fear to bring the soul back
this isn't out there anywhere it doesn't
exist out there and finally i'm like
look i get it there's man-made
meditations out there people are trying
to do stuff out there
but it's time it's time i bring this
anchor in so people get grounded and get
that fear out
and heal the soul it's time i was really
excited about this
okay julia wells says jump just jumped
on where do i find the brain meditation
okay medical medium podcast at apple
podcast okay
so subscribe to apple pipe medical
medium podcast at apple podcast
and subscribe so you get notified when
that medical medium podcast comes
through
um download the app the apple the apple
uh podcast app
or if you have an android and you don't
have an apple device if you got an
android or something like that or
another type of device
then go to medicalmedium.com and you'll
see the link
and you'll see the link here in the
description too
and the medical media podcast is
uncensored at apple podcast so if you
if you listen to it at other platforms i
can't guarantee that it'll
most likely be censored i'm hearing that
now
platforms that people have listened to
my old radio shows on they're they're on
these new episodes just because they
might be on these other platforms
they're censored and so apple podcast is
the official
launch pad you're looking for it sally
says you're looking forward to listening
thank you i'm can't wait for you to
listen i can't wait
um hi naturally i don't meditate
hopefully this will get me into it
um once you do this meditation you're
not going to want to do any other ones
out there
because when you go back to the other
ones even though you haven't
you know you're saying you don't do them
this is just for people who
do meditations you're going to be like
okay wait a minute i see the difference
i see that this is a whole different
thing because my family i have friends
they meditate they try different
meditations out there for years
and when they do the brain meditation
this one
they're like i don't even know how i'm
gonna go back because
yes everything changed are you just
subscribed carmen
thank you thank you awesome you're
awesome
um so maria said god we need we needed
this so much
oh bless your heart bless your heart
truly truly
you know and um yeah just you guys are
incredible
and i can't wait i can't wait um
so christina says please make an angels
meditation in the future in your podcast
absolutely christina i will i promise i
will um because i have the angels in the
medical medium books
talk about angels of the medical mean
books i will i will
yep for sure very important very
important
yeah and i'm proud of you guys so just
remember on other platforms um
when you if if you're listening to the
podcast the medical main podcast and
other platforms
they're censored most likely the
censored pieces are missing
it looks like it's the same thing sounds
like the same thing it's not
and you miss all kinds of stuff or it
doesn't upload right i'm hearing that
i'm getting
direct messages about that people are
contacting me
and and i keep on saying there's a
reason why i keep on saying apple
podcast
sun sensor that's the official platform
for this i don't know how many times i
could say it it's funny
i naturally says click on all episodes
to see any episodes you might have
missed
yes
right yep exactly so a little lemon balm
tea here
so see you guys so i'm just preparing
you
tomorrow morning this brain meditation
is unlike anything anybody's experienced
i am
very excited about this and i have to
tell you that
um i would i like my recommendation
repeat it
once twice a day it could be once a day
do it seven days a week
once a day seven days a week really
powerful
changes happen to compiles on itself you
get more fear out you get more fear out
you get your soul gets more connected to
neurons in your brain your physical part
of the brain
and tricia says i even private message
some
of my friends to tell people about it
trisha thank you
thank you thank you please share these
episodes around
share them around for other people tell
them to share it tell them to share it
you subscribed ever since you
subscribed amazing loving the podcast
carrie said saving your life they're
really
really special they are um
marilyn says not everybody has apple
that's fine what you do is you go to
medicalmedium.com
and you check the browser there you find
podcasts
in the browser and you just upload
upload the links
download the links to the to the
episodes on any
any device that's what you do so that's
what i would do so you know it's the
uncensored version so you know it's a
virgin that's off
that the medical medium website medical
mean calm okay
you click on the apple link right there
and
you can listen on the browser
michelle says great thanks michelle
you're awesome
so narelle says just subscribed it's
simple to do
the links are written in this live post
hey
thank you for telling everybody
thank you greta says we need you thank
you oh
bless your heart i'm so proud of all you
guys jen says can't wait i really need
this
jen um this brain meditation
every day do it once a day i like it
twice a day morning and night i'd
recommend it to friends and family that
have
things have happened in their life that
have stayed with them
and post-traumatic stress syndrome and
everything and i've recommended this
meditation twice a day because it's
short
short and powerful and not hard to
do you find a quiet spot you kick
back you lay down and you close your
eyes
and you listen and you do it twice a day
and it really
really helps connect
that divide that occurs from when we get
hurt that divide and then fear here's
what happens
as a soul as we get hurt through life we
get that we get betrayed
our soul leaves our body a little bit
and then what fills in in between is
fear so fear fills in the gap
so the soul starts leaving a little fear
fills in the gap
fear fills in the gap soul starts
leaving more and more fear fills the gap
and now we're fearful when we don't even
think we're supposed to or not and we
have it in the way even if we're not
feeling it in the moment it's there
and this brings the soul back rids fear
brings the soul back more rid sphere
brings the soul back ritz fear
and brings it back and then you do it
every day
um subscribe to be the first subscribe
to apple podcast the medical medium
podcast on apple podcast so you just
you're the first to get notified
erica said i did tell 100 people thank
you
thank you thank you did you tell 100
people to tell another another bunch of
people
i'm sure you did thank you oh my god
margie
what time is the brain meditation
tomorrow it's going to be
early in the morning depending on where
you are around the world but subscribe
though
to medical meeting podcast at apple
podcast so subscribe so you get the
notification
so so you you know but yeah oh my god a
hundred people you told a hundred people
it was the comment before i'm just blown
away blown away
samantha okay so i subscribed and i
can't find the brain meditation it's not
out yet it's out tomorrow morning but
you'll
you'll get the chemtrails meditation
that's not a meditation the chemtrails
yeah you're going to need the brain
meditation after hearing the chemtrails
episode okay because the
controls episode is not for the faint of
heart
it's not so um yeah i mean share the
chemtrail episode for sure with other
people that you think
should hear it i mean share it but it's
really a mind
blower and then the fruit fear episode
you can listen to
but yeah the brain meditation is
tomorrow morning and i can't wait for
you guys to do that
um pressing prince can't wait till
tomorrow i share all your info to anyone
that will listen
incredible thank you pressing prince
have bought a few cleansed heel books
for gifts too yay there's kinds of heel
right behind me there it is glenn's a
and all your info is amazing um
that book was really
that book's a medical textbook it's you
know how heavy it is then because you
bought a bunch of them
and oh my god it's so packed it's so
packed
okay so dave ash says i only see first
two episodes on podcast is the
meditation up now no tomorrow morning so
make sure you subscribe
to apple podcast okay to medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast so you get
notified first thing when it's out
tomorrow morning but tomorrow morning
it's out
melissa says melissa box says subscribed
yay cj and heavy metal detox smoothie
heavy metal smoothie saved my health
awesome melissa awesome so glad i'm so
happy i'm
so proud of you uh
maynard says this man help helped me
save my life
save myself and i've helped others i
couldn't be more thankful
i wouldn't be here bless your heart i'm
proud of you i know you worked hard at
it because
you you you did the information that's
in the book the cleanse of heal book and
you looked at all the information in
there you're learning you're learning
and you're learning how to heal
heidi says listen to the podcast while
drinking my celery juice this morning
so you did you listened to the fruit
fear episode um
did you listen to the chemtrail episode
um you're so
jackie you're so completely ready for
this the brain meditation
do it once a day try to do it twice a
day i recommend the family and friends
that have had hardships and struggles
and fear and worry and concern
and they've had breakups and divorces
and relationship issues or
just different emotional challenges and
what happens is your soul just slowly
leaves the body a little bit
so slowly leaves the body and fear fills
in the center and fills in the center
and it just starts to divide and
this brain meditation it brings the soul
back
makes the connection nothing i've ever
seen out there does that
i'm going to be releasing more
meditations medical on the medical
medium podcast
that are powerful all on their own for
different healing for different problems
and things
but this one here wait to you try this
jennifer says i have been so hurt with
infertility
this is a need need for sure right now
and for sure timing for the right timing
jennifer
you know um
this is really gonna help this is really
gonna help do this
every day and that's what i would do i
would do that i would do it every day
i would uh mim gardner you subscribed
yay incredible michelle
it opens in chrome okay
cool um
yeah so yep chrome browser
thank you michelle glenda says we need
you i need this so much
glenda this meditation
is really gonna be that anchor that's
what it has done for my family over the
years the decades
friends that i've shared it with and
it's like well you know what
now is the time to release the brain
meditation it's now it has to happen
it just has to happen i had to make this
happen it didn't
matter how much all of that i had to put
into everything to make this happen
it has to happen
so there's a newsletter if you sign up
to the newsletter
the medicalmedium.com and you sign up
for the medical media newsletter
you can get notified there too when when
each episode's released if you have an
android or something
thank you for giving darlene says thank
you for giving the heads up
amazing so michelle says
i don't see it on your apple podcast
site only chemtrails and fruit fear
tomorrow morning you're going to see the
brain meditation
first thing in the morning first thing
in the morning
oh you left you something
that's funny um
so yeah so i'm really excited about this
by the way you guys
really excited just letting you know and
did everybody listen to the chemtrail
episode um get ready for that one if you
haven't
listened to it twice i've listened to it
more than twice
because even though i did the episode
obviously
there's that much information i'm like
oh my god and i just you know it's it's
all that
please please leave a review on apple
podcast
it helps because it helps other people
find their way to be like okay
because yeah it's a lot of trolls that
like to leave
terrible reviews in a crafty way by the
way and so it's always good to
if you guys can put a put a review
if you like the podcast and stuff so
that people can find their way
and because i hear a voice perfectly
clear like you guys know my history
since i was a child spirit of compassion
i'm more susceptible to trolls than
anybody else
because they just don't like you having
that that ability
that gift you listen twice erica says
yes i listened two times
incredible marlowe says the chemtrail
was amazing
so it was that that that was amazing
right that episode the truth is being
revealed
yeah it's just mind-blowing that episode
um can young children listen to the
brain meditation yes narelle
they can i have family and friends
that do the meditation their children do
the meditation absolutely
absolutely um
kathy you left a review thank you god
bless you bless your heart
truly elizabeth says the first two
episodes are great
they're powerful they're powerful um
they really are kareem says drown out
the trolls
yeah if you leave reviews it helps
because the trolls just love to pick on
aw
yeah those trolls kathy says those
trolls are very active they are
they are you have lots of trolls
danielle says lots of trolls today
absolutely and
yeah the trolls don't like this truth
getting out there you have to remember
and trolls work for somebody so they
work for somebody you have to remember
that's how trolls do they work for
somebody
and um and they work for somebody to try
to stop truth from getting out there
chemtrails the
chemtrail episode is mind-blowing um
maria says do you have a book on
meditation medical meaning book one has
meditations in there
some other medical media books have
meditations in there um
liver rescue medical media book one and
live rescue have powerful meditations in
there but i'm going to do these
meditations on the podcast
bethany says listen to each episode
three times bethany
thank you because i know you're
listening to all the details
still mind-blowing right that's what
you're saying left a five-star review
today
thank you i hope other people do on
apple podcast they leave a five star
review
was it still it's still mind-blowing
right you're listening to listen to it
that many times
i have to listen to it again
uh audi says my husband now believes in
you yay
incredible listen i don't blame him for
being
a skeptic at all towards anything about
me so
always tell him tell them i don't blame
him at all i'm a skeptic
i was born a skeptic but had to have
this gift because
the gift is for you guys but had to have
this ability that spirit of compassion
has given me my whole life
that's why the medical books are written
where is it there it is the medical book
is written
these medical textbooks because it's all
information from above
um it's not information that's ever out
there it's packed with information for
people to heal millions are healing
around the world
and i would be a skeptic too so tell him
i understand but
i'm so glad he believes in me believes
in
in in the information um
i'm going to cover symptoms and
conditions in these podcasts so all the
different symptoms and conditions
autoimmune everything brain fog multi
sclerosis all that stuff
erica you're listening to chemtrails now
yay
yay share it with somebody too how do i
sign up to your newsletter go to
medicalmedium.com
and you'll find out you'll find the spot
to sign up and you can sign up to the
newsletter
you'll see a banner that she can sign up
you'll see a banner so you can
sign up looking at the monitor right now
you guys that's the answer your
questions
um diana says can't wait till tomorrow
morning
healing every day i'm so glad you're
healing every day and you're working on
the medical medium information to heal
and i am so excited about tomorrow
morning for you
yvette says indigo ruby and great
blue oh my god that's medical medium
book one
and that's the dedication indigo ruby
and great blue
that that's amazing that you have that
there
um jody says need this i feel so
disconnected since losing my husband
can't seem to find my joy our purpose
hope this helps
this meditation is for that it's it's
because
when we have great losses i'm so first
of all i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry for your great loss so
sorry for
this there's no words for that and um
but but that's what happens we go
through life and we have these things
like this happen and this brain
meditation
is to help bring your soul back to your
physical brain to the neurons because
we get it fills the the gap the fear
fills in the gap
and our soul just gets knocked out of us
from these
from these things that happen in our
life from these great losses
and that's why the meditation's there um
siri said where can we access the
podcast
okay um medical media podcast is on
apple podcast
okay so it's that apple podcast go there
subscribe
to the medical meeting podcast podcast
so you get notified first thing and get
that brain
brain meditation first thing in the
morning if you don't have an apple
device fine
use your android and then what you do go
to medicalmedium.com
find the podcast in the browser and just
upload the link
or download the link and you can listen
um victoria says thank you anthony
wow i saw my doctor today and we went
over my six month
labs i'm 64 years old been doing celery
juice
every am morning for seven months plus
healthy eating
and two three six nine cleanses no more
high cholesterol at all
no more high sugar blood pressure normal
now no meds
lost 30 pounds oh my god victoria
nothing bad on labs except the little
anemia which i never have
um she she thinks it's b12
so uh i'll up my vemma gb12 so thank you
anthony and
spirit of compassion so proud of you so
much healing is getting done
what happens is you cleansed a lot you
have to remember victoria that you were
doing
so much cleansing and you're cleansing a
lot of poison so 30 pounds
of weight all that poison and toxin left
and left so you know so yeah that's
that's incredible
sherry says i don't have apple okay
that's okay if you have an android or
something else go to medicalmedia.com
sherry and go to medicalmedium.com
and you can and you'll see podcasts in
the browser
the menu the menu podcast you'll see the
menu
right podcast and then you go in there
and you can download the link you can
listen right there
right there through your link through
the link on your android or anything
else you got
so yeah incredible um cindy two months
into healing feeling hopeful
incredible incredible
well you guys i'm very excited
i can't wait for tomorrow morning
catherine says love the episodes
share them please share them okay if you
can um
you know if you can share them
incredible when you do a soul podcast
lisa this brain meditation is to heal
the soul to
fear out of the soul and away from the
soul it's it's just
a whole other level so um share
the podcast share the episodes please
so other people can heal they're not
sponsored there's no advertisements no
infomercials uh um
it's it's it's a free resource and apple
podcast is the
is the is the platform the official
platform for it
apple podcast so it's not censored the
whole bit
it's just so you know uh moon goddess
will this meditation help while you're
going through an illness
autoimmune lime yes and i'm gonna do
episodes on autoimmune so i'm gonna do
an autoimmune episode fairly soon
um and lime episode and the whole bit
all that that's going to happen too but
yes this meditation
is a great great support and anchor if
you're going because when we go through
hardships with
chronic illness like lyme and we go
through hardships with with our symptoms
and conditions
in neurological symptoms that also puts
fear in us
this rids fear out of the soul this is
critical if you got
symptoms and conditions you're battling
lyme or anything like that
chris woods said my brain fog
drastically improved with the heavy
metal detox yes
and i'm doing a brain fog episode by the
way you might want to hear
i discipline and trust detox symptoms
are rough sometimes but it's healing
that's what you're doing you're healing
your brain fog is drastically improved
incredible
tatiana looking forward to hear about
plasma though but i'm very excited for
the brain meditation
um uh you're gonna love the brain
meditation
really are um incredible so you guys
incredible and how do you watch
if no apple podcast so natalie's that's
the question there
so if you can't do apple podcast because
you don't have an apple device or
anything
okay look for the menu on
mymedicalmedium.com medicalmedium.com
look for the menu
uh podcast right there you'll see it and
you can you can upload link download the
link
listen to it right on the browser right
there
you can listen right there through the
link
so incredible
tomorrow morning the episode it's going
gonna be a lot it's gonna go live
tomorrow morning the episode
so get ready just letting you guys know
very excited very excited
oh denise says great to hear you live
i'm live right now
celery juice for 12 months incredible
so you guys share the episodes if you
can please
um when a so carolyn says when are you
doing the one on breast implants
i'm going to make sure it happens that's
really important
breast implant illness um i've always
been
uh just somebody who's always put
tremendous amounts of information about
that throughout the years and i want to
make sure that
that by far the episode you're going to
hear about that is the most informative
most informative there can be out there
at all
that's the medical medium information is
always advanced and that's what's going
to happen there
you just signed up angus mcdonald
amazing
jen says she's so excited i'm really
excited i can't wait
um ciro says thank you aw i love your
meditations
it helps me a lot so looking forward to
the brain meditation so you obviously
then do the meditations in the books
um i can't wait for you to try
this and hear this episode i can't wait
i can't wait i just it's just i'm so
excited
so i'm going to do a dental one too a
dental uh
podcast episode medical media podcast a
dental episode
gonna do a depression one now andre's
how about
depression well with the brain
meditation
that's what it's for depression anxiety
it's for
all these things now you'll see it in
behind me you'll see the medical medium
cleanse the heal book
incredible resource for physically
healing depression
too so really important this is the soul
version of depression when our soul
just gets so tattered from experiences
and we get depression on that end when
it's depression from
experiences we we go through in life
so excited okay you guys um
bless your heart i'm i'm really excited
i will
i will listen out for you guys through
comments and everything else
and uh please share the episodes please
share the brain meditation and please
tell them go to apple podcast
if they can if they have a device to go
there and show me the other way too
um and share the episodes
let everybody know but the brain
meditation like i said i recommend
twice a day once a day every single day
katie says thank you aw been following
you for two years
can't wait for the dental one okay you
got it i'm gonna make sure that happens
i am i am
bethany says could you please do an
episode on spinal conditions
especially spondylo uh spondylosis that
one and scoliosis yeah thank you for
sure
gonna definitely do that
anyway you guys love you much
tomorrow's the day and
bless your heart god bless you take care