just want to announce the brain fog
episode has been released
it's called brain fog knock knock who's
there episode 9
all right medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
if you're somebody with brain fog you
might be somebody that doesn't know they
have brain fog
and you're kind of like kind of like in
a daze or you get confused easy or when
you're conversating with someone else
you kind of forget what you're saying
or maybe you forget what they said hi
everybody and
you know brain fog is a little bit more
difficult on a lot of people than
anybody knows
and it comes with all kinds of other
conditions
if you have a skin condition acne i've
known a lot of people over the years
with acne and some brain fog
and they're feeling kind of tired groggy
they wake up in the morning
they feel like they can't shake the
brain fog they feel like they're not on
their game
or they're wasting their energy and time
so episode nine
brain fog knock knock who's there on the
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
you don't want to miss this episode this
episode is an
eye opener it's just so you know and
it's critical to help somebody heal
there's an elixir
i share for brain fog that i haven't
shared before so there's
a brain fog elixir that i share
on this episode that's really important
to help
like ease that brain fog for people so
they can push ahead
i know a lot of you guys want to be on
your game you guys want to have clarity
you want to be together you want to be
on
i know a lot of people feel like they
lose a day because of their brain fog
even if they don't know that's what it's
called or that's what it is
they just feel kind of out at it
they feel kind of dizzy they feel kind
of spacey they feel kind of confused
they get confused easy
you know tasks are not easy to do and
all of that and if you have something
like thyroid conditions or you got
eczema psoriasis
or something like some fibro or you're
not feeling good and you just don't feel
well and you have intestinal tract
disturbances digestive problems i know
people who have just
a whole myriad of different problems and
conditions and they have the brain fog
with it so you have to check this
episode out you guys
i'm gonna answer some questions too if
you have questions about brain fog
too i'm here um so and then there's
triggers to brain fog so then there's
gluten
that's a major trigger for brain fog but
it's not the true
cause of brain fog that's why someone
else can do all the gluten they want
they can do all the gluten they want all
the weak gluten they want and they don't
have brain fog but somebody else
yeah the gluten will actually trigger
their brain fog there's a reason for
that
and in this episode at medical medium
podcast at apple podcast i talk about
that
you might want to catch this episode
it's free um the link is in the
description
just so you can find it and i want to
answer some questions too
cheryl says this show was so validating
to me so that means you've dealt with
brain fog
pamela says hello from london uk hello
how are you
maria says that's me every day so did
you hear the episode
i talk about all the different mild to
severe
symptoms of brain fog whether like when
you're trying to communicate with
somebody and you kind of
forget what they just told you but you
don't want to say anything about
it but you all of that pia says hey pia
you're here today
thank you anthony i've been brain fog
and i'm so tired of this feeling oh my
god so you're dealing with that brain
fog i'm so sorry you had to deal with
that throughout your life
then you're dealing with it now chanel
says i've had brain fog
since having coveted yes covet's like a
trigger you know and that's the whole
thing too i'm talking about that and
i'm going to talk about that another
time about all that too but the brain
fog
is brain fog's really difficult for so
many people
and they struggle with it so badly and
i'm so sorry you guys are doing that and
dealing with it
steph says love your meditations have
you guys tried to freeze the bird
meditation
really powerful the moon meditation the
brain meditation
so medical medium podcast at apple
podcast that's the uncensored platform
official platform it's on so if you
listen to it at other platforms you're
not going to hear the whole thing
pieces are going to be missing it's just
going to be problems it has to be at
apple podcast please share
and share the meditation share the
episode the brain fog episode with
others
so let's talk about brain fog for a
minute since you guys are dealing with
it so many of you guys are struggling
with the brain fog
and um bonnie says knock knock it's me
so you listened you listened to it and
the brain fog episode knock knock who's
there is a powerful episode
to give people answers so share it with
others too you guys
you guys are all about answers you know
what i've always known about you guys
like the medical medium community is
you guys have been there done that you
guys are seasoned and you know the
difference between
answers and no answers and you guys have
been around the block
and and you guys don't mess around
either you guys don't mess around you
guys
you do stuff you do your celery juice
you take care of yourself and i'm so
proud of you and i
i always have you in mind and with this
podcast here it's like
it's like yeah there's a tremendous
amount of work that goes involved in
this podcast the launch of this podcast
making sure you guys have these
episodes but knowing that the
information is there for you guys to
help you heal
it's just all that matters it's just a
matter it's a free resource
too there's no commercials no
infomercials no advertisements in it
it's just a free resource that that
isn't like annoying
so i want you guys to check it out brain
fog knock knock who's there
medical media podcast at apple podcast
the link is in the description
check it out i'm going to answer
questions about brain fog too sarah
sarah dillon my brain fog went away
after the 369 original cleanse what a
lifesaver
big hugs 369 cleanses in cleanse to heal
you guys right there
and you can you can get that book at
amazon for 16.99 in the us
right now it's unbelievable 51 off it's
a medical textbook
it's get you know like that really is
helpful for brain fog
i'm glad that the 369 really helped you
out
you get it free at the library too um so
great that you guys are here
janelle says can one really get rid of
brain fog yes
one can get rid of brain fog absolutely
because when you know what's
causing it like in the episode check it
out the the brain fog episode
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
brain fog knock knock who's there when
you learn
what the causes of brain fog yeah
you can get rid of it definitely you can
get rid of it
that's the whole point mega medium
healing tools are about getting rid of
things not
keeping things getting rid of things um
i talk about the different variations of
brain fog so that's something that's
really important you guys and what kind
of brain fog do you have
do you have the kind where you wake up
in the morning and you're foggy headed
you're dizzy you're not feeling that
great you're not all there
you like you need hours to kind of shake
out of it and to kind of reboot and get
out of it
are you like a person dealing with that
way or is your brain fog
the kind of brain fog that comes in goes
it's a little bit for a couple of hours
and then it's gone then it's a little
bit for a couple hours and then it's
gone
is that your kind of brain fog or are
you dealing with the kind of brain fog
where it's
only in the morning but it's not at
night you seem to come
alive at night okay like all of a sudden
you're bouncing back and coming alive
laura carter carter yep is brain fog the
same as not
having a good memory i forgot so much
even as a child it is the same and see
brain fog the term brain fog
is an encompass of like memory
um forgetfulness um you know a
compilation of all that combined
anything from depersonalization feeling
focus and concentration
feeling like you're dazed feeling like
you know
a lot of times people get blamed for
procrastinating when they have brain fog
if you just got on here i'm talking
about episode nine brain fog
knock knock who's there medical medium
podcast at apple podcast it's free link
is in the description
so you gotta check it out it's a free
resource it's the ninth episode of the
medical medium podcast
powerful information and then you got
the other episodes too you got the
chemtrails fruit fear
got the egg episode you can't miss that
one the caffeine
episode okay coffee matcha tea chocolate
episode that's a big deal you got the
moon meditation the brain meditation you
got the freezer bird meditation the link
is in the description i want to answer
questions
glad you guys are on here and
so if you don't have an apple device go
to medicalmedium.com
go to the menu you'll see podcasts in
the menu and you can
download it the the apple podcast is is
is the place that medical media podcast
is launched
because if these are uncensored versions
it's not like the old radio show and the
other platforms this is medical medium
uncensored some of it's just really
intense but i'm glad you guys are
enjoying it
tammy lee you just named all of the
things i have
i need to listen thank you so much for
doing this live tammy thank you for
being here
and i want to ask you this um you know
is
is do you ever think that your brain fog
could
ever go away or do you think you're
stuck with it for life because i want
you to know
there is a way to heal i always tell
everybody you can heal
you can heal when you know what's going
on
and you know why we're dealing with
something there is a way to heal and i
always always want you guys to
know that i want you to know it i want
everybody to know that it's so important
um kristin ward says i have acne with
brain fog
exactly that's what happens and what
happens too is we forget it's brain fog
or we don't really know it's brain fog
and when we have these other symptoms
brain fog's with it are encompassing
with it and people don't know it's like
yeah
brain fog my god so yeah and
the whole thing with acne and brain fog
you can have that you can have eczema
in brain fog you can have these other
things but it's really important sophia
says
major brain fog after covet and
trembling lips
yeah and and i'm working on writing
something about
that and everything about covert and all
this other stuff i'm working on putting
things together
so people have more information but just
so you know that
it's really hard when when we're dealing
with brain fog with any condition we get
so
anything that we get or anything that
happens to us then the brain fog just
kicks
up it just kicks up so it's important to
know that there are
answers out there for brain fog check
out the podcast if you can
medical medium podcast you guys packed
with information line for line to help
you heal
check out the brain fog episode knock
knock who's there so you have a chance
to heal
get your life back on track that's what
it's about
um anne marie says i have brain fog and
it's causing anxiety
that's really difficult just for just so
you know anybody and ann marie i'm so
sorry you're dealing with that
in living like that it breaks my heart
because it's like
it's just it's unfair you know it's
unfair that we have to
deal with this but there is a way to
heal
joy mccoy says the free as a bird was
awesome
incredible so it speaks to you that's
that's amazing i'm so
happy it does so link is in the
description for the medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast the brain fog
episode knock knock who's there
and the meditations the brain meditation
the moon meditation
the free is a bird meditation so
important all of these um
so mara ella she was saying something i
have terrible brain fog
oh my god that's awful it's such a
struggle through
uni i have hypothyroidism and i think
it's getting worse i would do anything
to get help
as the gluten-free diet didn't help i've
talked about that
i actually talked about it in the brain
fog episode too
about how there's all these guessing
games going on you're on a plant-based
diet for 12 years i still believe
it's my thyroid first of all i support
plant-based diets
i support also animal-based diets but i
support plant-based diets but what i've
always told everybody is
in order to heal because people on
plant-based diets and animal-based diets
both get sick
and in order to heal we need to know
what's causing it
what's causing the brain fog what is it
and in the episode you'll hear me go
oh look over there look over there
there's a new guessing game over there
you'll hear it in the episode and what i
was saying was
there's a lot of guessing games but
unless you know what's causing your
brain fog
we're just guessing and that's what
we're doing in fact i said something
else more than that
about it um pearl said listen to your
podcast
on brain fog today and you describe this
condition so
well pearl are you gonna listen to all
my episodes so you can spread the
information out there
share the information out there um you
know and
and and talk about the information out
there so others can heal
and i'm in and my job is to actually
know what's going on with people and
their symptoms i was known since i was
age four years old
as the person that people with bizarre
symptoms came to
because i understood them because of the
because of the gift with spirit of
compassion so
that's what i've always been known my
whole life that's why millions have
healed with
with the medical medium information and
i want you to know that i do
understand symptoms i do understand
that's why
that's why it comes out like that that's
why medical medium information and the
podcast is there for you so you can hear
these explanations and you can hear
these differences of what's going on
it's so important for your healing it
really is
so um paula says this pandemic has
turned me into someone i don't know
my energy and drive is totally drained
i'm overthinking and stressing and
extreme anxiety and worry since
quarantine paul
have you tried the brain meditation or
have you tried the moon meditation
the free is a bird meditation the
freezer bird meditation would be a great
one to try for that
um kate says yes brain fog is just
terrible
it really is it really is um
so barbara says i love the free as a
bird
um you should do it every single day so
you can heal
share the information for others so they
can heal anna says which meditation is
good for mental blocks for men
brain meditation right there brain
meditation
so have them do the brain meditation
definitely for sure valerie said thank
you aw love your podcast and lives thank
you for being here on this live
means the world to me that you guys are
here right now um
and i really appreciate you guys being
here really am michelle lots of hearts
there hearts back to you too
and i'm really proud of you guys you're
working so hard on your healing process
so with brain fog
what happens is you can be like fogged
out all morning you can be fogged out in
and out of the day
you can be fogged out at night or what
usually happens with brain fog
you're fogged all day long all
day long and then at the end of the day
at night
you're like coming back to life and
you're just springing back to life for a
little bit and you get clarity and you
get clarity and then you're up
later at night with that clarity and
then you go to bed and you wake up the
next morning and you're fogged out again
that's one version right there
another version is like when you're
talking to other people you kind of like
with the words that are coming
the words that are in your head don't
come out the right way they come out
kind of wrong
or they come out disjointed disc but
combolated they just come out all kind
of strange and it happens to so many
people and i've seen people struggle
like that or
it's hard to listen to what the person's
telling you because you're thinking
about what you're thinking
and then you're kind of not listening to
what they're saying but you miss it and
that happens to so many people the brain
fog is even hard on people they get
drained by being around other people so
if you're around maybe
people that you're not really that
comfortable with or people that you're
just
you're not in the mood to be around with
family and friends or something and all
of a sudden the brain fog worsens and
you feel drained
you know there's so many different
versions of brain fog and it makes it so
difficult
uh kenzie says wow didn't realize my
problem had a name
hello from uh brisbane brisbane
australia
um yeah that's what it you know that's
what it has it has a name
rosanna said thank you so much for the
bird meditation i have not slept so well
for a while rosanna i'm so glad you're
doing the freezer bird meditation at
medical medium
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
you guys check it out sharon says thank
you for making me laugh in the beginning
of this episode for brain fog
helps me keep a light heart yeah i mean
it makes me laugh too you know because i
listen to the episodes as well
alina says the end of the podcast made
me cry and made me feel so good
give me real hope i know i can heal
thank you anthony those are special
special messages at the end of the
podcast at the end of the episodes the
brain fog episode
and the other episodes too at the end of
the episode there's a message
from spirit of compassion to to help you
move forward and heal
and to heal your heart and soul those
messages are
special um allah says thank you
for your amazing incredible podcast i'm
so glad you're listening to them brain
fog is severe
whoa they got the severe brain fog hard
to work
thankfully celery juice and the heavy
metal detox smoothie are amazing and
very healing getting so much better
all uh i talk about that in the brain
fog episode
so i talk about that about the celery
juice and heavy metal detox
in in the brain fog episode so i'm so
happy you're doing it
so proud of you incredible serene
you're a true godsend literally no one
else has any solutions for brain fog
i'm so glad that you listened to the
podcast so it's
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
the brain brain fog episode is episode
nine knock knock who's there
uh lynette we ordered the omega juicer
the other day
can't wait to get it my husband is
always skeptical and is now
a daily celery juice drinker
incredible yeah the omega juicer it's
the mm-900 hds
just so just that's the one that really
juices the way it needs to juice
jennifer fry it felt too validating to
hear you understand all the many
different types of brain fog
i have felt it's so hard to describe the
p
to people and you're right that they
don't understand
you know one thing about brain fog is
when someone doesn't have brain fog and
they never experience it they're going
to do this you're going to be like what
are you tired
um what do you have what are you do
would you
are you did you get drunk last night do
you have a hangover
i don't understand did you stay up late
and party did you
you know why do you have brain fog are
you working too hard you just need to
rest
you just need to take a day off and that
will get rid of your brain fog it's like
people don't realize when you have bad
brain fog it's a whole nother story
luna l hey loon hello i'll listen to the
brain fog episode tonight thank you i'm
so glad are you catching up to the
episodes
um thank you for releasing these
episodes at this at the speed i'm
soaking up all the information thank you
so much for what you do
loon thank you so much for what you do
too because i know you're out there
and you're batting for you're batting
for a spirit of compassion soc
and you're out there you know fighting
for this information that comes from
above you're
you're helping people with it you're
telling them about it you're telling
them
about the podcast just know that it's
appreciated more
than you can possibly imagine okay
please know that
it's very very me it means more to me
than you know
because i know that you care you're
helping others you're sharing the
information
and plus you're seasoned what i've
noticed about you loon
is that you're actually really seasoned
you you've been around the block with
alternative medicine you've been around
the block with conventional medicine
you're you're actually
you know what's going on out there um so
the link is in the description it's the
uncensored versions at medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast
at apple podcast that's the official
platform
that i launched the podcast at so if you
hear it at other platforms
the episodes they're not they're they're
censored they're sense you have to you
have to see it at apple or listen to it
there
nikki says i am so tired and sleep and
depressed and brain fog too you know it
just breaks my heart that you guys are
all dealing with brain fog
um ayanna is social anxiety linked to
brain fog
it's there's definitely a link because
it happens is the anxiety and brain fog
that come together and then social
anxiety and brain fog
that's a whole thing too absolutely i'm
answering questions you guys up here if
you want to
ask some questions and
really the brain fog episode opens the
door to understand it like no other so
you know what's going on with everything
and all of it
loon says brain fog to me feels like i
am being dumbed down
as if i was under heavy drug abuse not
fun and also it's hard to do anything i
get very clumsy and confused
so loon you dealt with the brain fog you
struggled with it
and and that's just it's really hard
hard hard you know
and that's the thing if someone hasn't
had brain fog
and they never struggled with it on any
level and a lot of you guys might not
even know you have brain fog until you
hear the episode and you're like what
like huh i got them i actually have some
brain fog going on what
so and yeah just you when you when you
hear the episode stacy highland
i literally didn't know i had brain fog
until i listened to this
on day six of 369. yeah
stacy c like i know like a lot a lot of
everybo
a lot of people they don't know they got
the brain fog
so incredible i'm so glad you're doing
that you're on day six
lisa said caffeine episode i think she
said so i think the
comment went up there too quick lisa
marie
caffeine episode my husband quit the
next day after i made him listen to the
podcast
lisa what'd you think about the caffeine
episode okay what's my favorite episode
out of all the nine episodes so far the
caffeine episode is definitely one of my
favorite
i don't know i mean the chemtrail
episode is one of my favorites uh
the egg episode's one of my favorites
now i'm like what like
which one's my favorite now i think the
caffeine episode might be one of my
favorites ah they all are they're all my
favorites
i don't know what to say they actually
are christy says wow to the coffee
podcast
it was eye-opening christy wasn't that
mind-blowing
right the coffee podcast coffee munch
tea chocolate podcast
if anybody hasn't listened to it yet
medical meeting podcast said apple
podcast listen to that one
you guys i hate asking you i hate asking
this but leave a review if you feel up
to it please
if you can leave a review at apple
podcast it really
helps it helps it helps share the
message it helps so people can
see it and then hear the information and
heal their brain fog
and heal all the other different
symptoms and conditions i'm going to be
doing podcasts on
michelle miller hey michelle you're
amazing anthony there's real hope for
healing i'm living proof michelle you're
awesome
um proud of you truly truly truly proud
of you
and it's i really am i really am
and so you guys you know one thing about
brain fog is interesting
is that it's not even considered
anything like
medical research and science the
industries don't even think it's
anything
and even alternative medicine has a hard
time with it because when you
you when they when altered medicine they
kind of see it as brain fog are you just
are you really dealing with brain fog or
is it something else it's
we're always underestimated we're always
misunderstood with brain fog
and then we don't even know to call it
brain fog we're just like i don't feel
well or
maybe this is who i am where i'm bumping
into walls and
not even bumping the walls i can't get
anything done i know you guys want to be
like have the clarity
be on your game your intuition being
solid and strong
being like oh like all like all that
feeling like you're all there and
and it's really kind of hard for so many
people you know it really is
aisling hey hazeling uh i had brain fog
for years and now i could finally
understand what was going on
i'm new on my healing journey i've done
original and advanced
369 recently that's those right there
the advanced 369 cleanses in the cleanse
of heel book behind me
um that that's an amazing medical
textbook for people
i'm new on my healing yep 369 recently
drinking heavy metal detox smoothie
uh every day hazeling that's incredible
i have psoriasis joint pain and brain
fog
thanks to your inspiration i'm so proud
of you you need to know that
don't stop taking care of yourself keep
on taking care of yourself please please
please
so important to you guys subscribe so
make sure you subscribe to the medical
meeting podcast
at apple podcast so you get notified
notified when the episodes come out
how cool is that and if you don't have
an apple device
fine go to medicalmedium.com go to the
menu you'll see podcast on the menu
and you can listen to it there
so um back to brain fog just talk a
little bit about that for a little bit
more because so many of you suffer from
it and struggle from it
when it's really bad when it's really
bad
and you feel like you can't get work
done you feel like you can't get a task
done you feel like you can't get any
jobs done you feel like you can't
the day slips by us so difficult
um xenomar says where do i find the
podcast on brain fog
medical medium podcast apple podcast the
brain fog episode it's episode nine
listen to all the episodes there's
meditations in there that are really
powerful where i guide you through them
to heal
and on top of that there's the episodes
that are really
really powerful episodes and make sure
you subscribe
too and so you get a notification
so important reviews you guys reviews
are important so medical media podcast
at apple podcast if you can leave a
review
if you really want me to keep on doing
this it helps because then it kind of
then i see it too and i'm like
okay someone does like the podcast i'm
just just keep on doing this
i'll stay up all night trying to get
another one done i'll work
all day i want them to have the
information and they actually want the
information
it's amazing you'll continue to share
adele says i will continue to share
i love i love to see my clients heal
adele thank you for sharing
it share this is a grassroots movement
medical medium
information has always been grassroots
because it's about people healing
and then the message being shared okay
and
that's how it's always been all these
years there's no pr marketing
no scam marketing all that stuff that's
happened with
you know all the other businesses in
this industry and all that do all this
stuff
but it's it's which is fine but the
point is
if that's what you want to do some you
know a lot of it's good intentional a
lot of it's just kind of scammy but what
happens in the end that
this has been a grassroots movement
because people heal because it works
it's so important catherine elizabeth
says hi anthony another great episode i
laughed in the beginning
i left in the beginning of the brain fog
episode but cried when you spoke about
the boat
you know i gotta tell you when i spoke
about the boat
at the beginning of the brain fog
episode i was
i i felt it but what happened was when i
re-listened to it
after i recorded that episode when i
listened to it
i actually cried it got me choked
up right right in the middle of it
it really did um so anyway
um if you like the beginning brain fog
episode but cried when you spoke about
the boat the meditations are so powerful
the brain meditation moon meditation
freeze the bird meditation
guys check those out medical media
podcasts and apple podcast share the
podcast
with anyone and everyone that so people
can heal
so people can heal um ivory says can you
please
suggest something that will help severe
neurological brain fog
due to lyme disease infection it's like
being in your own
prison okay so um so iri
um what i would do is listen to the
listen to the episode too the brain fog
episode has lots of information
of why we have brain fog and i talk
about this
so lori i talk about um so what i talk
about lori
is that when you have lyme or you have
ra
or you have fibromyalgia or you have
hashimoto's thyroiditis
or you have any of this stuff lori what
happens is that the brain fog
is part of it all and then when you
listen to the brain fog
episode a medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast when you listen to it
you find out wait a minute wait a minute
so
this has something to do with my lyme
disease like
wait and you all of a sudden you can put
it together when you hear the episode
and you hear what causes brain fog then
you can kind of find out what's causing
your lyme disease
and then you can find out what's causing
other problems and that's that's
you know so lori check that out um
see terry says i have so many friends
that need this so hard i keep plucking
away
with putting the info out thank you for
doing that terry incredible
it really is um deborah says hello
that's me and
that's me is there anything i can do did
you did you check out the podcast brain
fog episode make sure you check it out
um lauren says i have been dealing with
vertigo for the last month i decided to
have some celery juice
today i started listening to you
recently
which book would be would help me the
most recovering this epstein-barr virus
since i
i'm sure that's what's going on with me
different doctors
different diagnoses will that book right
there cleanse the heal you can get it
free at the library
okay you can try that if you don't want
to pay for it try to get it free at the
library
you also can get it in the u.s at
amazon.com
16.99 51 off which is amazing it's a
heavy medical textbook
it's packed with information to heal
people around the world are reversing
their conditions with this right here
this book behind me
paula where can i find the meditations
yeah the meditations
they're my favorite they're one of my
favorites meditations medical meeting
podcast
apple podcast make sure you subscribe
okay
and the link is in the description and
you'll see there's nine
episodes three of them are meditations
how cool is that so can a possible uti
give brain fog
well uti that's urinary tract infection
which is bacterial infection
well which is a pathogen i talk about
the brain fog
episode and i talk about pathogen see
how i'm linking it all together you've
got to hear the episode
the information's there so
um so yeah you guys i'm excited i hope
you check it out
hope i answered a few questions or
helped out a little bit with this
because i know you guys are struggling
with your brain fog
share leave a review if you can at apple
podcast medical media podcast
apple podcast please share um you know
it's so important to help others out
there find the information so they can
heal
so get the chemtrail episode the fruit
fair episode the egg episode
the air fresheners episode you got now
the brain fog episode the caffeine
episode got the three meditations we're
at episode number nine
today uh catherine elizabeth says i cry
at the end of the episodes also
i get choked up at the end of every one
of those episodes i get choked up at the
end
of every one of them lori says i feel
almost in tears listening to you
describe brain fog
it's the first time i've heard anyone
describe in such a compassionate and
honest way of what they're going through
lori um i love the fact that you're
listening
i'm so happy you're hearing about the
information and what people are going
through like you know because you're
going through it you understand
and just know that i understand too that
i do understand
and that's what it's about it's making
sure that that
we know what's going on fern says thanks
for doing this
at facebook live it's a blessing to know
what i'm
that i'm not alone when i'm not alone
fern thank you for being on this
facebook live
i'm honored you're here i hope you are
on the next one
have your notifications on so you guys
can catch me when i'm doing these lives
because i never know when i'm going to
do them
tony says i had brain fog in the past i
had thyroid and anxiety
wow changed my life after reading
thyroid healing so thyroid healing
thyroid healing has healed millions of
people around the world right now
now i can recognize when i start to get
anxiety and readjust and meditate thank
you check out the meditations tony
check out the the check that out um
so the link there's a book for that
there's a link for that book in the
description
anyway i'm so proud of you guys i really
am and i appreciate you guys being here
check me ch you know check out check you
look out for
for any other notifications that come
through have you signed up to my email
list
so the medicalmedium.com sign up to the
email list too so because i also do the
emails i put the emails out once in a
while
to say hey the next episode's coming or
check out this recipe or
so you know so if you can you guys sign
up to the medical medium newsletter go
to medicalmedium.com to get
signed up to the newsletter and so you
guys get like the
articles the free information because
it's all about free information medical
medium
fern says i can't wait to listen to this
episode fern you're awesome
you're awesome thank you you're so great
and and i'm honored you're going to
listen to i
actually can't wait for you to listen to
it uh visibility says i have always
healed my brain fog because you
anthony william and spirit i'm so proud
of you
just truly proud of you really i'm
trisha is here today trish is here too
today
um so glad to say and hi i saw your
comment go up
you know and so anyway guys
i am going to let you guys go just know
that i care
and i stand with you and i know you guys
are struggling with your symptoms and
conditions
brain fog is really brutal check out the
episode you know where to find it
medical meeting podcast
apple podcast that's the uncensored
place for it and
i love you guys take care