we're live right now
so
the price has been reduced
unbelievable 40 off and as i was saying
before when you order the brain books
because there's two of them when you
order them you're only going to get
charged when the book is shipped to you
so you're not going to be charged right
now you're going to get charged when the
book is eventually shipped to you and
you're going to get charged the price
the reduced price and what's awesome
it's already reducing which is
incredible so it's 40 off the books are
26 dollars and 29
it's incredible
and you're gonna get the char you're
gonna be charged at the lowest price
lowest price is what you're gonna charge
when it shipped at the time and that's
what you're going to get george it's
incredible anyway you guys i want to
talk about the brain books for a couple
of minutes because it's so comprehensive
there's so much information
it is unbelievable so that's what i want
to do i'm live right here on tick tock
live on youtube live on facebook live on
you know the whole nine yards live on
rumble so you guys i'm excited live on
telegram i'm really pumped about this so
you guys ordered it you won't be
disappointed you will not be
disappointed your brain will be so happy
when you receive these when you receive
these and the reason why and it's gonna
take a little while right before you get
your copy but the point is the reason
why i'm doing this now too is because if
you don't secure a copy there may not be
a copy for a very long time or for
months and so that's the whole thing you
want to reserve a copy of each one so
each one the brain saver protocols and
brain saver they're two
different books and their companion
books but two different books it's the
first time
the publisher was telling me authors
don't release two books at once they do
not release two books at once publishers
won't let an author release two books at
once that's number one number two is
authors don't have two books in them to
be released at once right but we know
how soc is the information just comes
down and comes down and doesn't stop so
this was gonna be a mega mega size 10 15
pound book so the publisher wanted to
split it
and then
that's what we did we split into two
massive books which is incredible each
book is bigger than cleanse to
bigger than cleanse the heel the medical
textbook okay
so that's important to know right there
so i'm giving you guys a little bit of
details before we talk about what's in
these books which is incredible right
now 40
off amazon.com us
off
both the books are 40 off it's
unbelievable
and
they're hundred dollar books and they're
literally 26.29
the link is in the bio link is in the
description
check it out you want both these books
so
i just want to start with this okay just
a couple little bit of sneak peek into
these books if you guys have a minute
all right
and
these are life-saving books medical
medium books have saved so many lives
throughout the years right since the the
very beginning of the medical first
medical medium book right here okay
middle million books have saved so many
lives this is that next level because
what's happening right now is people are
falling ill everywhere neurological
symptoms brain related symptoms even if
they don't know that if that's what it
is or not okay
and they're falling ill that's where
we're heading so as i keep on saying the
next three the next five years
the amount of sick people and everybody
having a problem is gonna be
unbelievable and i say that all the time
because that's how it's going if you
guys just came on here
these are the brain saver books right
here brain saver protocols and brain
saver now your books aren't going to
look like this these are my manuscripts
right here these are my manuscripts that
i've edited and finished and everything
and given to the publisher that's what
this is you're gonna get when you order
these books
you're gonna get like exactly like one
of the series of you know of the medical
media books it's gonna look like this
there's two of them okay two brain saver
books so you're going to get a book a
medical textbook okay
but it's going to be looking like that
and this
so that's really incredible
i'm excited about this
over 600 pages each
every line packed with information
that's the forefront that's the
forefront research in science is going
to be poaching like crazy and poaching
and taking the information it's going to
be the leading
brain inflammation
brain books brain and nervous system
everything brain books in the world
coming is what these are going to be you
guys are going to be experts before
research and science even crack into
these
so what happens is when you receive your
books you're going to get what the
future is in brain health in your hands
and then you guys become an expert
at brain health it'll be in your hands
and then research and science will poach
it later like they've done with all the
medical books
the medical medium books they poach it
and take pieces of it later but but you
guys will be the experts at this
forefront this this legendary brain
inflammation that's going on just like
multiple sclerosis seven years ago i
published
right
the cause of multiple sclerosis was
epstein-barr virus
now
harvard now seven years later they took
the medical medium information okay
which
they're kind of in trouble for doing but
they took the medical medium information
and then they acted like they discovered
that when it was already published in
new york times bestselling book and
millions of copies around the world
countless doctors using the books so
that was that's a sign right there you
guys how it works with the medical meal
books not a sign but that's that's
something that happened but they've done
that with lots of stuff including long
beep
you know long beak
long beak right that too they took that
and you know long haul beep right
that was medical medium information
published first and they took it and now
science is using that way too they get
their hands on this later on but you'll
have it in your hands you'll become
experts you'll be able to use it and
they'll just take little pieces from it
here and there and they'll just abuse it
you know they'll take a little piece
abuse it put it out there as if they
found something but you have the
ultimate guides right here in your hands
so let's talk about a little bit of
sneak peek about what could even be in
here
let's go into that a little bit okay so
it's two new books released at once
never done before
authors don't release two books at once
it doesn't happen no publisher will back
an author to do it
okay it doesn't get done no no one does
it authors don't have that kind of stuff
in them but here's how it works
with
spirit of compassion it just keeps on
coming so this incredible information
keeps on coming so you know we had to
it's really a great thing
so so let's talk about this right you
got the protocols
you got the brain saver right here and
you got the protocols right here okay
both are critical to have so it's not
just like oh i'll just get one
and that'll be fine you're gonna want
both
over 300 symptoms and conditions
and protocols
all right
300 of them
and that's just the scratches surface 14
cleanses you can customize
a heavy metal detox cleanse that's just
for your situation
there's an advanced heavy metal detox
cleanse
because of the chemicals that
everybody's getting saturated with
that's that's just happened in the last
year there's all this level of chem
that's happening now right
seven different
heavy metal detox
cleanses
right
incredible so that that alone right
there seven
brain
shot therapy cleanses now i want to talk
to you guys about this there's something
in these books
called brain shot
therapy
brain shot therapy right
and it's a tool
right a protocol
to use for so many different brain
conditions someone might be dealing with
in that moment so it's called brain shot
therapy
and
i would the thing is you guys i would
when these books come out when they're
released and they're in your hand we're
gonna do
a brain shot therapy
challenge we're going to do it together
and it's going to be extraordinary
what's going to happen
it's going to be extraordinary about
what i mean with what's going to happen
literally mind-blowing i see we're
censored again on facebook
so we're here let's talk about a little
bit else that's in here i'll talk about
the brain shot therapy let's go into
that a little bit so the brainshot
therapy is a protocol
designed by soc
to shift and change brain problems
to shift and change them
rather quickly
so people have a fighting chance to do
the other
healing
protocols to recover
so we took people have that in their
hands i mean honestly another thing in
these books you guys know about the
medical medium shock therapies right
it's not brain shot therapy that's a
different protocol you guys know about
the medical medium shock therapies right
like the
zinc shock therapy you know about that
vitamin c shock therapy you know about
that and you guys know what that's done
for people
it's got them out of such jams and such
trouble right so many people it's
literally saved so many people's lives
the zinc shock therapy
and the vitamin c shock therapy right we
know that we've we've seen that happen
out there we know what's going on
but we have
okay in these books
shock therapies
10 shock therapies in this book
10 shock therapies
in these books
and
it's mind-blowing i'd like to tell you
what they are but you need the details
because i don't it's so comprehensive i
won't be able to give you all those
details
so when you get the books you're going
to be armed
with
those extra shock therapies that alone
is
legendary as far as soc goes
centaur's healing it does keep on
getting better it does
if you know
um
i know there's a question right there
when he says can we skip the time right
the thing is is i can't go into it
because they're so comprehensive i won't
be able to do that justice so if i sit
here with you guys and go through the
details you guys have to have the books
and that's what's really exciting when
you have these books you'll be like
armed ready you'll be reading them
you'll be like whoa i can't believe this
and every line is mind-blowing
i'm still learning i'm still learning
about what's in these books
just when i look over them and proof
them right because you know when they
went to print i had to proof them when
they went to print before they went to
print and it was just like oh my god i
can't believe that's in here or i can't
believe that's in here about blood brain
barrier i can't believe no one knows
this about blood-brain barrier
about
how absorbent the blood-brain barrier is
how much passes and crosses through the
blood-brain barrier in details and the
vagus nerve influence the vagus nerve
information
about it being inflamed
is in crazy detail in here
how heavy metals sit inside our brain
and why they twist us up is in detail
like you know how i always say heavy
metals toxic heavy metals toxic heavy
metals and this is what it does to
neurotransmitters and toxic heavy metals
with right electrical impulses you guys
know how i've always talked about it
well this goes into detail on how what
happens when the toxic heavy metal is
sitting in the brain right
this goes into detail about when the
toxic heavy metals actually sitting in
the brain what really happens
how come we go into we go into what we
go into ocd obsessive compulsive
disorder
how come we go into all these different
things in ptsd and ocd and depression
and then the depression chapter alone
talking about
how the soul is intertwined with
depression so that ailment that
condition depression the reason why one
of the reasons why it's so mysterious is
because because
it not only has something to do with
heavy metals but it has something to do
with the soul and the combination
the combination
is just incredible right the combination
is incredible information to know
so
look we'll keep on going a little bit
more i'm trying to give you guys a sneak
peek right now but i just want to tell
you if you just got on here it's f the
books are 40 off each book is 40 off you
want to get both
you want to pre-order them you're not
going to get charged until the book
shipped so you're just not even going to
get charged so if you order the books
you're not going to get charged
until it's shipped and then when it's
shipped it's getting shipped at its
lowest price
lowest price so amazon.com us the link's
right there in the description links in
the profile you guys over there links in
the description you want to check those
out
and the thing is about these books
is when they come out
especially right now with everybody
having brain problems
lower
because that's what's happening
these are going to be those life-saving
tools out there and and we need this out
here that's why i'm so excited i'm so
excited because i feel like i'm i could
really really make a dent
into chronic disease
and i'm really excited so it's 40 off
amazon.com us right now 40 off each book
so each book brainsaver brainsaver
protocols tell a friend tell a family
member they're not going to be charged
until it's shipped the links in the bio
links in the descriptions over 600 pages
each
so comprehensive with information but
you know guys you know how i always talk
about the blood draw problems you guys
know you know they take too much blood
right they take all that blood and not
only do they take all the blood but they
take your immune system with the blood
you know how i always talk about that
well the blood draw chapter
in these books
is so comprehensive to how it works you
can you can literally bring it to your
doctor and be like read this chapter
and it's there's it's inescapable
the comprehensive information about what
happens when we get our blood drawn when
you read it in these books it's really
inescapable as far as like the the
knowledge in there it's really exciting
so
talk a little bit more about it too so
both books right so let's go in here
let me do it this way so i'll keep these
up right here you guys good to see you
coming on
i'm excited
so i got like a few notes here too which
i'm excited about too you just
pre-ordered it heather incredible
it really is so part one is about your
brain story and there's part one in one
of the books okay so this is the first
book right here there's first second
book both of these are companion books
right and what happens is that
we walk around with inflamed cranial
nerves there we go we walk around with
incre
inflamed cranial nerves
sophie said sophia viewer says can't
wait for the breast implant illness
chapter it's really comprehensive about
breast implant illness
really an important chapter because what
happens is with breast implant illness
it heads into all these neurological
problems so
that's the whole point it heads into
neurological issues and when you have
breast implant illness you get so many
different diagnoses could happens like
lupus or ms or neurological lyme or
something else it's just either way or
brain fog or fibromyalgia chronic
fatigue syndrome and all of those are
neurological so brain so it's all about
brain and nervous system when it's
breast implant illness so it's really a
critical chapter in the book
comprehensive
really really really insightful and and
opens up the eyes i'm excited that you
you want to read that chapter i really
am
right
so
there's there's a chapter called
emotional brain in this book that will
just blow your mind right talking about
how it works with our emotions and how
it's connected inside the physical brain
and how our physical brain gets injured
and when our physical brain gets injured
in the emotional centers of the brain
it talks about exactly how
and why that affects emotions and why
we're all over the place and then how
that how that could even affect the soul
that chapter alone is just
off the charts right there's a chapter
about addictions like addictive brain
because
we get addicted to everything so
everybody's like well i'm not addicted
to
alcohol i'm not addicted to drugs but
you're yet you're addicted to these
other five things or you're addicted to
these other 10 things so the addiction
chapter is just crazy
lisa said is there anything in there
about schizophrenia i would never leave
schizophrenia out of these books for
sure there's over 300 symptoms and
conditions schizophrenia is one of them
it's in the books and
it's a mind-blowing you know the
protocol for schizophrenia is there
which is great here's one right here
that's critical to seizures
seizures
right
epic detail comprehensive
chapter
with with seizures
so people understand how it even happens
what goes wrong
protocol
to turn it around and that alone is just
so great
lesions too lesions on the spinal cord
brain nervous system lesions inside the
brain
a lot of people
they get their mris
right
and what shows up on their mris is a
little white spot what is that a little
white spot little gray spot gray matter
white spot you know black spot
all kinds of dots on their brain and
stuff so it goes into detail about all
the different spots that are developing
on everybody's brain and what's
happening in the future and as mris get
even more sensitive
they're going to pick up more spots and
that's going to be a major problem
because both medical research and
science and the patient is not going to
know why they have these spots on their
brain and it's going to lead to a lot of
bad problems
because they're they're uneducated as
far as why the spots are there and what
they are
so
this book with that alone is just
mind-blowing sarah said what about
bipolar totally there's a bipolar
chapter
in
these books
so you want to get both books right
betty says is bleep long haul or covered
yep it is
definitely
it is
so i gotta bleep some words because i'm
already censored so i gotta i gotta
believe words so it doesn't
go even worse
eating disorders chapter
is incredible
eating disorders chapter is incredible
by the way you guys i was censored
before everybody was getting censored
back a few years ago
anyway so the eating disorders is a big
one right there and how it works with
the brain when you when you actually
know why you have an eating disorder or
had an eating disorder because we fight
with the eating disorders again and
again so many people like well i
conquered my eating disorder
doing this and that out there and then
my eating my eating disorders back
or a lot of people their eating disorder
morphs into something else that's
different so it morphs into something
else that's different
right started out as an eating disorder
that was doing this and now it's
something else entirely different now
it's the worst ocd
now it's eating disorder back to ocd now
it's ocd and eating disorder
now it's eating disorder depression and
ocd or depression now back to eating
disorder
now it's anxiety eating disorder
depression eating disorder i mean it's
really incredible what happens to people
mary morgan says
is there anything in books about brain
tumors yes there is
would never leave that out for sure
thanks for asking heidi says my ovarian
cyst dissolved as la as of last week
after four months medical medium
protocol
incredible also both ibs irritable bowel
syndrome and constipation gone
boom right on facebook amazing
boom
so happy for you
so happy for you i can't even tell you
that's what i live for that i live for
knowing your life is better if that's
what i live for right there michelle
lynn my daughter has a seizure disorder
i'm looking forward to reading this book
i can't wait for you to get this book
to help i can't wait comprehensive
information
with that comprehensive details kelly z
wonder if it gives us some more healing
protocols for ocd
indeed it does ocd is far from left out
of these books
because ocd is really hard on a lot of
people and it can be brutal devastating
crippling
ocd is like crippling for so many people
right meredith do you talk about
concussions yes
a concussion
post-concussion protocol is in these
books
post-concussion protocols in these books
so important so important
you got to get both books 40 off
amazon.com us right now you're not going
to get charged until they're shipped and
you'll get the lowest price when they're
shipped
so worth it
you know people out there spending ten
thousand twenty thousand dollars hundred
thousand dollars on health care and all
kinds of different ways traveling around
the world trying everything under the
sun
and the books are forty percent off
they're the ultimate tools in your hands
their mingo says do you have something
on coffee addiction in there i even have
a caffeine
withdrawal protocol
unbelievable like there's a protocol
for when you're done with coffee or
caffeine if you're at that point in your
life where even if you're not at that
point now you're like okay i'm getting
his brain books because i got something
else wrong with me right
i got a seizure or this or i have that
or
breast implant illness or fibromyalgia
or ms or whatever it is or just i got
brain fog and i'm getting his brain
books
right
but i don't want to quit coffee and i
don't want to quit caffeine or anything
and guess what one day you wake up three
years later and you're like you know
what i'm in the mood to quit caffeine oh
wait a minute let me look
these books are the books that keep on
giving it's like let me crack one open
whoa caffeine withdrawal coffee
withdrawal protocol
addiction you know which you know
protocol
incredible
right
it's a caffeine chapter on top of it
but information i never talked about
before
someone might say well i know aw he
talks about caffeine
i know not like what's in here lynn says
looking forward to the epilepsy chapter
absolutely the seizure chapter as i had
and i have a protocol there too which is
really cool
excited
so you guys that's just some stuff in
here is that crazy
right christian says autism anxiety for
people over over than 18 yes indeed and
would not forget that
i would not
for sure
emily barth says do these cover pots
p-o-t-s yes they do
covered
i knew that question was gonna come i
said the soc we have to cover pots we
have to cover pots give me pots
information please please please i know
i'm gonna be asked and guess what
there's a pots protocol not just
information about it in detail
comprehensive but a pots protocol
exactly
it's that crazy
so
guys
i can't even scratch the surface i'm
going to try to scratch the surface but
it's not going to
happen kristen says does this have info
on adhd it does indeed protocol included
susan brun how about dementia my dad has
it yes dementia in here alzheimer's in
here big time protocol and everything to
pull and a loved one out of dementia
that's the key there's a chapter on
dementia alzheimer's and dementia a
whole chapter within intricate
information of how it works in here like
why is it happening
what happened to make us lose our loved
ones like that where they just don't
even know who they are they forget who
they are they don't even know what's
going on they're walking down the street
aimlessly it's getting worse they can't
eat all of that what is going on and we
have to have a protocol and it's in
there lulu says my migraine disappeared
thanks to your protocol incredible
incredible and i have that i have my
grain headache in here
too
yeah
cold light spring says do you talk more
about the mercury man man do i talk
about mercury
may i talk about mercury
in there yeah wendy i've healed so much
thanks to you
eczema free for life i can do a dance
for that that's incredible right on
youtube wendy
i mean
yeah
i would love to dance about that because
that is the best thing i've ever heard
eczema free for life
i love it love it austin austin what's
going on man
i almost killed myself because of my ocd
had no idea the human
the human could suffer to such an extent
austin ocd you understand then you
understand my whole life i've been
helping people with ocd i saw some of
the most devastating situations and and
struggling on on levels that no one
understands unless like you that had had
ocd
austin i'm just proud of you for being
here thank you for being here i'm so
glad you didn't kill yourself thank god
you're here
and um god bless you man and i'm really
glad you're in it you're in it to heal
heal your ocd i just love that and good
to see you by the way nothing about you
megan autism yes
yes
james says morning cleanse healed my
diverticulitis and chronic nerve pain on
facebook amazing james
awesome you're here you guys get it
right
you know
the medical medium books have always had
comprehensive information sophia said
can we order the books to germany
yeah i mean order to germany click click
the link the link should tell you where
to get it that's what i'm hoping i'm
hoping that works just like that but it
should
yes medical medium books have always
been there to have comprehensive
detailed information of why we're sick
before the medical medium books all we
had were doctor authors or health
authors that just told you to eat better
they didn't know what caused chronic
illness in
in 2015
2014 really when the book was was was
written
2015 when that book first medical medium
book was launched right
okay
for the first time in our history in
health
out of all the different venues out
there and health belief systems and
clinics and everything nobody knew why
anybody was sick you guys it was just
eat better they were all eat better
doctors come out with a new book food
science eat better another person would
come out with a book eat better uh
vegans would be like eat better the
vegetarians books will be like eat
better it was just eat better um going
on the doctor shows oh eat better lose
weight eat better that's all it was
the medical medium books were
comprehensive guides to why someone was
sick for the first time with
neurological conditions it didn't exist
before that people who have been around
the block and started with medical
mediums first book know the difference
they tried everything been there done
that and they didn't have anything out
there there wasn't anything there
it was just eat better or a diet belief
system to try or change your diet or
some kind of keto or some kind of blood
type or some kind of eat better diet
that's all there was
anyway i'm saying this
because being the first to bring
information about chronic illness about
viruses and all the other stuff
so people can get their lives back
fixing their hashimoto's fixing their
fiber and their multiple sclerosis and
fixing lupus wait you guys
have these books in your hands
you'll be like how is this possible
that he even took it to this level
he's not a smart guy never went to
college it's the source that i get the
information from
carrie anne says i'm healing my
hashimoto's alopecia yeah
vitiligo following your info so amazing
on facebook here again
thank you for being here bless your
heart
power of compassion totally epic
the books
are epic
they're done
they're at the printing press
it's just too exciting can't even tell
you they're getting going to get ready
to get shipped to you eventually
peripheral nerve protocols
absolutely because peripheral nerve
protocols are cranial nerve protocols
those are cranial nerves
and it causes these peripheral
neuropathy peripheral all these nerve
issues
gretchen what's the difference between
the two books yay
cool let's talk about it a little bit
right here
all right
so brain saver one
here
keep on going this way when i'm supposed
to be here
brings about one right here okay
right
get over a hundred conditions explained
in detail comprehensive nature
incredible chapters on alzheimer's
bipolar ocd depression anxiety
that's just to name a few
it's got 14 cleanses in here yeah
right
it's got it's got the micro dosing
caffeine withdrawal all these other
things alcohol addiction sections all of
that too
but even beyond that that's just
scratching the surface right there right
even beyond that it talks about having
an acid brain why we're bathing our
brains an acid addiction brain emotional
brain how the emotions
in the emotional centers of the brain
get damaged because of
the physical tissue being damaged and
then the emotions get twisted and people
don't even really know you never see
where someone's like that's not really
who i am but why did that happen
like that's not who i am
like i didn't mean to do that and it's
not even my fault because i don't know
how that happened because that's not who
i am as a person
the only people that that go through so
much emotional struggle and there's
there's information in here how it all
happens right
in this book here the depression chapter
is unlike anything that's ever been out
there in the world
from medical media and beyond it's
incredible
so i mean these are just some of the
things i've talked about i go in depth
over a hundred illnesses like in like
incomprehensive nature right so that's
that's just part of it there
there's a section in here called brain
betrayers
what happens is here's what slows people
down in their healing process wait what
um okay i'll try that over there oh okay
let me try that okay over there i'm not
getting better yet let me try this and
they end up burying themselves because
they can't get better because of all the
trendy traps right brain betrayers
really goes into detail on how people
are constantly stuck to this 22 you know
catch-22 vicious cycle of brain
betrayers harming their brain and that's
why they never heal
goes into depth and detail about that
right right there
and then there's a whole section i'm
bringing back your brain which is these
are so comprehensive i actually needed
no paper
when do i ever need no papers
i could already see what i'm up against
with these books man
when these
when these books come out i'm gonna have
a bunch of note papers
when do i ever have those
seriously sandra says
it is also for psychosis yeah i have a
um protocol for psychosis
not messing around with these books
right
neurological asthma i talk about that in
there gina
so i talk about that so
chrissy says we're so freaking lucky
i'm so lucky i'm still standing after it
came after all this information came
through and i got him into these books
i'm lucky i'm still standing
i was worried about that that really was
all right so we're doing talking about
we're going to talk about this one next
a little bit too okay
let's go into this a little bit
so
there's a brain betrayer section in this
book too
which is incredible
there's a hundred over a hundred recipes
over a hundred recipes in this book
brand new for the brain 100 recipes you
got the brain shot therapy in here which
is incredible all in its own okay but
like i said over 100 recipes you got
meditations in this book that i haven't
done
like i haven't done like publicly
meaning i haven't put up on a podcast
meditations that i've used in my life
meditations some i've never even used
yet until this book
because soc gave me the meditations for
this book
and i was like why didn't you give give
me this meditation i i could use for
myself
this is this is for the book
this is for brain problems for people
critical to heal their brains i'm like
okay so the meditations in here alone
are really incredible so there's that
michael says i've lost weight and got
off medication
and so much more because of your help
thank you so much for what you do
incredible
michelle thank you for being here
amazing
so i'm in my notes right here you guys
i'm talking about both these books 40
off amazon.com us right now you won't be
charged when you order them until
they're shipped so you didn't have to
worry right now you could just order
them you're not gonna be charged on your
credit card until they're shipped and
you're gonna get the lowest price which
is incredible
and of course they're gonna they're
gonna they've already lowered the price
underneath what it costs to make these
that there's that much if you actually
try to print one of these out on your
own
right and do that right there
it's really costly that's what i'm gonna
tell you right now that's how incredible
it is when you can when you can get a
book like this and get it just an
expensive 40 off
which is really amazing on its own
so it's really exciting
andrea
may we touch on
may we touch on stroke too yes we do we
talk about strokes in here uh protocol
for stroke which is exciting right blood
clot
talk about that too in here in these
books which is really great there's a
section called brain and soul rehabbing
that's amazing all in its own
we got the over 100 delicious recipes
full color
photos
breakfast lunch dinner snacks
desserts to nourish your brain which is
really incredible
seven heavy metal detox cleanses and the
advanced heavy metal detox cleanse
because what's happening is the
industries are getting real snakey
really really snaky so the industries
are vaporizing metals now
so that's what's happening
people are breathing in metals through
vapors
everywhere so the industry's put all
these vaporized methyl metals
inside all these different products now
and everybody's just everybody's just
vaping metals without realizing it i'm
not talking about like vaping vaping
where you're sitting in purposely i'm
talking about without even knowing it or
children or family members or pets
they're they're vapor they're breathing
in these vapors inhaling them absorbing
them through their skin so the
industries learn this new technique
this new learn this new technique
about
you know how to get metals through
chemical
transformation basically getting them
into us that way methylating them
getting into a vapor form
and so metals are different like never
before so that's something that's
happening now so we're going to the
future so these are the future
so the heavy metal detox cleanses
okay
all right
so we're we're moving on a little bit
you guys i am so excited it's really
incredible
are you guys
i'm going to head off to ig just
remember 40 off you got you gotta get
both these books their companion books
two
brain saver books
anyway check it out when you can
amazon.com us
just reading comments
yeah sea trails
chapter on sea trails in these books
which is really cool on its own chapter
on emf because everybody's always like
emf emf how does it work
really insightful information that the
emf people don't know when hear
so just read a few symptoms that are in
some of these like just a few symptoms
over 300 symptoms and conditions
protocols for 300 symptoms and
conditions right so adhd right als
alzheimer's anemia anxiety aphasia you
guys know about aphasia right autism
autoimmune disorders balance issues
bell's palsy
psychedelics totally mauricio
psychedelics 100
psychedelic withdrawal all of it
microdosing chapter all of that in here
which is incredible
bipolar disorder blood clots brain fog
brain inflammation brain lesions breast
implant illness like we talked about
before caffeine withdrawal canker sores
chronic fatigue syndrome cold sores
cranial nerve inflammation right
dementia depersonalization i'm just
naming a few just a few tourettes yes
tourettes is in here narcolepsy
myocarditis multiple sclerosis migraines
lyme disease lupus restless leg syndrome
pots
seizures swallowing difficulties tremors
trigeminal neuralgia i mean
over 300 i'm just giving you guys a few
right so it's an empowerment for sure
which is incredible
narcolepsy
that's in here too
anyway you guys i am going to ig going
to talk about the 40 off i want
everybody just reminded that it's that
accessible
it's that inexpensive
i mean yeah could i
not put these books out and create a
whole bunch of brain programs
and everybody has to pay absorbance
amounts of absorbent amount of money to
get into the brain programs
enriching myself
and just withhold the information from
soc
no
put it in two expense two inexpensive
books
that you can hold in your hand have in
your own personal library and in your
house
empower yourself and your health
recover and heal teach people how to
recover and heal that's what it's about
right there guys
gonna head off to ig and i'm gonna turn
telegram back on and i'm going to turn
tick tock back on i love you guys
links are in the description
links are are on the bio check out my
videos i'm doing too on tick tock lately
and my new videos exclusive videos on
tik tok check out my exclusive videos on
snapchat when you get a chance check out
my emails my newsletter where i do a
video every sunday if you can
so this this week's is going to be about
the tongue so it's about the tongue
that's one you want to see sign up to my
newsletter
so you can actually get that video sent
to you
exclusive video about the tongue because
everybody's got all these weird
stuff they got tongue they got
fuzzy stuff on their tongues they got
white tongue they got black tongue they
got all these different tongue issues so
wait to check that out anyway
i'll see you guys soon going on ig in a
little bit
putting telegram on and tick tock love
you guys