we're live right now and we're on day
four of the medical medium collecting
Stones meditation journey and I am full
of joy
and I'm
giggling with excitement and happiness
because
the amount of people right now that are
having a life-changing experience is
just unimaginable
nearly a hundred thousand people right
now
are in the collecting Stone's meditation
Journey
and
I'm having an incredible experience with
my Stones I see everybody bringing
stones to their garden they're they're
putting their stones
near their plants near their garden beds
they're eating with their Stones they're
sleeping with their Stones they have
their stones with them on bicycles they
have their stones with them in the car
they have their stones with them and
their pockets this is just an absolute
dream come true for so many people
healing for me it's a dream come true
that so many people are going to be
doing so much deep healing and that
right there is what it's all about
that's what it's about
it's about
moving the needle forward in emotional
spiritual mental healing an incredible
process is taking place right now I'm so
proud of you guys seriously I am so so
proud of you
I can't say enough about it now I have
to give you
just a little
couple little words
it's not going to be easy letting go of
your stones
it's gonna be so hard and maybe not for
everyone but for
probably most everyone it's gonna be
incredibly hard to release and let go of
those stones and I'm going to talk about
why in a minute too so I'm going to go
into why
this collecting Stone's meditation
Journey
was released in 2015
in medical medium right here by the way
so collecting Stones meditation journey
is in medical medium this is the revised
and Expanded Edition right here
so I want everybody to know
where it originates from
I want to prepare us because releasing
the stones is going to be an experience
all on its own
these stones
have become my friends
truly like I am connected to the stones
you see right here
deeply connected to these stones
and I know that so many of you guys are
deeply connected to your Stones as well
um I'm seeing all kinds of comments
there your daily videos are some special
illnesses on YouTube
uh pilly Rin says stones are making
awesome friends and healers an important
update by the way for anyone having
trouble receiving their daily emails for
the collecting Stones meditation Journey
you can access the day 4 video and PDF
from the same link from days one two or
three all you need to do is go back to
the email from the day or days before
and use the same link We suggest
bookmarking the page so you can return
to it for the remaining days of the
journey in case your emails do not come
through it is always the same link and
the content is updated daily if you are
still having trouble you can ask for
help at the link in the medical meet at
Medical meeting profile or description
of this video that's the help desk
hopefully you guys got that
it's a lot of words
all right
why is it going to be so difficult to
release our stones
we often get stuck in patterns
patterns that last a lifetime
emotional spiritual mental patterns
that seem like an impossibility to break
for so many
I think a lot of people who are
soul-searching
one of the reasons why they're
soul-searching is they're stuck in a
vicious cycle
they're stuck in a catch-20 too
they're stuck in a vicious cycle
so many people
are log jammed in that vicious cycle and
they can't swim out of it they can't get
out of it
and they go to therapists and they go to
psychiatrists and they go to healers and
they go to doctors and they go to
friends
and they look for words of wisdom they
look for advice to try to break the
patterns that are occurring these
patterns stem from PTSD they can stem
from experiences that started a long
time ago they can stem
from just about anything as we're going
through life on this journey
and then once a pattern has been created
and we're stuck in that pattern and
we're stuck in it it becomes a part of
us
doesn't Define us though
it can never Define us
even if it becomes a part of us
so I want to say
I want to say as these patterns become a
part of us it doesn't mean it's Who We
Are
it doesn't mean that's all we are
it's critical to understand very
important piece of it all
just because we go through life
and we have these patterns that we get
stuck in that we try everything to break
or we may not even know we have these
patterns we may not even know we have
any of these patterns at all
but we're stuck in him and someone else
may recognize them and be like what's
going on a loved one or a friend or a
relationship or a partner or anybody
they might be like what's going on what
are you going through what's happening
here and you're trying to describe it
and you're trying to figure it out and
you don't know why you got angry and you
don't know why really you're sad and you
don't know why you're struggling
emotionally mentally but you are
and so many people are in a pattern
without even knowing they're in a
pattern that they're stuck in because
something happened to him or is
happening to them in their life in that
moment that they are wrapped up into a
vicious cycle
a circle of confusion and they can't
break it and every time a trigger comes
along and triggers them and hits them
it's like boom they're back into it boom
they're back into that pattern and how
do we get out of it
Barbara from YouTube says thank you and
SOC I love this meditation
this
is going to be one of the most powerful
meditations you have ever done in your
life and you're never going to forget
this experience by the seventh day
you're never ever going to forget
he has been said on YouTube I love you
and spirit of compassion I take my
Stones everywhere and my pockets so do I
so do I I am so excited God bless you
so I want to go back to the patterns
that we get stuck in
it's a very real thing hard to break
and then we get tagged by others
as that's how we really are oh that
person's just really difficult that
person I think has OCD and Tourette's
that person seems like a really
difficult person that person just is so
sensitive and Hyper sensitive they can't
even like you can't even talk to them
that person gets triggered so easy I
can't talk to them
and then you get tagged and
misunderstood
for something
that you're going through that people
can't understand and you may not even be
able to understand yourself because it's
that difficult
but when we have emotional experiences
through life and we get into hardships
of any kind even if they seem small or
really small but they're actually big
and so many things affect us in so many
different ways and every single person
is different so every time something
happens in someone's life it's different
there's a different scale
people will go to like
therapists psychiatrists
they'll go through all kinds of
different courses and programs to try to
better themselves emotionally
spiritually
but the Stone's meditation the
collecting Stones meditation is unlike
anything you're ever going to experience
because this is going to absorb
something take something away that
shouldn't be there and that's the
difference with this entire experience
we're going through right now for anyone
who missed a day or wasn't able to watch
one of the videos at the end of the
seven days there will be a replay for 48
hours just so you know this is a big
deal that you can access
the videos you can still so still sign
ups to still sign up now and join us or
sign up then
so you can access the videos
Anna Brothers on YouTube says I'm loving
this meditation I didn't realize how
attached I would get to my stones and
it's only day four
only day four Anna only day four
when we get to day five which is
tomorrow and we get to day six which is
the day after tomorrow it's going to be
even a way different story and it's
going to be something very very
life-changing that's developing right
now as we speak
as you're sitting there right now with
your Stones your Stone's got to know you
they're getting to know you you're
getting to know them and they are
absorbing information
because stones are minerals
minerals that can draw
and when they draw they absorb
by the way
sign up link is in the profile or
descriptions of the videos so make sure
you sign up link is in the profile and
description if you
are here
so you can sign up
by the way I want to make an
announcement my YouTube channel
has advertisements running
not by my liking YouTube has done that
without my say
and so there are commercials on my
YouTube channel now
just letting everybody know I am not
being paid for it nor have I collected a
penny from YouTube
I've been avoiding those YouTube
advertisements for over 10 years
I think something like that I don't know
eight years whatever it's been and they
have now placed those advertisements in
front of my videos on YouTube
which is really annoying
and then some
and by the way I've been censored on
YouTube now for three and a half years
almost totally censored so it's really
annoying that they then throw
advertisements in front of my centered
YouTube channel
Disney over there on IG says I'm so
attached to my stones
incredible
yep May wow they did it without my
approval indeed they did
so Beauty cargo says where can you sign
up on IG please sign up right there on
IG on the link is in the profile Sensi
yoga said this is the real deal therapy
so we are moving into
the fifth day tomorrow we're on our
fourth day now I want to forewarn
everybody about something
Ambrose live said on IG Anthony I can
tell this is absolutely the most
powerful meditation I've ever done
and that's on the fourth day
I can't express it enough I'm trying my
best to contain myself I don't know if
you guys can tell or not but I'm trying
my best to contain myself because
this is gonna be unlike anything you've
ever experienced
someone can just take my word for that
take this clip and put it somewhere put
it somewhere whatever make the clip out
of this video and post it and be like
we'll see about that
yeah we'll see about that
sparkling nourishment on IG says I lost
all my three stones yesterday whoa can I
pick three new ones thank you for all
you do yes you can pick three new ones
but OMG you lost all three of your
Stones during this collecting Stone's
meditation Journey
what kind of meaning is in there
I'm positive there's tremendous meaning
you should pick your brain your
intuition connect and just find out what
happened right there wild blueberry
dreams on IG said yes aw I feel like the
stones are my little babies
I feel the same
RM javaro says it's giving me Comfort
after losing my father
so sorry you lost your your father
over there in IG Dell Hodgins said I
have taken my stones with me in my bag
today took them out when I got home and
sang to them
incredible have you guys did you sing to
your Stones yet that's what I wanted to
ask you have you picked chosen a song to
sing to your Stones I want to go over
that a little bit if everybody has a
minute or two
yeah
so when you're singing to your stones
it's not just an exercise
it's not just an exercise where you're
like okay what's the next exercise let
me sing to my Stones it's more than that
songs that you choose have great meaning
emotional meanings
if you're choosing a song
to sing to your Stones it could be a
song
that you nostalgically remember from the
past it could be a song that you
remember
that happened it was out at around the
time when you were going through
something it could be a song that makes
you happy because you're sad a lot so
you like this song it could be any song
but there's a reason why you choose the
song and there's reason why you're
singing to your stones
when you sing emotion
is released
and your stones are reading that emotion
they're absorbing the frequency within
each word as you're humming or singing
to your stones
there's information in the frequency of
the sound of your voice
coming from your soul
so as you sing you're singing from your
soul to your stones
and then a channel opens up
that channel opens up between you and
your Stones as you're singing and in
that channel there's emotions and
information hidden in there that's deep
within that because of the song itself
that you're choosing and how you're
singing it to your stones
and so information is then channeled out
directly into the Stone's emotional
information because of the song the song
opens up a channel within our soul
it frees the pathway
so that information can travel with
emotional
baggage on it or hardship or hurt or any
kind of emotion going into your stones
and your stones are absorbing that very
information
Kim Miller on YouTube Anthony if we're
bed bound and can't discard our stones
on our own can someone else do it for us
yes Kim someone else can discard the
stones
for you
it's just as powerful
it's just this life-changing
it doesn't get hindered on any level
so yes you can definitely have someone
discard toss those stones
for you
without any hiccups in the process of
the seven day collecting Stone's
meditation Journey
shiatsu said I lost one should I collect
a new one I actually don't feel like I
should
you don't have to get a new one
but you're welcome to get a new one if
you like
but you can go either or with that you
don't have to get a new one if it feels
good that stone may have absorbed
already enough that stone might have
absorbed a full amount and it was lost
for a reason
mukto Freedom over there on YouTube
thanks beloved Anthony
I feel protected with my Stones not
alone
the incredible
Nancy Newman over there on YouTube can
we write their names on our Stones yes
you can now I didn't put that piece of
information out there in a PDF
but it doesn't mean you can't of course
you can Erica Malek said it's mine day
nine oh sorry Eric are you talking about
369 which is incredible
Mildred over there on YouTube My Stones
put me to sleep as soon as I touched
them it's an amazing journey and as
you're falling asleep when you're
touching your stones
your stones are absorbing you become
clear
and hurt from the soul
from your spirit leave your body and are
entering your Stones they're entering
your Stones while you're falling asleep
is that you're falling asleep
your stones are taking the information
as you're falling asleep
they're taking in the information
Dawn says over there in Facebook I can't
discard my stones
I'm too attached it's going to be hard
Don
it's going to be so hard
in this seven day collecting Stones
meditation journey and we're all going
to be discarding our stones on the
seventh day
unless for some reason you can't get to
a place to discard them and if you can't
get to a place to discard them
completely understand it's going to have
to be the next day or soon as you can or
when you can if you can't discard them
on that day it's okay but we all
eventually have to let it go and let our
Stones go and let them do their job
Jennifer Cockrell says over there on
YouTube what could it mean by being
annoyed by the Stones
I feel like they are just something else
that I have to take care of along with
everything else I have to do haven't
felt like this the whole time Jennifer
it's an incredible emotional experience
right there there's a reason why you're
feeling that way
and your stones are absorbing some kind
of old hurt around that around having to
take care of something
so something that may have happened in
your life
is making that occur something that's
stored up inside of you from having to
take care of something and your stones
are going to be absorbing that because
remember I have to tell you guys
something really important a critical
piece of information right here so
important
is that as we're breaking patterns and
the stones are removing negative baggage
it's been inside of us old hurt that
we've been holding on to that's been
stuffed inside for years and years and
years as it's removing that empty spaces
are starting to
open inside of us empty spaces because
that's leaving you that stuff is leaving
you and then empty spaces open up those
empty spaces then can take on new
references new experiences and new
information so it doesn't get bumbled
together and confusing so we can have
more freedom and peace in our heart and
soul chatsu says bridged on YouTube
Bridge Over Troubled Water is my
favorite song I sang that one to my
Stones as well I guarantee you that you
did a better job than me
hmm I can promise you that you did a
better job singing Bridge Over Troubled
Water than I did Michelle said I have
slept so deep the last few nights
that's incredible
this is going to be one of the most
powerful probably the most powerful in
your lifetime to break patterns
patterns we didn't even know we had
I'm actually really thrilled Beyond
thrilled
foreign
can I read a couple of comments that are
on telegram if you guys are okay with
that
this is Rachel Haynes
the journey is profound palpable
I wasn't expecting what's happening
to be happening
when I found the first stone heartbreak
I knew it was the one it feels different
from the others
shaped like a heart with a white line
going through the center
I found that it has ended up in a
different pocket to the others by
accident
also noticed when I was connecting with
them the other day heartbreak Stone was
held between my thumb and forefinger the
others in my palm
it's just how they ended up
when I went to take
a photo of them my dog nudged them with
her nose and then took heartbreak in her
mouth
it was a cute moment I felt like it was
a sign she can Crush heartbreak easily
she was born to do that she's not afraid
of it
they are with me as I meditate
I place them on my body as I rest
it feels as though nothing is an
accident with the stones
every little thing is Meaningful I am
paying attention and so are they
and it's beautiful I feel supported by
them I took them to a visit to my
niece's grave yesterday who passed away
tragically a year ago tomorrow
they are
with me
not just by my side but they are with me
today they will be with me as I see my
daughter who is avoiding me and
distancing herself for years now it's
been so painful
I'm glad the stones will be there
and they will be absorbing
pain and any kind of Sorrow
so grateful aw and SOC thank you so much
I don't feel it will be the same after
this I know I will have received healing
for some painful hardships just what my
soul needed
Mary James says it felt natural I simply
knew
um nobody said
I did the Free as a bird meditation with
my Stones it was very special and I was
so relaxed afterwards I was laying on my
bed with them on my face while I
listened to the podcast and I could feel
a frequency admitting from my stones
Maria Velez says my Stone named annoyed
it's so annoying I was giving all three
a little kiss and it fell right out of
my hand kind of rejecting my love
nobody said day one of the journey was a
special day and I actually picked up
five stones but I knew the three that
were meant for me
one
was a ways away from where I started I
was drawn to it as it lay their waiting
for me
garden weed pixie said the day I
collected the stones I got up early in
the morning and got in my car and drove
to the beach it takes about two minutes
for me to get there it's cold at the
moment because it's winter where I am
but it was a beautiful that morning it
was beautiful that morning
and the sun was out
I chose my stones after carrying one for
a while and discarding it for another
one stone in my collection of the final
three feel so nice and soft to touch
so smooth but soft
I love it it's so comforting and
soothing I don't want to let it go it
took me ages to name my stones
it was so difficult to Define my
feelings to name them I spent the whole
day feeling basically high and happy for
no reason though I went and did things
for fun that I never go out and do it
was really strange to feel that way but
I definitely needed that day of joy
I only named the stones just before I
went to bed that night I never expected
to have had such a surreal experience
from doing something that I had
absolutely no expectations attached to
I thought I'd just be going through the
motions this experience has surprised me
in many ways
foreign
there
incredible
Elena says yesterday I felt annoyed by
them even though I love them and deeply
connected them they are there to try to
help us heal
so information from old hurt is leaving
us it's easy to be annoyed in any way
possible as information from wounds old
PTSD
scars
on our soul scars on our being
baggage we carry with us into every
relationship into every new experience
how many people
do something in their life
and they do it and they're like I need
to live this very second I need to
experience this Cliff I'm standing on
now over this beautiful view I need to
take it all in I have to take the sunset
in as much as I can they're desperate to
try to take in that new experience and
they want to be in the present moment
they want to have that mindfulness in
the very moment to experience that as
it's happening they want that connection
so bad
because they're struggling they have
hurt inside they have experiences that
are still clogged up inside they have
scars on the sole they're soul-searching
they're trying to find purpose they're
trying to
relieve any kind of internal mental
emotional spiritual suffering of any
kind possible and so they try their best
they're in it they're like I'm
experiencing this air right now I'm
experiencing this Breeze I'm watching
the sun rise
but yet
it's fleeting and I don't know if I'm
really experiencing it like I should and
I don't know am I numb I'm ha I'm
supposed to be having the best time I'm
supposed to be having the best
experience what is going wrong what is
going on
we battle a lot of deep-seated emotional
hurt that sits in percolates and festers
deep inside of us and the collecting
Stones meditation you guys is there to
suck it out of us to absorb it out of us
on IG tough as a mother says what does
it mean when your stones break or chip
it's very possible the stones
could be absorbing so much
so much
that they're chipping away
everybody's different and your
experiences are different than someone
else's experiences and what your stones
are absorbing is different than what
someone else is absorbing like we can't
you can't just take your stones
after they absorb so much and hand them
to somebody else and say okay let them
absorb from you now
now I can't take my Stones ew can't take
my Stones here
and say look I'm gonna give you my
stones after I've had them for a week
they've absorbed any kind of like
emotional pain with me like
discrimination that I've had for years
for hearing a voice
and putting out Advanced Medical
information that's been robbed from me
in spirit and use science uses it and
doesn't credit me and poachers and
influencers use it to try to get a leg
up so they sound like they know what
they're talking about and they steal it
and don't you know don't uh whatever
there's that and then discrimination for
hearing a voice right that's in my stone
and then broken trust from people I
trusted
who make up lies and try to like become
famous themselves because they're
desperate for fame so they try to like
say all kinds of terrible stuff that
isn't true about me right that's in here
broken trust
and there's people I've helped for
decades that don't even cite me or cite
my information people in the health
movement right that have helped that's
in there and the Betrayal
right
where you're doing nothing but like good
things in the world and you're doing
nothing but good things for people and
you're trying to help them and you're
trying to get people help and they just
stab you in the back because
they're sick
on that they just have a dark heart
so whatever it is
whatever it is it's in my Stones I can't
say hey look after seven days of what's
in my stones
I can't say let me give you these Stones
right here let me give you these Stones
sorry if I lost you guys on
up there I can't say here let me give
you my stones
and you let them absorb from you it's
not going to happen these were chosen
for me I chose them or the stones chose
them chose me themselves and the stones
absorbed all that pain or whatever
that's happening that's coming out of me
it's absorbing my baggage everybody has
it there's just the way it works in the
world it's human life it's you know The
Human Experience here on planet mess and
we uh we have that in us we've all been
hurt one way or another somewhere along
the way even someone that's never had a
bad day in their life because they're
say silver spoon fed and they're a trust
funder and I'm not saying anything's
wrong with that but I'm saying and
they've never had they've had full
support from all the love from every
single family member they're totally
protected and they never have to work a
day in their life and they could just go
and just do whatever they want all day
long they still get hurt
they still get hurt they still have pain
they still have sorrow they still have
emotional mental spiritual struggles
everybody does from people who come from
nothing to people who have something to
people who are in between we all have it
it's there and we can't exchange our
Stones I can't say all right give me
your three stones let me have your three
stones and I'll take those three stones
and I'll let me now absorb my pain and
struggles into these stones and then
I'll hand them to somebody else and then
they can have those right there and
that's something I've always been
concerned about
with lots of things because I've seen
people give crystals to other people
just like whoa unless that Crystal came
fresh out of the ground and was and was
um honed by a Craftsman just now and
then handed off to you it's different
when you know a lot of times we hand off
our favorite crystals of people what did
the crystal absorb and then we handed it
off to somebody else and someone else is
like trying to absorb their stuff into
that Crystal when it's already loaded
with other people's stuff these are
yours they're fresh they're brand new
from the earth they were chosen for you
you chose them and that's the difference
and your absorption of your pain and
struggles goes into these stones and
it's not meant for anybody else
Jasmine on YouTube says Anthony is it
normal to feel the three emotions more
intensely while having the stones with
us yes it is
I mean
yeah it does get more intense when you
have them with you and you're getting
close to your Stones me tube 787.
downhill athletic mountain biker in the
past man
um my 13 year old said last night that
he doesn't want to let go of his Stones
totally understand I don't want to let
go of my stones
at me on YouTube good to see you at me
what if someone else touches your stones
it's okay
it's fine
because you're not consciously or
intentionally or subconsciously
saying these are yours now
so say your child says well Daddy
Mommy I wanna like can I play with these
Stones it's fine
because it's not that Dad or Mom or
anyone else or friend isn't saying I am
I'm done using these I'm going to give
these to you these are yours now I'm
intentionally telling these Stones
they're not for me anymore I'm
intentionally saying no these are a gift
I'm giving these to you now that's
different and that's different than just
touching the stones or somebody else
touching the stones and that's fine
Sherry Weaver says if I wait a couple of
weeks can I do this again with three
more stones
can always do this exercise alone but I
will be telling you we're going to be
doing another one if you want to wait
then of course you can do one
through any time but we're going to do
another one pretty soon and I'll tell
you why
because I have three other names I have
to do three new stones with personally
in my own personally and I believe so do
you
I believe everybody has a few more names
and it was hard to choose
it was hard for me to choose I was like
I really want to use this name here and
I really want to use this name here but
I guess I'm gonna use this name this CNN
but I really want to use this name
Jane said over on Facebook one of my
Stones renamed itself
that's incredible
Marge over there on YouTube says I have
felt so good
oh and the comment one oh it felt so
good I hope I still release old feel
heavy feelings on IG
Alive by SOC aw can we make up our songs
yes you can you can make up your songs
you can do your own Originals you can do
I did Bridge Over Troubled Water
but you can definitely do an original
song of course and an original hymn and
everything
delhajan said on IG I think the more you
talk to the stones and sing
Etc they seem to answer you I agree
I agree allheartedly
flower jasmine on IG says I am releasing
a lot of emotional wounds that I have
been carrying for decades
see Lotus Helly says Healy says looking
forward to letting go of my Stones it's
going to be epic to let go of stuff big
stuff
it is going to be epic
on that note I know we covered a lot of
things already you guys but on that note
about the Epic nature of releasing the
stones
your words epic
which is mind-blowing
all of it
it's going to be intense
for some of us it may not be as intense
right that very second it's going to be
intense later on that day for some of us
it's going to be intense before we even
let go of the stone for many of us it's
going to be intense as we're heading to
the place to let go of the song
Serena over there on Facebook I bathed
with them and I cried memories came out
but I tried not to process it I think
that's brilliant I think that's
incredible because you don't have to
process it because the idea is to get it
out of you to the stones the stones need
to absorb it and it doesn't have to be
processed now if it's processed or
memories hit and come then so be it
that's okay but the job for the stones
is to take it on
oh
Charles says over there on YouTube what
does it mean when the stones go brighter
in color
anger looks like orange it used to be
reddish fear has
fear has
trying to find it
oh I think I lost you oh there you go
fear has a bright spot it seems to be
glowing growing it used to be black
that's incredible
as emotions like fear
is leaving you leaving your soul and
entering into the stone anything can
happen
anything can happen there's no rules
there is no rules here
metaphysically there are no rules Here
There Are No Boundaries Anything Can
Happen through this healing process
through the process of that information
leaving you and going into the stones
there are no rules
singing to your stones are humming to
your Stones is you know experience all
on its own
and one of the reasons why is because it
evokes emotion and then the stones are
going to pick up on that and read that
and pull that in and draw it in
Nancy and division over there on
Facebook says I want to do this but I
miss this cycle how can I do it
I would still sign up
I think there's a way to do it I was
talking about it earlier watch this
video again
and I say it in here already
I'm glad you asked
so you guys this was day four is day
four still going on is day four
checking on you see how you guys are
doing I know we're having interactions
with their Stones I've been holding my
Stones this whole time in my left hand
and they feel very warm very warm in my
hand
pretty interesting
there's my Stones right here
I'm proud of everybody you guys truly
so I want to get us ready for day five
and I think this talk helps because the
information that we're talking about is
really really powerful very helpful so I
believe it's
fortifying us
for day five which is tomorrow
D5 is going to be more intense day six
is going to be even more intense and day
seven is going to be extremely intense
vegan Allison over there on YouTube says
I feel like things are coming out that
aren't even the names that I gave the
stones and I had a profound experience
when I was meditating with them and
praying I felt they were
I felt they were the most supportive and
I have to say that vegan Allison you're
correct
very correct that even the names may not
the names Encompass more is what I'm
saying than what the name is
Buzzy Bee I see you I've been really
tired too I read your comment on YouTube
on the last YouTube video too Kim Miller
says every time I offer them a banana I
get chills and feel the connection
I get chills reading
your comments
Eliza on YouTube says we are not harming
the stones are we not harming them at
all truly not
they're doing their job and here's
what's incredible when we release the
stones when we let go of the stones
and they leave our hands and Go Back To
Nature
what's been in them and absorbed in them
is going to be neutralized
but not able to rush back into us
not able to rush back into us
it's uh look I'm I've always supported
therapy and all kinds of emotional
therapy for people of course I want
people to have people to talk to and and
get support emotional healing support in
all ways
but I noticed that a lot of people who
are talking about what they're going
through and they're talking about it and
it's coming out of them I noticed that
the minute they leave the office
or they get off their appointment
it doesn't take long before it kind of
rushes back into them
because there wasn't really a
neutralizer or a separator there wasn't
a bridge so what happens is that
when you release these stones into
nature and they've absorbed a lot of
what's Happening inside of us a lot of
our hurt
when we release them
what's inside of them
it gets neutralized can't just rush back
to you there's a distance there's an
incredible distance it's part of how the
healing works
yeah
Brandi says I name my Stones weak tired
dismayed to help clear my emotions about
being diagnosed with autoimmune diseases
but those emotions started in my
childhood and happened throughout my
life
Welby says my Stone's depression has
gone from grayish
to slight blue lines
while blueberry dreams says aw I was sad
I missed your live the other day with
all of the smokers
I used to smoke cigs in the past two
especially while I drank alcohol
I'm now smoke free for now one and a
half years
and I went out and couldn't have done it
incredible
Zen veteran says Aloha ew this practice
is so profound thank you for sharing
amazing and over there
incredible
frillis says on IG one stone I found
actually several small stones held
together by concrete it seemed so
appropriate for me I think that's
amazing
Concrete in the end it's just a lot of
sand so that's actually great your
stones are held together with sand
you guys many blessings
yep sorry about the smoking and and
drinking talk the other day meaning
sorry if anybody missed that
I'm going to have a cigarette myself
right when I get off this live
maybe a cigar and maybe something in
here
um
but you know I'm kidding because I do
not drink nor I do smoke
nor I smoke
I left an audio message on telegram last
night sure to listen please make sure to
listen
it's at telegram it's at T dot m e
slash medicalmedium.com
I think that's it it's my telegram page
can you find my telegram page
can you guys find it
Cynthia C says on YouTube I shared my
instant noodles with my Stones they
really don't like instant Foods
it's at T dot me slash medical medium
that's my Telegram
this is really good
hmm
[Music]
you guys
many blessings
and get ready for day five tomorrow
enjoy day four I certainly will
Melanie on YouTube says mind-blowing
information
it blows my mind
like my mind is blown by it
it's not my information it's from Spirit
of compassion but my mind is blown by it
like
Mildred on YouTube says I put my stones
in a purple see-through thin bag I put
them where it hurts
and it makes a difference that's
incredible it is
you guys I can't wait to see you soon
please look out for all kinds of
notifications check your emails remember
Hay House is emailing
the emails right for the collecting
Stones meditations or any hay houses so
kind of keep that in mind
so if you're looking and you know check
out medical medium emails too but if
you're looking for information in the
videos and everything else
make sure you kind of check your spam
folders check your desktop if you if
some reason your phone's not showing it
I love seeing and sharing all your
stories and your past your posts and
videos please tag at Medical medium and
hashtag at Medical medium on your insta
story meaning your insist story share it
on your insta stories so share your
reels or your posts on your insta
stories and tag at Medical me hashtag
medical meme so I can see them I can't
see them if you posted if you just post
your experience or you just do a real I
can't see it you have to then you have
to then take that reel in that post
and and post it on your insta story your
stories
and then tag at Medical Meme and hashtag
medical medium or I just can't see it
Jamie Jan over there on YouTube thank
you so much for supporting us with these
lives you're welcome I'm honored and
happy to do so truly
love you guys
many blessings