live live on facebook live on youtube
all right making an incredible dish
it's the medical medium broccoli and
cheese so i'm excited about that
um we're gonna talk about food cravings
are you guys having food cravings that's
what i'm wondering who's having the food
cravings
kind of wonder in there and what happens
is that
are we getting some people on now i
could see what happens with the food
cravings is they get the best out of us
and i'm going to talk about moderation
intuitive eating a little bit
right balanced eating hello everybody
you're coming on
incredible we're going to cover that
it's important to know
how to look out for those cravings
because what happens is
our soul yeah you see me pointing here
our soul our soul yep why am i pointing
here
right medical medium information is
about the soul being
in here is where it is okay
and that's the sole decisions we make
with our free will that's the sole
decisions like i'm gonna eat that right
there i'm gonna eat this right here
you guys are making broccoli and cheese
on a potato i'm excited
so uh broccoli and cheese potatoes is
what it is good to see everybody coming
on
amazing and um
i think we're gonna have to get ready
and make this right now i'm to add a
little water
add a little water in the pan chop up
some broccoli i'm going to get this
going now
that's what i'm going to do lorraine
lorraine l disaster relief
is it disaster relief right when i'm
always messing up in the kitchen
i thought i saw a comment on youtube
lorraine was like
you know what's funny is this yeah the
disaster relief
so i'm gonna cut these pieces up right
here i'm doing some broccoli
i love broccoli broccoli is a beautiful
thing it's so good for us
you guys are you doing any broccoli
lately i like eating this part right
here
just so you know i'm seeing you guys
come on sarah say hey
aw how are you how are you love the
color you're wearing today
amazing thank you i i can't believe you
like this color
i wasn't sure it's got like a a canary
color going on
yellow canary right
so what i'm doing is getting this
broccoli going making the broccoli and
cheese
dish right here you guys
going to talk about food cravings
moderation i'm going to talk about that
too
potatoes could be baked or steamed i got
some steamed potatoes right behind this
bagel
and coffee so right behind this bagel
and cream cheese
and coffee i got some steamed potatoes
going on so
that's the steamed potatoes i have right
here so i'm going to use these steamed
potatoes for this dish and
as you guys hanging around as you hang
around you'll see how i do it
so hello from sweden honored you're here
incredible i like dipping raw broccoli
and hummus hey that's tasty sounding
isn't it
doesn't it sound good linda is there
anything wrong with frozen broccoli
no you can use frozen broccoli i'm okay
with that i'm gonna put some carrots in
here too so i got broccoli in here
and i'm gonna put some carrots in here
too
i'm excited about this dish carla says
love the shirt i'm honored
i'm gonna throw a carrot in this pan
i'm going to slice the carrot kind of
thin because i'm going to use the carrot
in the sauce it's going to be used in
the sauce you guys hanging out
giving me a chance to do this right here
before we
slam you with questions which which i
love danette says hi anthony
finally made a life oh my god that's so
cool
that is so cool i'm going to slice these
carrots i want these carrots to be
somewhat
chopped a little bit i'm gonna use this
carrot in here we're live facebook we're
live youtube
we're chilling in medical mediums
kitchen right now
that's right now you need a utensil
disaster relief quick lorraine out where
are you
disaster relief what the heck's going on
here
where's my utensils
lorraine they're dirty and in the sink
what is it disaster recovery that's what
it was disaster recovery
barn all right we're gonna steam up this
broccoli we're going to steam up this
these carrots
can't medical medium do anything right
in the kitchen these days or what
so
all right let's talk about the guts of
it
let's talk about the guts we think
everything's in our guts too we think
it's all in our guts right
a lot is in our guts you better believe
it a lot is
but up here that's where we get gotten
okay we're saturday night live right now
so we're
it's great to have it saturday night so
it's exciting
we're live it's here keep that
keep that in mind right so i'm reading
the comments as we go
hello from new zealand honored you here
hello from finland
incredible seriously is i mean i'm blown
away
in amazing places so you know it's so
hey from carlsbad in california great
place too
so cool casey smith honored you here
catherine hey anthony thank you for all
you do so i can heal myself
can't depend on those hundreds of
doctors functional medicine
nutritionists
that have let me down for almost 30
years catherine i mean i get it
i really do there's so many people that
have gone through that journey and that
journey
you know you know what's crazy you guys
that journey's starting fresh for so
many people now
so many people now and you know what's
really sad they'll get
turned off by medical medium because
some
some troll or some paid for organization
puts a whole bunch of people on facebook
and instagram and everything because
that's how it works there's these
there's these organizations that pay
hundreds and hundreds of people to work
for them and their job is to sit at home
by the computer right
and they and they have and they'll have
medical medium on their list
and then these paid for people working
for these organizations
what it is is they sit there and they
try to find everything anything medical
medium
and they go and they try to discourage
people and they they make up stuff
they say stuff it's actually evil right
it's amazing and so someone's going to
get thwarted
and then they're going to have to go on
that 30 catherine they're going to have
to go on that 30-year journey because
they got thwarted
and they're going to be now they got
derailed so now they're going to go on
that 30-year journey
where celery juice nope it's bad for you
um
medical medium no he talks to ghosts um
you know and now i'm now they start
their journey there's so many people
that are starting their journey fresh
from the start and they're going to see
their next 30 years so they're 20 years
old or they're 25 years old they're
30 years old and they get told that
science has all the answers
it's science science has all the answers
and so they're just never going to break
from that and then they're just going to
be going on their journey but you know
what's funny
so many areas of medicine use medical
medium information that were originally
published from mm right
they use the info so tidbits are getting
into their protocols out there
and that's what's helping people who are
on that 30-year journey
they start to get a little bit better
because they're during a couple of the
you know protocols are incorporating in
like cats claw right
like the whole cat's claw thing it's
like no one touched cat's claw i mean
honestly
no one touched it i don't know if i can
find it no one even touched the cat's
claw right
it was it was one of those things where
i remember 35 years ago like no it's
cat's claw it's cat's claw and
that's going to be helpful for people
that are viral they got the cfs they got
the macfs they got the ra
they got the hashimoto's the
fibromyalgia whatever it is that's going
on
it's like the cat's lyme disease the
cat's claw for the lyme disease now
in the field of medicine they're using
cat's claw for lyme disease they're
still using antibiotics and other things
but they're like
we better bring in that cat's claw yeah
try not to make it look like the cat's
claw is really helping but we've got to
bring it in
here's your antibiotic like we've been
giving you for 40 years out there
here's your other stuff your your gut
health product
that we've been giving you for years and
uh here's the
cat's claw over here too we'll give you
some cats claw just don't tell anybody
the cat's claw's getting you better okay
janelle i haven't been able to eat
apples for the last 30 years
on day 11 of the of your 28 day cleanse
i can now eat them without my allergic
reactions
amazing oh my god incredible incredible
that that really is incredible it really
is so the cat's call is like one example
of medical medium information
that's the vimer g1 v is in victor i
victori.com i'm not sponsored but that's
the best cat's club that i've ever found
i use it for my friends and family just
so you know steaming up some broccoli
steaming up some carrots you guys
right there talking about food cravings
i got a bagel what looks like a bagel in
front of me
and some coffee some coffee
are you craving that coffee and bagel
and cream cheese
right diane says diane de campos says so
evil
it is it is um there's lots of that out
there
i tell you what blows me away when
there's people out there in the in the
spiritual scene and i'm not ranking on
them i'm not ranking on them
people in the spiritual scene that are
like there's no darkness out there no
way
there's no bad people out there it's not
how it works there's no bad people no
darkness out there
really uh tell that to the six million
jews that were gassed to death and
tortured and
all their gold teeth yanked out of their
mouth and god knows what else i mean
you know just no there's no darkness uh
there's no bad people out there
are you kidding just don't even say that
like don't even
how can you even say that um okay yeah
uh
aren't enough people murdered uh okay
yeah right like when like
every time a college student gets
murdered i mean there's no bad people
out there
no there's no bat no bad people out
there no no
whatever spiritual jive that is
that's just total malarkey nbs right
i'm talking about food cravings i
haven't hit there yet i haven't gotten
there yet
okay we're making the broccoli cheese
potatoes i'm steaming some broccoli you
guys see that
right broccoli steamed potatoes i got
some carrot in there too i got some
broccoli steaming it down
i got some steamed potatoes right here
austin what's up
my brother what's up why does anthony
have a bagel
laugh out loud austin good question
they're talking about food cravings
talking about intuition eating
intuitive eating we're talking about
moderation
a little bit of the moderation
yeah yeah sema what was that a million
native americans killed i got a friend
the same native american
tells me all the stuff about you know
things i don't even know
and that i didn't even know it's it's
unbelievable it's it's genocide
genocide because that's what they they
do on this planet it's like
it's like kill all the jews kill all the
native americans
um i mean it just it's even i mean it's
that
uh indigenous africans right in africa
just that's that's
genocide there's genocide going on out
there right
and genocide is real and it's been real
on this planet for a long time
right and that that's how it works it's
just you know but no there's no bad
people
whoa there's no bad people nope nope
whatever spiritual concept that is
that's just horrible um directory
uh i talk about the so lana turner says
which nonstick pan
are you using i got it on the directory
medicalmedium.com
checking the kitchen stuff in the
directory
you guys i'm excited you came on here
we're talking about food cravings
i'm gonna make sure it's fun and
interesting i'm gonna make sure it's
packed with info just steaming up some
stuff doing some comments here
i got my bagel and coffee in front of me
uh let's see let's see
ryan lowe you never talk about carrots
question mark question mark question
mark
dr sevi claimed carrots are me or
man-made
and not beneficial not saying they are
bad just confused
um well you know the whole i don't talk
about carrots too much
dr sebby where are you you're gonna have
it
where are you you're up there really
how long you been up there now you're
not in heaven
where are you oh my god
where which i'm not gonna talk about
that right now
you know i got everybody watching right
now we're live
uh-huh um hey
you know i think there's some confusion
about carrots
uh yeah yeah a lot of people are into
into your stuff yeah i know i know
i think you said celery was bad too
uh-huh
i think i think you said celery was bad
that people shouldn't be on celery yeah
yeah i i just want to tell you dr sebby
that was a terrible mistake
there's millions of people healing
around the world and for 35 plus years
with what i've seen i've seen celery
just save lives
anyway there's a carrot question on here
live dr sevi
archie savvy there's a carrot question
on here like
they're man-made are they bad is that
what it is
um you don't know you don't want to tell
them all right let me let me let me let
me fill
fill them in with some stuff some simply
simple healing
hey good i don't know where dr sebby is
i don't know where he is i'm not
he could be in heaven yeah i don't know
dr sebby we gotta take we gotta be
serious here
catherine king i just saw you on there
laughing okay i gotta go
um so god rest his soul
anyway uh michelle l good to see you
austin's laughing
look the whole thing with carrots is
this you don't hear me talk about
carrots a lot right
the carrot juice thing was never a great
idea okay it was never a great idea it's
first of all carrots are not man-made
carrots are not man-made man-made like
people think right they're not
unless you know you gotta understand the
difference between
gmo right and non-gmo you got to
understand the difference between
hybridization
okay and hybridization is a process that
we've been using we've been using um
you know the the whole thing is like
this it's it's
it depends on what you okay here's the
other thing all of our food
has been worked on in the sense
where we have crafted it along the
thousands and thousands of years you
always got to remember this
right you can't here's how food worked
originally
there's only so many there's there's
only so many foods you can consume
from the wild that you can eat enough of
keep this in mind all right because i'm
going to give you like a little bit more
info than just hey or carrots good or
bad are they man-made or not we got to
go we got to do better than that
and it comes down to this like wild food
is intense
really really intense and what we've had
to do
what mankind has had to do over these
thousands of years is we had to
we had to work our food that means when
you when an
apple tree grows right from a seed
okay right and those apples come out on
that tree
right those apples may not be so
agreeable
so you take the apple and then
you bite into it and you're like ah
that's a sour apple
that's a sour apple this is seven
thousand years ago
that's a that's a that's a sour apple
and then you see it's got a seed in it
right i'm gonna take that seed out let
me take the seed out of that apple
and i'm gonna plant that seed in the
ground and another tree comes up
and you wait years later right a few
years later some
five years later it's all of a sudden
you get all these flowers and now you
got apples again
and you're like let me try that apple
you bite it
oh my god that apples that apple's worse
that apple's worse
right let me let me open that apple up
and then take another seed out and then
you put the seed back in the ground and
you grow another tree
this is really important information
because there's so much confusion around
food
okay and now you got another tree and
then when that tree finally gives you
flowers
and you get an apple right you pluck
that apple
and now you bite it and you're like whoa
wait a minute
there was that one seed that was in that
apple
that last apple that grew this tree and
gave me an apple
that actually tastes pretty good but i
don't want to lose this
i don't want to lose this taste
you see i don't want to lose this taste
of this apple
so i got two options ready
where's lorraine tonight we got another
disaster recovery going on here
i think i just burnt my carrots and
broccoli turn it
just like in our comment um
so now we got two we got two options
and here they are we can now cut
cut a branch off that apple tree you
guys this is important
cut we can we can yeah we can cut the
branch off
and then in the spring before the leaves
come out on that
other apple tree that wasn't great
that tasted terrible we can now cut
that branch we can cut a little nook in
it
we can take the other branch from the
apple we like and then we can
graft that branch on yeah put a little
mud on it back then because 7 000 years
ago they didn't have grafting tape
or maybe a little piece of leather and
and all of a sudden now
the graft takes and now we got that
terrible apple tree that has an arm on
it now
of good apples you see how it works
okay that's not man-made
it's all natural baby all natural
right important to know okay
i think this is ready i'm gonna shut
this down a little bit
it's getting ready right okay so keep
that in mind
that's one option the other option is
the apple tastes good
right so let's get a seed from the apple
that tastes good
let's save all the seeds in the apple
that tastes good and let's plant
those seeds all of them and then all
these trees come up and now they throw
apples out and then you grab the apple
off each tree and you bite into and you
go up don't like that one
but it's pretty good oh bite that one
not bad oh this one's even better
and now that apple you hang on to those
seeds
and then you plant those seeds in the
ground and as time goes on
you get the most incredible apples and
that
is how we feed ourselves carrots
they grow in the wild there's wild
carrots in the wild
right but they are really hard to eat
there's wild onions in the wild there's
wild
chives there's wild all of it we have
we had to over the hundreds of years and
hundreds of years in order to consume
enough food
we had to pick the best that was to our
liking in every way right
we had to pick the best okay
we're going to cook this a little bit
more
put a little bit more water in there
okay here's how it works okay i'm
cooking
um i want the broccoli soft i'm steaming
the broccoli i want it soft
right i want the carrots to be soft i'm
going to use the carrots in the
sauce the cheese that's what i'm going
to do the broccoli
is going to go in the center of the
potato but we haven't even hit our
toppings yet of the night all right
people make a mistake with vegetables
they barely
cook them and then because the
vegetable's not raw anymore
it makes it harder to digest harder to
digest so
what happens is if you're somebody with
sensitive digestion and you want to
steam broccoli you
steam it soft so that fork goes right
through it right
so that fork goes right through it like
right through it you steam it soft so
that fork goes right through it
if you steam it lightly and it's still
crunchy
now it's going to be harder to digest or
you're going to
feel it rub things as it's going through
you of your sensitive digestion
annette why do you recommend cruciferous
vegetables
in your thyroid book they made me feel
worse so i stopped eating them
i thought you're not supposed to eat
them when you have a compromised letter
is it dr sebby no no it's not oh sorry
okay now uh yeah hello
yeah this is the head of the this is
head of the science research
alternative healing department right
here
we we told everybody
that don't eat cruciferous vegetables
because it interferes with the thyroid
because it's got gorgeogenic compounds
uh-huh yep were we wrong yeah
we were wrong a hundred percent
uh because we don't even know why
i'm the head of alternative medicine
right here yeah head of alternative
medicine
we don't even know why people even have
a thyroid problem
yeah you know right you know that yep we
don't know why people have a sick
thyroid
but we're gonna be experts on what
they're gonna eat
yep we're gonna be experts that's right
we're gonna scare them away from
cruciferous
uh-huh what people don't know is that
cruciferous helps their thyroid
uh-huh yeah and i'm i'm gonna hand this
over
let's hand it over to aw yep hanging up
so here's how it works with that
gorgeogenic compounds do not interfere
with the thyroid
um that's a theory theory
not proven no science behind it
theory okay keep that in mind number one
and that's a problem all on its own not
to mention
goitrogenic compounds they're in for in
foods there's anti-gorgogenic compounds
no one's talking about those
that's another thing all on its own it
would take barrels and barrels and
barrels of broccoli
to even consider the possibility of
possibly interfering and even then it
wouldn't
because of the anti-gorgogenic compounds
in cruciferous that's something to know
right there
um so i'm going to talk about also
another thing as well
so i'm just letting you know now if you
don't if you don't
feel good when you're eating broccoli or
cauliflower or anything keep in mind
if it's not steamed super soft it's
going to rub your inflamed areas
because if you're somebody already with
all these other conditions or even even
kind of digestion system issue or
bloating and that
it's it's steamed where it's lightly
steamed and hard really hard
it's going to be kind of still crunchy
and rubbing on everything and what i
like
for people who have sensitive systems is
to
have it you know have it soft right so
it's not rubbing so
it's not rubbing so keep that in mind
right so you guys um
but here's that's one thing right there
but there is there's a farce out there
about
uh about cruciferous they're gonna tell
you you can't do cruciferous because of
your thyroid
right stay away from kale collard greens
broccoli cauliflower
um you know and whatever else is in you
know cabbage
right so stay away from the cruciferous
family
that's what you're going to be told it's
it's misinformation it's painful
misinformation it's a really good
question um
that came up about it and yeah
malcolm why am i craving gluten so much
that's the only
no food i am craving for two years now
and really
have to have strong will to not give in
like this bagel that's got gluten in it
bacon cream cheese and that bagel's got
gluten in it right there right
um okay so why because gluten is feeding
a pathogen inside of you keep that in
mind
a bug a bug that lives inside of you and
that little buggy
loves gluten so let's do them little
demo here
demo depends on what bug i want to pick
we got the bacteria streptococcus eats
gluten
that right there can do it epstein-barr
sedimental virus
shingles they all eat gluten c diff
c diff eats gluten staph
eats gluten what else eats gluten um e
coli
loves gluten so everybody's got a
different range of bugs right they might
have different ranges of bacteria they
might have different kinds of bacteria
some people have more seed f
c diff then they do streptococcus some
people have more streptococcus than they
do e coli right
but that bacteria learns to feed off of
that gluten right
so that's what the bacteria does i got a
non-gluten-free cookie in my hand right
i get a bagel and cream cheese but i got
a piece of bread right so what happens
is that bacteria
loves that gluten so that bacteria
is thinking for you it can think
for you a little bit okay when it gets
hungry
it gets really hungry it's going to go
through withdrawal
when with when a pocket of bacteria goes
that's originally medical medium
information going back decades when it
goes through withdrawal
that's going to be a little bit of a
persuasion that's going to occur
a persuasion and because i'll tell you
why
some of these bacterias
come from places in our life
where there was an emotional connection
okay a relationship
right picking up the streptococcus from
somebody else
in a relationship right
this is now done
that alone can actually bring an
emotional component to it
that's just one thing we'll go into
other reasons too why it happens with
with
also gluten emotionally you might have
been hurt in your life betrayal
everybody this all pertains to all of us
betrayal trust breakage something could
have happened
right and guess what
we would since childhood we would eat
something like some pasta that had
gluten in it
some cheesy pasta right
some pizza some pizza right
pizza and we would eat something
and we would eat something for our
emotions
that gluten would stay in us too it
would sit inside our liver that's
another thing all on its own
these are just a couple of reasons right
here we're talking about cravings
that was a good question though it's
perfect because it gives us it gives us
stuff to talk about
right okay you guys this is done i'm
gonna get this on a dish for now
let me do that
you guys i love having you here in my
kitchen
is the camera over here yeah it is
amazing
[Music]
so i'm gonna get the broccoli out out of
here
kind of separate some stuff too i'm
gonna get some broccoli out of here you
guys
we've had already three or four disaster
recovers
linda what do you think about the
doctors and scientists now saying that
pathogens strep in ebv
are beneficial for our health crazy talk
crazy
yeah i had a re incorporated research in
science
medical board yep the medical board
you have the head of research and
science and medical board right here
we yeah let's just tell them
let's just tell everybody that it's
beneficial yeah
yeah do you think yep do you think
trigeminal neuralgia is beneficial for
somebody
oh that's right we're not supposed to
know that
shingles causes trigeminal neuralgia
that's medical medium information
that doctors are using now yeah those
dumb doctors we should tell our doctors
all our doctors
or our board board certified doctors not
to use medical medium information why
don't we try to
yeah let's see if we can booby-trap that
guy someday too right
what cause how many trolls can we pay
for to get on his
yeah yeah we we gotta figure something
we gotta we gotta throw that guy off a
little bit
okay yeah head of research and science
inc
let's see uh no medical board research
corporation here
yep um we need to just tell them it's
beneficial
is mono beneficial 103 temperature
out of out of college for two months
does that benefit the person
oh yeah it's beneficial uh yeah
epstein-barr is beneficial
it doesn't matter if the student lost
half a year
of uh of schooling it's beneficial
for god's sake see what else we can come
up with
it's actually demented to think it's
beneficial epstein-barr
can give someone a life of hell
a life of hell with chronic fatigue
where they lose their their they lose
their
their relationships their jobs their
careers
we call you call that beneficial what
about rheumatoid arthritis what about
now lyme disease because now they test
for epstein-barr with every lyme patient
right and what about that
um what about what about thyroid cancer
is that beneficial thyroid cancer having
to get your thyroid cut out
because that's epstein-barr okay right
talking about exactly what about
i could go on and on what about eczema
is x of mine a child beneficial
okay a child that's literally screaming
all night long and the parents
have to go to the emergency room again
two nights a week three nights a week at
the emergency room
steroid injections because of
epstein-barr is that beneficial
you know i gotta tell you something you
guys
there's one thing about the industry
it's so filled with stupidity i don't
even know what to call it
a lot of traps a lot of potholes a lot
of stupidity a lot of evil
a lot of everything right and
it's just so sad it's so sad it's it's
just
it's heart-wrenching really i mean
that's just just some stuff right
uh yeah lorraine just said ebv is so
good for people right so good for people
great hashimoto's thyroiditis after
delivering a baby that's epstein-barr
that's so good for mommy let's when
mommy have
hashimoto's thyroiditis let mommy get
all of a sudden hyperthyroidism
with hashimoto's thyroiditis all at the
same time because of epstein-barr
oh it's so good for her isn't it good
for her yeah
beneficial
you guys you guys there's
you ever notice this when people follow
that information out there
when they follow like misinformation
think about this
do you ever notice when people actually
follow
doctors or other people in the industry
that spew out that kind of
misinformation they follow them
do you think they lost all their common
sense
why would you even why would you even
do you think the doctors lost all their
common sense why would the doctor even
say that
why are you kidding these viruses have
put people through hell and back
leukemia leukemia
that's from epstein-barr virus and toxic
heavy metals combined
it's like the people who suffer and
suffer every day
and are you kidding oh it's beneficial
oh my god i didn't even know what to say
i didn't even know what to say you can't
even kid around
on any level with this did he finish the
info on carrots educating myself
probably not probably not
all right um so i'm doing right here you
guys
first of all i'm gonna make
some cheese sauce right
so i'm gonna do that okay i got potatoes
here but i gotta move the bagel
and coffee out of the way are you guys
okay if i do that for now i gotta move
the bagel and coffee out of the way
if you don't mind okay and um
so what i'm gonna do is let me make the
sauce first so i'm going to take a
potato
right and what i'm going to do is peel
the potato a little bit
yeah i'm going to take the skin off the
potato a little bit
all right on this one and i always keep
the skins on but i'm going to take the
skin off of this one right here because
i want a certain appeal
i want a certain color when i blend up
this potato okay
you guys i got some other potatoes
cooking i gotta take a look
okay these are done i got more potatoes
cooking over here i gotta get them off
the
cooker
what is going on today i have some more
more potato steaming over there and
[Music]
you know what it is you guys i just love
talking to you guys
and so i'm not paying attention to some
of the other things
good thing spirit of compassion reminds
me at least so i don't do any
real harm to the pan or burn something
really
bad so i get a little reminder okay i'm
gonna put this in here this is the
potato i'm gonna put in here so
i'm making the cheese as we speak
right and i'm going to put these carrot
pieces in here too
right you can do about a tablespoon of
chopped carrot i'm going to put a little
bit more
because i have more here and
so i'm going to put a little bit more in
here to put the carrot pieces these are
steamed soft because i'm making the
sauce
right that kind of blatant stupidity or
i don't know what it is negligence or
careless carelessness on
um ebv being uh beneficial or in the
virus as being
beneficial is really really difficult
you know for a lot i mean just when you
think about it because then
what's going to happen too is people are
going to also like
when they learn more and more about
epstein-barr they're going to want
epstein-barr because you'll be like well
it's beneficial i was told it's good to
have
and that's going to be ridiculous so
what i'm doing is i'm adding some spices
right here
a little bit of turmeric a quarter
teaspoon of turmeric
but put a little bit of that in right
and i'm going to do a little bit of
cayenne powder in here too right a
little touch of it quarter teaspoon of
cayenne mean
it depends on how spicy you want it but
that's what i'm going to say half a
teaspoon of garlic powder
put that in here
that one's a little dried up on the
bottom a little touch so i'm going to
actually open this up
and
shake it up some reason that actually
there we go get about a
half teaspoon of garlic in there that's
good garlic powder in there
and then two teaspoons of onion powder
right
guys this is fun we're in the kitchen
together we got a lot to talk about
two teaspoons of onion powder so i'm
gonna add a little bit more which we're
gonna get up to there
there we go okay
and we're gonna do one teaspoon of lemon
this is a very very juicy lemon so
that was nice right there okay we got
that i got to get the epstein bar
off the off the table here for a little
bit we're going to add a little bit of
water
okay a little touch of water and we're
gonna try to blend this up
give it a little quick blend food
processor works too really good for this
i'm gonna make the cheese sauce
without cheese
which is very important
if you want to stay if you want to stay
sick
if you want to stay sick make sure you
eat a lot of cheese
but i don't think you guys want to stay
sick right but you're going to crave
cheese because we're talking about food
cravings
you're gonna crave cheese
this is coming out really good it's
starting to mix a little bit
i don't want it too wet so i'm not
putting i'm not putting water in here
too much water but i might add a little
bit more water is what it might do
all right actually it's definitely
cheesy
no question there i'm gonna add a little
touch more lemon
juice might not have put enough of that
in there too
so we're blending it up blending this up
night at night diane night i saw that
you're throwing away all your cheese
as soon as possible
this recipe is posted on facebook and
instagram already
all right we got the cheese sauce here
nice
nice really good this is coming out
great you guys
this is coming out great i'm to cut this
potato in half
uh michelle i saw that canola oil is
awful yes
terrible terrible let's cut a nice
potato right here
we'll cut it in half we're going to
plate this right
let's get another plate
right and i'm going to do
two
[Music]
use one of these
let's get another one here
i'm gonna do two potatoes okay
all right they're gonna open the second
one up right gonna put the broccoli
pieces
little broccoli pieces in here check
this out you guys
by the way we're live on youtube and
we're live on facebook
i like to do it live because you know
it's just it's an awesome experience to
be with you guys
here in the kitchen right instead of a
studio
version pre-recorded studio version
right
i'd rather do it this way
i mean unless you guys don't like the
live stuff
and you want to do you know pre-recorded
studio and all that i'm not sure if you
guys
would rather have it that way
but i like it this way so i'm putting
some broccoli pieces in here i'm making
it look nice
right doing a little bit more broccoli
pieces
okay there we go a little bit more here
a little bit more here look at that
that's just really nice i don't know
i'll show you guys in a second what it
looks like
let's see if we can get some cheese
sauce trisha maria see ya
so i'm gonna put a little bit on here
right cheese sauce on here
i'm gonna devour these
i'm gonna devour them after we we're
done
here that's what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna tank them is what i'm gonna do
i'm gonna tank these
how much cheese do you guys like like
how much cheese sauce do you like right
do you guys like a lot i like a little
bit more
so i'm being a little bit more generous
on this cheese sauce
wow that is so good that's insane
okay and
so that's two potatoes right there okay
and i got the broccoli inside the potato
you guys checking that out
you just ate and that's making you
hungry incredible
no radical fats think about it there's
no fat in here just think about that for
a second right
now what i love about this dish right
here right look at that
look at that cheese sauce it's
incredible by the way this this tastes
delicious by the way
got the broccoli in there and then the
potato um
you can bake your potato and do this i
like the steam and i think it's better
for you also to steam it right michelle
cavanaugh doesn't this
doesn't this look yummy darcy lee right
it looks amazing
right good to see darcy lee i mean and
but i'm i'm pumped about this because
i'm going to be tanking this
after we're done between you know going
to uh instagram and stuff
right after here when i go to instagram
i'm going to be tanking this but we
still got a couple more minutes we're
still going to talk about stuff so
stay with me if you can unless you're
busy
if you're busy you can't stay with me
then i totally understand you guys
okay so let me bring out the
bagel and coffee
now i got a little broccoli on the side
of that bagel it flew out of the pan on
there
all right so don't worry about that
lorraine more disaster recovery tonight
than ever before
all right great job cooking susan i'm
honored
can't believe it can't believe you think
so you missed how the cheese sauce was
made
shonda it was it was i threw a potato in
there but i skimmed the potato right a
steamed potato okay
i threw in some garlic powder onion
powder turmeric in there right the
recipes on facebook
uh posted on facebook and instagram
right i diced up some
some steamed carrot i put in there too
with it to give it that color
blended it up put it on there okay let's
talk about cravings what are you guys
craving
i want to know can you guys tell me what
you're craving like what's the bad stuff
you're craving is it pizza is it mac and
cheese
is it ice cream what are you guys
craving give me the rundown
i'd love to know tara appleman good to
see you
uh honored you're here blown away you're
such an amazing amazing amazing human
being
um what do you guys lately bread
iris you're you're craving bread really
chocolate
sonia you're craving chocolate well yeah
you're gonna crave chocolate cause the
caffeine
the caffeine is gonna make you go back
for chocolate though that craving
is going to be a little different coffee
chocolate
tea matcha tea craving that craving is
going to be a little different because
that's the caffeine
addiction part right at the craving but
it's still craving i get it
pizza i see epf pizza salmon
fatuma salmon
crave dates wait a minute who craves
dates dates
that's a great craving potato chips
jamilla potato chips triple moon goddess
pizza
yeah leafy greens catherine leafy greens
leafy greens you're craving leafy greens
catherine king it's amazing tina craving
chocolate that's the
that's the caffeine crave right there
that i see a lot of pizza man
i see a lot of pizza you know you said i
see a lot of pizza
dove eyes salt craving salt
interesting yep yep
cheese popcorn maria just kind of
curious i want to see what you guys are
craving so i'm just
i'm just just trying to see a few other
things whoa
cheese popcorn right chocolate again
pizza and cookies
it's pizza and cookies man oh pizza and
cookies
huh you guys craving pizza huh
well i always say i'm at your service
so i'm at your service pizza
it is i see the pizza rain supreme
till this day the pizza rain supreme
i see more pizzas
i see more pizzas than
so many other things right the pizza
takes
over pizza wins wins all the time it
always wins
butter wait shaolin
butter should be craving pizza that's
the winner side
no no the winners the winners are all
they're
they're craving pizza no
ice cream i see that but i see a lot of
pizza cravings
i do see a lot of that
mac and cheese mac and cheese let's talk
about chocolate for a couple seconds all
right let me just kind of get rid of
this pizza for now
all right you guys um gotta watch out
that pizza
so uh deborah pizza deborah grace
yeah pasta i'm italiano
sharon you're italian
um yeah pizza and lasagna tara
lasagna anyway you guys okay talk about
the little bit
the chocolate craving right that
everybody has
that's from the caffeine side of it
right
that's from this caffeine side of it
it's a big part of it probably the
biggest part of it actually
that's the that's the coffee craving
chocolate craving matcha tea craving
right green tea craving
that's what that is so important to know
um yeah so
so what happens is when we go through
life a couple of things
one thing is we get emotionally wounded
we the betrayal occurs right
you know the betrayal the disappointment
all of that occurs and i think the
phone's ringing you know and
so we go through life we get
hurt and
okay hello
hey hi yeah
did you have a good week yeah why are
you acting so different
why why are you talking to me that way
huh what do you mean
we're done what do you mean
we're done what are you saying we've
been dating for a year
what do you mean i thought it was
working out
you can't do this anymore that
i don't even know what to say what do
you mean he can't do this anymore
you gotta go wait a minute what what
about
it's happened a lot that's just one one
version right there
i mean there's hundreds right there's
hundreds you know
there's friends there's relationships
there's family members there's siblings
there's
work relationships career relationships
business relationships and we we get we
get knocked around
in this world right from childhood
on from elementary school being wounded
there
and and the food it's like the food hits
where
this is comforting me you know this is
comforting me this is comforting me i
have to have this food
and that's one reason why we get the
cravings because then we go through life
ashley kevin it's painful and hard
totally
yeah i'm i'm sorry if you've even gone
through that right
and so it life is hard right
and then what happens is when we get
that bad news
when we get that bad news it's like i
just checking out my text right here
just checking them out here huh that's
that's the most terrible thing
somebody's ever said what is this
and what happens is hey you're my best
friend why would you do this
what happens is the the adrenals kick in
the adrenaline fight or fight i gotta
i gotta i gotta fight i gotta fight
or i gotta fly it's fight or flight it's
like
i gotta fight i'm in the game and i
gotta fight
whoa whoa i gotta fight i'm gonna i'm
gonna go for that fight
or it's flight i gotta get out of here
this is horrible
i gotta fly i gotta fly and the yellow
shirt doesn't really help the situation
actually i'm thinking about it the whole
yellow shirt probably doesn't help as
i'm flying
canary and you know what what happens is
that
or the toucan or something like you know
there's what happens is that
it's fight or flight when we go through
something right
and that fight or flight that adrenaline
surging
and that adrenaline scorches man
scorches and in that adrenaline
is information of that wound
instantly instantly that adrenaline
that's being released
from that breakup that hardship that
forgiveness that means
meaning that like trust breakage no
forgiveness in the moment
no resolve there's
the resolve's not even there you can't
even get resolved right
right that's when we're now praying to
god we're like god
i don't know why this happened to me but
i need your help
angels i need your help get down here
right we get that broken heart
we get that broken heart right and
what happens is we're hurt and
that adrenaline is surging through us
that adrenaline is
is information of our hurt
it's gathering information the adrenals
release an adrenaline blend that's
that has information of hardship and
hurt in it right
rejection julie rejection it's terrible
rejections terrible
elizabeth shavaria
um good to see you here in we uh we
we go through this and this hurt and our
adrenaline
is saturating every cell in our body and
we go for a food we go for a food
that that that well a couple of things
that happen
right away we can go for a food like i
got to eat this whole pizza right now
because i need to sop up this adrenaline
or i when i was hurt when i was eight
years old
i my mom made you know pasta
with cheese and i need to i need to go
back to that pasta and cheese
because i've been hurt right right you
guys
so true marissa and that's part of it
right there
that's part of it okay and then
something else could happen
right we stop eating we stop eating
boom i'm so sick to my stomach
i've been hurt so bad i can't eat for
days
when i even look at food i want to throw
up
when i even think about food my stomach
hurts
i'm in agony i'm in the mental agony
emotional agony
and i can't touch food but as that time
goes on
you lose all this glucose and mineral
salts to your brain
even if your diet was a poor diet it
still gave you some glucose to the brain
some mineral salts of the brain even
know if it wasn't even the best
but then as time goes on you start
losing that glucose
and then the flip side happens it flip
it gets reversed
boom you're now on the other end of it
and you're eating everything
and you're just you're you're just
you're having your bagels and cream
cheese
you're having your pasta cheese you're
having your mac and cheese you're eating
your ice cream you're still
sick over your hurt and hardship
but you're still you're still
you're still hurt but now you're eating
right and then the emotional wave comes
in again and now you're not eating
because you're you're hurt and it's
hitting you over again ptsd starts
happening
and it's this up and down rollercoaster
ride for a lot of people maybe a lot of
you guys have been through this right
and now we're we're like back and forth
from eating bad
to not eating at all eating bad to not
eating at all eating for comfort to not
eating at all
right this could happen when you're
eight nine ten years old five years old
this could happen when you're 20 years
old this could happen when you're 30
years old could happen now
but the pattern set in place and that
adrenaline
sits inside of us from those hardships
you have that breakup you have that
hardship
that adrenaline sits inside of you deep
in your tissue
from 10 years ago from 20 years ago from
eight years old from 10 years old
from when you were 10 or 8 or 12 years
old that adrenaline from
fight or flight when you got that
betrayal that trust that promise broke
whatever it was what happens is or when
you're in your 20s whatever that
injury was right that adrenaline sits
in your cells of your liver it sits down
in there in your liver that's where the
adrenaline sits in there
sits in the liver and it sits in cells
in your
pancreas your spleen especially your
liver and
when you start eating healthy someday
because you're getting
sick and now you've got to eat healthy
someday right
and well i'm going to try medical medium
or i'm going to try this other diet
and the diet takes away the bagels and
cream cheese the diet takes away
the pizza it takes away these things
right
it takes away all this stuff all of a
sudden
those emotions are going to come out
because that adrenaline
is going to start coming out of old
adrenaline
with information of when you were hurt
it's going to start
leaching out of the of the liver and
when it does
you're going to be like oh my god i
think i'm really i need this food right
now
i need i need this bad food i need that
that bagel i need something
and you're gonna be like maybe that's my
intuition maybe that's my
maybe i'm craving it because my body
needs it now we're going to be thrown
and confused
but really old adrenaline and old
hurt surfacing and then there's the
emotional wounds
right here the soul that's a whole
nother thing it's not even the physical
part i'm talking about next right that's
the physical part i just told it talked
about
you got injured right your adrenaline
surged
right you did all the emotional eating
right then the old wounds
ptsd that can last for 20 years 15 years
10 years 2 years
40 years the old wounds in the soul
in the soul and if you guys don't have
this book
this is the new edition i can't tell you
how critical this is for the soul this
book right here
this new edition i mean if you guys
don't have it you guys should be
trying to get the book i mean get a free
of the library if you don't have any
money right and you can't get it from
barnes nobles or amazon.com has a
discount i saw
if you can't get the book then get it
the library but this has that soul
information
and so does cleanse the heel too about
cravings and everything right and all of
it but the point i'm trying to say
is when our soul gets fractured and
injured right
that's the next piece of it you know
soul memories
soul injury to the emotional center of
our brain and that's what happens too
you get hurt right
and then the emotional center of the
brain is gonna get calloused
you get hurt your brain heats up
electricity
hot wires in the brain every time
someone
betrays you or something happens
emotionally
your brain heats up like heats up
hot and that heat fires and fires and if
you're not eating enough glucose and not
enough mineral salts
and all that that adrenaline can fight
literally scorch the brain
every time someone hurts you and when
you go too long without food like all
the intermittent fasting people do and
then they run into a crisis emotional
crisis
they don't got enough glucose for for
their brain to cool it down
because the glucose cools the brain down
and in the emotional center of the brain
you can have an injury
right there in the emotional center of
the brain physically but your soul can
get
hurt too soul wounds medical medium
information has always
been about always been about healing
both of them it's why
i have the meditations at medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast
the brain meditation the moon meditation
right
medical media podcast at apple podcast
you guys know the moon meditation the
brain meditation the star gazing
meditation right
fruit picking meditation that's there to
heal
the soul wound right from all our
injuries and all of our old
wounds fractures everything we've had
soul-wise that makes us crave
food too the soul injuries that makes us
crave food okay and
that's why those meditations are there
and that's what's in the book
the new edition golden heart brilliant
my dad has bad r a he says potatoes make
him sick
and joints soar a question bar
well aren't his joints sore anyway
periodically
without potatoes in his diet or all of
his re goes away and then he eats a
potato and the ra's back
so be your have him be his own detective
okay and is he eating his potatoes with
sour cream cheese does he remember
eating them with cheese sour cream
butter and oil
because potatoes help ra that's what
helps ra because the epstein-barr virus
causes ra and potatoes are antiviral
see so are the potatoes eaten eat
are they eaten with real cheese not this
beautiful
you know cheese sauce that we made here
is it with
real bovine cheese bovine cheese
makes the uh the problem
worse with ra right and then potatoes
right they they can't be dressed up with
all that cheese and butter and
everything else you can check out the
potato podcast medical meeting podcast
hey i just saw that yes
medical media podcast the potato episode
right
yeah so anyway this is a big all what
i'm talking about is the whole cravings
aspect
giving you different different pieces of
it that are so
important of how it works you know i
want you guys to be able to heal
anyway invite the light good to see you
you just came on we're going to ig
right now instagram and tick tock
fasten your seat belts for that ride
because after that we're going to 369
cleanse
on ig and we're still going to be on
tick tock too but
fasten your seat belts for today i've
had a little
too much wild blueberry juice
all right you guys i love you heading
over to ig
and instagram in about i don't know 10
minutes i just got to straighten up a
little bit
and get this ready again i love you guys
take care