protecting ourselves
lots to do
so as you can see here this is what i'm
doing for friends and family this is
what i'm doing for myself
i got it all sitting here and there's a
reason for this like what is this we got
the oranges over here because oranges
are really good you got the vitamin c
right that's something right there plus
hydration which is incredible right
cranberries in case i want to make some
cranberry water i got some ginger over
here for reason too right the ginger tea
time look at all this beautiful time
you know why everybody knows why for the
time right
and
and i got some supplementation here
all the
system builders right
all those right all the bleep system
builders right you guys so that's what
this is it's the bleach system builders
and it's all here right good to see you
guys right now here we're live
and
i just wanted to let everybody know you
know i mentioned it about what seven
eight months ago maybe 10 months ago i
would always mention it saying in the
fall and winter we're gonna need to keep
our system strong
right
so i talked about that all through good
to see everybody coming on i talked
about that all
through the summer all through the
summer i said wait till you guys see
you're going to want to have you're
going to want to be prepared you're
going to want to have your
you know your zinc shock therapy ready
you're going to want to have your
micro sea ready you're going to want to
have your at least your ginger and your
thyme water ready and your ginger tea
whatever it is you want to be prepared
you want to keep your system strong
is what you want to do trisha marie says
you sure did
and now we're heading into a place we're
going into the winter everybody's
systems need to be
protected and strong
is what needs to happen so everybody's
systems need to be protected and strong
you'll see i keep on saying systems
right exactly you guys know what i'm
talking about right you know what system
i'm talking about
so as we're going in there you see
people coughing you'll see friends
coughing you'll see people with the
runny noses the sniffles you see people
with all the cold stuff right
all going on wherever you are around the
world right now it's like oh that
person's not feeling good well that
person's not feeling good that person's
coming down with something that person's
coming down with something so how can we
protect ourselves
and how can we protect our own systems
so i just wanted to do a little reminder
i've said it was coming i said there's
been a lot of people
not feeling good
and that's where we're going to be
heading into a wave of that i talked
about this months and months ago you
guys you guys know
i saw it coming not because i'm smart or
anything like that it's only because of
my source right
uh spirit of compassion was telling me
that it was coming in the late fall in
the winter and that's what i was saying
to everybody so what do we do like what
do we do like what do we do to look out
for ourselves so if you can't get
supplements right can't get the right
supplementation
then there's other things you can do so
i do i do everything it's what i like to
do so
i like to have a supplementation going
on which i'll talk about some of the
best system builders
so that right and i also like having
like the time water and the time tea
going on i even like to do aloe right
here i know you can't see that probably
but i even like doing the aloe too so
that's another thing all on its own
every single day that's an immune
helper right there okay you've got the
outlook got the yellow right so that's
one
so let's make a couple of things let's
do a few things what do i do give me a
thumbs up if you can
um
if that's if that's something you guys
can do thumbs up or whatever it is a
like or whatever however it works
if you like the show today we're talking
about building up your system love you
anthony mm save my life i'm honored to
hear truly okay hit thumbs up or hit the
follow button
turn on your bell notifications turn
those on into you guys okay
and i know it's a crazy time right now
we got the holidays coming on right
there's a lot going on but i can't help
but to
let you guys know or give a reminder to
what you can do to help
to help your systems
stay strong
because that's important right there
okay so it really is let's go
let's get talking let's get let's get
into this now so what i'm doing every
single day right now is i'm taking
that right there
and the zinc right you guys see it every
single day i'm taking it that's what i'm
doing i'm having every friend
every family member every loved one i'm
having them do the zinc right now i'm
like make sure you do two dropper holes
in the morning you do two dropper holes
later on in the day or at night
since i'm telling family right now so
just two dropper holes twice a day you
could be somebody you can do six tiny
drops and then
because i'm seeing it out there too
i got people contacting me like oh my
god
i don't feel good what is this
is it a cold
and they're just like that i'm like look
you got to do the the zinc shock therapy
i do the medical medium zing shock
therapy
okay and that's important right there
you two dropper fools every three hours
you can do that two dropper holes every
three hours zing shock therapy
and so that's what i'm telling friends
and family i'm hearing it out there all
over the place everybody's running
themselves down this is the time of year
people run themselves down greatly and
then you got the critters going around
and everybody's got the critters going
around so that's something you know that
we have to look out for
you're doing zinc every day clara
amazing that's so good so what i'm doing
right here is the zinc so i'm going to
just start setting myself up with a shot
all right
so
i'm putting two dropper holes
in that shot glass right there
so i got two dropper holes in there okay
and then i'm doing some cats claw you
ask your doctor what's right for you
well this is the vimergy brand
so it's v as in victor i am as in marye
rgy.com i'm not sponsored
i'm not sponsored quality matters
it matters it's just the brand i love
and i know these guys you know become
good friends with them throughout the
years because of what they've done and i
reach out to all the supplement
companies and all the different
companies out there and i try to become
friends with them so then
then they can respect what i'm asking
them to like make sure that the stuff
stays clean to make sure the quality is
there to make sure they don't cut
corners to make sure there's no citric
acid to make sure there's no fillers in
there to make sure there's nothing bad
in there
and so what i love about the vimergy
company is they went above that they've
even superseded anything i've ever asked
anything i've ever questioned they
superseded
way above
and they're just like no we we we're
going to take it to a level no one's
ever seen before in our history of the
supplement world so that's why i use
those henna says yes quality matters
remedy supplements are the purest
so cat's claw is what i do too
that's one right there i just do a
little cat's claw i just put a dropper
full there but you know what a friend
reached out like i'm really sick right
now and i'm i'm just choking on mucus
and i'm just coughing my throat's
running my throat sore and i'm starting
to feel it in the chest and i'm like do
you have the cat's claw and i know let
me order it
and so you know and then i do make sure
you're doing like three dropper fulls of
that stuff make sure that's happening i
just put a dropper full in there i'm
making myself a little
a little one a builder system builder so
that right there is the olive leaf
so vimergy put out this incredible olive
leaf that just
just
goes over anything i've ever seen out
there in the olive leaf world so that's
what's incredible about this one and
that one i'm really excited about
because i've been able to offer friends
and family something else that's really
potent for what we're dealing with right
now so what we're dealing with right now
so anyway the olive leaf
incredible stuff right there i'm going
to do a couple things so i'm going to
make some time water
i'm going to cut open some aloe i might
squeeze some lemons i got some oranges
over here i'm going to do the medical
medium vitamin c shock therapy too so
i'm going to do some olive leaf right
there putting two dropper fulls in there
if you guys don't know vimergy it's
vimergy i'm not sponsored it's just the
stuff is that good
and you'll see i'm always talking about
vimergy uh mostly lately in the
supplement world because what happens is
with supplement companies they're all
trying to cut corners
and ever since the whole thing that
happened right the whole thing that
happened in the last couple years with
what we're dealing with
um it's it the supplement companies out
there because i've been talking to a lot
of them just doing like some balance and
check with them like are you keeping out
the natural flavors are you keeping out
the citric acid to these other companies
and they're like look aw we can't be
perfect
you wouldn't believe i was
i can't say the name of the supplement
company
but i had a meeting with a supplement
company last week right and it was to be
like look you guys i can show your stuff
because they asked they asked me to show
their stuff
if you take out this and this and this
you can't have the citric acid in there
you can't have the natural flavors in
there and this is what this is what the
ceo said to me the ceo said this to me
look anthony that's what he said to me
we can't be perfect we have good quality
stuff but we can't be perfect i said
but you said it
that's fine with me then
uh see you later they're like where are
you going i go i gotta get off this
phone call they're like where are you
going we waited a long time to talk to
you i'm like you just said you can't be
perfect if i'm going to be recommending
something to my people it's got to be as
good as bimergy
it has to be as good it has to they're
like we can't be perfect you don't
understand the bottom line we can't
afford this or can't afford that i'm
like
i get it i get it you don't want to rise
up to that occasion
anyway so the vimergy stuff is why i've
been showing it so much because of these
are some of the reasons that's the
licorice i'm gonna put some licorice in
what i love about the licorice is
it's so good
it's so good for you for so many reasons
um i'm actually running low on that one
i can't believe how low actually on that
one but yeah i just love licorice
shamima says thank you aw you are our
living prophet for sure
i have all the vimrji sups in canada and
bought the mm-900 juicer on sale cool
you got it on sale thank god
hands down it's the best juicer out
there been juicing for 30 years oh my
god that's been your experience if
you're juicing for 30 years
what like 30 years is what like 19
91 i mean that's unbelievable
that's incredible you're juicing that
long that's amazing um
jenny says kindly what is olive leaf for
okay
anti-critter
you guys notice i'm saying critter
anti-critter i just don't
i want to make sure
we can stay on
this is what i want to make sure so i'm
saying anti-critter anti-bug
right so that's what it is anti
anti
anti that
that's what olive leaves for
oh okay let's keep on going here
i said it wasn't gonna fool around today
i said i was gonna take things serious
i just can't stay serious for long
enough i can't how you guys doing on
tick tock we're on telegram right now
live in rumble
we're live on youtube right terry
appleman good to see you
courtney m a all right you guys
so what else do we got going we talking
about this thing so that's the lemon
balm right there what's incredible
that's lemon lemon balm
is the potency
so it's ten to one right
highly potent so all all the people i
know out there that reach out to me and
they're like i got really crazy anxiety
my anxiety is out of control i'm like do
you have the ten to one
just keep that with you right there and
just you just pull that out
boom
shoot some of that in
that ten to one
that that stuff
that's potent like
the thing is with the ten to one lemon
balm when it's a quality like this
is that when you send it down
you don't need
pot you don't need pot
people who are possible i'm not a pot
smoker
but people are pot smokers
like
send down the ten to one
and you're not gonna need pot
just give it some time
everybody who's like addicted to
marijuana and everybody's addicted to
marijuana out there because it's a big
people just smoking it left and right
right
they even kept at the same price so if
energy kept the same price right
companies would never do that companies
don't make the ten to one
so because when i was talking to the ceo
of this other supplement company that
was reaching out to me
and and and i said can you do any ten to
one or like no no way in hell we can
never do that
we could never do that we'd have to
charge a billion dollars for it i'm like
you guys are just so lame anyway they
kept it the same price but it's ten to
one
but i know everybody's smoking marijuana
these days because i know i hear about
it 24 7 out there right
and i'm like try a ten to one lemon balm
for the nervous system and brain for the
central nervous system for the brain
stem and then you might be able to
actually give up your pot addiction
you might be able to give up your pot
addiction we're talking about building
up our system because of everything
happening right now so i got to stay on
track talking about pot right now might
not be the
most productive thing
so let's let's let's talk about the
vitamin c
that's the microc
so
i wasn't going to do a live for a while
because i got a lot going on
but i'm getting phone calls
and texts
left and right people i haven't talked
to in years that are coming down with
the critter
right now they're coming down with a
case of the critters they got the chills
they don't feel good they got the
temperature they're coughing they got
the sniffles they got all that so
they're coming down with a case of the
critters and
and so that's why and i know that a lot
of people are up against that right now
with the holiday and everything so i
just wanted to cover just a couple
little things about it
so we got the the micro c so we do two
this is vitamin c shock therapy you guys
medical medium vitamin c shock therapy
let me move stuff over
right
we can do that right in here
so i'm going to open up two capsules
right
do this every two hours
every waking two hours you got something
happening you're coming down with
something
you're coming down the case of the
critters
do the microc two capsules every two
hours that's what i would do do what
your doctor tells you i'm just telling
you what i recommend family and friends
so what i just put in there with two
capsules of the microc
it's of emerging microc easiest stuff on
the stomach and the most potent
right
cheryl says aw what is the reason you
take the tinctures separately
well what it is here is the tinctures i
drop the tinctures in here
and i do a shot that's what i do i do a
shot of tinctures i put a little bit of
water in there so that's that's that's
what happens there right i put a little
bit of water in here
and i do
a shot with the tinctures okay
vitamin c shock therapy
is going to be
something a little different right
that's the medical mean vitamin c shock
therapy i do in here so we'll get a
little bit of hot water going so i'm
going to turn on the t petal for a
second
and we'll get some hot water going
all right and we're making the vitamin c
shock therapy if you guys just came on
here we're talking about
building
your system
for what's happening right now and just
a reminder you guys i hate bugging you i
i hate bugging you but
sign up for my newsletter if you get a
chance so you know what's going on you
go to medicalmedium.com after this you
sign up for my newsletter
because in january
we're doing
a medical medium morning cleanse
challenge in january
early january the medical media morning
cleanse challenge just letting you know
sign up to the newsletter so you know
when that is the whole bit the link is
in profile for my newsletter
link is in the description for my
newsletter sign up to the medical media
newsletter so you know what the medical
media morning cleanse challenge is
coming up it's coming up in early
january and we're going to have a blast
we're going to have a blast if you're
somebody new to all of that new new to
the cleanse challenges do you think
anybody's going to be in the mood to do
a clench challenge come early january
i hope so i hope so make sure you got a
copy of cleanse the heel get it free
from the library or get into amazon.com
us right 51 off but make sure you have
this book for early january so we can do
the medical meeting morning cleanse
challenge together sign up to the
newsletter too you guys i'm psyched
about it really honestly i'm really
psyched about it i'm just going to be
straight up about that really psyched
so i got some really hot water
right here
you don't have to use hot water i'm
supposed to use hot water in this one
okay
so we're gonna use
we're gonna use another glass
see what happens when we got too much
going on
so we got the vitamin c going in
you know what i love about being live
so you don't know what's gonna happen
cheryl aw is it okay to take the
tincture amounts all at one time as
opposed to twice a day is it less
effective you could take it all at one
time
cheryl ask also ask your doctor what's
right for you if it was me cheryl
right i like doing twice a day but if
you can't do twice a day i've always
said to people i've always said to
family i've always said to friends you
can do it once a day
you can all right and and here's the
thing about that question right there
that question i think is in here too
like the answer is in here too under
protocols supplements questions and
protocols and cleanse the heal but but
i'm glad you asked
pomegranates that's what these are
crackle and open have some pomegranates
they're good for your immune system so
we're making the vitamin c shock therapy
we got the two capsules right there i'm
gonna put a little bit of honey in here
too
some honey
i'm gonna crack open an orange
let's do that
we're gonna squeeze an orange in here
there you go
that's the vitamin c
shock therapy right there
gonna mix it
up every two hours
every
two waking hours do not wake yourself up
in the middle of the night
to take it if you're sleeping when
you're sick that's a great thing
because right now everybody's coughing
their guts out everybody's got the mucus
training into their chest they can't
sleep
they're just coughing coughing all
through the night and if yeah if you're
up and you're not sleeping sure you can
do another round
two capsules
every two hours
every waking hours
right of the medical medium and vitamin
c shock therapy
yeah
so that's important right there
you guys saw i put the honey in there
right mixed it up got the honey in there
i got the orange in there and i got the
vitamin c capsules in there too
lifesaver thank you anthony incredible
you must be doing this one you can also
use maple syrup if you don't want to use
honey because a lot of people don't use
honey you can also use maple syrup and
that's all right too okay
it is do you have any help for those who
have joint pain fibromyalgia
shia
check out the book get it free at the
library if you can okay it's 16.99 at
amazon.com us but you can get it free at
the library so if you don't have the 16
or anything like that and a lot of
people are on a really tight budget
go to the library try to get that book
out there for free
and check it out okay you can read all
about the fibro read all about like what
to do for it all of that including like
how to take little gentle steps to it
baby steps
the information's there you can just
go to the library for that for sure no
problem all right so talk about other
stuff for the immune system here's an
incredible an incredible product right
here
this is a system builder
and this is the elderberry syrup now you
might be like well i've heard of
elaborate syrup before i've seen it you
can get elderberry syrup in the store
you can't get this elderberry syrup
this is from
freshly
juiced elderberries
this is from juiced elderberries
all elderberry syrups
are
they're dried
and then boiled
so there's a big difference right there
so this is the vimergio library syrup
the other difference in the elderberry
syrup here it's got mulberry extract
so it's got a highly
medicinal charge to it with that
mulberry tree
mulberries from the big mulberry trees
put into here too so it's got the
mulberry extra extract
in with the elderberry that's juiced
with vitamin c
and there's nothing out there like it so
this is basically
what i love about like the vimergy
elderberry syrup and it's got the micro
seen it what i love about the vimergy
elderberry syrup is
they're like
the forefront
everybody's talking a good game out
there like do this do this because of
what's going on out there do this
because of all the you know the what
people are up against it's like really
no these guys are like
all the way on the forefront leading the
way
companies can't touch them they can't
touch them like they couldn't even do
this
it wouldn't be possible for them to
create this product companies could
never do it
they would have to charge a billion
dollars i'm just exaggerating for that
but they have to charge
so much
and they couldn't do it anyway they
wouldn't have that they wouldn't have
the connections or the technology so
there's no cane sugar in here
so that's important to know
so this is
literally a forefront product to build a
system that no one has ever
seen before
and if they didn't do that i wouldn't be
sitting here talking about it but it's
they're just they're creating things
that i can't help but to talk about
because it's like that it's off the
chart so when you're talking about
mulberry extract
and then
juiced elderberry
honey instead of cane syrup
a cane sugar honey instead of cane sugar
and then micro c
all in an elderberry syrup
you can't there's like you can't touch
that
you can do one tablespoon of this stuff
you can do
two tablespoons of this stuff you can do
a day i'm telling if you're sick i mean
i would be like a tablespoon three times
a day if you're sick i mean that's what
i would do if i was sick and i was
coughing and i would had a sore throat i
mean immune was down low low low low low
but definitely so it's just
no one can touch this product
i'm just letting you guys know and
that's the vimergy all the berries syrup
and
i always i always say it's like
basically the bottom line when it comes
down to it i'm like
how do you battle darkness right and
darkness is
what creates all the sickness out there
that's what darkness does right well how
do you battle it you need companies that
are light workers
and that's the thing out there they're
not just in it for profit and it's just
profit alone right you need companies
that are light workers that say well we
can battle
that darkness by doing something the
darkness did not expect
the darkness did not expect
like weapons like this
so darkness creates
what you see out there happening right
with all the games and all the different
critters
that everybody's up against everybody
coughing and sick
darkness purposely creates all that
to keep people down
to break them down
to torture them
and then you need like you need
light
with technology right so you need
companies that actually want to work for
the light
right you need companies that want to
work for god
companies that want to work for jesus
christ companies that want to work for
the light companies want to work for
they want to work for you know
the light of the universe right but the
point is is
that's how you battle darkness is you
create things that darkness never
expected
or never saw coming and that's what the
library so when i talk about when i talk
to a friend about it
i'll be like you will not see anything
like this
and this is to kind of upgrade for what
the darkness does so
to you know important things when you
think about it
really important
let's make a little time water
you could try that you guys
honor to have you guys here i'm talking
about building up your system protecting
your system that's the vitamin c shock
therapy right there i'm going to move it
over
okay and you can essentially do anything
you can take ginger
you can grate it you can chop it up you
can throw it into some hot water you can
make ginger water
so and just so you know if energy has
distributors around the world go to the
website bimrgy.com visa victor i am as
ergy vimorgy.com and look for the
distributed distributor that's closest
to you around the world if you're
if you're from another area you know on
the planet right it's for people asking
about it
all right so we talked about the olive
leaf that's something
that is really important right now the
zinc shock therapy so that's two dropper
fulls every three hours two days three
days and check it out medical medium um
information right there i got the
licorice got the lemon balm i talked
about b12 is a great one too
because what happens is when when we're
exposed to critters that knock us down
and then we're just beaten down from it
right
you need something to support the
central nervous system something to help
the central nervous system reboot back
up because that fatigue people get when
they get hit by that storm
they get that fatigue and it's like it's
critical that that you get b12 into the
central nervous system because the b12
just gets knocked right out of people
so when you're up against stuff and you
start getting that
and everything in it and all that with
it your immune system
it takes a beating but your nervous
system takes a beating too your whole
your whole system gets kind of beaten
down dr phonemd good good to see you
so there you go
so we're talking about that that's a
vitamin d3 right there
so that's a really high quality d3 so
what i'm gonna do is put some drops in
the shot glass
right here
so
one two three four five six seven eight
nine 10. drop 10 in there
that's the d3 from the energy right
there
i know that everybody's vitamin d crazy
but like d crazy d d d d d d d
you know and everybody's always asking
about d that's that's the one i use
right there
you'll notice that
that is definitely
a supreme product right
so that's my shot glass
so let's make some time water really
quick so
grab this
put a little time in here
if you can't get a supplement for some
reason because you just can't get one
or you can't get a really good quality
one so you're using a less quality one
and you the less quality one you can't
guarantee is like giving you what you
need
i mean you can just go to the store get
some time if you don't grow your own
time
just get some put a bunch in like this
this is what i do every day
i drink time water every day right now
look at that and you could put more in
there you can make it really strong you
can just put some
some sprigs and you let it sit overnight
in the fridge you can just let it sit
overnight there
sit over in it this is fresh thyme
water
and you can do fresh thyme tea too so
you can actually make fresh thyme tea
get the hot water going
put the thyme in here and you can make
yourself fresh thyme tea how incredible
is that
right
how amazing
what does thyme do
it stays in your blood system
for a long duration
and it has anti-critter
properties
lots of anti-critter properties you
don't know what critter is
use your imagination we're talking about
everybody being sick you know what i
mean coughing and everything else so
we're talking about people being sick
and there's anti-critter properties in
that time right there
so you can do the time water you can do
time t this is fresh time water fresh
thyme tea
so i could show you some fresh thyme tea
really quick too let's do that
so we're going to get this going right
here we're going to make some hot water
do that really quick make some hot fresh
thyme tea
hope you guys are having good holiday
holidays so far and
and all's well in your life
so what i love about the time tea is
you can have it every single day
you can have it all day long
i'll do i'll do what about time
essential oil no
joanne don't put
don't put time essential oil don't
ingest
thyme essential oil
don't do that like don't ingest it
not a good idea it's got to be fresh
elizabeth says it's got to be fresh
thyme it has to be fresh
cotton has to be fresh
watch my essential oil
video on rumble
if you're curious watch my essential oil
for sure
you love time t marilyn amazing so we're
gonna make some time tea i got some hot
water in there i'm gonna put some sprigs
in here fresh thyme tea look at that
you can put lemon in here if you want
how incredible is that for your system
right now this time of year with
everything going on look at that
do not underestimate time whatever you
do
steep for 10 to 15 minutes and then
strain
you can do that steep for 10 15 minutes
and then strain you can add some lemon
to that so it's lemon thyme tea you can
put a little honey in there if you
really want
but there you go
you got the time t and it's steeping
right now
you can steep it longer than 10 to 15
minutes but you want the minimum 10
15 minutes is the minimum that's what
you want so that's important so this is
incredible for what we're up against
right now today
okay
that's a great one right there
so we got the time t we got the time
water we talked about the vitamin c
shock therapy we talked about the zinc
shock therapy which is two dropper holes
every three hours we'll talk about some
wild blueberry juice
are you guys doing any wild blueberry
juice for your system right now keeping
your system strong for this type of time
of year
those intense antioxidants all those
intense strong antioxidants right
this is a really
important one too i do work with weimans
though so i'm just going to give you let
you know i work with weimans reason why
i work with wyman's
on this is because this is an entirely
different thing all in its own that i
don't want to disappear i don't want
this to disappear someday they pick the
wild blueberry
out of the field the wild blueberry okay
which cannot be killed nothing can kill
the wild blueberry plant because of its
strength so for thousands and thousands
of years
right it has adapted and it can handle
fire and then grow back
and you see what people don't realize is
that when fires go through forests
nothing grows back unless a bird or a
squirrel goes on to the property onto
the land and then poops a seed
so when a when a when a
bird is flying by
and goes the bathroom
and drops seeds down on that land that's
the only time you can get things to
start growing back when you've had
wildfires because wildfires when they
burn everything to the ground like
really burn everything to the ground
nothing will grow back
so you have to have a squirrel bring a
nut to plant a new tree right well the
wild blueberry plant
is the only plant on the planet where
you can wipe you can burn it to the
ground i'm talking we're talking flame
like no one's ever seen
like just burn it to the ground a
wildfire anything like that right you
can torch it to the ground and it'll
grow back up it'll grow back up fast
so
its roots are that strong and it just
doesn't get killed off and and so that's
one reason why just you know wild
blueberry is just an amazing species all
on its own
but i can't like i can't say enough
about
like wild blueberry juice so i work with
wyman's
because
for them to pick the wild blueberry
and press it
so it's not like when you go to the
store
and you see that hpp stuff or whatever
that's different that hpp stuff that's
not like this is actually they take the
wild blueberry and they press
those wild blueberries and you get
something that's like
this is this supersedes wine
supersedes wine all together right so i
don't know if you guys are doing your
shot glasses of this but the antioch
anthocyanin levels are something that no
one's ever you can't even touch that
with wild blueberry it's incredible
that's a tonic right
lauren brown
i thought you said no lemon in hot water
so
lemon for tea is great can do it anytime
you want
it's not going to flush your liver
or
flush your body
when it's used for tea and hot water
okay
but lemon
in 32 ounces of water or 16 ounces of
water or even 8 ounces of water just
even lemon
in water that's not hot
will then stay active and flush poisons
and toxins out of your liver and out of
your body
see so if you want to do the lemon water
to
flush poisons and toxins out of the
liver in the body then you have to make
sure it's not in hot hot water
or hot water you got to make sure it's
in
regular water like room temperature
water or cold water is fine or just
lukewarm water or something but you
don't want want it in hot water when you
put it in tea it's different so you can
do it medicinally in tea
and you get other
medicine out of your lemon when you have
it in hot water but that's not the same
thing you can't flush your liver then
you want to flush your liver you have to
have the 32 ounces of lemon water with
the lemon juice not in hot water
medical medium information
where do you buy the wild blueberry
juice shop s-h-o-p
dot
weimanns.com so wyman's is
w-y-m-a-n-s-shop.wymans.com
so that's the blueberry juice right
so i just took a shot of it i'm going to
take another shot of it
i've been doing so much today that i
really haven't
had much too much of anything i had some
celery juice this morning though
tammy but doesn't lemon warm up when you
put it in your body
well the temperature that comes out of
the kettle
is really hot
and if your blood was that hot
you wouldn't be here right now so you
can't have your blood
the temperature of your body
right
cannot
cannot be as hot
as the water
in the kettle
the water in the kettle
is
120 30 40 60 180 degrees
and that's what that is right
so you got to be really careful right if
you're meaning in the sense
heather says it's the cognitive
dissonance anthony once you say one word
some someone will get triggered and go
blank
well
look it's when it comes down when
when it comes down to it though so this
is important to know
is that yeah i mean it's true i mean
yeah i totally understand when it comes
down to it with the hot water in the
body and stuff your temperature is
98.5
97.4
97.8
98.6
98.7
so everybody's body temps run at
different temperatures right
a lot of people run like i run a really
low body temp
and a lot of people run a higher body
temp they'll be like 98.6
they'll be like 98.7
right they'll run a higher body temp
but that's that can't hurt
any it can't hurt lemon going in you
because that's not a 130
degrees
120 degrees
or if you here's the problem if you cook
your lemon so say your water comes out
of that kettle at a buck 40
and you put your lemon in there you just
killed your lemon juice
and then the water cools down and you
think well now the water's cool enough
for me to drink no the lemon won't flush
because it's been killed off in there
with the high temperature it had so
but you want to flush out your liver you
want to flush out your blood you want to
flush everything out you need that lemon
water being like it is and that's
another system builder right there
the reason why you see oranges here and
you see lemons in here because we're
talking about system builders so what i
like doing is making some fresh squeezed
orange juice that's what i like to do
lemon and tea
some abilities of the lemon survive
but not the flushing
and poison remover ability
so the flushing and poison remover
ability right
inside your liver that's not going to
make it if your lemon juice gets hot
that's not going to float you're not
going to flush out the intestinal tract
or the liver
it can't happen so you're not going to
be able to do that liver flush
that intestinal tract flush poisons and
toxins your kidney flush
you're not going to be able to do your
kidney flush if the lemon get got too
hot so if your lemon is in your tea
you can't do your kidney flush
and your liver flush and your intestinal
flush
but there's going to be still medicinal
chemical compounds in there that are
going to help you when you're doing it
in your tea
that's the difference
so it's important to know
so let's go let's keep on moving on a
couple more things let's cut some aloe
too what i do is aloe every day during
this
time of year especially
so medical medium information
there's some aloe right
there right it talks about aloe a lot
that's a great system builder right
there for what's happening for people
so what i do is i cut this just like
that i didn't cut all the way through
i cut that part so i ran the knife like
this
just like this
and then you can open it like that
now you can do it any way you want you
can take a spoon in there you can do it
that way i take the knife
and i kind of fillet
that top off of there right
there we go i'm going to open it up
you guys see that you guys see that on
telegram
okay and then i take the knife
and i fillet
that part out right there
and you can take this
now
this is incredible right now
as far as for a protection method
something that should be added in you
might be somebody that only
has you know access to aloe
like this fresh outlook but you don't
have access to time or access to an
orange or access to lemons right now or
access to these incredible supplements
and so
eating it like that is great really
incredible for you
so that's another option so we talked
about the micro c that's a big one right
there
olive leaf that's incredible for now
what people are going through right
you got the d3 for the people that love
the d3 and want the d3 got the lemon
balm that's the tender one i talked
about you got the zing shark therapy you
got the cat's claw
and then goldenseal is a big one right
now i'm just looking for the golden seal
like for some reason can't find it
but goldenseal
that's a big deal
and
i'll actually get a golden seal in a
moment too
what i love about the golden seal is
it's one of the most important things we
can do right now too at this time
i freeze chunks so you freeze aloe
chunks or frozen chunks the only thing
that you got to make sure if you if you
buy the frozen chunks of aloe
at the store or at the market
make sure
it's not laced
look at the package look at the
ingredient
list
check it all out
okay that's important right there
because make sure there's no citric acid
in there that's important citric acid
any kind of natural flavors any kind of
weird fillers any kind of other
chemicals any of that like make sure
that's not there
so here's the golden seal so i'm going
to drop that in
any friend
any family member
like i'm getting calls and texts
off the hook
some people i haven't talked to in a
year two years some people haven't
talked to some family members i haven't
talked to in like a year because things
have been crazy and busy like you name
it like
i'm good everybody's reaching out to me
right now because you're like oh my god
i think i'm sick
and i'm like where's your golden seal
because
you need to be doing four to six dropper
fulls of goldenseal four times a day if
you got that cough coming on if you got
that mucus coming on if you got the
sinus drainage on you better be doing
like four to six dropper holes
that's you know that's what i would
recommend a family member but you guys
do whatever you guys want to do ask your
doctor what's right for you call your
doctor up and say hey can i take hold
and seal but
it's this is a big one right here is the
golden seal so important
kathy said we killed the bug in four
days with all your stuff thank you kathy
awesome
you hammered it you hammered it this is
what you did
so you know if you guys want to know
okay lori says with goldenseal always
two weeks on two weeks off or for rare
with okay
two weeks on two weeks off right when
you're battling like the utis or
something or you're battling like bv
bacterial vaginosis or a stye or you're
battling like a scratchy throat right
and even then you don't have to do two
weeks two weeks on two weeks off right
now
if you're battling like a strep if
you're battling some kind of like mucus
and congestion because of what's going
on right now because of the critters
that are going around that everybody's
getting right now
i mean i i have i have family members
that are on it more than two weeks i got
them on it for like a month
now i got some friends on it for like a
month and then they can take a week off
sure
but you can do the on and off
right but you can also stay on it for a
while too and stay on it for a while i
mean ask your doctor what's right for
you but i'm just telling you what i
offer my friends and family like what i
would do is i would stay on it if i had
if i had something really going on that
was tugging on me and tugging on me
strong right
so yeah
so celery juice is a great one right
there you guys can use that for your
immune system
celery juice could bring that in
strengthen the body
that's something too that
every day
so
now what i also do is the barley grass
juice powder
i do the spirulina that's what i do too
so i do the barley grass juice powder
and the spirulina
so what i do is a teaspoon of each one
right there i'll mix it up with coconut
water that's something i do or i'll take
i'll take a little plastic bag i'll put
a few scoops of
of this in each in a plastic bag like a
little a little zippy bag and i'll take
that when i'm traveling and so i can go
in there and i could take it and put it
in some coconut water i can go buy a
coconut water somewhere where i'm
traveling and i could just literally
just get the spirulina and the barley
grass juice powder also to keep my
system strong also to help keep on
removing toxins so that's important too
so you guys
i'm going off to instagram i hope you
guys coming with me i'm going to go on
there pretty soon too i'm just going to
straighten up a little bit and then
we're going to head on
we're going to be on there
so
sign up to the newsletter
medicalmedium.com the link is right
there for the newsletter it's in the
description it's in in the profile right
and sign up to the newsletter so you
know about the medical meeting morning
cleanse challenge
giving you guys a full warning it's
going to be fun as heck so we're going
to do the medical medium morning
challenge in january
somewhere in early january somewhere
around there i'll keep you posted
through the newsletter so make sure that
you sign up to the newsletter all right
and you might want to have this book
handy at the time for january so if you
don't have the book for january make
sure you have it handy okay now just for
the record the medical media morning
cleanse challenge is free
it's free free free it's okay it's free
it's not that you don't have to sign up
you like and pay all this money to do
the medical media morning clen challenge
it's free
margin says i signed up but still don't
get emails did you sign up recently
though because we had a glitch
so marjah try to sign up again
so check out the link right there and
try to sign up again because we had a
link that wasn't working and nobody
could sign up to the newsletter for
quite a while and you might have been
like one of those people that were
trying to sign up and you couldn't so
try to sign up again so check it out the
link is in the description
and check check spam
too
in case we send it to you when it went
to spam so we send the emails to you and
they they go to spam so check that out
as well
all right and you guys for january make
sure you have cleanse the heal right
here i'm going on ig we're gonna have
some fun we're still gonna be talking
about how to keep the system strong
and how to keep the critters away and
how to protect yourselves you guys you
know i love you i'll see you soon
i can't wait
going on ig pretty soon i'm going to
turn tuk-tuk back on and telegram back
on so i'm going to keep you guys back up