and medical medium new edition i'm
making this recipe right out of here you
guys the books coming out like i don't
know what's next week or something
but it's coming out soon and i'm excited
about the new edition
revised and expanded the lyme disease
chapter
wow i mean the information here about
cfs epstein-barr
most advanced information about
epstein-barr ever because it all comes
back down to these books and this book
right here
and that's the information people are
using in the world right now about epson
bar it all originates from the first
publication but this is the new edition
you guys got to check this book out it's
coming out soon
anyway making the burrito bowl there it
is and you guys are going to like this
one because you guys
love avocados i know that you guys love
your avocados so
definitely using an avocado so get ready
for that one good to see you guys coming
on
we're live on youtube we're live on
facebook i'm excited good to be here
i'm going to talk about toxic heavy
metals because there's so many
questions about metals in tattoo
ink okay i'm going to talk about copper
thermoses
copper jewelry is it good is it bad you
might want to be on there for this one
okay talk about even copper iud that's a
concern for a lot of people
copper pipes because for some reason
everybody thinks copper is a good thing
so wait till we cover that that's going
to be interesting
i'm going to talk about managing
your chronic illness your autoimmune
versus
actually healing it okay because they
teach you now
to manage it that's all you're just
gonna manage it for the rest of your
life
and not fix it because it's not fixable
but we're gonna talk about fixing it
that's what it's about this is exciting
you guys i can't wait to make the recipe
or here's those are some of the topics
and um
yeah good to see you guys great great to
be on right now see
so look i'm gonna start out with uh
some cauliflower right here so if you
guys take a look i got a nice
cauliflower
i don't know if how good you can see
that with the lighting but there it is
and so i'm to
use a lot of this i'm going to start
with about a half of it
i'm going to cut the florets florets are
going to go in the food processor
um so tina says
i've been drinking the heavy metal detox
smoothie with botanicals feeling so
clear
heavy metals are transforming confusion
and clarity incredible
what i do is i use the vimergy so i so i
know it's working it's the best there is
for the heavy metal detox smoothie
not sponsored by these guys but that's
been reggie spirulina v is invictus i
m e r g y the vimergy barley grass juice
powder
critical for that vermice wok blueberry
powder too
but that's what i use in mine and what i
tell family and friends because people
say how like how can i remove metals
what's my
best chance of removing all that
copper from all those copper toxic
sources removing all the mercury
removing all the aluminum i'm asset all
the time my family friends
doctors what's my best chance and
they'll say something like
i got some krill i'm like that's not
going to do it they won't
then they'll say oh i got this other
kind of spirulina i'll be like uh
that spirulina is not coming from a good
place or a good source
and if you know when people say what's
my greatest chance of getting the medals
out and i'm like look
this is what i do if you want to know
what i do so it's the bemidji spirulina
barley grass juice powder
wild blueberry powder because it's
important i mean
it's either you do it or you don't
meaning like you have the best there is
or you do it half ass and that's okay i
mean people do that they'll do it like
now this is enough i could just do this
i got enough i'll just use a little
cilantro and i'm good but
it's like look do you really got some
stuff going on if you're really worried
about your tattoos and i got to talk to
you guys about the tattoos while we're
cooking
if you're really worried about all the
different metals that we have you just
i tell my friends my family let's do it
right
do it right because we can't avoid all
the medals they're out there we get
exposed to it every day we're exposed to
it
in every way possible all the time and
that's fine
that's fine but we got to do something
about it at least be proactive
in removing more than what's coming in
so it's about removing
more metals than what's coming in it's
like
i want more metals coming out of me than
what's coming in all the time
so that's really important right there
and
metals settle in your brain that's the
number one place they
all go so if you're doing
pharmaceuticals pharmaceuticals got all
metals
in them if you're doing pharmaceuticals
they go to the brain
all the metals go to the brain all that
titanium
all of it on the mercury all of that
stuff
all the barium barium is in
pharmaceuticals lots of barium
goes to the brain and then your brain
becomes a magnet
for because of the electricity panel
that's in your brain
that electricity panel that's in your
brain right
becomes a magnet for more metal more
metal it can't get enough it just starts
to stick to all the deposits and spots
right
anyway we'll talk about that we got a
lot to cover on all of it
so if you don't have frozen wild
blueberries substitute with two
tablespoons
of the wild blueberry powder so that's
what you can do substitute
see guys i'm here let's start making
some stuff i got my food processor good
to see you guys michelle l
good to see you everybody's coming on
um so i'm gonna just cut these florets
up like this
i'm gonna throw them in the food
processor
okay so i'm just kind of cutting these
back a little
so i'm going to pop them in here and
pulse it in a minute let's talk about
tattoo ink
really important that's a question that
came up because you guys
many of you guys saw the video my tick
tock video right
and i rolled up my sleeves and um
and it's important to be proactive if
you got ink
it really is because ink
is a delivery system for toxic heavy
metals
to go to your brain and liver your whole
lifetime your whole lifetime so once you
get inked that's it
you got it you got the ink whole
lifetime right
so all that metal and then i'm going to
talk about
oh wait i don't i don't have the toxic
my ink my my tattooist my artist
he says that mine is it's it's cruelty
free
it's animal product free it's vegan
my ink is vegan it's non-toxic
so anthony you're just i don't know what
kind of tattoo ink you're talking about
anthony
is not mine my tattoo artist would never
do that to me no he said it's cruelty
free it's animal free it's non-toxic
it's sterile it's sterile ink
certified sterile and so you'll hear
that right
but i'm sorry to say it's got toxic
heavy metals in it
and a whole variety of toxic heavy
metals because i'm going to drop the
bomb on you right now
really important to know and ink
reflects off the sun and light
because of toxic heavy metals they can't
put ink in your arms
okay like you saw in my video they can't
in your neck in your side if they put a
little scripture on your side you know
like some kind of like
some kind of some scripture from buddha
or something some scripture
and then whatever you got on you right
or some kind of you know
some kind of feathers or whatever is
going on that you have
in order for it to show up really good
and
pop through the skin it has to have
metals to reflect the light that's
coming down to your skin
so when you roll up your sleeves you
pull up whatever you're wearing shorts
you have them on your ankles wherever
you got your ink
for when light hits it in order for it
to
pop it has to hit the metals
in the ink you see how it works that's
how it pops
and in all makers of ink
because ink we're rich all the products
from inc comes from china so it all
comes from china it's all made out there
then it gets shipped overseas to the us
and then you know and then and they make
it in the u.s too but most
inks come from there at least a lot of
the supplies come from there so they
make it in the u.s but the supplies for
the inc
come from from china it's where they
come from right and
where you know we're where most
everything comes from right you guys but
what happens
is that that these this ink
okay is filled with metals and it's
filled with a variety of metals
and it has to be so that the ink pops
and you're a happy customer
so it's like whoa that looks so good i
got some colors in there it looks great
you're a happy customer and it's to make
it so it pops for years
eventually you get older of course and
the ink starts to not look as great
doesn't pop as much because your skin
kind of
what happens is it gets buried deeper
into the derma it goes deeper into the
derma and it sinks deeper into the derma
but what happens is
these metals leach into your bloodstream
for your entire life
and hey that's all right i mean that's
okay i'm not i'm not trying to scare you
that's not it i'm just saying
that that you got to be proactive
because all that metal goes to your
brain i don't care who tells you
no it's non-toxic no there's no heavy
metals in my ink
um it's it's cruelty free it's non-toxic
no
it's got solvents in it it's got other
poisons and chemicals in it
the best ink there is on the market has
solvents and poisons in it it does
it's okay it just does it's got toxic
heavy metals in it
it just does and so
keep in mind that that's all right it's
not about getting rid of your tattoos
it's not about trying to get your
tattoos removed no not at all
i don't recommend that i don't i don't
recommend you trying to get them removed
i don't recommend you try to do anything
like that that's not it
it's just what i recommend is being
proactive
get your metals out of your bloodstream
get them out of your organs and your
skin
is one of those organs and so you're
working on
basically making sure you're removing
metals that are coming out of the skin
from the bottom
down so from the bottom down from your
derma
down and those those metals they leach
over time and they drop down
and that's what happens they go from
your skin on down deeper to the derma
until they finally get to all kinds of
blood vessels
and they leech like a leech field over
time so when we get our ink
it's leech fields of toxic waste
because that's what ink is made out of i
don't care when they say it's non-toxic
that's not true
that's not true because all ink is toxic
so
and that's okay and i don't want you to
go run and try to get rid of your
tattoos i don't want you to worry about
that if you're somebody who loves
tattoos and you've been really wanting
to get another one
you do what you want get another one
whatever but
be proactive and work on getting the
metals
out that's the key it's about you know
it's about the information you know
having that information it's so
important
and um so you don't want to do the re
remove i i don't recommend removing them
because trying to remove them through
laser techniques and stuff because
when you do that um they leach quicker
they leach even more they leach in a
large amount i'd rather have ink
sitting on me let's just say
okay or anyone i'd rather had have ink
sit there and leech slowly year after
year
month after month for the rest of your
life because you can
when you're proactive and you're doing
your heavy metal detox smoothie
um and you're doing your spirulina
you're doing your barley you're doing
your dolls you're doing your cilantro
you're gathering whatever's leeching
you're gathering your gathering you're
taking it out and you're sweeping it out
right
and that's what you want i don't
recommend really removing any because
when you do the removing
of any kind of way they do it laser is
the most uh
common right now it's your your all of
it's dumping into your system then you
you can't get a control over that too
easy so a lot of it can go to the brain
let's work on this right here for a
little bit so
i'm going to pulse up actually i'm going
to add some spices in here to pulse this
up too
so let me do that um making the rice
and do a little paprika okay
about a half teaspoon i'm gonna put a
little in here
okay put a paprika in that i'm making
cauliflower rice you guys just so you
know
okay a little cayenne actually that's
not actually not the cayenne putting the
cumin
em in here right got a little that
and uh yeah and that i am putting a
little cayenne in there a little touch
of it
okay but just a little bit quarter
teaspoon
so a quarter teaspoon in there
[Music]
and i'm putting uh two tablespoons of
finely chopped
uh cilantro so i'm going to chop up some
cilantro here
i was right it was cayenne going in
there
it's a little touch of it half
[Music]
so this is all one serving so
look you can even use less of that if
you if you're not a big fan of cumin if
you're not a big fan of cayenne if
you're not a big fan
of paprika you can use a little bit a
little bit i'm using about a tablespoon
of cilantro right here
it's about a tablespoon of cilantro in
there
there we go
i'm gonna pulse this real quick pulsing
into like a rice
is what you guys are doing
dan says what do we do about having ink
what do you suggest about being
proactive
hi diane i'm glad you're on here i'm
just gonna pulse up this
cauliflower
getting the metals out being proactive
and removing toxic heavy metals
and other toxins that that are in the
ink that
you've gotten a lot of people who have
older ink they have ink
that was even higher in toxic heavy
metals
but all ink whether it's vegan whether
it's you know with cruelty free
whether it says it's non-toxic is high
in toxic
heavy metals no matter what because they
have to that's how it's seen through
your skin i'm just giving you the 4-1-1
on that now i know
a tattoo artist might be upset when they
hear that and they may like he's not
right that's not true
my supplier says this or i got this but
what
they don't realize remember they're the
artist it doesn't mean they're an
expert at the chemical composition of
where
and how these inks are made and that's
really important to know you know
regardless of what they're told in in in
order
for your ink to pop through your skin
it there has to be metal in the ink
that's
what reflects off the light it's the
metals in the
ink that will send out that red that
will send out that yellow that will send
out the orange
that will send out the purple the blue
that will send out the black
it that's the reflection that it needs
it's about that so talking about being
proactive here
so i made the rice proactive is actually
doing the heavy metal detox smoothie
that's what i have friends i have
friends that have ink got lots of
friends that are loaded with ink
okay they got them everywhere they got
an ink on their neck
they got ink on their legs they got ink
everywhere and
um and they're doing the heavy metal
detox smoothie so the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie so they're
being proactive in that way
they're doing uh vimergy spirulina the
memory
barley grass so they're using the right
stuff i mean you could use whatever
you want to find a spirulina you like go
use it you want to find a barley grass
juice powder you like go use it that's
what i recommend my friends and family
that's what i use
um i don't i mean personally i don't
have a lot of faith in the other
products out there when it comes down to
those i'm not sponsored by
by bimergy um but anyway terry says
misinformation
um yeah i mean
it's not misinformation and i love how
you use my word
because that's that's funny because all
these years that's what i've always used
is misinformation
unless that's for someone else that
might have been for someone else
um but anyway it's interesting though as
far as uh stuff goes
if it was for someone else thanks
exactly but you know
but yeah it the metals have to be in the
ink
in order to reflect the light that's how
you get your
greatest maximum color out of there and
that's how it works
um so let's just keep on making this
here's the rice i'm gonna put the rice
in this bowl i have this bowl right here
it's a blue bowl
let's get a spoon now
this isn't the only ingredient okay
this is just one of them i'm going to
lay some lettuce down here first inside
this bowl i think i'm going to do that
first a little lettuce at the bottom of
here so i'm going to chop up a little
lettuce this is butter leaf right here
this is butter leaf lettuce
so the medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie is about being proactive
lots of people are using it around the
world it's saving lives
what i love about the the medical medium
heavy metal detox movie it's already
helped people
with depression anxiety bipolar
schizophrenia
alzheimer's dementia depersonalization
adhd
autism and ticks spasms
tourette's ocd did i say that one
and um it's already helped so many
people heal around the world i'm putting
a little
lettuce in the bottom of this bowl
so um
but i like that the the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie for that
i like it for chronic illness too you're
dealing with lyme disease you're dealing
with cfs you're dealing with ra
hashimoto's thyroiditis eczema psoriasis
whatever it is it's great for that too
because when people are sick with
viruses like epstein-barr virus and
shingles virus and all that
viruses feed off of toxic heavy metals
so that's that's a reason why to do it
too all on its own
i got some lettuce at the bottom of the
bowl now i'm going to put some rice down
in here
so there's going to be i'm going to have
a salsa in here
okay
i'm going to have some guacamole in here
so i'm putting some rice down on one
side of it
i'm laura says i'm a much calmer person
thanks to heavy metal detox smoothie and
mmm
oh that's amazing it's incredible that's
incredible
what's the name pamela says what's the
name of those powders
it's vimergy it's a v is in victor
i emma's in mary e-r-g-y
dot com bimrg.com not sponsored by them
but
it's the best stuff there is so stuff i
use
people always ask me you know i never
used to say what i use so much
but now just i have to because
everybody's asking me all the time in it
and i feel bad if i don't say it
so i'm just getting the rice in here
this is going to look really pretty this
bowl too
so i'm going to start with getting that
rice in there for now
so i started out with getting rice in
there to start with it's not done so you
have your cauliflower rice right there
then you have some
it's on a bed of chopped lettuce but
this is the
burrito bowl abigail where can we find
the recipe of the heavy metal detox
smoothie
um in books this book is coming out the
new edition
so revise an expanded medical medium
amazon.com you could find it on the blog
medicalmedium.com you could find it in
my other medical medium books cleanse
the heal
so this book is out of course now you
guys
and this is cleanse the heel
you can find the recipe but in here is a
heavy metal detox cleanse so
medical medium heavy metal detox plan so
there's that right there you find it
there
um for anybody who doesn't know anything
about this book right here over 200
symptoms and conditions
protocols supplements and dosages
true causes of the conditions and
symptoms this is
a medical textbook it's saving lives
around the world right now
the number one best-selling book on the
planet
uh in health it's it's really helping so
many people out there and
there's there's different cleanses in
here there's 75 recipes if you guys
are interested go to the library for you
can get it for free at the library
if and it's on sale at amazon.com 51 off
i just have to let you know once in a
while
what what you know what's really in this
it's it's just and now i'm not even
scratching the surface
so i got the cauliflower rice right
there so i'm excited
let's start making the salsa how about
if we do that we're going to make
guacamole
in a little bit a little bit of that too
let's start making the salsa let's do
that so let's get the tomatoes going
i got these vine ripe tomatoes you see
this if you guys are afraid of tomatoes
i feel kind of bad because
there's no reason to be afraid of them
they're so good for you it's there's
misinformation out there on tomatoes
always has been
hanging there we're about to talk about
copper in a minute too but i wanted to
cover the
ink as much as i could right now
i know a lot of you guys have ink i
totally get it
but we're gonna go into the copper
that's next let me just dice up some
tomatoes
so there's a trend happening right now
and
it's a trend of copper's good for you
dear lord
that's a nightmare okay it's far from
good for you copper thermoses
copper water
storage units copper
anything like that copper jewelry
copper wear the reason why
copper wear people swear by it sometimes
is because it's it's um it's support
is what it is so it's actual supports
compression
compression support so it can be without
the copper and someone's going to swear
by it okay
so it doesn't it doesn't matter any kind
of compression
sleeves compression knee braces
compression
socks compression elbow braces
wrist bands rich wrist braces
any kind of compression therapy is
helpful and people swear by it
they didn't have to stick copper in it
copper's toxic so then people get copper
leaching through their skin
copper is not anti-inflammatory it never
was
and anybody who thinks copper's
anti-inflammatory
it's coming from a place any kind of
professional any kind of authority or
health authority that thinks
copper's anti-inflammatory they don't
know what's causing inflammation to
begin with so you got to remember that
so it's coming from sources that don't
know why anybody's sick
before i released the truth about
epstein-barr no one even knew
that there was even a possibility that
viruses caused any kind of inflammation
so the medical media books have brought
that out there okay and
copper is toxic copper's in pesticides
it's one of the leading reasons why
pesticides are so bad and we get sick
it's because of copper copper's in
fungicides
pesticides fire retardant it's it's
actually
it's actually a toxin it's dangerous to
us
copper pennies are bad for us to be in
our hands and you play around
if you ever counted a jar of old pennies
and you counted them by hand and wrapped
them in you know the little
the little you know coin sleeves and you
put them in there right
your hands will smell like straight
metal like straight
copper and it absorbs into your system
anybody who's counted pennies
you know and they put the 50 pennies in
the sleeve and
you know and you make and you make do a
bunch of them because you have a jar of
pennies kicking by
you get copper poisoning from that it's
critical to get that copper out of your
body because it leads to eczema and
psoriasis dermatitis
rosacea it leads to so many problems it
just leads to skin skin conditions
uh galore it just leads to them so
because copper is responsible for
excellent psoriasis a huge part of it so
here we go
let's just do copper thermoses let's
just do copper mugs let's just do copper
everything and um and
it's really a toxic toxic heavy metal
copper pipes the reason why family lines
are sick
and riddled with skin conditions like
eczema psoriasis
and other autoimmune conditions is from
copper pipes
and so now we got this trend that
believes
when they don't even know why anybody's
sick because science research doesn't
know anybody why anybody's sick so why
would the copper trend people know why
anybody is sick
um so so the copper trend people are
like
making products out there and people got
their water sitting in that
dear lord i mean it's really bad like
really bad
it's just gonna lead to sickness it's
gonna poison their livers it's gonna
poison their brain
but it really is you keep that water
inside that copper unit
and your water is now contaminated
that's
just yeah that's just a few things i can
say about it so i'll talk about copper a
little bit more on how trace copper's
different
in the soil and even that is not
something we want lots of
just so you know copper
is not something that we are
lacking of we have too much
copper all of us there's copper
in the foods we eat too much
there's too much copper in avocado
that's a high copper food too much
copper and avocado
all right because avocado trees tend to
absorb copper more than others
alex says the copper trend comes from
ayurveda for thousands of years
there might be more to it than just the
trend well
here's how it works okay i know what
you're saying because okay airbag so
here's how it works with water there
wasn't
fresh water supplies okay there weren't
fresh water supplies
and a high amount of copper can destroy
an amoeba so in a meat because it's
toxic
so amoeba okay certain water parasites
actually get destroyed from copper
poisoning
you see how it works alex so the the
whole thing it went back years ago they
didn't have running
fresh water running water an ayurvedic
in ayurvedic medicine they know this
that going back thousands of years okay
they knew that it was hard to get fresh
water back then you didn't have
fresh water pipes you didn't have spring
water coming out of places it was rare
you can find something like this
villages would be just out of water so
whatever
rain water came down they would keep it
in copper
barrels because the copper poisoning
would kill off not everything you still
can get the worst dysentery
you can still get sick but it would kill
off certain amoeba
certain parasitic um you know
microorganisms that's what it would do
okay and that's what it was used for it
was used for a
partly for a war water sanitation
control okay because you can poison
a microorganism with copper
see how it works that's all it was and
kind of kind of think about stuff okay
does those thousands of years of
smartness that you're talking about
does that fix all the millions of people
with chronic illness um
i'm not gonna pick on different
countries and different places
but disease is rampant rampant and
america
disease is rampant here it's rampant
everywhere okay just in the u.s alone
250 275 million americans in the u.s
alone have symptoms they can't get rid
of
symptoms they can't get rid of millions
of children are sick okay
and i get it you want to find some kind
of mysterious thing that's thousands of
years old that might have an
answer but when babies are riddled with
eczema psoriasis and they got ticks and
spasms
and severe tourettes and severe ocd and
autism and everything else it just so
you know
copper makes those conditions worse so
does ayurvedic medicine know that no
they don't
so i get i get it though you want to
kind of you want that nostalgic like
whoa
say your vatic there must be something
to it going all the way back
they must know so much they must know
everything and i understand that
i totally understand that survival
doesn't equal healthy
a survival technique to keep your water
from getting
too riddled with a certain microorganism
by using
copper to control it doesn't mean it's
necessarily healthy and going to give
you
good standing health but see that's more
advanced information than thousands of
years
of of um you know antiquated information
you have to think about something a
thousand years ago 2000 years ago they
thought you can fix your brain by eating
brain
that was 2 000 years ago it's antiquated
it doesn't work but am i supposed to
like respect it to the point where
i'm supposed to be like bowed down to
whoa i better bow down to that because a
thousand years ago
they said they said that if you ate
brain you fix your brain i better stitch
a thousand years old alex i better
i better bow down to that aerobatic
medicine well you copper
you can use copper and water to control
bad microorganisms so we better get lots
of copper in our water
because that must be the reason why
we're sick we'll just we'll just drink
the copper
i better bow down to that and here's
another thing too
um mercury elixirs right for thousands
of years
mercury elixirs were big they were big
all around the planet
you drink mercury tonics i better bow
down to it they were right
two thousand three thousand years ago
okay and
in the east okay it was mercury elixirs
mercury elixirs
emperors would take mercury elixirs and
you know
uh presidents would take mercury elixirs
just in the 1800s
are we supposed to bow down to the
mercury elixirs because it's two
thousand three thousand four thousand
years old
i'm curious is does that make sense yeah
i get it
you know there's some things that travel
a long way like massage
like acupressure and they travel
thousands of years
and those are great things but you can't
just all of a sudden assume
that every single thing that comes from
two thousand three thousand years ago is
a great idea
because it's not and fermented foods was
a survival technique
not right there because fermented foods
comes from two thousand three thousand
four thousand years ago that it must be
the panacea to heal us it must actually
be the cure
the cure but you gotta understand
fermented foods are just decomposing
it's it the microorganisms in fermented
foods are the
microorganisms of death that are feeding
off of something that's decomposing
right but that's not the microorganisms
that give you life inside of you
that those microorganisms are only on
living foods when you have cilantro in
your garden
the microorganism that's sitting on the
cilantro why it's sitting there floating
around in the sun and the wind there's a
microorganism in that
that's the one that gives you life so
when you eat that that cilantro that
came out of your garden
that elevated biotic is what gives you
life not
the bacteria that's on something that's
decaying and dying when an animal dies
in the woods it gets engulfed by
bacteria
microorganisms that go to it because
it's dead
when we when we pass on and we start to
go
stale fast after passing on
microorganisms start to devour our body
that's not the microorganism that we get
life from so when the reason why they
did this
is they fermented vegetables was a
survival technique
technique because they had no fresh food
delivered there weren't stores
there weren't grocery stores there
wasn't fresh food grown around the
planet
that can be delivered you know through
plane travel and truck travel
right so what happened was they were in
these little villages
thousands of years ago in the hills and
when your garden ran out
you were you were you were in big
trouble you had your chicken eggs
you had your you had your goat's milk
and you had whatever vegetables that
were left over and you know what you had
to do
you had to take those vegetables and you
had to throw them in a vat a big old vat
and throw a lid on it and hope that god
they just did their natural decaying
process
fermented and broke down and
because you needed to eat that slob
all winter long in order to keep you
alive see how it works this is important
information this is advanced information
and i teach this to doctors i've been
teaching this stuff for years okay
so that fermented foods was a survival
tactic
to try to preserve the food long enough
to get you to the spring
because you would starve to death
because you had no freezers and
refrigerators
and you had no fresh food coming in
that's
what happened but we take these old
things a long time ago and we think
they must be so good for us and but yet
there's better things for us fermented
foods not better than this butter leaf
lettuce that's fresh and alive and
filled with enzymes right now
okay and it's certainly not better than
butter leaf lettuce that you grew out of
your garden this year that has
microorganisms all over it the kind that
gives us life
and fermented food can't beat
lime right here a lime with the vitamin
c and the calcium in it
and it can't be the power of what the
sun can do and
and what goes in this orange here and so
but
i get it we think thousands of years ago
ayurvedic medicine
ayurvedic ayurvedic information um
copper in the water it must mean it's
good for us
that's funny because i talked to the
best ayurvedic doctors that contact me
around the planet
and they don't know why anybody's sick
they don't
they have they have their their your
their guesses about maybe it's
too much dampness in the body and maybe
it's the liver acting up somehow or
maybe it's something
but they don't know why you have eczema
raging
air vedic doctors don't know why
someone's sick with severe
chronic fatigue syndrome me but i
respect them
greatly i have great respect for the
best doctors on the planet functional
medicine doctors ayurvedic doctors
chinese medicine doctors conventional
medical doctors
on the plan great respect for all of
them i have respect for all of them
because they're helping people and they
do help and they do have a lot of
knowledge but what i'm trying to tell
you is
is they don't have answers to why
anybody's chronically ill they don't
science research believes it's the body
destroying itself or it's genes
that's it so i guess we could package it
up be like just because
you know copper holding water back
thousands of years ago must be the
fantasy of answers
just so you know you get you put your
water in copper
and you're going to be sicker than ever
before down the road you're going to get
so much copper in your system
in your organs and you're telling me
everybody just stayed alive and all
happy no one was ever sick
you don't know how that stuff was making
people sicker and sicker and sicker and
sicker and sicker
no one's watching that no one's watching
how how much water did you drink out of
that copper vat a thousand years ago
who knows how the person died of a
horrible death years later
is anybody studying that no one's
studying any of that you can't study it
it's all guesswork it's all guessing
games so let's make a trend let's make a
new trend off of some old outdated
thing that wasn't great so let's make
copper thermoses so we can poison women
because that's going to be real good for
their babies when their babies get all
that copper in their brain
can you think about pregnant what about
pregnant women doing all the copper
stuff
if you're going to wear jewelry i would
wear gold plated because it's protect
it's going
over the copper or i would wear gold i
don't wear jewelry
but if you're into jewelry i would wear
gold that's what i would do
there's always a little copper in gold
unless it's 24 karat there's always
alloyed in there but the point is it's
very much less
but i wouldn't wear straight copper
jewelry i wouldn't wear that
i wouldn't wear copper copper items i
wouldn't wear copper clothing
i wouldn't do copper and water god
forbid if i was a pregnant woman or
wanting to have a baby
i certainly wouldn't do any of that
copper stuff without there's no doubt
about that unless
the baby's just gonna get copper uh
copper in the baby system
um all the stuff's important so but alex
i get it and i really appreciate you and
i appreciate you talking about that
i actually um wanted to talk about that
too
okay plastic pvc i want to talk about
that that's important too
is it healthier than copper pipes oh big
time that's not the leaching plastic
pcv the hard pcv they use in plumbing
okay the hard stuff the pvc they use
in in plumbing is not the leaching
plastic
and i would rather in a million years
have leaching plastic
any day because plastic comes out of the
body easy just like lowering your fats
you know lowering your fats not on too
much milk cheese butter bringing all
that down
making you sure you do the heavy metal
detox smoothie because spirulina does
remove plastic
there's an anti-plastic tee in this book
right here so um in the new edition but
the point is plastic comes out easy
and hardened pvc piping
doesn't leach up anything practically
practically
nothing it's it's a whole different
story than other types of plastic right
that's one thing the other thing is
copper pipes
that's poisoned families for years the
amount of damage
copper pipes have done to families and
their health
is catastrophic it causes green
green that green corrosion that goes in
all the sinks in the toilets if you
don't have your water softened
and even if you have your water softened
you're still going to get copper
leaching now you may not
have any control over that if you got
copper pipes but yes you do
okay you do have control over that first
of all make sure your water is filtered
don't drink it out of the tap that's one
thing you can control
the second thing you can control is
making sure you're doing a heavy metal
detox smoothie
so you're proactive in getting the
copper out faster than it comes in
so if you're taking your shower and you
think there could be some copper stuff
going on in the water
you can do that check with your doctor
and see what you're do what's right with
your doctor you know if you want to do
the heavy metal detox smoothie some day
in your life if you want to learn
about it if you want to find the recipe
in the book or on the blog
ask your doctor if it's right for you
and see how they feel okay if your
doctor says don't do it don't do it
but the point is is that you can be
proactive
but yes what they're trying to tell you
now is they're trying to tell you this
copper pipes
those are good for you and it's a bad
trend
it's a dangerous one i think it's really
ignorant
really negligent and it's sad that the
guessing games have
to go on in alternative health over and
over again because in alternative health
nobody knows why anybody's sick they
never did and so it's back to the
guessing games let's go try this now
okay let's try this now
you know let's take tons of vinegar and
destroy all our teeth let's
you know and and and give us and give us
osteopenia
and you know like it's always a guessing
game and it's so sad you guys
and if anybody here is watching this
doesn't believe me and you're like oh no
he doesn't no
fine fine do whatever it is you want to
do do whatever it is you think is right
do all the copper you want do all
whatever you want do all the fermented
foods you want perfectly fine with that
if you're sick down the road remember
this information is here for you down
the road you might have a different
opinion 10 years from now
you guys are making some salsa
so much sherry says so much
contradiction information
with fat everyone does different i guess
on different diets no one size fits all
sure i wish that was true that's not
true here's how it works
we're all human beings and our livers
don't like a lot of fat
period but we react differently
because some of our livers are better
how in better health than
other people's liver livers okay
someone's liver
could be less toxic in the moment in
their life so they can handle more fat
and then all of a sudden you're thinking
well that person's just different
they're different than me and one one
size doesn't fit all
and you know but that's not how it works
it does fit all if it's all as a huge as
human the human race
our pancreases hate a lot of fat in our
diet and one person's pancreas
that can get weakened over time can go
into pancreatitis faster than someone
else okay
someone else's liver can get fatty liver
and get more fat built up in it than
someone else
faster than someone else but in the end
every body gets something
you can be the one someone can be the
one that just seems like they do fat
fine with all that high fat and then
later on they get their heart attack at
they get their heart attack at 72. they
did good all those years
they were eating all that fat and
finally all that fat builds up inside
their arteries
that fat build up inside their heart and
boom they got their heart attack just
like that you know
so it's important to know okay and like
all that fat that we're told to eat
whether it's nuts and seeds and avocados
and milk cheese butter
and whatever it is right chicken fat
gets built up in these arteries
over time it gets built up inside the
veins and what
fat does is it pulls the toxin in and
then becomes plaque plaque
is rancid fat hardened on the inside of
the
the inside of the heart in arteries and
veins and blood vessels
and it's infused with toxins or toxins
are infused in it
okay these are radical fats milk cheese
butter
eggs coconut oil canola oil olive oil
all different oils avocados now i'm not
saying they're not healthy fats i'm not
saying avocado
and coconut's not a healthy fat it is
but what i am
saying is we inundate ourselves with so
many fats of all kinds it all becomes
one in the end
you're doing chicken too much chicken
every single day you're doing 10 000
chickens in 15 years
it's and then you're still doing coconut
oil and you're still doing avocado and
you're still eating nuts
it builds up and it builds up and you're
still doing oils and it builds up and
you're still doing chocolate and it
builds up and guess what you get the
plaque
and you need the stints later on you're
55 years old you're 65 years old and
they're running a scope up your arteries
and intervenes and they're putting
stints in to keep them from collapsing
because so much fat build up inside
those arteries
meanwhile no one's going to pay the
price you think all those gurus that
told you
tons of fat do you think they're going
to pay the price and when you're 62
years old and you're laying on the
operating table
no they're not going to care about you
no one's going to care about you
all the trend setters that are like
they're they're like parroting each
other
and everybody's afraid to speak up about
anything and they're all like no no
fat's great
lots of fat okay lots of fat too over
there you think any of them are going to
care when you're on the operating table
again you're getting your valve replaced
because it was just lined with total
fat and corrosion and all kinds of
plaque they're not going to care
but you're going to pay the price 10 15
years 20 years later
that's how it works they don't care
about you all the trendsetters and gurus
that's that's how it happens
i'm not saying you can't eat fats we're
having guacamole tonight
not saying that taryn we're not all rich
these products are expensive
medical medical procedures are expensive
i got friends that got the co-payments
whatever that is the whole bit with it
whoa i mean and and trying to keep good
health insurance and then
that's expensive all on its own and then
it's not just that it's out-of-pocket
expenses when you're sick
all of it it's just wow that stuff can
just boom slam you but i get it if you
don't have
money go to the library get the book for
free
that's all and learn other things you
can do
that maybe you don't have to spend money
on a product maybe there's things
which there is you can help yourself
with foods certain foods like lowering
your fat
you don't have to be rich to lower your
fat
and learn how to eat a few other foods
you know what the you know what the
number one food are the number one foods
i tell everybody to eat guess what
it's the cheapest food there is out
there it's potatoes
you can even eat a conventional potato
it's the cheapest food out there
so i'm scratching my head saying do you
really have to be rich because
you know what the other food i tell
everybody to eat is
bananas okay i tell them to eat bananas
and you can do conventional bananas
right you guys so
i'm confused because conventional
bananas are like one of the cheapest
foods out there in the world whoa
potatoes are one of the cheapest foods
out in the world and you don't have to
be rich to eat them and guess what you
can walk into your library and get this
book for free
you already got to start and you don't
have to be rich
but i get what you're saying i get what
you're saying it's not easy it's not
easy at all
making a burrito bowl i got the food
right here
um we're tilt we're talking about copper
that's what we're talking about i'm
going to make
this salsa
i'm going to put in a bowl here first
mix it up get my tomatoes in here and
i'm going to get it ready to put it in
my other bowl
so i'm just getting some tomatoes here
i'm going to do more tomatoes than this
i'm making a salsa
this is going to be a really cool meal i
hope you guys stick around for it lots
of stuff to talk about too let's do some
more tomatoes
let's talk about copper a little bit
more iuds yeah i mean i understand if
if you have to have the iud and that's a
decision and choice you're making in
your life
completely understand or you got no
choice for some reason i
completely understand right but people
always ask me
like is it great no copper's not great
it's not great it's copper in the
reproductive system
um and and that that's very
it's very toxic but but but listen
i'm not saying you have to change your
choices
and be like well i can't have an iud
that's not it at all once you do what is
ever right for you and your doctor and
what your doctor believes too
but i got friends that ask me about with
iuds and they'll be like
family friends and they'll be like what
do i do and i'll be like
be proactive work on getting any copper
out of your system so
you can have your iud you can you can
get copper exposure you could eat
conventional produce that did
copper and pesticides your neighbor
sprays pesticides you buy new clothing
with fungicides it's all got copper in
it
and you're getting exposed to copper
every day be proactive
let's just work on getting it out so
um you know it's it's that's all
chopping up some tomatoes here
[Music]
making a salsa
and it's coming out great love it love
it love it
my son has type 1 diabetes advice on
that get
you can take the the books to the doctor
and talk about diabetes in the books
medical mean books get this free at the
library if you want it's also on sale at
amazon.com 51
off right now it's really an incredible
book your mind will be blown
what if you're a diabetic lowering fats
is actually
the best thing you can do is diabetic
okay you can always ask your doctor
what's right for you but that's what i
recommend friends and family
to do is lowering their fat intake so
try not to eat too many fats
what that means is that you're keeping
your fats like
say chicken or beef if you're eating
animal products to once a day maybe at
the end of the day
during the day you're not having a lot
of avocado you're not having a lot of
oils oils
really get the diabetics i'm just going
to be straight out if there's one thing
you can do and you can ask your doctor
what your doctor thinks
the one thing you can do is minimizing
your oils
right there that that alone is a big
deal
so i'm going to make this salsa what's
going to do
and the other thing is it's it's sugar
isn't the demon when it comes down to
diabetes okay
uh you shouldn't be on table sugar you
shouldn't be on unprocessed sugar
i'm talking about fruit is not the
problem with diabetics
it's fats so here's how it works when
you eat too much fat and fats in your
bloodstream
it stops the sugar from getting into
your cells
we only live function from
sugar entering our cells that's how we
can talk walk
hence blood sugar is why we're alive
right it's blood sugar but the more fat
you eat
the more your pancreas gets stressed out
more your liver is probably gets more
problematic
and the more insulin the more fat you
eat the more
insulin your pancreas has to release
that hormone
in order to bind onto sugar to enter it
into your cells right
you lower your fats less insulin needs
to be produced
and type 2 diabetes i can't tell you how
many cases reversed reversed 100 percent
they don't even have type 2. i i know so
many people that had type 2
including using insulin with their type
and other drugs and drugs and they beat
it
their type 2 diabetes free for life
they just had to lower their fats learn
how to heal you know i mean
it's just it's great information all
right let's just make the salsa right
here we're doing that
um need a clove of garlic it's one thing
you can do less garlic you can do a
little bit of garlic i'm just going to
use a small clove of garlic
okay you guys don't mind
so dark good to see you um you gotta you
gotta
you got a thought there question well
the heart primarily runs on fat the
heart's a muscle
it runs on sugar that's how
misinformation works i'm putting a
little
garlic inside this this salsa
your heart is a muscle
insulin drive sugar into your heart
cells
that's how it works um
why do you think doctors still are
worried about too much red meat
why do you think doctors
were worried about too many eggs and too
much red meat
because it'll get you a heart attack
because
fat here's how it works okay the more
fat you put in your bloodstream
the harder your heart has to work now
they didn't know that part that's
medical medium information
but the more fat in your bloodstream see
doctors just believe
that in the medical the surgeon general
many many years ago
many years ago decades ago believed
and they taught us at the medical
universities that too much red meat
and it's going to lead to a heart attack
and they're right about that
all that fat's going to plack up and
build up inside your heart right
so all that fat running through your
heart okay
is going to build up inside your heart
right
fat thickens the blood and when the
blood gets thick
heart has to kill itself to pump it
through
it's like it's like sucking a milkshake
through a straw versus water through a
straw
so when your heart's pumping so so dark
right so dark check this out when your
heart's pumping
it's killing itself to suck that fat
through the the veins to draw that fat
up through the veins
the heart is killing itself whoa there's
so much fat in that blood it's so thick
i
can't that's why they give you blood
thinners you start getting all those
problems and heart problems and blood
vessel problems they're just like oh my
god they start giving you blood thinners
is what they do
they're trying to thin out your blood so
your heart can even pump that stuff
see so no fat kills your heart
you can't doesn't mean you guys have to
quit your fats i don't want you all
upset
like oh my god i can't listen to this
guy anymore he he just wants us all fat
i can't live like
that and that's not it at all i'm just
saying look
baby steps get rid of the eggs is what i
would do get rid of the butter
the butter will kill you just get rid of
butter anybody tell you butter's healthy
man i mean it's just not i would get rid
of that okay you guys eat animal protein
fine you guys like salmon you like guys
like fish
even though there's metals in it that
i'd be doing if i was doing it if i was
eating salmon
i'd be doing you know my my medical
medium heavy metal detox movie that's
what i'm saying but
what i'm trying to tell you is you don't
have to change your life but you can go
as far as you want to heal
cooking with rebecca how are you doing
great you're on here high blood sugar
insulin resistance that's blood sugar
that's your sugar
that's any kind of sugar in your blood
okay
getting stuck it can't go into your
cells because there's too much fat
that's insulin resistance okay that's a
healthy fat
you guys should have some avocado here
and there if you're really sick
and you're trying to heal i got a lot of
different cleanses in the book
talking about how to do it how to lower
the fats how to eat a certain way to
heal different conditions and symptoms
you guys should check out the cleansing
i don't talk about this book enough this
book is life-saving because it's already
saved
countless lives around the planet right
now okay that's a book you guys might
want to check out
and then the other one is the book
coming out right now
which is incredible which is the new
edition medical medium new edition
revised and expanded you guys
that's that's the recipe here that i'm
making which is the burrito bowl you
guys got to check that book out
all right got some garlic in my salsa
i'm making a salsa right now
i've got garlic in there um and then i'm
gonna put a little bit of
cilantro in here there we go got a
little bit of cilantro i'm gonna chop up
some red onion oh no the red onion
[Music]
no
i know this onion's gonna do i got this
batch of red onions
it's so strong i'm already getting
nervous
this this onion messed me up last time
where my my eyes were crying
i was crying like a baby
i know it's coming again tara anthony i
love your books and info but seem to
have built in
forgetter and dumbfounded that
that i have worse acne after a year of
being faithful but not perfect
i have grains sometimes and maybe seven
grams of fat
one week is this is this it
i'll just give you some quick tips real
q real quick right
make sure make sure the nutritional
yeast isn't there make sure the caffeine
isn't there
make sure there's no chocolate there
because that'll lower your immune system
chocolate lowers your immune system the
caffeine
lowers your immune system very important
okay so keep that in mind
all right i'm gonna chop up a little
onion real quick here you guys
um nutritional yeast
that's an acne bomb
be cautious about that okay caffeine
like i said
chocolate like i said be careful these
are acne bombs
get the acne periodically vinegar apple
cider vinegar
be careful right there acne
okay these are just giving you some
quick quick tips
seven grams of fat what fat source is it
is it just avocado
because that's what i would do if you're
if that's what i would do
if i had acne or anything like that i
would be like probably i would do hemp
seeds or avocado
that's the fats i would use if you still
want some fat
um so give me any any any other tips i
can
um these are just some right i'm gonna
put lime juice in the salsa so i'm gonna
put a little lime juice in there right
now
there we go
and think about any new medications any
new pharmaceuticals that might be
kicking around or you might have gotten
or something ask your doctor about it
but
a lot of times that can lower the immune
system stimulate something but you can
ask your doctor about that info
friends will say well i've got something
going on here and i've been like what's
going on and they're like i'm not doing
anything i'm all just
this new whatever and you know this new
medication and be like well
ask your doctor but it might be
something going on there and then
i mean that's that's you know these are
just some things and also
are you around other people you can
easily pick up another strap strap is
behind acne you can get rid of your
stress you can get rid of your
you can get rid of the strep that caused
acne in the past okay
so you can get rid of that so what
happens is you're doing the medical
medium information
are you doing the protocol for acne ask
your doctor if it's right for you but if
you're doing the protocol for acne
all the different stuff you might have
killed off and got rid of the first
strap
causing acne a lot of people might have
two straps in them they might have three
straps in them
and so you kill off the strap and your
acne goes away and then
you're at a public bathroom somewhere in
in some kind of place or a restaurant
and you end up picking up another strap
they're so easy to get
and um and then that incubates over time
and now you got a new acne now you got
to do all the same stuff and get rid of
it
these are just a few tips right here i
can throw at you guys
okay so now i'm going to make the
guacamole
so let me mix this up here this is the
salsa a little garlic little onion so
you guys can see right here
i'm gonna put this in my burrito bowl
right here okay so i'm gonna put it over
here in the corner
this is what i'm gonna do so i'll show
you what i got so far
you guys are with me
so this is my burrito bowl i got
salsa on one side i got cauliflower
flour rice on the other side
i got some lettuce down here but i'm
also going to put the guacamole in now
so let me get that going
just having so much fun with you guys
hanging out it's just such a it's such
an honor to have you here in my kitchen
i never tell you guys that enough
i just want to say thank you for being
here and um
i'm proud of all you guys all of you
guys
a lot of people who start medical medium
information are already getting sick
why else do people just start doing
stuff you know
or they've been sick a long time they
start medical meme information because
they've been sick a long time they've
had problems going on for a long time
but a lot of people go to medical meal
information after being healthy for a
long time or feeling healthy and what
happens is they got something coming on
they're starting to feel it and they'll
get this instinct like whoa i'm not
feeling that good i better start
something and then they start medical
medium information
but what was coming on was already
coming on and then
they're like whoa wait a minute is it
the mm info is it whatever but what they
don't know is the mm info is really
protecting them so it wouldn't come on
even worse or they can get it better
even faster later
a lot of people also you know but yeah
so let me get this guacamole going let
me get a fork out and do a little mash
um in this guacamole i'm gonna put a
little lime juice
i'm going to put another clove of garlic
in here now if you guys are
sensitive with garlic because it's
pretty strong it's a pretty strong
flavor and everything if you're
sensitive garlic you might
you know you might you can hold it back
if you want
so i got some garlic going here what i
would do if i had acne i'd be doing the
clean advanced cleanse repeatedly as an
option
that's what i would do so i'd do the
advanced 369 repeatedly
as an option if i had acne or i would do
a mono eating cleanse in there i'd be
doing 32 ounces
of celery juice if i had acne
okay guys i'm gonna get some garlic in
here making some guacamole as we speak
and i would make sure there's no grains
including oatmeal
oatmeal won't feed strep it won't but
it's a grain
that that takes up space and you could
be eating something else it could be
more healthful like potato
or something okay so i'm making the
guacamole i put some garlic in there and
i'm trying to look
and i will see i'm looking at your
comments you guys see if i see anything
else
um and then i'm gonna put a little red
onion in this guacamole
a little bit of red onion
[Music]
that one onion the other day you
remember that you guys i don't know if
you've seen that other video there or
that other live one onion was so strong
and this one
this one got me a little bit too
put some onion in there
so i'm going to mash this up
look the whole thing with medical medium
information is you can
take it as far as you need to go if
you've got eczema you've got psoriasis
if you've got acne
you've got lyme disease if you've got
chronic fatigue if you've got
hashimoto's if you got anything even if
you have fibrosis whatever you've got
going on whatever
you've been tagged with whatever
autoimmune you've been tagged with
you can go you can go places
so i got a little bit of guacamole here
i put a little red onion in here
okay so i got that now that's going to
go in here
[Music]
i'm going to put this in the corner
you guys might be able to there you go
then i put a little lettuce over here
little pieces of lettuce what i like to
do is put a little piece of lettuce that
i can actually
put a little guacamole on the lettuce
and i'm gonna sprinkle some lime over
everything so i like to put a little
lettuce here
in the corner so what i have is
i have my salsa this is the burrito bowl
that came out of medical medium new
addition
all right i'm a slice of lime in here
[Music]
i'm even going to make this a little
pretty here i'm going to put a little
slice of lime in there to you on the
edge now actually i'll hold that off
and
put a little wedge here
a little lime wedge on the side is what
i put there
anyway you can do it any kind of
anything you want to do
some people don't like lime some people
do you can put a wedge on here too
i put it on the edge of the bowl but you
can put it on the side
[Music]
like this just giving you some options
which is awesome
like that i'm gonna put it with
the tomatoes over here so you can see it
so
but i got what i have here is and let me
get some chili flakes
just going to put a little bit on i'm
not going to put a lot of chili flakes
but i'm put sprinkling a few chili
flakes on top like this
i mean i like heat personally but i
don't like it too too hot
i'm going to squeeze a little lime on
here too
like that so this is salsa
i got the guacamole right there
okay i got a little lettuce here and
it's also on lettuce that's been chopped
up underneath it
cauliflower rice which is really
delicious so that's the burrito bowl
right here you guys
incredible right so you guys if you
haven't already
this is coming out soon and guess what
i'm not going to be holding the
manuscript pretty soon next time i do a
live i'm going to be holding the actual
book in my hand
and this is the manuscript i gave the
publisher
after i finished the book
check out cleans the heel and if you
want to learn about
toxic heavy metals you can find out
about it in the books of course i just
showed you
that's what i use for myself right there
that spirulina that barley grass juice
powder
um ask your doctor what you can use okay
but that's what i tell family and
friends to use
i'm not sponsored it's just great isn't
nicholas doesn't it look good
is this incredible i mean you guys this
is going to be really good so i might
even take some extra lettuce pieces
and put it inside the lettuce pieces i'm
heading over to instagram are you guys
coming
because i'm going there i'm going to be
live and tick tock so tic toc
at the same time as instagram
okay and um i'll see you then
love you guys