how many people do you know who struggle
with their health chances are whether
they show it or not most of the people
in your life do and chances are you're
one of them whether you're dealing with
anxiety depression endometriosis acne
eczema autoimmune thyroid lime brain fog
fatigue or any other symptom or
condition you're far from from
alone living with symptoms has become
The New Normal so no more guessing games
it's time to get answers welcome to the
medical medium podcast I'm Anthony
William today we're on round two of
problematic and damaging supplements now
let's face it you don't make friends
talking about this stuff because there's
a lot of people out there greasing each
other's Palms scratching each other's
backs looking the other way it's a dog
eat dog world in the health business out
there but people need to know what's
going on what they're ingesting what
they're taking what the potential is to
cause harm and other problems it's
critical get ready for round two fasten
your seat belts because we're definitely
going on a ride with this
one yep there's the deer it's right over
there are you ready
are you locked in loaded I got my gun we
just got to get one bullet in the deer
and then the deer drops and then we cut
the antlers off you know like
everybody's doing the deer antler I told
you it's going to fix your Ed it is your
wife's going to be happy okay yeah just
get ready stop
complaining I know we've been out here a
couple hours but we're going to save a
lot of money we just got to kill the
deer we can eat some of the meat we
could sell it it's venison make more
money I don't know no you have know the
deer velvets on the
antler and then you can use both I think
and we can like grind it on top of food
like pepper like enough of this yeah we
just have to get the deer and then we
can leave the deer behind if you don't
want to lift it well just cut the
antlers off just leave the deer
behind yeah yeah okay okay yeah well
it's going to help my libido I've had no
libido for a long time now and the deer
antler is going to help with you it's
going to help with your Ed and you know
that you know how that problem you have
where you keep on having to scratch your
ass that could even go away yeah and
your feet they're so stinky where I
can't even be in the truck with you that
could get better too yeah of course it's
like it does
everything just get ready there's the
deer it's walking right into our sights
where you going you got a pee all right
just go behind a
tree when it comes down to creature
Parts creature Parts they're willing to
spin anything in everything out there
they'll take a piece of a shark's fin
they'll take a gizzard from a turkey
they'll take a testicle from a bowl
they'll take a fin from a catfish
they'll take a wing off of a
butterfly they'll just try to say
anything and everything and they'll spin
it they'll just work on creatures take
creatures apart give you pieces of
creatures colostrum is a really good
example of that they'll take that away
from the little baby cows the baby
calves and they'll just
colostrum they'll tell a whole bunch of
women in social media how good it is for
them they'll think they're glowing when
they're consuming
it they'll be dly in any way they can
out there collagen is a prime example
they remove it from creatures and then
they sell it to a whole bunch of women
out there that get promised they'll
anti-age by 20 or 30 years another
example is the black market with whale
meat whale meat is supposed to bring
life to people rejuvenate them bring
back their libido so let's kill a whale
out in the ocean just so a bunch of
people bunch of men can think they get
their libido back and people still
believe out there that if you eat a
creature part it could fix your part if
you eat brain it'll fix your brain eat
an eye it'll fix your eye eat a kidney
it'll support and fix your kidney eat a
liver and it will somehow heal your
liver or heal you same thing with eating
Hearts beef Hearts to big one out there
a lot of people doing beef Hearts that's
another example a prime example of
eating creatures creature Parts organs
and thinking it's going to fix your
organs so eating a beef heart will fix
your
heart it's back to the Dark Ages with
this stuff it's back a thousand years
ago 800 years ago ago 500 years ago it's
the Dark Ages it's actually
darkness and the thing is it's an easy
cell for some reason everybody believes
it almost almost everybody out there now
medical meme information published info
about this and how that's not how it
works like collagen you can't grow
collagen or produce collagen inside your
body by eating collagen it doesn't work
and now that information's getting
poached and people are talking about
that out there now you can only build
collagen by having building blocks that
you're eating and
utilizing you can't fix your eyeball
problem eating a whole bunch of
different eyeballs cow eyeballs sheep
eyeballs all sitting inside your gut
putrifying and rotting it's not going to
fix your eye issue but you probably know
this already you probably understand
that definitely right cuz it only makes
sense but yet so tricky out there it's
easy to fall prey for creature Parts
Dear Antler that's a prime example every
now and then you'll hear something about
Dear Antler dear velvet and it's like
the Panacea once again this will fix you
and people believe it they do and then
they look for sources of Dear Antler
dear velvet they're looking out there
and they find different sources like
this stuff is the good stuff kind of
like the CBD thing this is really good
CBD here at this place better than that
CBD we have this in our CBD we have that
in our CBD you're looking for the best
stuff Dear Antler the same thing people
become connoisseurs they look for it now
the hormones in Deer Antler do something
that you don't want to do to your body
it's disrupt naturally producing and UR
curring hormones it's disrupting your
hormones so when you do the deer antler
thing you're throwing a monkey wrench
into your hormone
makers so how does the monkey wrench
happen What goes wrong well the hormone
compounds in Dear Antler they interfere
with yours how they're steroid compounds
steroids do something terrible to our
hormonal production our adrenals our
glands our endocrine system it
interferes with it steroids taken long
term can really cause all kinds of human
growth
problems Dear Antler it can throw off
your thyroid profile your thyroid
hormone production your adrenal hormone
production your reproductive system
hormone
production and your liver hormone
production your liver produces a lot of
hormones and deer antler the steroid
compounds can interfere with that and
keep in mind the deer antler thing it's
really a man's thing once again not
looking at women women's needs how their
bodies really work and it's all a trick
when it comes down to Deer Antler it's a
bunch of guys trying it out playing with
it seeing how it works if it does or not
it's like one big experiment and then
women
they're told you should be doing this
too this is really good for you
meanwhile it's a disaster and deer
antler steroid compounds can knock the
hair off of women's heads over time can
create adrenal fatigue can create really
dry dry skin it's just really not worth
it it's the definition of snake oil this
next one pains me and I mean that it
pains me it slipped through the cacks it
really did and it's finding itself in
all kinds of different places and Health
Products dious Earth dious Earth
particles talking about a real meoo it's
this one I'll never forget something
that happened someone reached out to me
who needed my help a
doctor he told me that he got really
sick from something and I saidwhat and
he said diecious Earth
particles I said tell me what happened
and he said I dumped him on my
couch to take care of cat
dander
fleas cat fur and cat smell because I
have cats said okay and he said and then
my life was turned upside down it
destroyed my life he told me he was
triggered his body started falling apart
he inhaled the dious Earth and it broke
his immune system down and things just
started to go wrong he was in full body
pain he was suffering couldn't function
couldn't sleep could barely eat anything
could barely walk all because of the
dious earth he was completely convinced
and positive it was a dious Earth
particles that he inhaled he spent
months trying to get it out of his house
he got rid of his couch he got rid of
all his furniture he vacuumed over and
over and over again and he said well I
had my friend come over and vacuum
because I couldn't even use my arms the
tops of my shoulders hurt so bad that if
I bumped into a wall it floored me he
was stuck in his apartment living there
saying that he was still breathing it in
he can still smell it it drove him mad
he asked me if I recommend iaus Earth I
said no and I said that s so agrees with
him and I said to him s so agrees with
you on it being a trigger I helped him
with his recovery brought him back to
functioning brought him back to life he
was able to live his life but he was
injured from it emotionally mentally and
even physically
the dious Earth was a trigger a trigger
lowering his immune system allowing
other things to creep up and take over
and this isn't the only time I've seen
it happen dious Earth should not be
eaten and it shouldn't be used for
anything it agitates and clings to the
intestinal Linings it doesn't leave the
intestinal tract quickly it's
abrasive it creates a problem with
sensitive nerves it's a trigger for all
around anything it's just a menace and
when it's
inhaled it lowers the immune system it
confuses the immune system white blood
cells see dious Earth as foreign
Invaders and when the immune system
drops because dious Earth is lowering
the immune system when you're breathing
it in then anything in the body can rise
up Invaders that live with people
stealth vir es come out of dormy Epstein
bar shingles hhv6 herpes simplex one can
all of a sudden get a leg up and still
to this day when I see dious Earth in
health and beauty and all kinds of
different Health stuff food supplements
I scratch my head and I go nobody gets
it this next one digestive bitters is
kind of funny because really it's
useless every now and then you'll see
out there an influencer be like I'm
using these digestive bitters I'm using
Bitters and they're all into it like
here's bitters my practitioner gave me
these bitters or I got them here online
from this place and when they do that
what's really happening is they're just
drinking basically they're taking shots
of alcohol they're drinking bitters have
always had alcohol in it they've always
had alcohol in it corn grain alcohol now
in the earlier days it would be bourbon
whiskey rum it would be vodka it would
be another type of alcohol in there but
now it's shifting so now it's shifting
to something different set of corn grain
alcohol or some other variety of alcohol
they're doing glycerin and they're
usually doing a blend now be like
glycerin and alcohol because let's face
it they're drinking bitters because of
the alcohol people don't know it but
they get addicted to it helps them sleep
at night they're basically having a shot
of alcohol before bed but it's shifting
because of medical medium
information all the years letting people
know that alcohol destroys the
phytochemical compounds the medicine the
nutrients herbal tinctures with alcohol
in them makes them ineffective bottom
line so now that system out there that
was built on alcohol and all the
tinctures and the bids is Shifting and
changing so now bids they'll have
they'll be split they'll be glycerin and
alcohol tinctures now too glycerin and
alcohol and there's even bitters out
there now that are just glycerin now
truly in order for a bitter to be called
a bitter and a bitter to be a bitter
alcohol has to be there so when someone
purchases a bidder now they purchasing a
fraud a fraud bidder it's missing the
alcohol now it's just an herbal tincture
with glycerin in it that's all it is now
it's not a bitter anymore has to have
the alcohol in it to become a bitter and
Bitters with glycerin without the
alcohol have all these natural flavors
in them now so if you buy a bitter it
may not have the alcohol it's not a
bitter anymore it's a fraud then it has
the glycerin so now it's just a tincture
with glycerin an herbal tincture but
worse it's an herbal tincture with a bad
glycerin not even a good glycerin and
then it's got all kinds of different
flavorings and citric acid and all kinds
of other stuff in there Bitters and
digestive bitters are essentially
useless and when it comes down to
alcohol it's bad bad bad there's no good
good good in any of it it's bad and what
happens is that alcohol was taboo over
the years and medical medium information
talked about it being bad all the
different podcast doctors and health
authors and everybody in the last just
couple decades always recreationally
drank they drank they had martinis they
had wine everybody laid off the subject
nobody said that alcohol was bad nobody
said wine or alcohol or any kind of
alcoholic beverage was bad medical
medium information said no no know it's
bad for the brain it'll rot your brain
we have all the information Spirit and I
it's in the books brainsaver book is one
example right there and so everybody
thinks alcohol was okay and just keep it
at that no one wanted to even approach
it it was just like hands off hands off
now you see out there you see different
articles out there people on social
media talk about how alcohol it's bad
for you it's bad for you and you hear
that now they're just paring medical
medium information but alcohol and
tinctures is disastrous herbal tinctures
alcohol and Bitters disastrous so let's
head into our next topic essential oils
now I know what you're thinking off the
bat on that one is like no way why would
there be a problem with essential oils
it's not possible what is he talking
about what is this going to be oh you
must be talking about the fake essential
oils that's what it is no it's not
talking about the good essential oils
the stuff where it's the best of the
best of the best and all these people
are trying to sell them and they're in
everything and people are putting
essential oils in everything and
essential oils are used in all kinds of
stuff body products and everything else
yes talking about essential oils if
you're someone with a sensitive nervous
system a sensitive sensitive nervous
system cranial nerves inflamed nerves
maybe you don't even know you have a
sensitive central nervous system and
you're just fatigued and don't even know
you have neurological fatigue but if
you're somebody with all kinds of
different headaches all kinds of
different ticks spasms burning skin pain
throughout the body roving pain
throughout the body insomnia anxiety
nervousness maybe you're somebody with
tingles on your body numbness on your
body all kinds of different aches and
pains you're just a sensitive central
nervous system person inflamed cranial
nerves don't even know it probably
essential oils aren't a great thing sure
if you smell them a little bit maybe
it's thinned out and put into an oil and
you use it as a little type of body
lotion or something and even there
that's fine but if you're somebody
really hypers sensitive and you're told
to ingest them digest them ingest them
drink them eat them take them internally
that's where it goes all wrong a lot of
people are living with sensitive vagus
nerves they're spasming they're
inflamed they're causing problems in
their intestinal tract they're causing
problems in how they feel overall
they're giving them fatigue they're
giving them all kinds of different ticks
and spasms and then you drink or eat an
essential oil like a therapy some kind
of therapeutic way where someone's like
yes do these essential oils take them
internally drink them on a regular basis
therapeutically weekly every day twice a
day and then you flare the nerves up
they go on fire they light up and
symptoms actually get Advanced versus
Retreat and essential oils can make
nerves hypers sensitive like OV excite
them your senses they can be over
excited by them especially when you're
somebody that's really sensitive where
it gets into the sinuses and it's in
there deep and it's actually exciting
the nerves if someone's inflamed and
they got inflamed cranial nerves this
could be an
overload now whenever I utter this stuff
out about essential oils people just
start throwing stones and
pitchforks torches all come out people
do not like hearing this first thing you
hear is not my Essential Oils not the
ones I use this is the best of the best
they extract it from the bark of a
Amazon Tree it's handcrafted it's put in
the bottle just right nothing's added in
it and that's different and I use them
for healing and my therapy and
everything else and my client's therapy
and all this other stuff and you hear
this stuff and I'm like okay okay I get
it I'm listen I'm talking about chronic
illness here I'm talking about people
with central nervous systems that are on
fire they're already on fire from all
kinds of viruses and they got
neurological lime and multiple sclerosis
or just a host of symptoms no one under
understands mystery symptoms they're
already suffering they're already
struggling and when you ingest these
when you actually take these in
internally it could literally stir the
pot I've seen it it
happens and I'm just saying taken
internally drinking them eating them
ingesting them that's the bad part
that's the part that's risky that's the
part where people are telling everybody
at the time especially during the
explosion the essential oil explosion
when everybody was like a dealer an
essential oil dealer and all of social
media was taken over by essential oil
salese well they'll just be like drink
it um use it in your enema um use it in
your ears I mean people were just
screaming to use it in any way possible
but when it comes down to The Chronic
Leo they were getting injured left and
right I'm not anti- essential oil that's
not what this is I'm not anti- essential
oil if it's in some type of Body
ointment and you got to be careful there
too something will say it has essential
oils in it but yet it still has perfume
and perfume with an essential oil a lot
of products say they have essential oils
in it or it's essential oil when it's a
mixed bag of nuts it'll have a whole
bunch of different fragrances mixed with
essential oil and once again I'm not
anti- essential oil I see the value in
it it does hold value especially high
quality essential oil oils but ingesting
them and taking them internally is risky
especially when you have a sensitive
central nervous system and so many
people with chronic illness really
struggle with that another thing about
essential oils that isn't a great thing
is people use them in a way that gets
oil all over the house they put it in
the laundry gets on the couches they
have it on their arms and Body in the
sense where they're wet they're wetting
themselves down down with essential oils
and they're being told to so they got it
all over them they lean against the wall
they rub it on the wall they put it on
the kitchen counters they clean with it
they're diffusing it all day in their
house so it's clinging to everything
clinging to the walls they're actually
using it when they go to bed at night
it's rubbed in their sheets it's on
their pillows and remember it's in oil
and it's usually in carriers when
they're rubbing it on their bodies so
what's happening is that oil is getting
everywhere and then when that oils on
the couch and it's on the blankets and
it's on the furniture food particles end
up landing on it dander ends up landing
on it it collects it collects stuff it
collects dust the oil collects dust it
goes into the oil when it's just
floating around the house and then over
time mold starts to grow and everybody's
worried about mold everybody's freaking
out about mold essential oil s can bring
mold it doesn't mean the actual medicine
extraction in the essential oil or of
the essential oil or the essential oil
is the worst thing as far as mold
creating it's just when it gets away
from us when it's on everything when
it's on the blankets then you wash the
blanket but it doesn't all come out
everything just starts to stay damp oil
dampness that's what it's called and
what happens is that oil damp is on
everything it's in the carpet it's on
the floor it's on the hardwood floor
it's on the tables it's on the curtains
it's everywhere and oil dampness
collects mold now it doesn't mean you
can't use a diffuser it's just that
people overdo it they do it where
they're not even diluting it it's
straight lots of oil going in everywhere
and it's on their skin it's on their
body it's on their clothes they're
sitting on furniture it's everywhere
it's not controlled it's not balanced so
diffusers fine you could use diffusers
to put some Rosemary in there and try to
keep mold down but if there's oils
everywhere including the carriers
everywhere all around the house on
everything it gets out of control and it
changes the
balance keep in mind this is light ears
from the synthetic oilbased air
fresheners the plugins that people have
every day out there that are admitting
this disgusting oil filled with
chemicals and it's just leeching
everywhere and landing on everything
this is different but still it creates a
dampness and oil dampness and brings
about mold over time there are many more
problematic and damaging supplements to
talk about and we're going to get
through all of these as we go along if
you want a definitive guide pick up
medical medium brain saver
oh my God this deer is 800 lb just grab
the
legs where you going why are you sitting
down why are you
crying it was a good shot you hit it
right between the
eyes yeah that was an unbelievable shot
we just have to cut the antlers off but
once we cut the antlers off could just
leave this out here to rot for All We
Care yeah
we just need the deer antler you know
I'm don't you want your Ed fixed it just
hurry up grab the other end of the deer
there we just got to pull it a little
over here and we can then saw off these
antlers once again
fold by another experimental game and
Trend that makes someone who's unwell
feel like like it's a win but it ain't
and it comes with hidden unforeseen
pain so easily
tricked time and time again I think it's
a
sin these days it's all about the health
Fame God Is Watching every one of them
God is watching the hustlers the wealthy
biohackers and knows almost everyone
playing the health field is bought and
sold it used to be only in the fashion
world and store households rightfully so
but now it's weeded its way into every
chronically ill person's home up above
it's all seen they're in it for
themselves not the ones who suffer these
days it's all about the bread and butter
what what a
conundrum what a
mother healing is constantly
misconstrued the chronically ill get
misunderstood the goal is for them to be
used they want to heal they're solicited
a magic pill The Carpet Baggers and the
Sharks want a steak they come out of the
woodwork the replicas they fakes
what does it take for the truth to come
out and shed light upon the ones that
are unwell and in need of help they
should be outed they're Devils that
scream and shout confusing the bear
throwing them all in a forever snare
it's time to be wise beyond your years
doesn't matter how old you are it's time
to learn and grow and heal
original published medical medium
information gets stolen and poached by
podcast doctors social media doctors
influencers and medical clinics medical
medium information has never yet been
proven Wrong by medical science and
research instead the opposite only
proven right and then taken from medical
medium published material and used in
the conventional and alternative Health
communities medical medium information
continually sets the stage for medical
science to understand chronic illness
better if you choose to share or use the
original unique content from the medical
medium podcast books or medical medium
social media please site where this
information comes from so others who see
and learn of this information have a
chance to know where it all originates
to give them an opportunity to heal so
they don't end up losing years of their
life searching for answers like so many
have before them the medical medium
information here on this podcast doesn't
come from broken science interest groups
medical funding with strings attached
botched research lobbyists internal
Kickbacks persuaded belief systems
private panels of influencers health
field payoffs trendy traps or gathered
bits and pieces of gimmicky confusion
because chronic illness is exploding
like never before in our Modern Day
history it takes a greater force than us
down here it takes a helping hand from
above medical medium information has
street cred it's an organic movement of
countless people around the world
healing more healing stories of real
people not being paid to tell their life
Chang ing experiences of rising out of
the ashes of sickness and entering into
the light of full recovery getting their
lives back and finally healing when
nothing else in the world of Health
could move the needle and get them
better the information on this podcast
is not man-made it comes from above from
a higher source whatever you believe in
whether God the universe the light or
the Creator or if you believe in nothing
at all that we're just floating through
space together on this rock know that
the information you hear on this podcast
is separate from all the other noise out
there it comes from a different place
appear here on tampered with Advanced
Clean uncorrupted original primary
source a higher source Spirit of
compassion