I'm at Cafe Gratitude a Legendary
Legendary restaurant everybody knows
about Cafe Gratitude and what we're
looking at right here I'm with Chef Drew
right here okay and I am honored to
actually be standing here for a lot of
reasons the food's incredible here but
what's happening is medical medium
dishes are going to be on the menu here
they are right here Drew just dressed
them up this is an incredible thing
happening I don't even know what to say
because I'm that excited Drew thank you
for doing all that you've done to help
this happen to make this happen and I
think people are really going to love
this because this is incredible healing
food no oils we don't even have nuts in
these dishes this is incredible no soy
in these dishes these are clean as clean
and pure can ever get here at Cafe
Gratitude where only that could happen
here that's incredible that's how
incredible this restaurant is so I'm
excited Drew thank you thank you for the
opportunity to work together I think
this is an incredibly inspiring
collaboration I'm really really excited
about it well I'm honored can you tell
us a little bit about your work right
here what Chef Drew did he elevated the
medical medium recipes and he was like
look we can do this and we can do a
little bit of this your people will love
it and I'm like oh my God bring it on
and now they are unbelievable so medical
medium food is like now was here now
it's here and in here so it doesn't get
any better than that so that's how
excited I am thank you I mean it's it's
an alignment of working with Whole Foods
working with with herbs rather than
spices no oils which you know really
allows you to explore other palletes
which I think is really an exciting
opportunity as a chef I love that I'm
excited I can't wait to see people come
in order these dishes taste them and
taste that healing effect that clean
incredible Pure Food going into their
body here at Cafe Gratitude I mean that
I'm so excited about this to see people
their reactions how they feel with the
food they're going to love it already
people love the medical medium you know
recipes the medical medium Entre and all
that but when they come here and they
actually have your work collaborated
with these medical medium recipes and
you I mean Drew you were amazing Cafe
Gratitude they're just like what do you
like we'll do this we'll do that what
what do your people look out for what
are they worried about right right all
well Organics for sure that's something
that we're really focused on Whole Foods
for sure we don't use any of the
processed you know sort of plant-based
foods and I just really feel like people
will come and have the experience this
menu in a way that doesn't feel like it
was an afterthought you know to be able
to come in and have the dietary
guidelines that you're promoting out in
the world coming into a restaurant
setting and still having a really
flavorful Rich experience I mean it's
it's incredible and you worked hard on
these that's the thing you weren't like
hey aw give me a couple of dish is
you're like let's work on this let's
work together on this and you worked
hard we did it this is incredible and
it's right here and when people come in
they're going to be like oh my God I'm
actually able to get medical medium
dishes in Cafe Gratitude yeah that is a
big deal that is huge for the medical
medium community so many people they
they have a hard time getting dishes out
there getting foods that they want out
there and restaurants and they're always
in restaurants saying can you give me
this can you give me that they don't
know what they're getting they're always
worried and so they don't have to worry
when they come in and Cafe grat at you
that's what's incredible it's like all
that worry goes away you just come in
and you get the best of the best right
here don't even have to think about it
the highest quality and that's
mind-blowing right there and I'm excited
that the caic Gratitude customer is
going to be able to experience this
other way of eating which they may have
not have had the experience before so
another exting yeah yeah totally it's
like people are going to be like what is
this medical medium you know like what
is what is the protocol what what does
it heal you know how can I learn more
about it so that's what they're going to
get from from this menu C incredible and
then you elevated you actually brought
even more flavor to it and that is you
took it to the next level of more flavor
so I really appreciate it and the
medical medium people are going to
appreciate that too they're going to be
like this is better than making it
themselves or this is better than any
any place they can get it's not even
possible actually this is where you get
it it's right here at Cafe Gratitude so
I'm grateful and thank you for all your
hard work this is amazing
[Music]