so true give me the uh load down on this
on some of the masterful work that
you've done with the medical medium
dishes I know they're no oil no nuts
which is incredible all on its own
glutenfree soy free soy free and easy on
the salt exactly so tell me a little bit
about how like working with those
parameters and everything well I mean it
was like I said it was a great
opportunity to look at cooking in a new
way so it was and and to look for
alternatives to the traditional flavor
builders that we usually use in food um
as you know part of the collaboration
that we have here is that we assign
affirmation names to all of our food
which actually helps the healing process
in our opinion um and mine too yeah
right it is a good thing so here we have
imys which is our green papaya and kelp
noodle salad um with a coconut based
dressing and lots of Thai spices and
herbs here we've got the I Am Noble for
the noble potato because it's the spicy
potato burrito bowl with your cheese
sauce and the potato is Noble for sure
exactly and a healing food a lot of
people don't know that so that's really
powerful the name goes perfect with it
right there and we've got a black bean
picadillo that goes with that and then
some water sauteed kale and some great
Pico deallo W you got the kale that's
incredible to got some greens in there
to sort of lighten it up a bit and so
this is I am trustworthy which is your
uh original portabello and uh pepper
fajita dish we've dressed it up with a
little bit of lemon marinated red onions
some guacamole and some P DEA with a
squeeze of lime as well and we serve it
with the Millet tortillas which are I
think you're sort of famous for those
right you can see it's the Perfect Blend
and you got the Millet tortilla you can
put a little bit of guacamole in there
you can put a little bit of the onion in
there you can make it the way you want
it that's incredible and then it becomes
like finger food then you have in your
hands you can enjoy it then you can add
a little bit more that's exciting I'm
actually I can't wait that's the first
thing I go to is that right there cuz I
want those little tortillas in my hand
and I want to put a little bit of that
guacamole and you know your guacamole
that's a whole different kind of
guacamole and I know that because I've
tried guacamole in different places and
Cafe Gratitude guacamole is another
level it actually has flavor and that's
the key well in part of the affirmation
healing you can trust that everything in
this plate is going to be good for the
body right so that's what we're calling
it
trustworthy and the last one that we're
having as part of the menu here is the I
am insightful which is a jasmine rice an
organic jasmine rice vegetable Sushi we
serve it with uh pumpkin seed tofu which
is something that I think is a really
great sort alternative another whole
food avocado some vegetables carrots
cabbage and also some cucumber in there
as well you got the zinc and the Pumpkin
Seed so there's just there's healing
there's all kinds of different aspects
of these dishes that are healing in oh I
want to go to the papaya which is
incredible you're not using the Hawaiian
papaya no that is mindblowing right
there because you know like just if
somebody's going to use papaya it always
seems to be the Hawaiian papaya and I'm
like no this is incredible so you got
the shredded papaya and that's IM Amy
yes we we work with Organics pretty much
exclusively and I believe under the
organic certifications you can't have
the genetically modified papaya so
that's why we don't go with the Hawaiian
one unfortunately but that's just the
reality it's just the reality of it oh
we forgot the precious the uh wild
blueberry and cherry smoothie there it
is right there an mm smoothie okay and
that's the wild blueberry that's the
Cherry people are going to love the
flavor it's B orang juice oh it's so
good and so so rich but yet so light
you're satiated but you won't leave like
we're feeling real heavy and greasy and
all that it's absolutely not absolutely
not just healing food people can fill up
get satiated and then they can do
whatever they need to do they're
workouts they can go to the beach
whatever they got to do live their life
but they got the best food purest forms
they don't have the uh the nuts and the
oils and I'm not saying that like nuts
are terrible or anything like that it's
just that these are breaking those rules
it's like the no oil the no soy the no
gluten the no nuts and then the easy on
the salt I mean it's mind-blowing well
the more the more guidelines that we can
follow here the the more people we can
bring into this way of eating right so
if somebody wants to eat healthier but
can't eat nuts then half of the menu you
know is not going to be available in
this case they can have the whole thing
there's no nothing that they don't have
to uh not have you know I challenge
people to come in and try it I really do
I want to see what their pal how their
palette responds how they feel about the
flavors I want to see them give it a
shot try it see what they like about it
I want them to be honest about how they
feel everything and that's what I'm
excited about is having people come in
and being like hey okay you know what
let me take a look at this let me try
this wow you know what we got something
here and like I said before and this is
a big deal to me you took you took the
the recipes and you said aw let's do
this let's do a little of this let's do
a little of this and that is incredible
and I'm so excited about about that
seriously that's what chefs do I'm going
to be coming in that's what chefs do
that's what that's what amazing chefs do
and I'm going to come in and I'm going
to be ordering it too so and I want
people to know that I'm going to be in
here a lot so it's not just like once in
a while um you know if you come in here
there's a chance you're going to see me
somewhere sitting in here I'm going to
be enjoying these dishes and I want
people to know that that I'm making a
home here and I want people to know hey
aw's going to be in here you know catch
them when you can I'm going to be
ordering these dishes I'm pumped about
love it I love it very exciting thank
you so much