I'm standing in Cafe Gratitude right now
and I'm honored to announce a
collaboration between Cafe Gratitude and
medical medium medical medium recipes
are going to be in Cafe Gratitude so
people can find the food they need to
heal with and Cafe Gratitude which is
incredible the chef here elevated
incredible medical medium recipes but
elevated them to a level that's mind
blowing and you have to taste it
yourself seriously it's going to be
incredible and you know what's amazing
about this because when you go out to
restaurants you're like does this have
this in it does this have that in it you
know what's in here is there this bad
vinegar is there white wine vinegar in
here is there soy in here is there
gluten in here so many people are
worried but no more not here Cafe
Gratitude okay because they already go
by so many different requests for people
they look out for people but they took
the medical medium recipes that were
already clean and pure and for healing
and they were like yeah we're taking
this to the next level we're going to
have it here that's the collaboration so
I'm really excited about this no oils in
there which is amazing easy on the salt
you know what happens is when you eat in
a restaurant and you get filled up a lot
of things can happen afterwards you can
feel like okay now I'm starving again
shortly after and then you feel kind of
like ripped off because you just ate and
now you're hungry again or you feel
bogged down and greasy and heavy that's
not happening with these recipes and CA
gratitude it's a whole different
experience I challenge you to try it out
and see what you think it's healing
recipes for people where you feel
satiated your body gets fueled it gets
what it needs you can then go out and do
what you need to do go out and exercise
go out to the beach go live your life go
work whatever it is and you feel like
your body is being cared for by these
incredible recipes that Cafe Gratitude
just elevated which is a whole another
level of incredible so you guys I'm
letting you know this this is it right
here so there's going to be an event too
coming up so look out for that because
pretty soon these recipes are going to
be on the menu I'm going to be in here a
lot I'm excited I can't wait
[Music]