you said that you're hoping that the
work you do will help bridge the gap
between the sick
and the not so sick yeah because
yeah what happens is you have the not so
sick the not so sick of people that are
still living their lives
they're living their lives nothing
stopping them from living their lives
they might have a little bit of acne
they might have a little bit of bloating
maybe a little fatigue periodically okay
maybe
a little bit of that maybe um
maybe some brain fog that's come that's
intermittent right
and then
you got someone who
they could barely get into a shower when
water hits them and almost knocks them
over
they need help with somebody making
their food they can't take a walk
outside for more than 10 minutes or five
minutes they can't sit in the sun it'll
knock them out they'll be sick for three
days
you've been there right been there yeah
i know and and so there's there's the
not so sick and this
and the sick right so sick and what
happens is there's a confusion between
them both because the not so sick
haven't been inconvenienced enough
to know what the really sick are going
through
and so what i'm trying to do is i'm
trying to bridge this great divide can
you explain a little bit of what you do
as the medical medium
sure i started out when i was young
right at age four
and i heard a voice
and that voice gave me information
about
others
meaning what they were feeling a house
if they were sick if something was wrong
and then
beyond that gave me information
on
advanced
advanced stuff about you know viruses
and
bacteria and toxic heavy metals and the
nervous system and vagus nerves the
voice was teaching me
teaching me
how to pronounce things how to say
things how to identify them in people
how to
understand the information
and it led to a life of where i am now
where i put the information in the books
so people with chronic illness
can have a chance to heal when we talked
um about this stuff specifically last
year when i was going through my
troubles and i asked you to just kind of
help me out again
you checked in what did you tell
everybody what you what you noticed
because i i remember you told me celery
juice and to um do the heavy metal detox
and then you also said to eat a lot of
potatoes yeah i was trying to put you on
an antiviral
you know diet keeping foods out that
feed bugs that feed viruses because
fibromyalgia is epstein-barr that's what
creates fibromyalgia so what happens is
you can go to a fibro doctor they'll be
like you got fibro you can go to a then
walk into a lyme doctor's doctor's
office and they'll just be a lyme doctor
and they'll be like you got lyme disease
i can go into you know a lupus doctor
like you got lupus yes it's exhausting
but those three are epstein-barr let's
get a little bit into the celery juice
exactly like what are the
exact the benefits besides what i feel
which i want to say is i feel
clear-headed every time i drink celery
juice you know the cool thing about it
it's a neutralizer it's neutralizing
acids then it's neutralizing toxins then
it's diffusing and neutralizing metals
it doesn't pull metals out but it it
diffuses it neutralizes their damaging
effects and then it neutralizes other
things too like chemicals like the
fragrances and the air fresheners that
get in us and all that other junk that's
getting the chemicals that are there
that are we're breathing in every day
it's helping to neutralize all that
right the other thing it's doing it's
restoring the hcl and the stomach glands
which helps you have strong hcl and the
strong hcl kills pathogens
and that's like your that's like your
bug killer what um is your favorite
podcast or what was the one that you're
most proud of
i like them all but the blood draw one's
critical the blood draw
bloodletting and vampirism
episode is critical to know and learn
about because it can save your life what
happens is we're in a situation right
now where people are staying sick
because you're getting too much blood
drawn
too much
seven vials 10 vials 12 vials 30 vials
20. i had 30 bottles you had 30 miles
yeah yes and i was sick so sick
afterwards not even funny a lot of what
you say can be overwhelming to somebody
who is suffering brain fog and on
mattress island and is exhausted from
the whole process of talking to
everybody and trying every single thing
for those people who are on their like
last breath of hope and are reaching out
to you like what's the best way to get
started how can they do it in a way that
well well the thing is is medical medium
information isn't one size fits all
right so it's the only health community
or health set of health information
right the books and all that that's not
one size fits all keto is one size fits
all you do the keto and that's what it
is doesn't matter where you are or what
it's like you do it or you don't it's
one size fits all and i'm not i'm not
ripping keto or anything you know
whatever or anything else i'm just
saying that
that the mm info is is customizable
and it's
customizable
vastly i'm gonna ask you a few questions
you're gonna have seven seconds to
answer and um i'll time you
what are the top foods people need to
add to their diet right now and go
wild foods leafy greens fruits herbs
those are the four things we got to
focus on that means like wild
blueberries that means like celery that
means like herbs like lemon balm parsley
cilantro use cilantro like a leafy green
spinach lots of spinach eat a leafy
green you have a cooking show on amazon
live what's the coolest cooking gadget
everyone needs to add to their kitchen
right now and go
mm-1500 that i'm working with the mega
the mm1500 it makes all these things it
makes salsa it makes hummus it makes
like nut butters it makes nut milks it
makes sellers use it makes anything what
are the three things that you do daily
to keep yourself healthy and go
okay
i
in the middle of the night i'll look up
at the sky
and
look at the stars
that's really important right there
what's the greatest part about having
your gift and go
people healing that's the greatest part
there's nothing better than that