[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello this is Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week we bring you the most advanced
healing information ahead of science and
research in chronic illness so you have
to think about that if science and
research was so ahead of things if we
were so good and Advan in science with
chronic illness why is everybody getting
sicker and sicker and sicker and I'm not
talking about heart disease I'm not even
talking about cancer I'm talking about
people that can't function anymore they
can't live their lives they have
symptoms upon symptoms they can't think
they could barely walk talk function
they can't exercise they can't live
their lives I'm talking about people
with not just high anxiety and
depression people with body aches and
pains you know ache Facial Pain body
pain neck pain back pain it's not even
just that severe fatigue eczema sasis
skin disorders dermatitis the worst
cases of rashes that are unknown hives
lupus Lyme disease you can go on and on
CFS mecfs brain inflammation completely
completely just missed by science and
research everything toxic heavy metals
that are causing all of this pathogens
that are causing all of this I talk
about the most Advanced information I
brought this to town thanks to spirit
cuz Spirit brought this information to
me since I was a child if you're brand
new to the medical medium and you don't
know what's going on check out the
medical medium books just give it a shot
look into the medical medium series and
pick out a book that you feel like you
know speaks to you and work on your
healing process you could save your life
you could save other lives around you
this information comes from Beyond and
it's already helped Millions over the
last 35 years so let's move forward
we're talking about slow
metabolism and uh celery juice too we're
always talking about celery juice how it
helps with metabolism issues but let's
talk about metabolism Al together like
what is it a slow metabolism was never
behind anybody's symptoms or conditions
so you need to know that so metabolism
isn't the cause of somebody being sick
or a problem happening or a symptom or a
condition the term
metabolism is only the discovery of
being alive so slow metabolism isn't
responsible for weight gain see that's
that's that's unbelievable right I'll
say it again a slow metabolism when
someone's diagnosed with a slow
metabolism and diagnosed what does that
mean that means that someone's like oh
you got a slow metabolism oh you must
have a fast metabolism oh you must be
one of those people that seem to you
know have a fast metabolism I mean come
on right think about that is that
advanced is that like Advanced Signs and
research is that where we are today so
come on you know a slow metabolism that
person's gaining weight so they must
have a slow metabolism I mean let's just
let's get real let's really get real
here so the point is is that slow
metabolism that we believe we have the
term metabolism is only the discovery of
being alive that's all it was see it was
a discovery that something happens when
you put food in your mouth hundreds of
years ago
yeah you put food in your mouth and it's
it's a discovery that blood is moving
through our body blood is actually
pumping something's pumping blood
through our veins and arteries that's
what metabolism was the discovery that
we're a living creature that when you
consume an energy source via food that
you're utilizing it it's giving you
energy and you're able to function we're
alive that's the discovery of metabolism
by the way way that's the that that's
the great scientific discovery right
there a slow slow metabolism does not
give us an answer of what can truly go
wrong to create a condition such as
weight gain or losing too much weight so
when somebody's losing too much weight
and we say hey they must have a fast
metabolism it's ridiculous it really is
cuz that's not how it works see
metabolism became law it's one of those
old old grandfathered laws that has
taken over the consciousness of the
human race I know that sounds drastic I
know that sounds a little too much maybe
but when you really think about it it's
literally all everybody ever thinks
about I mean we have so many people
suffering with chronic illness dying or
living lives that aren't at the fullest
potential it's it's really funny how all
that self-help self talk out there that
self-help talk and all that good
Feelgood positive talk and all the just
all of it the Law of Attraction talk and
all of the all the talk out there about
living to our greatest and our greatest
potential which I support I've always
supported that I've always supported
living to our greatest potential I've
always supported living in a positive a
most positive being that we have most
positive sense that we have inside of us
you know our our souls elevating to a
point of you know being positive living
at our best you know living life at our
best the best quality we can can can and
the best quality of life we can I've
always subscribed to all of that I've
always been a supporter of all that but
then when we think about we leave the
fact out of all the people that are
struggling and suffering and chronic
illness from young people to teenagers
to young adults to college students to
young adults to older people to you know
people middle-aged or however we want to
say it now these days you know everybody
is struggling and they're struggling de
with real real chronic issues all the
time you know debilitating to some you
know plaguing them to some degree and so
when we think about you living the best
quality of life and living their best
full potential what about the millions
of people that they can't even think
about that they can't even think about
you know wh what's the best quality
what's the best greatness they can even
achieve to when they're suffering and
struggling and so when you think about
metabolism
taking over it's almost like another one
of those things to derail people who are
struggling and suffering is what I'm
trying to say it's another way of saying
well you know what it's your metabolism
it's another way of just blowing off
people that are really sick that's what
it is it's another great mistake I call
it is what I'm trying to say it's
another one of those derail people is
what I'm trying to say you got people
suffering and struggling left and right
all over the place with all kinds of
symptoms and conditions right and what
we throw at them the best science and
research we go to dietitians we go to
some nutritionists we go to different
people and the best science and research
get thrown at them it could be your
metabolism it could be that or that's
what's responsible for it and you can't
live to be at your greatest self because
your metabolism is messed up you can't
get that best quality of life because
your metabolism is messed up maybe
you're not thinking positive enough
maybe you're creating your own illness
and it's messing up your metabolism see
that's what I'm trying to say right here
it it's it's it's really something when
you get these roadblocks out there that
are out there they're set in place to
mess you up kind of like the autoimmune
Theory I always talk about where they
say your body's destroying itself when
it's not when it was just a theory from
the 1950s and if you read the books the
medical medium series books you learn
about how that's not true the body
doesn't attack itself well these other
great mistakes like metabolism and that
and everything being blamed on your
metabolism that's another prime example
of to derail people to confuse them to
throw them off the scent of what they
really need to be doing is why isn't
science in research stepping up to the
game why aren't they stepping up and
helping out women kind when health
professionals all over the world are
consumed with the term metabolism as if
it holds any Merit any credibility any
science research really any scientific
discovery really when it holds any kind
of credibility it's
unbelievable especially what's going on
with people suffering that's why I'm
trying to talk about this a little bit
more I mean I'm going to go into
metabolism a lot you know a lot more to
where we're heading and so just hang in
there fasten your seat bels get a cup of
tea just relax because we're going to
cover this and this is going to be good
but I wanted you guys to make sure that
you knew how kind of disastrous the
metabolism theory has been and how it
has been a roadblock for so many for so
long so when someone's struggling to get
weight off of them and they're severely
depressed because the weight is bogging
them down they can't function good they
got extra 50 lbs on them extra 70 lbs on
them they're being made fun of you know
they're being not they're not being
taken seriously they're not being taken
seriously that they even know how to
take care of themselves or know how to
take care of their families or whatever
because people look at weight in such a
negative way and it's so sad that people
do that because it's not about it's that
the weight on someone has nothing to do
with their soul who they are as a person
their accomplishments who they who they
are inside and what happens is that you
know weight is so judged in this world
right and then to smack on a label like
it's their metabolism they must be
eating too much and they're not burning
it off or something it's just
unbelievable when there's bigger reasons
there there's bigger reasons the weight
is happening there's bigger reasons
they're struggling with problems There's
real reasons that science and research
doesn't want to touch or go near because
it's completely negligent completely
negligent and you know you know how
science of research you know how they
trick you know you know how the whole
science thing how it's all all trickery
I'll tell you how it's trickery science
is incredible in some areas because of
technology and where it is today but
then people are suffering with no
answers that's where we are people
suffering with no answers metabolism is
the scientific word somehow still
holding credibility to just throw
everybody off the scent that science of
research has failed everybody in chronic
illness so let's go into this a little
bit deeper so we want to go along with
all this yes it's a man it's a manner of
speaking we can talk about that you have
a slow metabolism we can call it what
you want then but let's let's talk about
the truth of really what it is and
what's happening let's go into there the
true
cause of what's called a slow metabolism
is a sluggish liver so the true cause of
a slow metabolism or what we call a slow
metabolism is a sluggish stagnant toxic
liver it's that simple a sluggish
stagnant toxic liver that's a metabolic
problem that's your metabolism so
anybody you know anybody including
yourself that may have heard or been
told or diagnosed or anything like that
that they have a slow
metabolism understand that they have a
liver that's a little tired a little
toxic a little stagnant A little
sluggish because something is going on
inside that liver and we're going to
explore what those things could be this
could be pesticides and herbicides
fungicides synthetic chemical sitting
inside the liver our livers are filled
with a variety of what I call
troublemakers if you get the Liver
Rescue book if you get the Liver Rescue
book the medical medium Liver Rescue
book and you'll see you know the you'll
see uh it has Xmen psoriasis on the
subtitle and all kinds of it has I talk
about acne on the subtitle and so forth
and you'll see that that's the book to
get so you learn about this I talk about
the
troublemakers and the troublemakers are
all these different things pesticides
were exposed to all the time herbicides
were Expos you know always exposed to
fungicides synthetic chemicals you've
been exposed to those you may not know
it but you have I could talk about all
about how viruses that's right we're all
exposed to viruses we are there's no
question about that Epstein bar being
the number one bacteria Plastics we've
always been EXP OS to Plastics toxic
heavy metals were exposed to Mercury
were exposed to aluminum lots of it in
our system and in our body it's been
passed down throughout the generations
into our bodies through our forefathers
ancestry even toxic hormones such as
excess adrenaline from stress when
you're stressed out what happens is your
adrenals pump out toxic hormones toxic
adrenaline that's how we we cope with
stress this stuff is like battery acid
it's corrosive to our bodies corrosive
to our immune system and it fills up in
the liver the liver sponges it all up it
sponges it up have you been to the gas
station pumping have you ever pumped
your own gas at the gas station before
in your life let me tell you something
all those gas fumes that's a solvent all
you have to do is breathe in gasoline
gasoline fumes all you just have to
whiff it and it's instantly inside your
bloodstream and then being absorbed into
the liver and we do that over and over
and over again pumping our gas and I'm
not saying be afraid of life don't ever
get you know don't ever go and get gas
lean that's not what I'm talking about
I'm talking about the fact that we're
exposed what do we do it clogs up the
liver it clogs up it cogs up fat cells
fat cells at the liver stores to protect
you because we end up eating too much
fat and so all this fat gets stuck into
the liver and then all these toxins get
stuck into the fat from our high prot
protein high fat diets so when we eat
the high fat high protein diets which
everybody is still stuck doing science
and research being so Advanced meanwhile
we don't even know what to eat yet it's
incredible the most advanced best
doctor's diets out there and on the
scene and on the circuit and the best
the best kinds of diets out there and
diet plans and different names and all
those different diets and all that
they're still completely void of what
reality is to what our body needs
they're always high fat and high protein
and they slowly bog down our livers and
slowly kill our livers so when you think
about it back to the whole thing back to
the whole thing what I was saying are
you living your best quality of life how
can you with all the misinformation out
there how can you with the term
metabolism being so backwards and so and
so you know so misinformed or just wrong
how can you live your best of life with
this stuff going on this these are traps
to stop you from living your best life
and your greatest self and your full
potential and your positive self and
everything else and that's how the
world's set up it's set up with this
Darkness out there whether anybody likes
it or not it's set up for a reason the
medical world did this they do these
things for a reason they create sand
traps purposely so you get stuck in the
sand traps and it slows down your best
self or best quality of life or what
you're trying to achieve in your life
that's what it does that's what it's for
so you end up for some reason needing
Pharmaceuticals earlier on in life and
earlier on in life you needed more
Pharmaceuticals and more Pharmaceuticals
you better believe it the troublemakers
these pesticides herbicides these toxic
heavy metals Mercury aluminum synthetic
chemical solvents cleaning agents
cleaning chemicals you know fabric
softeners air fresheners plug in in the
house all those things we absorb into
our livers viruses bacteria Plastics
hormones all of this gets inside our
liver celery
juice is one of the
tools one of the tools Spirit brought to
town for me when I was when I was a
child in spirit said look it's going to
be celery juice for people that's going
to be one of their tickets out of the
madness an herb called celery you know
it revives the liver flushes out these
various toxins and helps dissolve and
disperse the fat cells trapped inside
the liver from high protein high fat
diets that surround
and contain all of the toxic substances
the troublemakers I talked about
originally just a minute ago essentially
celery juice cleans out the liver
removing a variety of toxins and
reducing viral loads what does that mean
by reducing a viral load like what does
that even mean it's the first time
listening to this and listening to Med
medical medium podcast and or reading in
any of the medical medium books what
does that mean a viral load is something
like an Epstein bar sitting inside a
liver
proliferating
growing expanding over time to
eventually give you the heart
palpitations The Hot Flashes eventually
give you that per menopause symptom
thing eventually give you reproductive
problems fibroids eventually giving you
all kinds of different cysts ovarian
cysts how about that get chronic fatigue
syndrome fatigue that's what it can do
anxiety depression epine bars just
sitting in there waiting to give you
fibromyalgia your first fibromyalgia
diagnosis when you're age 42 it's there
waiting to give everybody this it's a
viral load it's a virus sitting inside
the liver percolating year after year as
we feed it high protein high fat diets
of all kinds whether it's vegan
plant-based whether it's animal- based
whatever it is and we just feed it the
wrong Foods we feed it lots of eggs and
these viruses grow so what is a viral
load it's a virus such as Epstein bar or
the shingles or hhv6 or cyto virus or
some many other viruses or
HPV even HPV why not sitting inside our
bodies feeding off of the wrong Foods
feeding off the chemicals and poisons
that are trapped inside her liver
percolating proliferating and going to
give you symptoms later on down the road
and all the Geniuses that write the
Books and they're on the circuit and
they're doing the podcast about health
and talking about this diet and that
diet and all the all the all the
brainstormers think about science
studies and science research don't even
know any of this and if they do know a
little bit of this it's because they got
it and gleaned it from the medical
medium series books or practitioners
that actually use the books or they
heard a podcast of mine and so forth so
this is information you need to know
celery juice awakens the liver you
should be doing your celery juice you
should get the celery juice book the
medical medium celery juice book and you
should be doing the celery juice awaken
the liver clean it up so it can improve
so everything else in the body can
improve and if you want want to call it
quote metabolism is is why you're
gaining weight metabolism is why you're
sick metabolism is why you're tired then
fine get your metabolism better using
celery juice is is part of it every
organ becomes cleaner because that's
what it really is it's not a slow
metabolism your organs are becoming
cleaner your liver is getting cleaner
blood and lymphatic system become
cleaner think about that blood and
lymphatic system become
cleaner unwanted weight gain let's go
into that a little bit let's go into The
Unwanted weight gain that's
important when someone is gaining
unwanted pounds it means the liver has
been collecting and storing an abundance
of fat cells so why is that happening
you got a tired sluggish liver okay it's
been beaten down by chemicals and and
all kinds of stuff going on you got a
pre fatty liver that's completely
undiagnosed so you got a pre fatty liver
because there's pre pre pre fatty liver
it's just basically you're just not
getting a diagnosis of a fatty liver but
you're going to someday and if you don't
you're still getting a fatty
liver and then these fat cells collect
they store they collect and they store
and they have poison inside the fat
cells inside the liver and that's when
weight gain starts to show up that's
when it starts to show up it shows up
when the liver's already been filling up
it's already been filling up with these
fat cells you see you guys see the
liver's already been filling up over the
years so if you're one of those where
you're always battling a pound or two l
pounds on you say you're somebody you're
young you're in the gym and you're
trying to knock off those two pounds
your college weight and then you're
knocking it off and then it's coming
back on as you're eating your high
protein diets and you're trying to keep
your low carbs and then you're
exercising and you're breaking it down
coming off that means your liver already
filled up with fat if you're getting fat
on the outside of the body it means your
liver already became pre fatty even at a
even at 18 years old 19 years old 20
years old you already got a pre fatty
liver you already have a problem and
then sure you can say well you know hey
my girlfriend or my boyfriend or
something has he he's got more weight on
him it's a slow he's got a slower
metabolism he exercises in the gym but
he can't keep it off and what happens is
that's just a sluggish a more sluggish
toxic liver with more pollutants inside
the liver including possible viral load
a viral load the very thing I was
talking about earlier right remember the
viral load and then you got that sitting
inside the liver you got the weight
coming
on and then we deem that as slow
metabolism like what a great mistake
that is weight gain is not a result of a
slow metabolism the liver is responsible
for weight issues throughout all parts
of the body so remember that you wake up
one morning you see you see fat on the
body that you don't want there that just
it's the liver it's you got to get the
liver healthy you got to get the Liver
Rescue book the medical me Liver Rescue
book and you got to start taking your
liver seriously because as you go grow
older it's not it's not going to it's
not going to go down good people dealing
with weight issues are also often
dealing with lymphatic issues because
when the weight's gaining and the and
the and and the liver getting sluggish
and stagnant and the lymphatic system
gets sluggish and clogged up and it's
harboring an abundance of fat cells in
the lymphatic system because of an
overloaded liver and then the lymphatic
system gets
overloaded with poisons and toxins
because the liver's so filled up at this
point you know when you're drinking that
celery juice the chemical compounds from
the celery juice enter the digestive
system absorb into the intestinal tract
walls go up to the hepatic portal vein
and enter the liver they start to
revitalize the liver cell so when you're
drinking that celery juice it's dropping
down through the digestive tract getting
down into the intestinal tract getting
down going up the hepatic portal vein
that's the highway up to the liver
because everything has to go up to the
liver everything it's like a medicinal
infusion for the liver that celery juice
is being driven up into the liver it's
an infusion into the liver to wake it up
to get it out of its stagnancy to get it
out of its to get it out of that whole
stagnant sluggish State that's causing
your
slow metabolism
diagnosis our liver is a filter that
becomes clogged over time if we don't
give it relief you have to remember that
our liver is a filter that becomes
clogged over time if we don't give it
help if we don't give it relief it clogs
up over time think about that a little
bit often in addition being clogged up
with fat cells a slow sluggish stagnant
liver is a sign that's loaded up with
toxins and the troublemakers I kept on
talking about earlier these can range
from conventional detergents like I said
colon did you ever smell cologne did it
ever bother you did it it's one of the
things that bothers me probably the most
if I'm in a crowded area going through
an airport or whatever it is the cologne
is so thick it's so toxic it gets into
the sinuses it sticks in there I've had
people tell me for years how it affects
them how it actually gets them like in
instant migraine makes them sick makes
them feel nauseous the amount of cologne
the perfume that's out there because
they're toxic they're chemical they're
chemical agents they're not natural no
one's wearing a natural cologne it's a
chemical company's concoction of garbage
to make a smell occur that for some
reason seems to be pleasing to somebody
but yet not pleasing to most people
that's the irony to it all I mean I mean
I heard you know a friend of mine who's
a health practitioner in a different
realm of Health the different whole
different realm of Health it's a health
of like chemicals and stuff like that
all that other different stuff and said
that the majority of people when they're
interviewed 95 people out of 100 say
they hate the smell of cologne then how
is it possible everybody's wearing it if
95 people out of a 100 hate the smell of
cologne then then how is it happening
I'm there's some of these things there's
it's a mystery it's a total mystery
perfumes the same thing there there
there's so many toxic varieties of
perfumes and they really affect
sensitive people you know I don't get
affected by Perfume so much but colog
definitely bother me it's the craziest
thing but I've seen people where they
can't handle any of it and then you got
the gasoline fumes like I talk about
when you're pumping gas air fresheners
air fresheners that's a really bad one
the chemical companies the oil the
vaporized air fresheners the fake
candles the fake candles it's not
essential oils in the candles candles
when you burn them these are chemical
company Delights these literally
intoxicate us I mean we're talking about
they break down our immune system when
you're burning candles that aren't
natural like essential oils and the wax
isn't you know it's not like a natural
wax or a soy wax or something like that
where you know whatever it is and it's
just straight chemicals that's really
bad with those candles so many people
what happens is if you're burning
candles for 30 years in your life and
breathing that in you can develop
conditions and diseases and problems
because it'll feed pathogens pathogens
inside the body lower the immune system
it could really hurt you it's it's just
as bad as smoking I mean if you're
anti-smoking cigarettes and you think
cigarettes are bad for you just think
about you know just think about the air
fresheners trust me think about the air
fresheners think about those and the
candle whole another game
Pharmaceuticals also get trapped inside
her liver they sit inside her liver
these Pharmaceuticals bacteria and
viruses sit inside our livers forever
where do you think hepatitis C comes
from it's from just a low-grade Epstein
bar virus from be from when you're
younger and it sits in there percolating
causing scar tissue by the time you're
60 years old then the doctor sees you
got a little bit of inflammation in the
liver with a little bit of scar tissue
and he deems it hepatitis C he doesn't
even know that he doesn't even know the
hepatitis C virus or she doesn't even
though the hepatitis C virus is just an
EBV virus that's been in there forever
they never found or singled out a Heep C
virus by the way it's never been singled
out under the microscope ever in history
they singled out the Epstein bar virus
they never singled out a hepatitis C
virus isn't it interesting it doesn't
exist but yet it does there is a viral
condition that's sitting inside the
liver and that's what's happening
there's over 60 varieties of Epstein bar
virus over 60 varieties many of them sit
inside the liver some of them cause
hepatitis B hepatitis C they cause
conditions inside the liver Scar Tissue
over time from viral inflammation
feeding off of scented candles the new
air fresheners that we're dealing with
to this day to colog and perfumes to
makeups that are really toxic to toxic
heavy metals to you know all these
detergents to solvents to pesticides
herbicides they get clogged inside the
liver the liver loses its ability to
function at its Optimum level celery
juice helps this but it's not just
celery juice you want to get on the
medical medium you want to get on the
medical medium um the heavy metal detox
smoothie you want to get the heavy metal
detox smoothie you want you want to get
on that vimergy spirina the vimergy
barley crash juice powder you want that
vimergy right inside the Smoothie you
make the heavy metal detox smoothie with
the wild blueberries I use the the
Wyman's ones you can get another wild
blueberry if you want you just put the
Frozen wild blueberries in that smoothie
you blend it up I mean that's what I do
to get the metals out because you're
exposed to Metals we're all exposed to
Metals no matter what we're doing where
we are you want to get them out of the
liver because over time they feed
viruses that create liver issues down
the road and never mind slow metabolism
you get that liver too bad and too beat
up and too problematic you're going to
have a lot more problems in slow
metabolism and a little bit of weight
gain you could have a lot more issues
like people have some serious eczema
psoriasis all kinds of different
conditions people have acne acne is a
liver related issue it's stripto coctus
inside the liver and lymphatic system
that's what acne is and you know it's
it's actually unbelievable how people
don't realize what they act they still
don't know what's causing their
acne they don't because there's no
information science of research doesn't
know anything I think it's set up like
that on purpose to be honest listen you
should read the liver book you should
read Liver Rescue so you actually can
see the difference meaning learn and
then see the difference in the results
when you do the 369 cleanse the liver
rescue 369 cleanse and you actually
start getting your liver back and then
you start getting better there's a big
difference that happens there's
something in celery juice I call sodium
cluster salts I know some of you guys
already heard about that cuz you got the
celery juice book um the medical medium
celery juice book and the sodium cluster
salts that's a powerful powerful um
phytochemical compound basically what it
does is it helps dissolve poisons that
are trapped it helps to disperse them
out of fat cells it helps to break down
fat cells it helps to get these toxins
these solvents these pesticides these
toxic heavy metals loosened up it helps
to bind on to debris that's caused by
viruses viruses that create debris
byproduct I just want to tell you a
little bit about something about that
byproduct thing so it's important to you
know you guys hear about like
methylation issues like mt hfrg mutation
you hear about that you hear about other
things too and you know then you got
Lyme disease you got um you got bofilm
you hear about that out there right I
mean I'm sure you guys are listening to
all kinds of stuff out there and or
reading stuff out there but all that's
caused by viral byproduct and none of
those sources none of those sources or
studies or or practitioners or people on
the circuit even know about any of this
viral byproduct from Epstein bar hhv6
hhv7 shingles cyeg virus viral by from
Simplex one Simplex 2 viral byproduct
produced by these viruses inside of all
of us okay that's what causes all of
that that's what causes C reactive
protein test Elevate Ana anti-nuclear
antigen test that's what elevates the
inflammatory tests MTHFR gene mutation
tests that's what actually inflames
everything okay that's homosysteine goes
up that's the whole point it's from
viral byproduct inside people's bodies
that's Advanced information you're only
going to get here from the medical
medium from medical medium radio show
and from the books and that's that's the
whole thing you don't want those viral
loads
increasing and when they increase and
produce all this viral byproduct you get
slower metabolism meaning it could get
diagnosed or seen from the outside by
somebody who doesn't know what they're
talking about about health a
professional that sees it as like a
dietitian that sees it as slow
metabolism meanwhile you're building up
viral byproduct your liver is getting
sicker your weight's coming on you're
getting different symptoms through life
the liver becomes a nesting place for
this these troublemakers and these
viruses these toxins and poisons they
they feed the bugs inside the body the
liver becomes this nesting Place celery
juices sodium cluster salts have these
chemical compounds that bind on to viral
debris and viral byproduct and help
Purge the liver this is so important
this strengthens and awakens the liver's
ability to operate at its best and
perform over 2,000 chemical functions
that are undiscovered by research and
science think about that research and
science has even tapped into a a little
bit of what the liver does how it works
that's how it works sodium cluster salts
strip the membrane of pathogens down it
strips the outer membrane of the cell
the viral cell that keeps the thing
strong it keeps the virus strong it
strips it down it breaks it down and
then you know that's how it kills these
bugs you know and also celery juice
breaks down and helps dissolve the fat
cells that are stored inside the liver
so we can pee those fat cells out I was
on the Instagram live recently and I
said piss the fat cells out I probably
shouldn't have said that but it's peeing
the fat cells out okay you know the
bottom line is celery juice is loaded
with vitamins and minerals that
strengthen and feed the liver making it
less stagnant too feeding it are you
feeding your liver the heavy metal detox
smoothie feeds it the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie feeds the
liver and you know you do the 28-day
cleanse in the medical medium book one
powerful it save lives long before I
published it long before it was
published the 28 day cleanse brought
people's lives back decades before that
book was even
published okay so that's the power of
these things the the 369 and The Liver
Rescue book and The Liver Rescue
smoothie bring the liver back I mean if
you don't have all the medical medium
series books get them all if you can't
afford the book that mean some of them
are like $10 $9 I saw that uh celery
juice was like $9 or something on Amazon
I know they're in Costco and Target if
you can't afford the book go to the
library take out the whole medical
medium series and start getting your
life
together listen celery juice is a
godsend for The Unwanted pounds when
people just don't want those unwanted
pounds they want them to come off it's a
godsend it really does help but then
when it's unwanted weight
loss unwanted weight loss when you're
losing weight when you don't want to
celery juice does the opposite there it
stabilizes the mineral salts bring the
liver back because that's still a liver
issue that's still a liver problem and
it's still an adrenal problem if you're
really
underweight and you don't want to lose
any more weight celery juice can help
you because it assists in that
circumstance too whether you're trying
to gain weight or lose weight it helps
you Hold Steady in between it's a
balancer you know that word balance
right well I got to eat you know
balanced diet I got to be balanced I got
to live more of a balanced life that
word is overused out there or it's used
all the time regardless and that's what
celery juice actually really does it
really does balance things it keeps
things stable stabilizes I love when
something really does work it's another
thing to say the word with all these
so-called balanced diets that aren't
balanced you know and all these balanced
Lifestyles that aren't balanced at all
that aren't balanced at all like eating
chocolate all day like eating chocolate
all day and coffee all day you know and
and and eating one meal a day and
thinking you're balanced or whatever it
is all these different balanced diets
that are developing left and right are
eating way too much way too much protein
and fat thinking it's balanced or the
whole moderation thing everything in
moderation and moderation that's just
unbelievable it's ridiculous it really
is ridiculous ridiculous I have to be
honest you guys but celery juice
actually does balance things I love when
something actually is it's real and not
just talk it's not just all talk you
know it's critical to know that celery
juice also is not a meal replacement
it's not a meal replacement it's a
medicine it's a medicine it's not a meal
replacement especially if you're
underweight if you're underweight it's a
medicine so you can actually get to a
point where you're not going to be
underweight anymore meaning what it does
is it fixes the liver it fixes the the
endocrine system it fixes the liver the
endocrine system the
adrenals it it actually gets rid of
viruses that are keeping you underweight
because that's the whole thing what
people don't realize who are underweight
and they can't put weight on they're
dealing with a viral load too viruses
produce what what happens is viruses
stimulate adrenaline production that's
what they do there's certain varieties
of Epstein bar out of the 60 varieties
of Epstein bar that stimulate adrenaline
production keeping you underweight but
the one thing I've learned about people
who are viral and they're underweight
for a portion of their life eventually
their liver just just craps out the
other Direction and their liver becomes
stagnant and sluggish really heavily the
adrenals get tired and they gain weight
and now they deal with a weight problem
later on anybody who's living
underweight where they got this
underweight problem and it's underweight
too it's for years and that person's
been just they can't keep waiting on it
changes and they end up with too much
weight on them and they're on the flip
side that always happens celeres can
help prevent that too from happening to
them you can't rely on celery juice as a
calorie Source though always remember
that don't skip a morning meal like a
fruit smoothie or the heavy metal detox
smoothie or any of the recipes in the
medical medium series books or you know
don't skip those just because you know
you think it's a meal
replacement it's not so always know that
have both the celery juice 15 20 minutes
later enjoy your breakfast after celery
juice 15 to 20 minutes a half an hour
later enjoy your breakfast I like I
personally I like anywhere from 20
minutes to 30 minutes I like 30 minutes
A Lot the reason celery juice helps with
both unwanted weight and unwanted weight
loss is because they both stem from the
struggling liver with the viral issues
unwanted mystery weight loss is usually
a result of the low grade viral
infection like I said the Epstein bar
inside the liver setting off the body's
alarm system essentially creating an
allergic reaction that prompts the
adrenals to release consistently high
levels of adrenaline like I was just
saying earlier the adrenaline acts as an
amphetamine and that's what happens but
the unwant The Unwanted weight loss I
talk about just doesn't last forever
like I was saying earlier eventually
liver becomes tired sluggish exhausted
and then you know the high fat high
protein diet all that you know going in
there you know Mass amounts of
adrenaline saturating inside the liver
long term because of the low-grade viral
infection that doctors can't pick off
that no practitioners can't pick off
that nobody sees because I try to get
every Everybody the inside information
about their body so they can be ahead of
everything in everyone and when people
start to gain weight instead it can
happen 10 years later 5 years later 4
years later it can happen 15 years later
that's how it
works but celeries use helps out with
all the viral situations that create
unwanted weight loss and unwanted weight
gain because the sodium cluster salts I
was talking about those chemical
compounds enter the liver's hepatic
portal vein and break down viral cell
membranes which weakens and reduces the
viral load you want to weaken the viral
load you want to reduce it you want to
break it down celery juices compounds
also grab onto toxins such as heavy
metals pesticides herbicides fungicides
solvents that feed viruses and pull them
out of the liver celery juices compounds
flow through the rest of the bloodstream
collecting and disengaging viral toxins
that are hot I call them hot because
they're bad they're they're charged
they're hot charged they actually have a
frequency they float around in the body
and what happens is you can
disengage that frequency you can
disengage those toxins these are unseen
allergic reactions that trigger adrenals
too we have all these poisons and toxins
floating around in our body triggering
off the adrenal adrenals and we're just
adrenalin flying everywhere people with
mystery weight weight loss have a higher
heart rate too because of this allergic
reaction of all these poisons and toxins
floating around the bloodstream and you
can have that same thing with weight
with weight gain when you're having
weight gain too you can have the same
you know the same toxins floating around
acting as an allergic reaction mild low
grade allergic reaction triggering
prompting the adrenals to release
adrenaline and this is left over
adrenaline surging through the body due
to this allergic reaction from a viral
load viruses produce poisons and toxins
by feeding off of poisons and toxins
these are toxic to our body they float
around they create low-grade allergic
reactions prompting adrenaline to flood
it's Advanced information I mean listen
to this show again cuz you know this
this Advanced information and it's good
to kind of just you know hear it once
hear it a couple times this whole radio
show I've been sharing information from
the medical medium celer juice book
that's how packed it is and I haven't
even scratched the surface the book's
packed with information about gaining
weight what happens when people gain
weight why what's happening in their
liver to you know unwanted weight loss
all of it but it's not just that I talk
about metabolism I talk about all kinds
of different symptoms and conditions
that everybody's walking around with in
the celery juice book it's it's that
packed with information I talk about
what the celery juice does with for our
liver and and reversing these conditions
so what I've been doing is giving you
information right out of medical medium
celery juice book is what I'm doing and
because there's that much to share I
can't even scratch the surface of it
it's not even possible and so the whole
thing with with metabolism you know
that's a big topic all on its own and
it's important to learn about it because
what happens is you're going to be told
one day regardless that your metabolism
isn't right you're going to be one day
you're going to be 32 years old you're
going to be dealing with you know at the
gym wondering why you can't get weight
off why a trainer is going to be telling
you that it's your metabolism or you're
going to be 20 years old and sick and
fatigued and some doctors's going to say
you have a slow metabolism or you're
going to be 45 years old and some
doctors going to say you got you you got
menopause and you have a slow metabolism
that's why you're gaining weight
whatever it is you're going to be told
you got a bad metabolism one way or
another along the way you may as well
get familiar with how to defend yourself
see we defend ourselves in all kinds of
different ways in life right you've
defended yourself right haven't you with
different things like different things
you felt weren't just or you felt you're
being called out on when you have
then because you weren't doing anything
wrong I mean did you ever have that in
life in a relationship or a work
relationship or just a stranger or
whatever it is you know what I mean but
we're not allowed to defend ourselves
with illness with chronic illness like
we're we're supposed to be sick and have
to just obey obey these grandfathered
laws that are set to just ruin our lives
along the way your life is precious
right okay Precious these are your years
right here these are your days these are
your months these are the years of your
life
you want it taken over by BS like the
metabolism theory that it's responsible
for all these things going on in your
health do you want it taken over by that
that's the same thing like the protein
thing I talk about all the time the
whole thing with protein where protein
is God are you getting enough protein
it's all about protein every diet's
about protein meanwhile everybody's
getting plenty of protein but why is
everybody still sick if you want to be
if you want your lives eaten up by these
monsters
then go ahead but if you don't want your
lives eaten up and your days wasted and
your time Wast it if you don't want them
eaten up you can defend yourself for the
first time when it comes down in the
medicine field in the world all of that
and I don't care if you're the smartest
cat on the planet where you're so smart
where you're into you know the these
crazy foods from the Amazon and you're
totally smart on everything and you
think you know everything about keto
diets you think you know everything
about every diet in the book and all
this stuff and you think medical media
my he hear a voice and that's just too
whatever that's just not not information
that's peer-reviewed and studied or
whatever it is you might be the smartest
cat you think but you're still going to
be a sucker to the
metabolism law you're going to be a
sucker to the protein law you're going
to be a sucker to Conventional medicine
big Pharma and all these other ways and
you're not you're not going to be able
to defend yourself you may as well learn
how to
and start really taking control over
your life what's control over your life
if you can't really take control over
your life I don't understand is there
fake control over your life because
that's what people do they're taking
fake control over your life over their
lives it's amazing what about real
having real choices being able to make
choices and say hey I hey it's not a
metabolism issue I'm sorry but it's not
it's actually my liver needing help my
liver needing care it needs to be
cleaned up my lymphatic system needs to
be cleaned up it's not because I'm aging
it's not because I'm just somebody with
a genetic thing where I'm born born with
a genetic issue and slow metabolism you
got to put your hand up and say no no
I'm not going to get suckered into this
one I'm here to give you the truth so
you can protect yourself and make your
own decisions for you and your family
that's what I'm here for that's the
whole point point and you know I'm never
going to stop doing that I'm always
going to give you that information so I
put the books out like the medical
medium celery juice book you know
someone said to me the other day they
said I said Anthony I said what and they
said you know so what you wrote a book
about celery juice what is it like a few
celery juice recipes or something silly
like that and drink some celery juice I
said are you kidding me I said are you
joking I said do you know what's in that
book and they go no and I go of course
you don't know you didn't read it I go
read that book the person went and they
took a book and they read it and they
said they never read anything like it in
their in their life they couldn't
believe it had almost 200 different
symptoms and conditions explained to how
we get sick and how celery juice can
help heal it they were blown out of
their mind their minds just were blown
they they the person shared it with two
other people already and they were just
mind blown they didn't know there's so
much information about what celery juice
does and what it has inside of it and
what it can do for you and how it can
literally change your world around if
you do it right and take the direction
right to do
so and you so it's so you just have to
realize it's about you your health your
family your friends the people you love
it's about the people that matter it's
about your life that matters does your
life matter does it matter at all does
it you know right it has to right it
matters to me it matters to me I had
someone tell me years ago said you know
my life doesn't even matter it doesn't
even matter I don't even care anymore I
said you know I do I said I care and it
matters to me your life matters to me
and they said you know what you know
what it turned their life around when
they heard that because they realized
that if it mattered to me in every way I
wanted that person better I wanted them
recovered I wanted them moving forward
their life was important and they said
you know what that changed your life and
they started applying the information
they recovered themselves from multiple
sclerosis that's what they did and
they're still better today and here now
because of it this was years ago years
ago years ago and so it should matter to
you to heal and so when you go back to
the metabolism Theory it's really a sad
situation I've seen it used there's
hundreds of books pamphlets this and
that about it people still talking about
it it's literally one of those Devils
one of those Devils one of those demons
or something is what it is it takes over
the mind of millions and millions of
health professionals all around the
globe you know that are innocent that
don't realize it they just don't realize
it and it takes over their Consciousness
is what it does and it's a seed that
makes it so they can't look further no
one wants to look further no one wants
to doubt science's Discovery with the
metabolism and back to what that is what
is it it's just a discovery that we're
actually breathing air we're taking in
oxygen we're taking in fuel we're going
to bathroom that's it I'm just letting
you know that's metabolism right there
you're eating something you're you're
using it as energy and you're going to
bathroom you're breathing air which is
oxygen we're utilizing it and that's the
discovery basically the bottom line when
you're dealing with eczema when you're
dealing with edema and swelling how many
people are dealing with edema and
swelling they're dealing with skin
problems like eczema psoriasis they're
dealing with fatigue you know fibroids
reproductive disorders re reproductive
problems aches and pains nerve pain
fibromyalgia which science research has
no idea about any of these things yet
the causes you know headaches migraines
heart palpitations when we're dealing
with lupus that you know with the
diagnosis of Lupus which is still a
mystery to research in science think
about that right there Lyme disease
still a mystery still a mystery you know
methylation issues you know everything
that people go through right now they're
going through PCOS that one right there
is really difficult on people and then
the sibo diagnosis the diagnosis the the
digestive problems and all that
sinusitis issues vertigo tentis Vitiligo
lyan sclerosis all of those what happens
is the bottom line is we have all these
different conditions and symptoms and
and diagnoses diseases all of this stuff
science of research is behind the
eightball and all of it so keep to your
celery juice keep strong do it long
enough do it long enough and do enough
you know when you get the celery juice
book you'll read the dosages you need
you try to get on 32 ounces every single
day I got people that are on 64 ounces
every day it's changing their life and
turning them around but you want to make
sure your foods are right too I'm going
to give you some tips right here stay
away from eggs stay stay away from milk
cheese butter stay away from kefir stay
away from yogurt stayed away from yogurt
stay away from any kind of dairy
products whatever you do stay away from
all the dairy of course stay away from
gluten but you want to know why to stay
away from gluten cuz no one ever knew
why no one ever knew why the reason you
stay away from gluten is so you don't
feed any bugs like strep octus causing
acne so the whole reason behind acne is
Strep bacteria that's behind acne it's
strep in a sluggish liver and in the in
a sluggish lymphatic system sitting in
there causing cystic acne so you want to
make sure you're doing enough of the
celery juice you're doing you're staying
away from the foods you should stay away
from stay away from bacon stay away from
pork I would even stay away from corn
I'd stay away from soy I would stay away
from those too and I would keep your
animal proteins if you're into animal
proteins lower them do them once a day
not twice a day not three times a day if
you're an intermittent fast faster and
you like to do animal protein once a day
at the end of the day do a vegetarian
meal at the end of the day do a vegan
meal a plant- paste meal at the end of
the day one time and then do the animal
protein on the other day do every other
day you know if you're if you're
plant-based if you're vegan lower your
fats lower your proteins lower the nuts
and seeds the oils the avocados don't
have them so high all the tahini I was
talking to a plant-based person and
you're a really cool person you're like
you know what I do tons of tahini I do
two tablespoons of tahini on my salad
every night I have two avocados in my
salad I put 2 tablespoons of tahini in
my salad put a little olive oil in there
I said oh my God you got so much fat and
you got so much protein and fat going on
in there you shouldn't do that you
should have a half an avocado in that
salad and bring in some red bell peppers
bring in chop up some celery put in some
red bell peppers in there lots of
tomatoes I said why don't you put those
things in there steam if you're not all
raw steam some vegetables throw in some
uh throw in some asparagus throw in some
some um
brussels sprouts in there steam them put
some steamed zucchini in there or make
some fresh raw zucchini noodles if
you're into raw do that but whether
you're plant-based or your animal
protein lower the fats lower the protein
so your liver can get a break bring in
that celery juice and watch your life
change get the medical medium book so
you can learn all the tips and all the
things to do including what supplements
to take to get rid of conditions but the
bottom line is all of this is really the
power this these are pieces and tools of
the power you can use that really clean
up what you could think is a metabolism
problem always remember that anyway I
love you guys thanks for listening to
the show can't wait for the next one
bless your heart I believe in you I
stand by you 100% I'm honored to
actually be of service to you okay bye
now