celery juice contains undiscovered
life-saving medicine when we hear that
drinks contain electrolytes it doesn't
mean it's a completed form celery juice
contains a complete electrolyte one that
enters into the brain and recharges your
neurons celery juice also contains
undiscovered plant hormones these
hormones enter the endocrine glands most
people with chronic illness all
experience endocrine problems whether
it's the thyroid the pituitary the
pancreas these hormones restore them
celery juice also contains a vitamin C
that does it have to be converted by
your liver all other vitamins see in
every form and in every food has to be
converted in order for it to work so it
instantly gets used in the body and it
builds up your immune system bringing
people's health back
celery juice contains unique digestive
enzymes these undiscovered I jest of
enzymes help strengthen your digestion
reducing bloating constipation cramps
diarrhea all kinds of different issues
people have with their digestive system
the antioxidants celery juice are unlike
any other antioxidants out there in any
other food they cling to toxic heavy
metals I ended up developing severe
anxiety insomnia tachycardia anxiety
panic attacks old CD anxiety and
depression trying to get off like my
medications when heavy metals oxidized
they create Alzheimer's dementia memory
problems anxiety depression these
antioxidants literally are the ones that
repel rust from growing off of these
metals she started the medical medium
protocol within 30 days started coming
out of it you can recover and you can
reverse these symptoms I am healing and
there's so much hope for me and for
others
this is undiscovered medicine reversing
disease in our bodies and bringing
people back to life and back to their
best health
[Music]