facebook youtube clubhouse we're talking
about
celery juice the power it has and
how it's the bug killer and that's
really important to know because
everybody's sick because of some kind of
bug some kind of bug
with its virus bacteria different
pathogens we all walk around
what happens in alternative medicine in
conventional medicine
people got sick went to their doctors
and no one knew what was wrong with them
nobody knew
for years decades yeah they can have
hashimoto's
thyroiditis they could have ra they
could have
anything aches and pains and the vertigo
and the dizziness and the eczema
psoriasis but people don't know
they don't know that all these decades
it's like well
um here just take the steroid cream um
just take the steroid injection uh just
take these antibiotics uh you got lyme
disease take these antibiotics
oh you're getting worse well apparently
we're wrong about as being bacteria
but the point is is people walking
around
sick with so many different problems
including migraines
and then the chronic infections utis
chronic sinusitis and everything else
you got to think about it all these
years people walking around
sick they're sick with pathogens
and one of the reasons why people
recover with medical media information
was because of celery juice that was a
powerful tool and still is today
by the way you guys twenty percent off
the omega
mm 900 right here it's the mm-900 hds
and mega juicers.com just so you know
that's there's a sale going on for a few
days
on this juicer making some celery juice
and i want to i want making some celery
juice and i want to remind you guys
that next week i'm doing
the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse
and i hope you guys are totally into it
because we're going to do
the medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanse so i am pumped about that
one of the keys and the reason why i got
the celery juicer out right now
is one of the keys of that cleanse is
celery juice
so whether you have some juicer you have
right now
or you're looking at this juicer or some
other juicer it doesn't matter just have
a juicer
and have one ready because the heavy
metal detox cleanse is going to be next
week i'm pumped about it
so i know we just did the medical medium
mono cleanse right you guys remember
the mono cleanse and we did the morning
cleanse
power doing the medical medium heavy
metal
detox cleanse which is a big deal so i'm
pumped about that
32 ounces this morning celery juice
incredible
incredible so good to see you guys so
what's amazing about celery juice really
is why does why does it work why is it
helping people
people that have taken everything and
done everything done done everything
been there done that people seen
tenderologists taking every single
natural supplement every single
uh alternative medicine thing you can
candida cleansers and gut health powders
and probiotics they're still sick
migraines still sick with problems still
sick with aches and pains
fatigue still just really ill going
through so much
and celery juice you bring in celery
juice and how come
it moves the needle like it moves the
needle
how is that possible one of the reasons
why it's possible
it kills the bugs it whacks the bugs man
darcy said i'm going to start juicing
how much
should i start with i do 16 to 32 ounces
in the morning but i like every morning
i really try to push it 32 ounces
that's what i do try to get you know
what you can in you
right that's what i always say to people
glad you guys are coming on
it makes a difference it really does and
celery juice also keeps people out of
trouble too
unless they're doing death by a thousand
cuts too much
and then they're doing like everything
wrong
and anything wrong they're reading
really bad
they're picking up new bugs left and
right
they're doing new medical treatments all
kinds they're getting blood draws
extensive blood draws the blood testing
all the time so they're removing their
immune system out of the person all the
time
and then and then the celery juice might
not be enough because it's death by a
thousand cuts
so your celery juice is trying to
sustain you it's trying to keep you okay
it's trying to keep you hanging in there
while you keep on doing all the wrong
and all of a sudden you're doing now
another blood draw because your doctor
wants 20 more
vials taken out of you and 10 more vials
taken out of you
and then you're doing now you're doing
the wrong foods
now you got the wrong supplements and
there's citric acid and alcohol in them
and natural flavors and msg
and you're doing all these things and
celery juice is trying to keep you
hanging in there i've seen that with
people where they're doing celery juice
and it's the only thing they're doing
right
they're doing their sandwiches and it's
the only thing they're doing right
and they're doing so many things wrong
that that the seller juice is like hey
hey uh you better do something right
because i can't do it all
for you you got to do something right
you're doing you know and
and that's people don't realize it
you're doing your caffeine you're doing
your apple cider vinegar
you're doing your nutritional yeast with
all that msg right
and celery juice is trying to keep you
there
and then we're doing all these other
things and summer juice is like trying
to keep you hanging in there i've seen
that with people where they're drinking
their celery juice
there's other juice is keeping them
hanging in there
while they're doing all this other stuff
high fat they're tanking fats
left in right they're on the high fat
diet always on the edge of a heart
attack with their high fat diet
always on the edge of the heart attack
always on the edge of a stroke with
their high fat diet
and the celery juice is keeping them
hanging in there
amanda says my friend just passed away
hlh high blood
blood drawn daily i tried to tell her it
was terrible
get the word out please my god i'm so
sorry truly
breaks my heart it really breaks my
heart
um joy and anthony why do doctors say
to blend not juice just they just have
the wrong information
just misinformation that's all i mean
that's what it is
you know and and uh to be to be not mean
or to be to be
kind about it they don't have the
information
it's as simple as that i spent decades
helping people and having people fly all
around the world to my office and they
went and saw
lots of doctors and the doctors didn't
know why someone's sick
just my friend told me the other day
that he was watching some conference
he's a doctor and he was watching a
conference with a bunch of doctors on
there
talking about like that they thought
they were on this breakthrough with
microbiome
it's like what you're on some
breakthrough microbiome
um that's fun and all and that's cute
and all but
why aren't you talking about what the
real problems are why people are sick
it's a shingles virus in the
epstein-barr virus they got their
hashimoto's because of it's not they
don't have their hashimoto's
and hyperthyroidism because of
microbiome they don't have their ra
rheumatoid arthritis because they're
microbiome they don't have neurological
lyme because of microbiome i mean why
are you do they don't have adhd because
of that
so it's doctors just don't know and you
you know doctors they play in a lot of
doctors they play in a land of
if it's make-believe they don't know
what's wrong with anyone
so then they hear about oh microbiome's
getting popular let me look research it
let me do my first microbiome implant in
somebody it's like okay um
yeah uh let's wait 10 years for that um
let's wait for 10 years for your first
microbiome implant to help out your
patient when
jesus christ your patients suffering and
suffering terribly
with like real issues like all kinds of
different pathogens and
those pathogens are giving them the
vertigo and the dizziness and tinnitus
and the brain fog
and the pain in the neck and pain in the
back and the pain in the legs and feet
and they're suffering and they're
struggling
and you're doing your first microbiome
implant if that was that's even gonna
help
and it's really sad it kills me really
and then make sure you
blood draw the person to death make sure
you take another eight vials and another
10 vials and another 12 vials and
knock their immune system down more and
more
you know and that's what happened so
look the reason we'll expect that with
the fiber okay what happens is the
doctors don't know when other people
don't know and health professionals
don't know
you guys is that this is herbal medicine
and this is a medical device i don't
care what juicer you have this one's 20
off it's the mm-900 and i'll show you
what it does and how
dry the pulp is and how much you can
save and money and all that
when you juice celery but besides that
any juicer you use you guys
anyone it could be the crappiest juicer
out there it's a medical device
it's a medical device that's what it is
what you're doing
is you're creating your own herbal
medicine
your own form of herbal medicine is what
you're doing
so lydius has been juicing for the past
three years
it has changed my wait sorry and changed
my juicer to omega
the 900m uh mm-900 amazing i get so much
more juice
and the cleanup is so much easier i tell
people all the time
the cleanup's easy it's not noisy you
get so much more juice
and it pays for itself and it pays for
itself
and it just does like the amount of
money it has saved me with celery okay
you guys
has paid for the juicer over a dozen
times
it's like getting 12 new juicers for
free over time
that's what this does as far as how much
it saves right
so let's go back to this though i got to
tell you guys this is a medical device
got to keep that in mind whatever juicer
you have is a medical device
that's what it is the purpose is to keep
you
off of medical equipment
it's to keep you off of medical
equipment because you're
sick because you're in the hospital
you're sick or you're you're at home and
you're sick
this is a medical device its purpose
is to help keep you away from
trouble that's what its purpose is you
guys it's to help keep you away from
trouble that's what it is and what
you're doing is
you're making herbal medicine
that's what happens doctors don't know
and so
a lot of doctors do know now i mean they
do a lot of doctors follow medical
medium information
they have the medical medium books
they're medical medium friendly doctors
for their patients
because so many so many books have
gotten around the world and so many
patients have healed for medical medium
information that the doctors they do
they there's so many medical medium
friendly doctors right
that practice medical mean information
there's a lot of doctors that don't so
they'll say
blend up your celery in a smoothie they
don't know that
when you leave the fiber and you're just
throwing in a couple of sticks
and you're putting a couple sticks in
your smoothie and you leave the fiber in
there
it's not enough you have to extract it
they don't know this is an herb
this is an herb you guys it's an herb
okay it's like when you go to your
natural uh
professional doctor or alternate
medicine doctor or now conventional
medicine doctor and they give you a
bottle of pills and there's some herbs
in there
right you know some kind of multi
vitamin powder or any powder or anything
and it has a couple of herbs in it
this is an actual herb right here
and what happens is your doctor doesn't
know this is an herb
they think this is a vegetable for
crudite or for a little hummus
that's what they think and that's how
sad that is
truly so sad it is
you got the juicer a few months ago and
love it
the celery pulp is actually
dry it is i want to show you guys on
tick tock
good to see you thank you so
you can't consume 32 ounces
of herbal juice
if you're gonna blend in the fiber with
it
if you're gonna blend the celery with it
in a smoothie or a blender
you can't get 32 ounces you can't get 16
ounces
of the juice the met the medicine the
medicinal
juice so important it's a couple of
things you guys will
maybe you guys have figured this out
okay
you'll hear it out there anyone ranking
on celery juice
anyone ranking on it right discrediting
it right
they don't even know it's herb it's herb
it's it's actual medicine it's herb it's
medicinal
it's an herbal extraction they don't
even know
they think like i said it should be
chopped up in little pieces and put into
your tuna salad
that's all sarah i healed brain fog with
medical medium tools the 369 cleanse is
so powerful
everyone needs anthony's life-changing
books i had
50 symptoms only two left and i'm on the
way in healing those two incredible
sarah
amazing amazing amazing there are
doctors out there that have a practice
for years like a decade they get one
patient better with one
symptom and they get heralded as god
[Music]
one patient better in a year just a
little better they put him on a keto
diet they weren't that sick to begin
with
they had a couple of symptoms they get
one symptom better now they're god
because of a keto diet it's like
there's the difference between like the
not so sick and people who have 50
symptoms
sarah so you get 50 symptoms it's so so
much to bear right
that you've been through and there's a
difference there
between having a lot of symptoms and not
being sick
and then cleaning up your diet and
exercising big difference
big difference and that's when the
celery juice matters so you'll see the
people who rank on celery juice and
stuff you guys
they're people that have never been sick
they don't know what it's like when that
needle won't move no matter what powder
or what probiotic you're trying or what
fish oil you're trying or what charcoal
powder
or what whatever whey protein powder
when you when the needle won't move they
don't understand that because they've
never been sick yet they haven't gotten
there yet
they haven't gotten the pathogens yet
and they haven't got enough toxic heavy
metals so when they do they go
more down and then
that's what moves the needle
mary fox says so focused on my digestive
issues i didn't even realize
i'd lost my eye floaters amazing
one thing that happens when you start
taking care of yourself and you start
doing the right things and celery juice
is one of them you start getting rid of
symptoms
some symptoms you weren't even like
getting like weren't even thinking about
or got so used to having right
guys if you just came on here there's a
sale running for a couple of days
just on this juicer omega juicers.com so
megajuicers.com
and at megajuicers.com this is the
mm-900hds
mm-900hds you're gonna want this juicer
over any other juicer there this is the
one that squeezes
out the medicine squeezes out the
medicine like no other juicer out there
in the world
and so i'm gonna juice some celery now
so hey i got this under here
one time i did it wasn't even there and
it was just pouring out
that's why we're live so
this is a medical device
helping to prevent you from being on
medical
equipment in a hospital
or somewhere else what you'll notice
is there aren't metal gears here
there aren't metal gears in here there's
not metal gears
okay i
don't like juicers with metal
gears bump grinding and rubbing
against each other that is a nightmare
for me
because metal on metal wears
you don't see it wear
but it does and that metal wears out and
and so here you are juicing your celery
and you got
metal on metal in here and you're just
getting little tiny bits of metal you
can't see
so i don't like it's really
annoying when someone's like hey there's
this other brand of juicer
it's so great top of the line
oh really yeah yeah it's masticating the
whole bit oh really
it's got the metal gears huh okay great
not great terribly
[Music]
debbie rhodes says a mega juicer saves
you money
and energy it's so smooth and easy isn't
it i just love it i can't even i can't
say that
you need you need it when you're really
sick
[Music]
the mm-900 hds by the way you guys
anybody coming on here right now please
hear me out on this next week
medical medium heavy metal detox cleanse
i'm doing a heavy metal detox cleanse
next week are you joining me
doing a heavy metal detox cleanse one of
the reasons why
i'm juicing celery today i'm going to
give us a little reminder about the
celery juicer is because
do you have a juicer it's part of the
medical medium
heavy metal detox cleanse because it's
not just
the the smoothie it's also the the
celery juice is part of that cleanse
[Applause]
heavy metal rock and roll cleanse you
saw that
so right now what i'm doing is what you
see is
dry dry pulp coming out right here
a couple of tips don't add anything to
your celery juice
the medicine has to be by itself
has to be by itself it's easy to clean
isn't it so you guys are happy with it
i love it i'm in love with this juicer i
can't even tell you
love it love it i've tried every juicer
out there
love this juicer
don't do high pressure pasteurization
celery juice from the store
you're getting ripped off every time you
buy celery juice from a store
and it's in a bottle in the cold section
and wasn't freshly juiced that morning
it's high pressure pasteurization hpp
do not do hpp celery juice
it's b you may as well just dump it in
the parking lot buy it
pour it out in the street in the parking
lot that's how useless it is because of
high pressure pasteurization
keep that in mind they'll say it's raw
on the bottle
it looks like raw green juice it looks
like raw celery juice
but it's not it's been cooked in a
different way
[Applause]
[Music]
cell brook says how much celery juice
medicine
when i'm on mattress island with cfs if
i was on mattress island with cfs
if i was there okay
i'd be doing what i can to start with
like what can i do
can i get up to 32 ounces i would do a
minimum
of 16 ounces on an empty stomach in the
morning
if you're really sensitive start with
four ounces six ounces
if i had cfs i would work myself up to
32 ounces
or at least 28 ounces eventually all
right there's plenty of celery juice in
here right now so
that's what i would do all right
so i want to show you guys and i think
you guys know this right this is light
and fluffy
so this is light and fluffy so this is
dry
it's dry there's no juice in the bottom
of this
this is dry the pulp see that see the
pulp pieces
it's not sticking to the bottom it's
actually dry
right there's a reason for that the
mm-900
squeezes out so much juice
that your pulp is dry
let me just tell you what this equate
equates for for me
i've already saved i mean
thousands at this point where it's paid
for
free juicers meaning i could have gotten
12 new free juicers
with the money i saved because i buy so
much celery
that's the difference right there it's
it's incredible blows me away still
trying to read a comment because there's
a movement the only use organic celery
no
no i don't i i use conventional celery i
wash it really good
i wash out the stalks conventional
celery
i take my thumb i take a little bit of
natural dish dish soap right
i have a big bowl of water i put a
little bit of natural dish soap in there
it's a little bit right
i stick the celery in there meaning
actually i get i get it ready for where
it's
it stalks like this i put it in the bowl
and then
i rub it with my hands really good in
that water
and i take my thumb and i go down the
stalks like this and i clean all that
out really nice
yeah i use conventional celery
absolutely i mean i use organic when i
can but
if i can't find it i'm still gonna juice
um conventional celery
100 because because you're still
yeah you you don't have an organic herb
you're not using
organic herb at the moment but that's
okay because what it offers is an herb
outweighs it where do you buy the juicer
omegajuicers.com it's their
mm-900 hds
celery juicer model it's the only one on
sale there
thenmegajusters.com and i'm working with
the mega
on this machine just so you know and i
always tell you guys that
but use whatever juicer you have if you
have one because it's still a medical
device
i call juicers medical devices so
important
the celery juice helps sibo does it ever
does it ever
does it ever because what sibo
right sibo is small right
intestinal bacterial overgrowth
well as i was talking about before
celery juice
is a bacteria killer
it's a bacteria and viral killer celery
juice
kills viruses and bacteria
that's right sibo is streptococcus
specifically research and science
doesn't know that they just think it's
some type of bacteria they don't know
what kind
but it's streptococcus that's what gives
the bloating
that the whole bit that's that's the
bacteria that takes over that's the
dominance
that's the dominant strain of bacteria
and everybody's got to streptococcus
there's so much to be had tons of it out
there people
share it spread it some people have five
different strains
10 different strains of strap in their
system picking up so many different
strains
and celery juice helps to whack it
see if you guys know if you guys just
came on here there's a sale on the
mm-900 hds
and the thing is with this pulp is dry
you won't be disappointed it's dry
it's flaky it's flaky and dry
and because it squeezes
the juice so then what i'm doing when i
go to the store i'm buying less celery
it's like okay i'm going to buy some
celery at the store now okay thank you
here
it's less celery than it was okay
so you guys always ask me what juicer i
use
this is it right here and i'm working
with the mega on this juicer because i
because of what it does it saves people
the money i want to be involved making
sure that this thing sticks around
you have that juicer it's amazing
incredible heather
amazing so let's just pour this in here
so it's talking about how the juice
kills pathogens very important
you have to strain your juice
so you have to strain it okay that is
key got to strain it
glad you guys are coming on
straining it is very important
you want that pure herbal juice
pure herbal medicine is what you want
you want that as pure herbal medicine
okay so what you'll run into is stupid
talk about celery out there
okay let's cover that real quick if you
guys got a few seconds
just want to let you in on something
okay this is the only trend
in health in the world that's not backed
by money
think about that all your probiotics all
your fish oils
all your different all your stuff all
your fulvic acid it doesn't matter what
it is
your sodium bicarbonate whatever it is
whatever your
whatever is happening in trend world
kombucha tea all of it
is backed by money investors
and shareholders just so you know
and that's why the stuff is out there
it's not out there because it
moved the needle when someone was on
mattress island
do you know how this survived because it
moved the needle when someone was on
mattress island
that's why this survived whey protein
powder is only surviving
because it's got money behind it apple
cider vinegar is only surviving
because it's a billion dollar industry
these are only surviving
because they have investors and
shareholders
and there's money propelling it into
millions and millions of dollars of ads
celery juice stays alive on its own out
there without any money behind it do you
guys know what that means
that means it really works it stayed
alive with the naysayers that
the attacks on it because you can't make
money on celery juice
right on celery robin says your
information rescued me from mattress
island
that means everything to me everything
yes acv is bad for you on tick tock
it's terrible for you and in so many
ways i'm not going to go into it right
now but you can listen to my podcast
episode if you want
medical mean podcast at apple podcast
the acv episode episode vinegar
um so robin i'm so glad you're off
mattress island
thank god thank god that that means
everything to me
everything so you guys this stayed alive
and millions of people are drinking
worldwide
and alternative medicine and
conventional medicine hate it
they hate this because it's not making
the podcast doctors money
it's not making the podcast doctors
money it's not making the youtube
doctors money it's not making anybody
money
but yet it's in the way there's no
shareholders
and that are dumping in millions and
millions of dollars in advertisements
for for this
this isn't being advertised all over the
place but know all
your tricked out supplements
that won't move the needle like your
charcoals and
your zeolites and your bentonite clay
and
you know your whey protein powder and
your charcoal and your acv
gummies and all that stuff propelled my
money your kombucha tea propelled my
money money money money
this isn't do you guys know what that
means
that means that this is the only trend
in existence in alternative and
conventional
medicine that literally survives because
it actually heals people not because it
has
billions of dollars being dumped into it
and advertisements non-stop left and
right
right god when you think about it
when you think about it that's a big
deal
survives with all the hate and the
negativity to it and how many
nutritionists say you you shouldn't
juice celery you should make sure you
just have it in a smoothie with
other things yeah you can do that too
celery is good for you but it becomes a
medicine when you juice it this is
herbal medicine
and it's one of the medical medium tools
and many people don't use this tool
correctly
has to be on an empty stomach if you can
that's usually its best ticket right
there
16 ounces on an empty stomach right
that's that
right there is really important check
this out right that one
don't add ice no lemon no water
don't add that into your juice keep that
in mind
stacy highland how are you had a tickle
in my throat monday
zinc and c shock therapy plus fat free
back to normal today incredible the
vitamin c shock
medical medium vitamin c c shock therapy
and zinc shock therapy incredible
but vimergy products though
vimergy i'm not sponsored by vimergy but
it's got to be vimrgy to really do what
it's got to do
because i heard someone tried it with a
whole bunch of other different stuff
crappy stuff from other companies and it
didn't work because it was bad zinc
wasn't stabilized terrible vitamin c
yeah so it has to be the good stuff like
the vimergy
chris you seem fine to me celery juice
healed so many of my debilitating
symptoms
and chris you tried all the other stuff
out there you know what i'm talking
about
about all that other stuff out there
yeah
um stefan says i have been drinking
about 500 milliliters for many months
but don't feel any big change but you
know stefan
you're not going backwards right you're
not going backwards
and i bet you stefan if i was a fly on
the wall there'd be a whole bunch of
crap you're doing
that just like i said at the beginning
of the show right now i said
celery juice will keep you stable even
when you're trying to kill yourself
you're trying to kill yourself dumping
that vinegar in you
too much salt too much fat here you are
you're trying to kill yourself but
celery juice is keeping you going you're
doing your caffeine
staphon you haven't had any chocolate
you haven't had any chocolate
you haven't had any caffeine no no
caffeine huh stefan
no vinegar so your vinegar you mean to
tell me no vinegar has touched your lips
so here you are trying to kill yourself
no egg stuff
on did you do any eggs no dairy products
at
all not even kefir not even a yogurt
what about new medical treatments huh
what about gluten no gluten
so yeah you haven't seen your benefits
but celery juice is saving your ass
it's sitting there saving your ass so
you don't go down the drain
but meanwhile you're sitting there
trying to kill yourself and mosquito
you know mosquito spray all in the air
chemtrails jumping down
air fresheners there could be air
fresheners in your home
scented candles you haven't breathing
any scented candles
because people are sucking that stuff in
and it's killing them
and new bugs what if you picked up a new
bug and
celery juice is knocking that down so
here we are we're trying to kill
ourselves at all this stuff that we
don't even know about and celery juice
is keeping your ass afloat
and you're going to say it's not getting
me any better it's not getting me any
better
no it's only saving you or keeping you
level
are you doing all the other doing 369
cleanse advanced
they're doing the heavy metal detox
cleanse we're doing the heavy metal
detox cleanse next week are you guys
going to be on board i can't wait i'm
pumped
you're going to need your cleanser heel
book
you're going to need your cleansing heel
book you don't have you know it's
51 off at amazon.com us if you can't
afford the 16 go to the library try to
grab it
but we're doing the medical mean heavy
metal detox cleanse next week
sharon says what about this new weight
loss kick
of lemon in coffee and honey so they
take a medical medium tool like lemon
right the lemon water and they stick it
in coffee now
an empty stomach that's a that's
no no offense right because i know
you're just
talking about this new trend out there
right but it's
it's the dumbest trend that's so dumb so
let's just
let's add okay okay instead of putting
table sugar in our coffee or raw sugar
in our coffee let's put honey in our
coffee
now we just we we stepped up a little
bit i mean
how crazy is that right
why did you promote conventional celery
because there's people out there
that can't always get organic and the
but yet okay if you can't get organic
celery
and it means not juicing celery at all
because you don't want to use
conventional celery you just wronged
yourself
bad there's times i can't get organic
celery
you better believe i grabbed
conventional celery dang right
and i'm juicing it so
that's why i promoted conventional
celery 100
hands down hands down you're somebody
that you're not going to juice celery at
all because you can only get a hold of
conventional celery so hey i won't juice
it at all oh my god
that's crazy you know why because you're
going to get pesticides somewhere else
your butt's going to be getting
pesticides somewhere else you're going
to be getting pesticides from all kinds
of stuff you don't even know about
including your neighbor spraying it on
the lawn next door
in your apartment building being sprayed
or all around your parting apartment
building
you're going to be getting in the
mosquito spray that's being dumped on
everybody right now across the world
you're going to be getting all these
pesticides and insecticides in you
anyway
but you're going to stay away for a
conventional stock of celery
and not use something that can actually
help you i mean do i make sense or i
don't make any sense
i don't make any sense i'm just a
dumbass i don't make any sense at all
ellen celery juice is saving me
incredible listen i'm glad you guys are
on here we're talking about do's and
don'ts
we're talking about what celery juice
does we're talking about the kind of
the silly stuff out there and
right celery juice
you're doing it it's helping you while
we do things to actually injure
ourselves
death by a thousand cuts we're doing
this and we're doing that wrong and
we're doing this wrong and we're doing
that wrong hey let me buy this crap over
here and take that
let me do this and do that let me go do
this new medical treatment let me go do
this let me go do that and the celery is
keeping you going while you're drinking
it
could you imagine if you knew enough
medical medium tools and what to avoid
and how to help yourself can you imagine
what celery juice can do for you then
lord
yeah important to know
really important though susan walker my
legs keep cramping and pain
been juicing carrots and celery no
gluten fresh
living food diet what am i missing well
first of all susan you're juicing
carrots with your celery
nothing wrong with carrots i like
carrots
but carrot juice has never gotten
anybody better
carrot juice never gotten anybody better
back to going 35 years ago 35 years
ago okay right nobody knew about juicing
celery i've been
teaching about it since i was a child
back in the 70s okay
and let me tell you okay carrot juice
never got anybody
out of a crisis celery juice has
carrot carrot juice doesn't work it's
cute it's
okay i like carrots i have recipes in my
books and
there's grated carrot in one here and
there's some st
you know some sauteed carrots here
carrots are good
read my books so you know the true cause
of why you're sick and then how
to heal get it from the library bring it
to your doctor and ask your doctor if
it's okay
it's okay to actually work on your
healing process
janet huffman story celery juice keeps
me up
and mobile i like the sound of that
i have double hip dysplasia
bone on bone in my hip sockets
but celery keeps me mobile and pain free
god bless you
god bless you and i'll tell you why
because
there must have been some inflammation
there
behind that inflammation is those
buggies i talk about
those buggies those buggies
and over the years that inflammation you
get that bone on bone
and celery juice is now keeping them
buggies back
that's right how do you like them apples
you guys it's important to know out
there for everybody that's got
inflammation
she's doing amazing and i'm proud of you
patty
my bloating goes away when i drink the
celery juice
tell you why let's go into that a little
bit
by the way you guys just one more
reminder here the medical medium heavy
metal detox cleanse next week you need a
couple of things
you gotta have a book right it's
important
and you got to have a juicer do you have
a juicer
if you don't this one's on sale right
now at omegajuicers.com
on sale 20 off it's the only juicer
that's on sale there right now okay
megajuicers.com it's the mm-900 hds
and you it's a medical device you won't
be disappointed
renee can you put an apple with the
celery to help with the taste
you can just not gonna do what it's
gonna need to do
ain't gonna do what it's gotta do okay
you can put an apple in there and still
get some benefits but it ain't gonna
take you
to that finish line or it ain't going to
take you to where it needs to take you
it ain't going to do it
or shouldn't say it's not going to do it
okay all right what you see right here
sorry guys see
my little dummy over here and
what's happening is your bloating goes
down to the person that was saying hey
my bloating goes away
your bloating going down okay why
couple of reasons let me give you the
rundown all the different reasons this
is important
you guys take your pen you guys got your
notepad
this is important notepad pen i don't
charge for these courses
i'll give you guys free courses 24 7. i
don't charge for so you don't have to do
a
2500 charge on your card in order to
get the anthony williams school here
right this is all free and it's all me
juicing it's fun
okay your bloating might not go away
overnight
sometimes it takes time plenty of time
you might have more than one thing
causing your bloating
some people will have the bacteria
right or even the viruses
they'll have the bacteria and viruses
inside their liver
their liver gets stagnant and sluggish
from all their high fat diets
all their vinegar all their other stuff
their caffeine
and their liver gets burnt out chalked
out choked out
so pathogens tend to thrive in the liver
even more then your liver doesn't
produce as much bile
so it doesn't produce as much bile as it
needs to produce
and so because of that now your fats
aren't being
broken down celery juice has
significantly
significantly reduced my chronic hives
amazing cleaning up your liver a dirty
liver
valerie one year on celery juice my life
is so much better
my husband even drinks it and loves it
now yay
awesome husband thank you aw for
fighting for us
finally ordered this juicer today
incredible and you got the discount
20 off of megajuicers.com incredible
incredible eventually you can't produce
the bile you need to produce
weakened liver stagnant sluggish liver
mm info
and then you don't break down your fats
and now your fats are clogging up your
highway right here your gut
then your stomach starts to lose its
hydrochloric
acid because the stomach glands get
toasted out and then you can't break
down your proteins
you can't break down your proteins you
can't
if you can't break down your proteins
the stuff rots and then you get gut rot
gut rot ends up feeding all the bad
bacteria
and viruses and then when you're
dropping your celery juice in
right drinking your celery juice it's
going down the pike
you're whacking those bugs you're
restoring your stomach glands
this is a medical tool right here this
juicer
any juicer you have is a medical device
a medical tool
you're creating herbal medicine you're
using herbal medicine
to take out the bugs restore
your stomach lands clean up a stagnant
sluggish
liver bring back your bile reserves
and come back home baby to homeostasis
and that's what you're doing when you're
using a medical device
and you're taking that medical device
and you're creating
herbal medicine right there if you guys
don't have the juicer
it's the mm-900 hds 20 off it's
important for the heavy metal detox
cleanse next week it's part of it
because celery juice is part of the
heavy metal detox cleanse it's part of
it
so go to megajuicers.com and check it
out that's where you want to go to
megajuicers.com
so let me put
in back i used to have intense
bloating but thanks to your info no
longer get it incredible
gianna incredible i think that
i think dr nesbitt just got out of
surgery and dr nesbit says gianna
uh amazing dr nesbit is
isn't she doing incredible no more
bloating is that worth it
dr nez but what do you do when someone
has bloating you remove their stomach
what dr nesbitt says he removes the
patient's stomach if they get bloating
he cuts the entire stomach out worse
than you know the
the this you know where you stitch the
stomach so people can't eat as much
so worse than that he removes the entire
stomach out do you remove the entire
stomach out
he says he removes not only the entire
stomach he even considers it recommends
removing the person's brain
so they choose not to eat and get
themselves bloated
he says yeah does that make any sense dr
nesbitt is drunk right now
he actually had a shot of whiskey in
between surgery
i trust dr nesbit sometimes but lately
he's been off the mark
doctrine has been all kidding around
[Music]
is this a medical device it is
so what's the difference in juicing and
not eating it let's go into that doctor
can you head back to surgery because i'm
worried about your patients under
anesthesia right now
okay all right um
so what's the difference between juicing
and not eating it let's do that right
now
okay
emcee traditional chinese medicine
doctor third generation master very old
and saved
tens of thousands of lives and said
lemon and celery are
both cold foods and not good every day
can you please speak to that
well yeah i can definitely because in my
35 years of
practice when i was working one-on-one
with people
the most powerful people in the world
would travel
take their private jets and and come to
my office
after going to china after going
all up to asia all over the world to the
best traditional chinese medicine
doctors
that were second third fourth generation
okay
and so what they learned was they were
told the same thing
celery was too cold and lemon was too
cold
on the liver but that wasn't an answer
was it an answer so when they had their
vertigo and their floaters in their eyes
and they were dizzy and couldn't
function and they were part
basically bedridden and on mattress
island and they had five diagnoses
and already seen 50 doctors and traveled
around the world
to the best traditional chinese medicine
doctors they realized when they went to
the traditional chinese medicine doctor
they didn't have an answer they weren't
told what was causing their their
problem
they weren't told why they were
suffering they were told they had liver
heat
they were told they had dampness of the
spleen and that's what they were told
emcee
okay and i have no disrespect
towards chinese medicine i know chinese
medicine doctors
known them for years they like to learn
and they like to break out of that box
okay and they like to learn about
different things because we're now
in a world of chronic illness
neurological chronic illness caused by
pathogens and chinese medicine doctors
of the past did not know this
and now they're starting to learn and
start they're starting to talk about
bugs for the first time
okay and so and the other thing is
millions of people worldwide are healing
and getting their lives back because of
medical medium info and celery juice
millions and medical medium information
has tens of thousands of healing stories
so just so you know no disrespect
but that's just a tidbit cold foods have
nothing to do
with what somebody being sick or not
it has nothing to do with it okay lie
there
lie there on mattress island you know
how many people saw
saw third generation second generation
first generation trans medical
medicine doctors i mean and still were
bedridden with severe fatigue brain
inflammation
vertigo sickness dizziness couldn't even
eat
raging raging panic attacks that
and they they were due next thing you
know they brought in their celery juice
and all the other tools and they got
their lives back
it's no disrespect wild lizzie flour my
bloating issue considerably went down
within two weeks of celery juice and
medical medium protocols after 60 days
was completely gone
oh my god why lizzy flower that's funny
that's amazing and that's incredible
so proud of you guys so we're talking
about a couple of things right here
so let's go into this a little bit more
so you guys know it's critical to have
a couple of things a couple of pieces of
information one is
for years for decades people suffered
with lyme disease right
you guys know the lyme disease story
okay celery juice wait so
celery juice so i'm checking out a
couple things on here
sorry juice has helped me
with my inflammation incredible
for fibromyalgia amazing on tick tock
incredible
so let's go into this a little bit
neurological line let me tell you about
a little history you guys okay
tens of thousands of women suffering
losing their lives
because of lyme disease right
late 70s early 80s
mid 80s late 80s and they were
antibiotic to death
that's what happened horrible and they
were blood drawn to death
so they had blood taken out of them over
and over again
constantly all right you guys
so it's important to know about the
suffering from lyme disease
right and it's still happening now
there's still doctors doing the
antibiotics for the lyme patients
they're doing a little better because
they're doing less antibiotics so
they're keeping their patients alive
by not killing them so fast i support
this guy completely he knows exactly
what he's talking about
on tick tock
this person is this person is a scam
artist
it's not about the celery
it's about the sky
so so smart meditation that's your
handle there on tick tock
so i'm a scam artist is that what i am
now um
do you want to come here do you want to
come here let's i have
my assistant is giving you an invite
right now
so you're on your way all right i'll see
you here in a minute okay
i'm glad you're smart meditating oh
you're at the door smart meditation i'm
glad you're here awesome
so let's bring smart meditation out
smart meditation you're really smart
so let's make a handle what's with the
word smart
thing is donkeys are actually really
smart though you guys donkeys
so so but smart meditation isn't though
um smart meditation it's more like it
right smart meditation
i'm glad you i'm glad you came out here
so thank you for telling me i'm a scam
artist that's so great
make smart meditation you're so smart
that you might be the smartest person in
the world smart meditation
well okay i'll let you go you can go
back
smart meditation thank you for
smart meditation supports me oh sorry
oh wait did i pick the wrong handle
did i pick the wrong handle sorry you
guys i might have picked the wrong
handle
when comments are flying up it's kind of
hard to catch them all especially when
you're like talking
all right i picked the wrong handle
sorry smart meditation you do support
medical medium
what a day all right
we're live i don't know what else to say
when you're live everything and anything
go wrong
all right let's go into this a little
bit more let's make sure we move
forward it's important so it's talking
about
okay so it's b rad 19 that's who it was
so b rad19
i hope you stick around you might learn
something
and smart meditation thank you for being
here hey i did say
the donkey is like really smart donkeys
are really smart
and you know i saw somebody put a
comment about the donkey and said
donkey's really are mistreated they
really are just
you know i love donkeys and they really
are mistreated out this is terrible
really
poor donkeys all right
so when someone when someone the whole
lyme disease movement i can't tell you
how many people rolled into my office
with lyme disease
barely alive and they've been to
everybody and anything
especially the people that had money
that rolled into my office
even when i wasn't charging anything in
my office well i worked for free at my
office and there were lines out the door
out my shack
literally out of my shack lines of
people and they were do you know how
they were paying me an apple
they're paying me an apple they'd leave
two apples
they'd leave a banana they leave
dried lavender okay even when i wasn't
charging for years right until i
couldn't keep the lights on so then i
had to
so the bottom line is it got to it you
know it
it the amount of people that rolled into
my office from around the world
with lyme disease and they went to all
the different people they went to all
the different chinese medicine doctors
the acupuncturists the nutritionists the
dietitians
the functional doctors they were called
something different back then the
alternative doctors the holistic doctors
so functional doctors functional
medicine doctors were called holistic
medical doctors back then they weren't
called functional medicine doctors
and so with all that
they had to learn that this isn't why
they were sick
they had to learn that that wasn't why
they had to learn that's why they were
sick
that's what they had to learn they had
to learn they were sick
because of this not because of this and
that's what saved their lives
in in no disrespect to the person that
said third generation
uh chinese medicine doctor there was no
third generation chinese medicine doctor
back in that time period that can tell
somebody they were sick
with a virus that was making them
neurologically inflamed
and they weren't sick because of that
and so medical mean information really
blew up with healing people with lyme
disease that's what it was known for for
years
two decades known for that recovering
people with lyme disease and even
earlier
laurie starr your information has helped
me so much more than anything else i
have tried
you're an answer to my prayers honored
you're here truly
because lyme disease wasn't caused by a
tick that's why people who got
aj good to see you that's why there are
so many people
that weren't even around a tick in their
lifetime in areas of the world there
were no ticks
never even seen a tick in their the
region but had lyme disease
because lyme disease is caused by the
epstein-barr virus the shingles virus
the simplex one the cytomegalovirus all
combined or just the ebv
can do it too sus sue says can we push
to grow more celery so the world can
heal
they try to stop it they're trying to
stop it right now just so you know
and i predicted in the celery juice book
they tried it they're trying to you know
they're trying to make it
they're gonna eventually put a ban on
celery growing down the road
i know that's coming it's already the
biggest crop in the world and the media
won't cover it
celery is the biggest crop in the world
and the media next to the caffeine crops
and the media won't as far as vegetable
meaning they list it
vegetable it's the biggest crop in the
world vegetable
herb it's the biggest crop in the world
and they won't even talk about it whole
foods can't even keep cases of celery
and they have to get it by the
truckloads and truckloads
did you know it's talking to somebody
who works at whole foods right
they have a whole system for just celery
did you guys know that
a whole system for just celery
and the media won't cover it because
i'll tell you what
you can't make money off of it and it's
healing too many people so it's a
nemesis
it's bad so this is the mm-900 hds it's
off omega juicers.com you guys might
want to grab it
before next week because we're doing the
medical medium heavy metal detox cleanse
next week i hope you guys are there
a juicer is required so whatever juicer
you've got
whatever teaser you have if you don't
have a juicer still be there
she'll be there make the the heavy metal
detox smoothie
still be there and make the heavy metal
detox smoothie without the juicer if you
don't have the medical medium book then
you don't have a medical medium book
like
i don't judge anyone if you're gonna
come to school
ill prepared i don't judge you when i
was a kid
i never brought my school books in i
never went to college i told you guys
but more people healed with chronic
illness around the world because of my
source
cold light spring good to see you
so okay so a couple of let's just do a
couple of uh
recaps don't put anything in your celery
juice
make sure you strain it try to get 16
ounces minimum an empty stomach
realize you're dealing with a medical
device and realize
you're dealing with a bug killer a bug
killer even if you believe your lyme
disease is caused by a tick because of
bacteria like borrelia
then you want a bug killer
you want a bug killer if you got sibo
you want a bug killer if you got
anything in the chronic illness
autoimmune world
autoimmune world you want a bug
killer it's important
herbal medicine is in your hands
it's in your hands um
i want to give a shout out to smart
meditation for educating trolls
so smart meditation is a smart
meditation
thank you for educating trolls and
i'm pumped you're here
you guys have to realize they made yeah
all right
dr fon
okay glad you're here all right you guys
so smart meditation thank you for
education
educating trolls on tick tock you're
awesome okay
um
so you guys let's do a quick rundown on
how celery just works real quick
and how important it is why one of the
reasons why it's so helpful and
it clears up brain fog too is because
it's a complete electrolyte
i want to cover that nina says i feel so
much better i drink 20 ounces in the
morning
no food or drink for 30 minutes i feel
great
awesome it's a complete electrolyte
please know that a complete electrolyte
we don't have one herb
one food one vegetable one fruit one
piece of meat
we don't have anything that has a
complete electrolyte
we don't we don't this is the only thing
that has a complete electrolyte
okay sodium cluster salts are a complete
electrolyte
so when this goes to the brain it helps
to revive your neurotransmitters
your neurotransmitters start to revive
so that's another very important part of
why celery juice is so incredible
really is you guys i'm heading off to ig
instagram i'm turning tik tok back on
turning clubhouse back on so i'm going
over to ig
in just a little while just give me like
15 minutes
i want to clean up a little bit you
won't want to miss
instagram you won't want to miss it
everybody definitely you don't want to
miss it
it's going to be interesting i'm just
giving you the forewarning right now the
4-1-1 it's going to be pretty
interesting
it really is if you think you saw the
show today
uh-uh you didn't see the show today all
right
remember mm-900 hds sale right now
atmegajuicers.com
the pulp is dry just dry
nice and dry sucks the every last drop
out of the celery
saves thousands in the end and that's
the way to go so i'm pumped
jf 24 gt that's a quick one
are you coming to ig with me i'm going
instagram
i hope so head in there
all right guys i'll see you there soon i
love you wait
wait sue nell says hi aw and soc
been consuming lemon water and cj for
almost three years daily
and making great progress healing my
psoriatic arthritis
wondering should we soak celery in water
prior to juicing or not you don't have
to soak it in water to juice it
just give it a good wash you put it in a
bowl and you can give it a good wash
that's what i do
i wash out any dirt in in here in the
stock right here
and i'm so proud of you incredibly proud
of you psoriatic arthritis
is a combination of both ebv and the
liver with
copper and mercury and so what happens
is you get a little bit of that
dermatoxin
and that dermatoxin goes to the joints
or
it causes some flare-ups to you and
everything i talk about that in the
books
right here you guys next week medical
medium heavy metal
detox cleanse we're doing that next week
have a cleanse to heal book if you don't
already amazon.com us
it's on sale and then have a juicer if
it's not this one
have another one but make sure you've
got a medical device
so you got a juicer for that heavy metal
detox lunch if you don't have either or
be there anyway and hang out dino rubio
good to see you brother all right guys i
love you
let's go to