celery by itself is so medicinal it's
literally the undiscovered medicine of
our age what it does for the body how it
works is really just profound celery
juice is cleaning up the mess inside
your body and that's one of the things
that does it has a sodium cluster salt
an undiscovered sodium cluster salt this
is a subgroup of mineral salts this
mineral salt strips pathogens gallon it
damages them it kills them it destroys
them it kills off bugs bugs behind your
autoimmune condition that's why people
are getting better so fast and rapidly
with celery juice it's that powerful I
feel more connected I just I can't even
explain it this whole health journey
that I started a month ago maybe a
little bit over a month ago has totally
flipped my world the right way up when
you see people who have gone to 10 or 20
doctors looking for answers and and
years are passing in their life and they
don't have that quality of life and yet
it turns around from celery juice alone
just from this very humble herb celery
celery juice revives liver cells it
helps bring them back it flushes out
toxins flushes out old pharmaceuticals
metals petrochemicals pesticides
herbicides different toxins that we get
every day in our life they're inside
your liver I've been on the protocol for
20 months now and I'm ninety-five
percent better I'm off all my medicine I
have no symptoms a year and a half later
I am off of all medication for
everything I love life I have joy I have
so much hope many people shortly after
drinking 16 ounces of celery juice on an
empty stomach every single day
experience less digestive problems they
get rid of acid reflux they feel more
energy they feel more clear their brain
fog dissipates they feel like they're
moving forward moving forward finally
out of their illness finally out of the
condition I've been doing it and look my
hands
so much better no lesions 98% of my
symptoms are now gone I've actually
decreased my medications like by 50%
within one year celery juice is one of
those tonics that cleans out the liver
so you can heal and that's how you lose
weight that's how you heal overall you
should not be able to hold a glass now I
have a lot of strength in hand so much
better today a lot of my sentiments have
dissipated I have my life back
I'm the mom and wife that I know I was
meant to be everybody has a different
story they have different things
happening in their life with celery is
the one thing though that everybody has
that they're doing that's all United and
combined that's making everybody move
forward regardless of where they are
[Music]