facebook live on youtube got the celery
juicing going on and my phone is ringing
right now
this is what live is all about so what
i'm going to do is
put my phone on silence we're talking
about the benefits of celery juice is
what we're talking about so this is a
very expensive there's a very
like unexpected moment happening when
we're live like that
look um i'm going to talk about why
celery juice is so powerful what it's
done for people
what has happened with people's lives as
they're drinking celery juice why it's
so important
why it's not just juice it's not just
it's not just
vegetable juice it's not vegetable juice
good to see you guys
uh lisa says pink phone and
so um you know the one thing you guys
have to know is that the track record
the street cred
is unbelievable like never before
unbelievable okay uh sunday's in good
see you
um so it's it's a time period
in history where we have such a tool
like we do
and this wasn't there before yeah unless
somebody knew me in the past and they
knew me
over the years and they came to me when
they were sick like when i used to see
people one-on-one by the thousands right
and
then i could be like celery juice celery
juice celery juice right
shannon you finally caught the live
margaret good to see you um
tomato shirt exactly so the the whole
thing is with celery juice is that
it's moved the needle for people right
in that matter so when you're sick for
12 i've
seen people sick for 20 years that would
come to me they sick for 20 years
and they would knock on my door because
i was known as the bizarre
symptoms guy right the doctor would say
you know what i heard of this guy that
another doctor i heard
you know use this guy right me right and
i heard of this guy
and he handles all the bizarre symptoms
he knows why
people are sick courtney m a good to see
you he knows why we're
people are actually struggling aches and
pains tingles and numbness kind of
strange buzzing popping in the ears
got the vertigo and the dizziness got
the eye headaches the eye flashes got
the
flutters the flutters in the ears right
got the
the flashing in the eye right like i
said before they got
uh the uh like the floaters in the eye
the black spots in the eye right good to
see you guys so glad you're coming on
and basically the bottom line is all
these strange symptoms burning skin
right bladder issues that are
unexplainable that just get a diagnosis
that really doesn't help
all these things people have gone
through along with like chronic
sinusitis and all kinds of other stuff
and good to see you guys and so i was
known as this bizarre symptoms guy and
one of the tools
powerful tools for spirit of compassion
was
juicing a minimum of 16 ounces of celery
right on an empty stomach on an empty
stomach
okay and you know once a day
and that was we're talking game
changer man game changer
like a whole another level
and so look if you're not juicing celery
if you haven't tried it that's okay
right that's all right i haven't had
celery juice today so i figured i'd get
the juicer out
and run some celery through it because i
haven't had any
amy tang said yay glad you're doing a
live on my birthday happy birthday amy
that's so special i'm honored you're
here
on your birthday okay and you're a
monitor here
incredible so good to see you guys so
this is a really
a special live because i'm going to be
talking about
what this does what this herbal
medicine does you might heard some of
the stuff before i've talked about it
raises your hcl cleans up your liver
charges up your bile reserve right
you know jennifer says how do i adjust
to the taste of celery juice i'm sorry i
hate the taste look i don't blame you
there's sometimes i don't like the taste
some batches of celery you guys i don't
like the
taste i'm just telling you right now and
this batch of celery juice isn't the
tastiest i've had okay
sometimes the big crisp stalks are so
good
okay jenny says celery juice totally
moved the needle for me
especially when i got up to 56
ounces per day incredible
jenny 56 ounces per day that's amazing
you got me beat today because i'm
probably doing like 40 ounces or
something like you got me beat
um so yeah so this is really an
important time
really is so some batches are some
batches you guys i want to give you
all the tidbits okay some batches
are astringent right they're more
spindly and green
check this out have you seen this kind
of batch
this is what i call like the paper thin
batch
the stocks look big right the stocks
look big
but guess what it's a trick they're not
they're paper thin and they're kind of
like strange in a way like when i get
this kind
and i know i've known this kind for so
many years it's like a
paper thin stalk you see that kind right
there
and interesting and it's it's okay it
tastes alright right it's not my
favorite one
and sometimes you'll get in in this this
batch of celery i have now
right this batch of celery i have now
it's got this
thick cord in the center you know and
you can
chop that up and use it so let me take
this knife right here right it's got the
thick
cord so you can you can cut that in half
right
and you can put it through the juicer
like that too so that's something you
can do
so that's that's one kind right there
that i'm talking about
um okay yatro mckay
i can't tolerate even a small amount i
get
full on diarrhea wondering what to do
one teaspoon
help would be appreciated first of all
you might be straining it
right meaning you might be straining it
or you might
not be straining it which one is because
you have to strain it
it's one thing that's important you guys
you can juice your celery
but you still have to strain it through
a fine mesh strainer
right so that's one thing
because the little the little the little
tiny
the pulp left over can be a
like sometimes promote that kind of
peristaltic
action it's one thing the other thing is
if
cell like for okay here's the other
thing be your own detective
so that means there's nothing else
that's giving you diarrhea
like you have never never had diarrhea
before
just a question right so i ask everybody
that okay
if celery juice gives you diarrhea just
a little bit of it
is your stomach upset on a normal basis
so everything's perfect your stomach's
fine
nothing's ever happened with your
stomach like nothing goes wrong with it
you don't have bloating you know
cramping diarrhea no stomach digestive
issues whatsoever
everything's completely perfect until
you have a little celery juice
and then diarrhea comes or did you have
diarrhea last week
um did you have diarrhea three days ago
did you have diarrhea two months ago a
week ago two weeks ago
or do you have a little bit of it on and
off every other day
and it's hit or miss it's like whoa got
the runs now i don't know what i ate
i got the runs now something's irritated
oh i've been to the doctor i got ibs
like
so be your own detective that's one
thing there so
then you can distinguish how you know
you got the tummy
the tummy stuff going on right you know
or
is everything perfect and you drink a
little celery juice because if
everything's perfect
and you drink a little celery juice
right that celery juice
is doing some cleansing so it's killing
off some bugs
if everything's not perfect and you have
stomach problems anyway
and stomach issues anyway it's killing
off some bugs too right so we'll go into
that a little bit here's a close here's
a sodium cluster salt right here
it's an orange it's an orange eva lopez
i've been drinking celery juice for the
last four months
every morning went
went and had a wellness check it came
back with no issues
my doctor was amazed because i'm 49
years old
and i'm not on any pharmaceutical the
doctor said keep drinking
that celery juice amazing and you know
look you guys got to look out to you for
triggers i
call them new medical treatments you
gotta always question them
look out for triggers be careful because
you could have some good health and then
a new medical treatment could set some
people back
if they're not checking into stuff you
know what i mean kind of give you kind
of heads up
and then not only that um
other triggers like are you going to
your doctor and getting blood tests
regularly
and are they drawing a lot of blood they
drawing 70 milliliters 50 milliliters
100 milliliters 140 milliliters 200 ml
are they taking blood because then you
lose your immune system and eventually
you go backwards that way too keep in
mind that there's always a couple of
triggers
that we have to keep you know always
look out for because yeah
the celery juice can help us help us
help us and then we do things
then knock us down knock us down knock
us down
right that's how it works you're going
up you're going up with your celery
i'm getting better whoa moving the
needle moving the needle this is great
moving the needle this is amazing i'm
going to put these celery sticks in here
moving the needle drinking my celery
juice getting better
and what just had a whole bunch of blood
taken for me just had a whole bunch of
blood taken from me
said going backwards don't know why
maybe it's the celery just no
it's the blood taken out right or you're
moving forward you're moving up
you're drinking your celery juice you're
moving the needle you're moving the
needle
and then boom new medical treatment that
was offered or something
something you didn't do enough research
on something you know that
maybe you got peer pressured into
right something you might have been peer
pressured into
right and boom back going back
going back going back going back you
know and
so i mean keep that in mind too i forgot
to do my blood extraction you guys
i got some bio nature tomato paste let
me use that this time
um by the way we're live on youtube
we're live on facebook
so i got some bio nature tomato paste
which actually is really good
tomato base is clean it's it's really
good stuff all right and i got my little
needle here so so let's see
here this is such a big syringe i can't
get it in here
so i might have to get a smaller syringe
we're live
i don't know what i'm saying if anything
can go wrong
it will right um
i'll go look for another syringe but so
we
we do these things that we don't realize
right
that could set us back when we move the
needle
and we're moving the needle forward and
then there's this war
right this war that's happening
this war of you're doing something good
and then you're getting hit backwards
with something that you don't know might
not be so good like i always tell
people yeah i want people to go to their
doctor absolutely okay i talk to doctors
all the time
and i want people to see their doctors i
want people to get blood tested
i want people to take advice
recommendations prescriptions from their
doctors right
but at the same time doctors are in this
playing field where they don't know
what's wrong with people right they
don't know what causes chronic illness a
doctor
doesn't know what causes fibromyalgia
doesn't know what causes ra
they don't know what causes lyme disease
because they were wrong about the
bacteria
so when when they don't know what's
going on with people but they also
here's how it works with big pharma and
doctors i'm going to give you this
little tidbit right here and this is
really important to know right
is big pharma puts pressure on doctors
because i talk to doctors all the time
been talking to doctors forever about
this stuff right and big pharma
they put pressure on doctors
pushing out the pharmaceuticals that big
pharma wants
see and you guys don't know that you
guys go make an appointment to doctor
doctors there and but well you don't
know that the doctors all had to have a
meeting
with the uh with the uh big pharma
dealer right the dealer that comes to
the clinics the dealer that comes to
they come to the they fly around they
get off the plane
they got their black bag they go into
the clinic
they go and they're in the clinic now
right
and all the doctors get around for a
minute and they they take out the black
black bag and they go we got this new
anti-anxiety medication right here yep
right we got that one we got this is big
pharma this is somebody working for big
pharma
we got this new treatment here you guys
want here's the pamphlet
the doctors know nothing about the
treatment they know nothing about the
drug
they know nothing about anything they
can hand it a pamphlet
the doctor doesn't know any history
behind it
doesn't know what happened really in the
studies on the drug
doesn't know anything big pharma comes
with their bag
their bag of goodies they come to the
doctor
the chick this is really important
information i actually never told you
guys this i don't think maybe i did
years ago
they go to the doctor's office right and
then they sell
their bag of goods that's how it's done
so your doctor sits there and or group a
doctor sits there and he's sitting here
like this and he's like okay what else
you got
like well we got we got uh this we got
this new drug coming out for anxiety
this is for women that are
suffering from anxiety it's a new
variety of anti
okay what else you got we got this here
this other drug here for inflammation
you can put it in a needle put in
syringe and inject it if you need to
into them here's another drug we have
here here's a new painkiller we have
right
and but the doctors don't know anything
about if these drugs work or not because
the doctors are the experiment
part of the experiment okay they're part
of the experiment
the doctor's like well i got all these
patients walking through the door
and all these patients are hurting with
something um
the drug dealer came here
and with his bag of tricks his bag of
goods he told me
that try this new drug for this woman's
depression
try this new anti-anxiety for this
woman's depression
try this new prostate medication for
this for this man's prostate problem
try this new whatever right so they have
and then they just they're just part of
the experiment
see how it works so now you come in well
i got an appointment of doctors
met the doctor said uh time anthony
time to time to come okay let me get up
let me go see the doctor right i guess
i'll go in there right
and you go in there and the doctor looks
at your you know whatever looks at your
tests or
makes his conclusions and says okay well
and
he goes and he goes well let me give you
a prescription for this drug
he was only told just recently
by a representative of a big pharma to
try these drugs so now you become the
experiment
you're the experiment now right doesn't
this make celery juice so much nicer
when i think about it
does this make celery juice like what
you know
you can take celery juice and work on
getting better
millions are healing around the world i
mean doesn't this other process sound
horrifying in a way
so we become an experiment to every
single drug that comes out
so every single drug the big pharma
peddles
that had they have their drug dealers
right
bring their black bag to all the clinics
if you just got on here i'm talking
about big pharma's drug dealers they go
to all the clinics and all the doctors
in all the hospitals and all doctors
offices
and they take their black bag out and
they show the doctors the new drugs
coming out and then you become the
experiment
and if that drug's been out already for
two months you're now part of the
experiment for two months if the drug's
been out for two years probably
experiment for two years
christine k did the doctors make money
off each prescription
yes i talked to one doctor and every
single prescription that the doctor
prescribes he gets five dollars
um off that prescription
for a lifetime like a stipend kind of
thing
now i don't know of all doctors they
don't know all around the world
i talked to a lot of doctors i talked to
one doctor and he says he gets five
dollars
for every single bottle or prescription
that's sold so that means that then this
doctor told me it's going to give him a
lifetime of playing golf right
so you're going to be able to play golf
not every doctor is signed on to this
program i don't think i don't know how
it works really i mean i should find out
bet more about it but he told me that
it's like okay well
so now you know that means he said when
he retires
if people are still using those
prescriptions because they're sick for
their whole lifetime and he's still
getting five dollars for every bottle
that's filled right
but that was him i don't know if it's
like that for but he said don't don't
don't quote me on that for everybody
every doctor every country
this country that country don't quote me
on that but i did hear that um
and i'm gonna look into it more too but
the bottom line is
the bottom line is we become an
experiment right so the drug dealer from
big pharma ashley kevin i saw
the drug dealer from big pharma comes to
the doctor's office
shows him what he's got whether it's
five years ago four years ago three
years ago today tomorrow
and then everybody's now an experiment
on that drug right
so everybody your experiment right so
with that in mind
right there could be some new medical
treatments that are really really
peer pressure peer pressure
you know
[Music]
right under pressure people go like
under pressure
and to actually partake
and so here you are moving forward
moving forward moving forward moving
forward moving forward moving forward
moving forward
you're healing you're healing you're
healing what
going back so that's you know and then
there's
so many different there's so many
different potholes and
and trouble spots out there and
everything else that could happen
um so i just want you to know
that we have to we have to be
also our own caretakers right
we gotta be we gotta just we gotta know
discernment
right the funniest thing i've seen
people out there say i don't know about
celery juice
i don't know about it i don't trust it i
don't
know i heard it's okay um i'd rather
keep on taking all my drugs
and trust the newest medical treatment
that comes out you know meanwhile
meanwhile it's like all right
that's fine with me dr phone
hey you thought it was isis baby i think
it's david bowie under pressure right
yeah but exactly so the bottom line is
be open-hearted good to see you today so
glad you're here today
aw thanks soc good to see you
open-hearted
awesome cool cool um so yeah
i just so the bottom line is you guys is
when we're healing
there's there's ways we can go backwards
and we have to be careful we have to
look out right
the blood draw is one of them that's one
right there all on its own
um there's a lot of reasons
that we have to be careful not just one
right there
i'm not talking about getting your
carpets cleaned right there that can
set somebody back can't tell you how
many people they get their carpets
cleaned by toxic chemicals boom
uh household cleaners that aren't
natural
boom right msg and natural flavors uh
bug bites bug bites can set people back
i've seen bug bites set
people back right so you know they're
it's swimming in the ocean as beautiful
as it seems did
everything cold white spring um hearing
about odd reactions from people living
with those that
had certain things going on huh out
there so yeah i mean the bottom line is
you know it's it's there's a lot of
things happening
that we get stuck in right so we get a
lot of radiation
you go through the airport that's a big
one i can't even tell you right
like i tell family and friends like
hey be careful in the airport you know
be careful opt
out for certain things and stuff because
you go into the airport
and the radiation you can get whacked
with when you're traveling is
unbelievable right and then your luggage
too
i tell people you gotta throw out your
luggage every now and then you got to
throw your luggage out
keep that in mind you know it's it's
like because
the luggage is a radiation collector
right when you go through the airport
you got a knapsack
what i do is i throw that knapsack out
every time yeah it gets expensive and
it's annoying but i try to balance my
own personal life budget to that
you know so when i travel and i have to
stick that
that knapsack that on through that
radiation little spot right there right
if i do that i know that that thing's
gonna collect so much radiation
that if i have it in my house or
whatever it is or wherever i am and i
have it it's going to constantly be
radiating that radiation right so
it's these things that matter all these
little things add up so what can we do
for ourselves celery juice is one of
those things that can also help us
um yeah susan gross is a harmful
fly choice of years twice a year isn't
bad but just look out for those very
things right
so um here's the thing about celery
juice if you're gonna buy celery juice
don't do hpp don't buy it with
hpp that is a bad
trick going down right now and i know
i'm not going to make any friends
once again every time i look out for you
guys
i don't make friends and
that's another one right there high
pressure pasteurization
right and you know high pressure
pasteurization just
isn't gonna work uh cat conte celery
juice daily for six months i am healing
and had an excellent checkup new book is
god send two the new
book you guys i didn't even show you my
book right
revise and expand it new edition the
medical medium
new edition it's gotta be the new
edition definitely
definitely gonna be a new edition right
so
hpp is something that's a new uh
pasteurization process that's fairly new
in the last decade right
and it allows juices
on the store shelf to look like they're
raw
and to look like they're fresh just
letting you know
so and and they don't use heat
to pasteurize so they're allowed to say
hey this stuff is fresh this stuff is
raw right
and it's got a shelf life on there for a
month or to have a shelf life on there
for three
three weeks or a shelf life on there for
you know two weeks you'll see it right
but if it was really fresh juice
it only has a few days a shelf life for
two days
right so what happens people don't
realize that they go in the health food
store
they walk in here i'm gonna grab
something after my yoga class here let
me grab
whoa celery juice hey it says fresh whoa
it says raw let me grab it it's in the
cold
section let me just grab that celery
juice and they grab it
okay and they think they got some fresh
raw celery juice they go that
you know they cash out and drink in it
like okay
it's not gonna work it's not gonna work
it's not
it's been injured so it's been injured
through high
pressure pasteurization
high pressure pasteurization right it's
not
fresh it's only fresh if you saw a dude
there at the health food store running
that celery through that juicer or
if a dude or whoever right or if
somebody working there
right um was was running that juicer
and running juice through it right
meaning creating juice
and then putting that on the shelf for a
day or two
for a day or two you know so that that
right there
that's fresh right and that that is not
going to have a shelf life it's not
going to have a long-term shelf life
i'm just telling you right now
so the juice a little bit
don't add anything to your celery juice
i said it before i'll say it again
what you'll see out there too is those
high pressure pasteurization celery
juices
hpp which don't work
what you'll see is they'll have lemon in
it
it's a bad idea that's strike number two
and
strike number two you add something to
your celery juice it's not gonna work
the way it's supposed to
you dilute the sodium cluster salts
it's what you do right you dilute the
sodium cluster salts
you don't want to add anything to it no
ice
no water no ice and no water
very important to know okay you don't
want to add
ice or water right by the way this is
the mm-900
hds um
i'm working with omega on this juicer
you guys know that
so one of the things that happened that
happens all the time is
people will say they did celery juice
and i've been doing this for so many
years and
people say they i i tried celery juice
no they didn't
i can't tell you how many people in the
health scene no they tried carrot
celery apple and beets together is what
they tried
no one was juicing celery by itself
therapeutically
therapeutically right it would be this
if if it ever happened it would be
because someone just for some reason
happenstance had only celery in their
fridge and not one other vegetable or
fruit and decided to juice right
but nobody ever did it therapeutically
right as as
as a medicine an herbal medicine and
what i love about
like a good juicer like this one right
here and you can use any juicer if you
have a juicer use any juicer you can use
a blender and strain it through a
cheesecloth
and nut milk bag right what i love about
this juicer is
is this pulp comes out so ridiculously
dry so i'm saving money
that's what i love about this one
so the tr that so where people get
fooled
is they put ice in their celery juice
they add water to their celery juice
if you're gonna blend it don't add water
to your blender
you're just gonna have to keep on
blending it pushing it down and blending
it not adding water
ichota good to see you you're here too
so why is celery juice helping people
heal i'm going to talk about that in a
minute like the power
it has why it's helping people and
bringing their lives back and moving the
needle
to cover that in a couple of minutes
you're someone sensitive to celery juice
there's a lot of bugs in your system a
lot of people got bad bacteria in their
intestinal lining
right right on their intestinal lining
bad
streptococcus that's one of them right
there a lot of people have that strep
right that's a bacteria right there they
got the strep
in there that's what gives you your sibo
your bloating
all kinds of other issues it's that
strep
and when you put the celery juice in you
you're actually killing off that strep
you're killing off those bugs and you
may only have you may be somebody that
could only do a little bit to start with
you start with a small amount
for somebody that can only do a little
bit of celery juice and that's that's
what you do then you start with a little
bit
um
and don't go like oh don't do a ton of
it
well a ton of it don't do 16 ounces
don't do 32 ounces then start small
do four ounces do two ounces start at
that level
joy and sago says are you doing celery
juice
after doing celery juice for about nine
months my endocrinologist lowered my
daily synthroid intake
that's incredible that's incredible
are you doing other tools medical medium
tools too
are you doing medical medium
supplementation protocols as well
because that's there too people can go
as far as they want with their thyroid
problems
when you have the right tools
peggy says don't add water to blended
celery juice peggy you're so right peggy
o'connor thanks for being here
today debbie manning how long is it good
for
in the fridge um
celery juice is good in the fridge
for a couple of days but honestly
i don't like i don't like keeping it in
there that long
i don't i like to drink it right after i
made it that's when it's best and the
most powerful
so celery juice is the most powerful and
and at its best
right when it's made fresh yeah
tara appleman tara good to see you uh
audrey antler pretty sure that they they
are being misleading
in saying that it's cold pressed
maybe but then hpp terry you're
spot on incredible actually because
people don't understand
hpp out there so that that's amazing you
know but then again you know a lot of
stuff
you're really knowledgeable um high
pressure pasteurized hpp which lengthens
the shelf life
but destroys the healing power of it
that was said
so perfectly tara appleman like that was
so perfectly said
it's actually said way better than what
what i was talking about
you know about it i don't even think i
was clear that was really to the point
um incredible really
so i'm gonna strain
some right here and put some in here
through the strainer
so i have
a glass here i think i'm gonna have
plenty left over
in this big tall glass
there you go put that right there for
now
um you know what's incredible about
this juicer is this pulp is dry to the
bone
bone just dry that's it i mean when i
think about it it still blows my
blows my mind really um daniel
anthony i wash i wash my conventional
celery with sodium bicarbonate is that
okay
this week you said you would not consume
sodium i would not eat it no
i i wouldn't i wouldn't take it i
wouldn't consume it
if you're gonna wash with it just wash
the sodium bicarbonate off
make sure that that's washed off good
okay and you can even use a little bit
of natural
dish soap if you wanted to like in like
a little gentle studs in a
big bowl of water but if you want to do
the sodium bicarbonate just make sure
that sodium bicarbonate is
is washed off that's all if it's washed
off then
you know you're looking better
but it could have some residue so make
sure you wash it off carefully
that's all like really good um
i mean honestly with celery you don't
even have if you're using warm water
that's an option right there a lot of
times i'll just use warm water in the
bowl
and i'll massage the celery and rinse it
massage it rinse it
and get the inside of the stalks like
this right here with my thumb
and i'm using just warm water and i'm
not using anything else right
with conventional too but yeah if you
want to use sodium bicarbonate
you can but just make sure you're
washing off
as much as you can of that too and
there's no residue left over
try to be cautious on that level because
you don't want to ingest sodium
bicarbonate i mean it's you know
but there's a question on the juicer
it's uh
mm-900 hds so mm-900 hds
um i mean honestly it saved me so much
money it's
ridiculous at this point i can't tell
you how much celery i would buy
and any juicer i've tried i don't care
what kind of juicer it was and i've
tried them all
it would just be like you're you've got
the wet pulp
right because you're not getting enough
juice out of it so you're literally
losing money while
you're trying to do it and that's why i
like the mm-900 it's an affordable
really compared to so many models out
there
and then it's dry to the bone and that's
the
that's that's incredible it's like my
favorite
um yeah julie
jewel julie says that juicer is the best
my pulp is very dry thanks anthony it's
incredible right
i've given the the company my full
endorsement this is omega juicers.com
you get it there um this is the mm-900
hds salary juicer i'm working with the
company
as far as like to try to really like
benefit people's lives with this
adriana adi i don't have any reaction to
celery juice does that mean i don't have
bad bacteria
a couple of things it means is that
there's a good chance
that you don't have um
there's different kinds of bacteria some
bacteria is more toxic so that when it
dies
you you feel it you feel it when it dies
so that could be some runs that could be
some extra bloating it could be anything
like that right so
you feel it okay then you can have
different varieties of bad bacteria like
low-grade strep that's
not aggressive doesn't it's not as it
it's not as
toxic and that's one thing or you don't
have
a heck of a lot of toxins in you so that
the bacteria
in you isn't loaded they're not like
loaded guns
so you know it's it's like or bombs
right the more toxic stuff you have in
you
the more the bad bacteria that you have
in you gets
extra toxic so when you kill off that
bacteria
there's a splash right there's an
aftermath awake
right so there's a good chance maybe you
don't have a lot of toxins in your
intestinal tract
maybe you have more toxins in your liver
see and when they're in your liver you
may not feel it like that
some people they got a ton of stuff in
their gut a lot of it a lot of toxins a
lot of bacteria that's eating the toxins
the minute that celery juice goes down
in there it's like a bomb blows off
right these bugs they'll just you know
we can weaken
and explode the sodium cluster salt i'll
just use this orange as a sodium cluster
salt
that sodium cluster salt sticks to the
bug
that's what happens stay stuck to it
and stay stuck to it and eats away at
the bug
until the bug just falls apart kind of
kind of concaves in right and when that
does that
boom all the poison in that bug comes
out so
your bugs might not have a lot of
different poisons in them that are more
aggressive some people have bugs and
they're they're
filled chalk full of poisons right so
there's all these different variables
that's one thing right there um you
might have more stuff going on in your
liver
you might have some more stuff going on
in your nervous system might have stuff
more stuff going on in these other
places
but in somebody else to just have a
trail of
bad stuff inside their gut right their
intestinal lining bugs of all
kinds dehydrated proteins stuck to the
walls
with bugs behind them e coli c diff
streptococcus staph all in their gut
you know maybe throw a couple of worms
in there too which aren't parasites
they're worms
it's very important to know two
different distinct distinct
distinctions really important
heidi hey what if what if diagnosed with
celery allergy well okay okay so be your
own detective right
and i talk to doctors about this one all
the time like what if you're diagnosed
with a celery allergy and i've been
asked that by doctors okay it's like
wait a minute does that mean something
happens when you eat the celery like
is something happening is it where
is it where your um
is it where something happens in the
sense where you eat it and your throat
closes up
is that that kind of allergy or you eat
it and your mouth does something weird
and swells
is it that kind of allergy like what's
going on there is it something like that
because these are things to consider or
nothing happens
nothing happens okay you're just
just living your life and nothing
happens is it that
and and but yet you had
a practitioner do you know an all cat or
or a food sensitivity test and they
listed the celery on your test
now here's the first question i'll i'll
ask you right
what do you think about this okay what
do you think about this
all of our doctors and practitioners
don't know why we have chronic illness
and they don't know what causes
autoimmune okay
they're trying their best to help in any
way they possibly can
so we have our practitioners
they might be good at looking and
reading at a test
say a test like a food allergy
sensitivity test right
but it is is it even right like it is it
even
on is it even spot on is it even like
is it right is it correct because what
i've learned
is there are foods that help you that
show up as an allergen on your test
because that food that's helping you is
battling the bad stuff
okay i've seen that in tests too
i've also seen foods that don't help you
show up on a food allergy test but
more more occasions i see foods that are
actually
helping people show up on the allergy
test they'll be like oh
strawberries strawberries are really
good for us they're incredible right oh
figs you're allergic to figs right
oh no you're allergic to cilantro too
we're reading your test right here
and it looks like we're allergic to
cilantro looks like we're allergic to
parsley
you know the whole bit and and um and
then we'll we'll think
that okay wait a minute there's
something here you're allergic to rag
rad wheat ragweed
you're allergic to cilantro parsley
you're allergic to star and nice
allergic to ginger allergic to
strawberries allergic to a blackberry
allergic to rutabaga you're allergic to
you know you'll see the weirdest thing
radish you're allergic to you'll see
and celery you'll see all of a sudden
then they'll say oh you're allergic to
gluten too
right they'll throw the gluten in there
you're allergic to
you're allergic to uh sheep's milk and
they come out with this
random random stuff like on the test
right
you're allergic to caseopod
you're allergic to chamomile you're
allergic too and they got this
whole thing going down where it's like
now you're like allergic to all this
right you're just allergic to all
this stuff
okay and meanwhile
the the guy right he or she
doesn't even know why anybody's sick out
there that's what's amazing
they don't know why everybody's dealing
with fibro and hashimoto's they don't
know it causes anything they don't know
why people are sick with exomus rises
they don't know why people have all
these symptoms they don't know why
people have anxiety depression but it's
like but yeah they're spot on about
reading a test
which is a whole other thing all on its
own so um
so what happens is with the food
sensitivity test if if a
food is killing off pathogens
it might show up on that food
sensitivity test
if it's killing off bugs and then
if a food is feeding bugs
it may show up on that food sensitivity
test too but are you really allergic to
it
see what i talked to this this other
doctor friend of mine
many years ago it's like 25 years ago
right
and um i talked to him recently and he's
like 94 years old now you know and i've
been helping him with his health his
whole life right all these years and his
whole life but
for as long as i've known him i mean his
his his
elder life i've been helping him with
right and not the beginning in his life
i wasn't born yet but the point is is
that what i've learned
from him is that he said an allergic
reaction to a fruit or a vegetable
right or anything like that okay or an
herb
you have to experience it where your
throat's doing something like closing
off you know
your mouth swells and you can't breathe
your lips swell up right and then
that's how the old-school way to
determine if you're really allergic
because the new school
which he's seen too out there with all
the food sensitivity tests
the new school doesn't add up unless
you're experiencing
like every time you bite onto a celery
stick
do you break out in a rash every time
you bite out mine in a celery stick your
throat swallows up
like that's the allergy like that's the
same thing with any food right
mirrorless um aw with the cj and
hmds cause an ear and headache
from detoxing the brain have been in a
screeching pain for 10 days
i've never seen it cause any of that um
but
if that was me i'd be glad i was doing
cj
if that was me do what your doctor tells
you to do if he doesn't watch on cj or
not you do what your doctor tells you
but if it was me
um i'm i would be happy i'm on cj
because i'm
i would be hoping the cj could be
helping
so that's not worse than it would be and
then i always backtrack what else did i
do what else did i do
is it a is it a new medical treatment i
might have gotten involved in
is it is it um exposure
without realizing it is it um
exposure to air fresheners exposure to
cologne perfume is it exposure to
scented candles
is it was my immune system down did i
get a blood draw a month ago and
i didn't know it but my immune system
dropped down did i get a blood draw two
months ago and now i'm on this road of
now getting sicker because i had
all this blood drawn from me right i
would do all the like
the spot checking like what else is
happening am i under a lot of stress
you know how's my relationships going
did i have a hard time did it
trigger me into something um anything
like that i would go through
all the paces all the paces right and
then i would look into i would even look
into look get this free at the library
if you don't want to buy it this is the
new edition medical medium new edition i
got a migraine chapter in here and then
you can really look into all the
migraines and see
what's happening all the migraine stuff
so that's important to know right there
juicing a little bit more celery
so these are all things to consider
so we covered a little food sensitivity
stuff is really cool
i love talking about that because people
really don't know a lot about it you
know
so it's so important to have that
information it really is
monica l smith says i don't have a
juicer but i cut up my celery into small
pieces
add to my blender add a banana blueberry
spinach and cilantro love it i don't add
no water rice
well first of all i just love that
you're doing that monica
i love it okay you want to make a
smoothie
you want to make a smoothie and you want
celery in your smoothie
it's healthy right it's not going to do
the same
thing it's not going to be the same
thing
as celery juice on its own okay because
you're mixing it with something you're
mixing it with fruits and vegetables
right
so you're mixing it with all this other
stuff so it can't
do the same thing it's supposed to do
right
and but you made a really healthy
smoothie
totally now if that was me you do what
your doctors tells you of course but if
it was me
i would add you know bemergey spirulina
i would add some barley grass juice
powder
it wouldn't be the medical medium heavy
metal detox movie but it would be
getting closer to it and then
and then i would i would you know amp it
up if you're gonna makeshift a smoothie
of some kind wanting it to help
but it's not gonna do what celery
celery does on its own when you juice
celery by itself okay
so keep that in mind too that's
important to keep in mind
um so
why does celery help us so much i'll
give you a little
give you a little show in a second too
to see you guys today i'm really happy
about this
i'm just juicing a little extra i used
to be glass a couple seconds ago and i'm
gonna i'm gonna juice a little bit more
real quick right now
i'm gonna pour some as we speak um a
little extra
is what i'm doing
what i like to do is any pulp left over
i like to press it with my fingers on
top of it too
there's so it's just so great
maria says common sense when i do the
food sensitivity test
and they told me i am
all w-r-g-i
gender to spinach oh you're allergic to
spinach and such
i instinctively knew it was complete
common sense
yeah yeah and that's that's incredible
you know
um so
it makes a lot of sense exactly honestly
they'll tell you you're allergic to
spinach right they'll say you're
allergic to spinach or something
and but you're not allergic to spinach
right
food sensitivity test i think was one of
the biggest scams
of our like alternative medicine days it
was could still at half conventional
it really hit the alternative market
more a lot of functional medicine
doctors do it doesn't mean the
functional medicine doctor isn't smart
doesn't mean the
functional medicine doctor isn't it
isn't up on some other stuff
it just means the functional medicine
doctor doesn't realize that the food
sensitivity test really has holes in it
everywhere
um i don't even trust the labs on any
level really
[Music]
so red says what brand of juice
press that so this is a cold pressed
juicer this is
a mega juicers.com but
it they have a lot of juicers there
don't get them confused this is the
mm-900
hds mm-900hds
this is their celery juicer model but
you can juice anything in it it's
incredible
the pulp comes out so dry it's
ridiculous
and i'm saving so much money every every
year with this now i mean
it's my end to my second year of saving
money because i
get so much so so much celery and i you
know i juice so much of it it's such a
great machine
so what do you do with all the pulp
it goes to my garden valerie yeah goes
in my garden
it does don't get thrown by the whole
thing where
you juice and you're wasting all this
pulp right even if you threw the pulp
away
in the garbage bin and didn't use it for
your garden you're not wasting it
there's a reason for that first of all
you're extracting medicine out of the
celery so you're using it as a medicine
you're extracting herbal medicine right
you're doing herbal medicine so you're
getting all the
what you need out of it to turn it into
something just like a tea
right just like a tea where you throw
the tea grounds away the other thing is
and keep this in mind this is an
important one too is when we
eat something it all gets thrown away
the fiber right all the pulp and fiber
we poop it out in the toilet right so is
everybody like saving their poop
because i'm confused about that one i
had i had some like an r
an rn registered sorry are not an rn
nurse an rd
right registered dietitian confront me
one time right when i was doing a
lecture years ago
and she said okay well that's really
great so you're just gonna have
everybody
throw away and waste all of that fiber
and pulp and
that's what you're doing with the
juicing it's such a bad idea i don't
believe in juicing i don't believe
you're doing anything right and i'd be
like listen listen i said
everybody who eats she was like you eat
it you eat it i go okay well you eat it
and then all the pulp and fiber that you
can't use
just like this pulp and fiber here
because you squeezed everything out of
it you can't use there's nothing
in here anymore like this here there's
nothing you can do with this
this if you ate the celery this would
still come out of your back end
this would still come out of you right
your bottom end would still
this would come out right here this this
this would not get utilized
every single like the pith from the
orange
and the the pulp from the orange is
going to come out of you
you're not going to utilize all that
fiber
it's going to come out into the toilet
and
anything you extract with a good juicer
especially this juicer right
because there's nothing left right
anything you extract with a good juicer
um it you would be doing the same if you
ate it
right but the difference is you can't
get you
so the question would be we'll just eat
it then why juice
it no that's not how you can actually
create herbal medicine
a large extraction of an herbal medicine
that takes
no digestion no digestion
that right there you don't weaken your
digestive process you strengthen it you
strengthen your hcl you strengthen your
stomach glands that's a whole other
thing there
okay so you're strengthening your gut
your digestion you're strengthening your
hcl
um your gastric juice production
from your stomach glands you're
strengthening your liver
that's the difference durable medicine
you can't strengthen so much
when you're eating all the fiber and
pull so the argument is this
is they're like well let's just eat it
because you're just wasting it anyway
what are you kidding
um this is going to come out of you
everything you eat apples
meat whatever is coming whatever's left
of what you're eating that can't be
broken down
is going out the toi into the toilet
right so what are you gonna do i mean
you may as well
juice a medicine throw this in your
garden
so you're actually being able to use the
fiber much
better than if you just ate the stuff
went to the bathroom and it went
out to the septic right so and that
that's important to know
it looks like this model juicer is just
for celery it's it's not just for celery
it's for
everything not recommended for any other
fruits but actually it is
am i understanding this right no beverly
i'm glad you asked it's a really good
question no it's a juicer for everything
it just has a celery juice attachment
and you can use that attachment and
still juice everything and squeeze a lot
more out of everything
be open heart it says i needed this
today thank you awb open art good to see
you i saw your comments and
uh on the youtube that you the last
youtube i think it's the last one
i think you left a couple of comments or
it was the one before that um
lorraine i did the same show that my
budget's really low but i'm still
healing lorraine good to see you
today auburn i'm so grateful for the
work you do
thank you for the info it's healing you
incredible
lorraine the disaster we think it's the
greatest
thing i've heard that's why i repeat it
over and over again
it's made me laugh for weeks um it
really has by the way
okay so you know that's why i say it all
the time
i see it all the time because it's
actually perfect it really works with it
it does because every time i burn
something
every time i remember the ginger he told
me the ginge like the ginger flew off
the counter
disappeared went off down the floor
somewhere it's hilarious you know and
then i try to pick up the pace
at the beginning this youtube my phone
in my back pocket was going off i didn't
have it on silent it's disaster relief i
don't want
it's just hilarious dr phan allergy
tests are bogus
that's coming from medical doctor an
amazing medical doctor right there
incredible really is um so
because i mean really we can't go by
that
mishi madness that's a cool handle
celery juice is a game changer it really
is it's such a game changer it really is
having some right now um
so okay so the whole thing what do you
want to do with your fiber
it's not going to break down anyway in
your gut okay
you're going to get plenty of fiber
anyway i'm not telling you to live off
juice only
you're going to eat and you're going to
get tons of fiber your berries your
apples your melons
your your grapefruits anything you eat
right any vegetable you eat
cucumbers that's a fruit tomatoes that's
a fruit right zucchini
you know that's a fruit hey i'm hitting
all the fruits right now but vegetables
like the
crucifix cruciferous right you got your
kale you got your
broccoli you got your cauliflower you
got your cabbage right all that fiber is
just
gonna come out of you right you're gonna
get plenty of fiber plenty of fiber
so so when someone says oh you're you
know you're juicing the celery
what a waste it's like okay well that's
really funny because
we're going to poop out all the stuff
we're not going to use and it's going
down in the toilet at least with this i
could throw it in my garden
some you know
but anyway it the whole thing about
let's talk about this part too
right so um so as far as
intestinal tract goes let me grab an
intestinal tract really quick
i'm going to grab a liver too i'm going
to show you guys
all right so what i like to do is i like
to think about what the celery juice is
doing when it's going through my gut the
beginning
to begin with when it starts at the
stomach which i don't have a stomach
right now but that's okay
meaning i don't have a stomach here but
what it does is it already charges up
those stomach glands
it's bringing back the stomach gland so
the trace mineral salts the sodium
cluster salts are bringing back
the the stomach glands it's the one
thing right there off you know
right off the start with your stomach
when it leaves your stomach starts
heading down into the
the duodenum right and when it heads
down to your wad a lot of people have h
pylori
you don't know it but just almost
everybody has h pylori
and and they'll have the h pylori at
different levels some people have it
where they ca
it can't be detected it's not at this
raging level
so and that's what most people have at
but it's there so as it starts heading
down to the duodenum it's
knocking down some h pylori left and
right so the celery juice
is going through and just boom right
then it hits
the the top of your small intestinal
tract okay
where there's always some bacteria
sitting right there all on its own
sometimes viruses too
viruses and bacteria right some some
unproductive
fungus bad fungus right fungus
mold right and even though mold doesn't
cause
a big problem when it's in us the
viruses and bacteria cause the most
problem
you'll still have some mold in there why
have that in there
everybody has it in there but celery
juice can start to clean that up
so it starts to go down to small
intestinal tract and now it's heading
down and it's hitting different pockets
what happens with everybody is our small
intestinal tract
is pocketing it's it's expanding in some
areas
shrinking in some areas expanding in
some areas
shrinking in some areas right or it's
the same size but internally
it's shrinking because it's inflamed
that's the other thing too
you could have narrowing some people
have a lot of narrowing some people have
a little bit of neurons some people have
expansion some people have
mega colon colon
and that's with you know the large
intestinal tract mostly with mega colon
right
where it just keeps on it keeps on
expanding it loses its elasticity it's
losing that it's starting to expand
right diverticulitis but diverticulitis
is all that e coli
streptococcus right c death
and mostly strep and e coli with
diverticulitis right diverticulosis
so as the celery is going down it's got
a lot of work to do
it's heading on down and it's starting
to just get into those pockets and nooks
and crannies right
you know what happens when you guys
vacuum your house what are you doing
you're like vacuuming in the bathroom
then you vacuum in the corner and
vacuum here you're vacuuming this corner
and trying to get all the different
corners right
the celery juice is trying to hit every
corner as it's going on down and running
on through you
and and that's what's happening you guys
and it's
it'll run into a pocket of e coal like e
coli festers these little pockets
they fester and here's the other thing
inside your small intestinal tract right
you got you got caked caked on
um um putrified proteins
they're kicked down the walls of your
small intestinal tract you got rancid
fat that hardened you got actual
fat that hardened all in the small
intestinal tract right i've talked to a
lot of colon surgeons over the years
intestinal surgeons you know
gastrointestinal
surgeries that that people have had that
i would talk to the surgeons
and and so forth right and and
they would talk about how the inside of
the intestinal tract when they really
took a good look the inside
from the eye not from the scope
the eye sees things that the scope can't
see and the scope sees things that the
eye can't see
the scope sees things when your
intestinal tract is sitting inside of
you
right so the scope goes up you right you
know you know endoscopy
colonoscopy right but what happens is
that
from the surgeon's eye is a whole other
story when they have a piece of small
intestinal tract that they cut out
so they cut out two feet of your colon
or small intestinal tract combined or
they cut your ilium out and part of your
small intestinal tract and part of your
colon out right
and they slice it open and look inside
a good gastrointestinal surgeon right a
good surgeon
colon surgeon will see you know things
differently in a lot of people and a lot
of times the higher you go up
into the small intestinal tract the more
caked on rancid fats built up in the
testosterone lining the more um the more
uh putrified proteins hardened on the
lining
up higher right celery juice starts to
work all the way down right the top
the the bottom of your stomach there's a
little divot that starts to occur
and sitting in it is all this junk and
sludge
celery just starts to knock that down it
gets down your dwadding starts to knock
off each pylori boom boom boom
starts to get down the small intestinal
tract starts to hit pockets of e coli
streptococcus starts to go through there
heading on down head down down
it's it's wham it's hitting things and
then
it gets absorbed and starts heading up
the hepatic portal highway
veins and that are
driving up to your
liver right okay and you know veins
arteries that are running in and out of
the liver right so all of a sudden now
you've got it going up the paddock
portal highway
heading to the liver and that's where
the solar just has to go and when it
goes there
we do some shock treatment you got a
liver full of all kinds of poisons and
toxins
stagnant sluggish liver giving you
gaining weight the reason why you're
gaining weight
all of it why does celery juice start
fixing things where we start losing
weight start getting our lives back
because it's getting into that liver
it's cleaning up that stagnant sluggish
liver you got viruses inside that liver
right here you got viruses inside that
liver
you know and all of a sudden boom
the celery juice is hitting it so this
is this isn't
be open-hearted you said best medical
medium community
medical mean community is the best
community ever in health uh
raquel jane i've been doing it for two
years doesn't help me at all
have lime now mold h by laurie sibo i
was praying it worked it would help
um so here's what you have to think
about what would happen if you weren't
doing celery juice for the last two
years
with your h pylori and everything else
would it be
the same or do you think it would be
worse
so and what else is happening so
i want you to do everything your doctor
tells you to do but if i
was doing that i'd be like well what
else am i doing
right am i getting rid of the eggs the
milk cheese the butter
am i getting rid of all of that am i
mixing medical medium information with
other information out there
am i doing apple cider vinegar am i
doing nutritional yeast am i on caffeine
and chocolate
am i doing those things am i doing the
eggs like i was saying
am i doing too much pork did i have pork
at all
how much fat am i on two right
how much blood is being taken from me so
what about my blood draws right
so how much blood is being taken from me
two how much medication am i on
right so what meds are what meds am i
taking
too you know was i on a lot of
antibiotics for my lime
was i mean all these things add up right
so was i on antibiotics for my lime two
years ago three years ago four years ago
how much damage did the antibiotic do
how much repair do i really have to do
am i doing a lime protocol
right so that's the next thing too am i
exposed to other things am i exposed to
clones and perfumes
does somebody i live with have a lot of
cologne going on maybe they don't am i
doing scented candles am i doing air
fresheners right
am i doing this so i'm giving you the
run down right here am i getting
dental work and i'm getting my immune
system knocked down with dental work did
i get hit with some fluoride
fluoride treatments right so all these
things
matter like what else am i eating am i
still eating tuna fish
what what else is going on am i still
using deodorant with aluminum in it
right
so all these things matter and or am i
just doing celery juice
have i looked in the lime chapter so if
that was me
i'd be in the lyme disease chapter right
here and i would be looking at like
the lyme protocol take it to your doctor
if it's you take it to your doctor
do what your doctor tells you but take
it to your doctor see what he thinks
but what i would be doing is the medical
medium protocols i'd start to read the
supplement chapter
learning what's happening in here that's
important what kind of
supplements are you taking right like
what kind what kind of supplements
now for i want you to do what your
doctor says but what i recommend a
family member when when they get lyme
disease right
i recommend like the vimergy cats claw
the vimersy zinc
the vimergy vitamin c these are just a
few things right there
so that's a critical aspect all on its
own the vimergy lysine
no msg no alcohol no added
no added natural flavors which is the
msg that's important too
am i taking goldenseal for my h pylori
see so if it was me or a family member
i'd be like you got to be on the golden
seal and you got to be on the right one
you got to be on some cat's claw don't
do what i what i'm
what i recommend for a family member you
do what your doctor tells you to do but
this is what i would do
with my family i'd be like are you on
the golden seal
you know are you on the micro sea are
you on the cat's claw because that lyme
disease we gotta get to that epstein bar
we gotta get to the cause of what you're
really going through
and then what kind of how much celery
juice are you doing i tell my family
member are you doing 32 ounces of celery
juice
what is it you're doing 32 ounces so
that's another thing all in its own
right
and then you know i would be another
thing i would learn from medical medium
information
lyme disease then i would say wait a
minute that's neurological
so a lot of neurological symptoms with
lyme disease how much b12
am i do i need how much b12 should i be
on am i doing the right b12 the right
kind
that's the vimergy so you guys know
bemidji it's v is in victor i am as mary
e r g
y uh bemergee.com and i'm not sponsored
but if there's lots of traps out there
so what are the traps what's going on
right there's a lot of different
supplements out there with msg and
alcohol
and casey of gum and citric acid what
would you know what's going on like and
i would be my own detective and saying
you know i need to look into the medical
media books
i need to know where i'm stepping into
those potholes i need to know where i'm
tripping up i need to know
why am i not getting better how many
blood draws have i had
now i know as is being in this in this
for so many years
that people with lyme disease have the
blood sucked out of them
they have the blood sucked out of them
three years ago
someone could be getting 40 vials 30
vials
10 vials regularly and then they get
sicker two years
later because they've had so much blood
taken from them before that
so so it's not just hey celery just
isn't working for me
celery juice is trying to save save you
while there's all these other things
going on dr fong celery powder isn't
effective at all oh it's terrible
save your money on that real salary your
celery powder is awful
it's terrible terrible it's the worst
worst stuff
it's just this so all these things
matter you guys
all these things are critical
esther what if someone doesn't want to
do mono cleanse to give digestion a
break
can we do a juice cleanse all juices
look i'm not a big fan of the juice
cleanses because what happens is you go
under calorie
well do what your doctor says your
doctor wants energy just let's do it
but esther what happens is juice
cleanses you go
under calorie then you go under calorie
too long right so i don't mind a juice
cleanse for two days but is it a juice
cleanse that that's actually like
efficient enough is it does it have
enough glucose the reason why people are
sick is because
they're missing the mineral salts and
the glucose so when you go on these
juice cleanses it doesn't mean it's the
right even the right combinations it
doesn't mean it's enough calories to
give you the glucose and then
you can tank right and in juice cleanses
if they're not done right can lower your
immune system
versus help your immune system so keep
that in mind too
um but yeah incredible you guys i'm
heading off to ig and tiktok
i didn't even get a chance because the
pink phone didn't even ring
i don't know what happened
we had a lot to talk about um you guys i
love you guys greatly
and i'm heading off to tick tock ig in a
little bit
just a few minutes i hope you guys come
with me so i can't wait i'm looking
forward to it
incredible
and if you guys get a chance i'm doing
the star gazing meditation tonight just
letting you know
so stargazing meditation doing that
tonight medical meeting podcast
apple podcast i hope you do it with me
tonight that would be incredible
um and i'm going over to ig now it's
going to be a different show probably
it's not going to be the
same show here i think we're going to do
something a little different on there
i love you guys and i'll see you guys
soon if you come over to ig
and tick tock with me alright