[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello this is Anthony William
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week you hear the
most advanced healing information that's
decades ahead of what's out there now if
we think science and research knows
everything thing about chronic illness
we're actually blinded by something and
I don't know what that is exactly
besides maybe trust in the medical
system and maybe that happens when we've
never been sick we're we're not
struggling we're not suffering we
haven't gone to 10 neurologists I mean
I've talked to people over the years
that have come to me over the years I
decades ago that have gone to five or
eight or nine or 10 different
neurologists looking for answers about
their different symptoms 250 million
Americans alone in the US don't have
answers for symptoms they're dealing
with and if they have an answer it
doesn't mean it goes away and that's
what we're up against right now so when
you think about it you guys the science
of research know everything about
chronic illness they don't why would we
ever think so at this point and and you
know everything is blamed on us from
genes and also our bodies attacking
themselves we're told it's faulty you
know our bodies are faulty our bodies
are problematic and this is a example of
how the industry is because what science
and research does is it protects itself
before it protects people that's how it
works now not in every single field but
in chronic illness I'm not talking about
making Parts you know making nuts and
bolts nuts and bolts you know that are
put together so we have braces for our
legs and we have different kinds of
pieces of medical basically medical
equipment we need in all kinds of
different areas that science is working
hard to try to perfect so we can live a
better quality of life while we're sick
I'm talking about every day aches and
pains the tingles and numbness the
vertigo the dizziness the balance issues
the headaches the migraines the anxiety
the depression I mean everything neck
pain back pain sciatica from everything
from planter fasciitis to bladder
infections constant chronic UTI uh sinus
infections that never go away to fungus
on the skin to eczema and psoriasis to
dermatitis to lyan scosi and Vitiligo to
all kinds of what's deemed autoimmune
diseases like Lyme disease and
rheumatoid arthritis and Hashim modus
thyroiditis to all these things we are
in a bad place and it hasn't gotten
better and yeah the world has gotten rid
of processed foods not the whole world a
lot of people are getting rid of
processed foods they're getting now
cleaner high fat diets versus the
dirtier high-fat diet so instead of
people getting fried grease with their
with their bread and you know their
bread and butter they're off their bread
a lot of people are off their bread and
they're off the fried grease and instead
they're eating you know like healthier
grease so they're eating their oils and
they're eating their nut Butters and all
that and that's actually healthier stuff
but the keto diets and the keto way of
thinking whether you're paleo whether
you're paleo keto whether you're high
protein keto whether you're plant-based
keto still isn't fixing everybody it
helps people with mild symptoms who have
been on all the different diets I mean
actually have you know it's been helped
it it's helped people with milder
symptoms who've eaten all not so great
and don't take care of themselves and
they seem to be okay but anybody else
chronically ill with real problems the
higher fat diets hasn't been helping and
I'm going to talk about why cuz Today's
Show is about toxic heavy metals and how
the relationship of the higher fat diets
that we're on whether they're clean and
healthier ones right now okay how this
doesn't work with toxic heavy metals and
how toxic heavy metals are responsible
for all the brain fog the Alzheimer's
the Parkinson's the anxiety the
depression the memory issues the OCD and
that's just some of the things and these
toxic heavy metals they feed pathogen
illnesses that are not autoimmune it's
called fibromyalgia CFS Ms lime disease
these aren't autoimmune these aren't the
body attacking itself these are there's
real problems behind there these are
pathogens behind this has nothing to do
with autoimmune these are actually
viruses and bacteria reproductive system
problems econ rri it's PCOS and so much
more and in the celery juice book I hope
you guys have that celery juice book by
now because almost 200 symptoms and
conditions in that book I talk about
about what the causes are what causes it
and what to do for it this is an
important radio show it's we're going to
talk a little bit about the history on
heavy metals toxic heavy metals where
they come from and where we're going and
you have to know I love science and
research I love it and here's the funny
thing
hardcore conventional science and
research hates all the other science and
research so all the different things
everybody's citing around like science
science is behind that science is behind
that study science is behind what how
the Body Works science is behind this
about autoimmune or this and this and
this and no one
realizes that those sciences that are
all being created right now for even in
alternative medicine thrown every
everywhere like in in different
countries and in the United States and
everything that hardcore science
conventional science doesn't doesn't
back up any of it on any level so
everybody's throwing throwing around
different Sciences around every single
day but we use the word as if
everything's concrete and everybody's
happy and the Science World is all happy
the Science World is at war with itself
right now totally completely at war with
itself they're literally they're
literally battling each other there's
all kinds of different Sciences now and
alternative medicine and someone's
trying to prove the MTHFR G mutation
Theory which was a theory that's all it
was there's no science approve it till
this day there's not one single bit of
science regular science in conventional
world doesn't believe in the MTHFR gen
mutation they think that that's fake
science isn't that
incredible and because it actually is
skewed by the way but there's also
hardcore conventional science that's
skewed too because it all is there's a
reason for that in chronic illness
there's a reason for that agendas are
behind every single study they're behind
it all and guess what all the things
that make us sick are all avoided
everybody just you know has to stay sick
because of the wars because of the food
War because of the science War
everybody's got to stay sick that's how
it works the food war is like the the
animal High animal protein people
against the vegans against the plant
based there's that war and everybody's
throwing their F fake Sciences back and
forth you know the Paleo stuff this is
why paleo's better this is why vegan is
better this is why vegetarian's better
it's all being thrown everybody's
throwing their Sciences back and forth
while everybody else has to sit there
and suffer and get sick with their toxic
heavy metals why everybody has to sitck
there sit there and get and stay sick
and get sicker with their pathogens
their Epstein bar their hhv sixs their
um there different varieties of strepto
octus their shingles virus is their
herpes simplex ones and twos all the
mutations all the different varieties
everybody just has to sit around and get
sicker and sicker and sicker while the
animal protein people are against the
vegans vegans are against the animal
protein people they're all thrown away
bogus they're all thrown at each other
bogus bogus fake science and then at the
same time hardcore conventional science
where you know Harvard stands behind it
or whatever they're they're throwing
things they're they're they're doing
everything and throwing things at people
too at the at the what they think is the
alternative fake Sciences but they're
all backed by money and funding to try
to prove a point whether it's true
accurate not true whether a thumb is on
the scale they're all in it together and
all these wars are going on why
everybody just keeps on building heavy
metals in their liver and in their brain
doesn't know how to get it out of them
doesn't even know the first thing to get
it out of them and they get all the
different problems and neurological
problems and all the different viral
problems and all our all all the kids
are getting sick now teenagers all the
different young adults are getting sick
sicker than ever before in history we
never saw this 30 years ago and
everybody's busy with their War they're
funded Wars just think about that you
guys they're busy with their funded Wars
isn't that interesting don't you think
about it isn't it incredible where do I
sit in the middle of it I work for you
guys I work for God and I work for you
guys and look you may not believe in God
you may believe in something else that
it's a big light in the sky that it's
the universe maybe you believe in Gods
maybe you believe in something else
maybe you don't think it's a big man
sitting in a chair with a beard maybe
you think it's just this Creator or this
Creator power or whatever whatever you
might believe I I'm just saying whatever
it is you believe I work for that I work
for that and I work for you and that's
what I do and I hear the information
from my source since I was 4 years old
so that it isn't tampered with and isn't
tampered with and the wars don't
interfere with it exactly and we're
going to talk about heavy metals and
that's where we're going right now so
where did all these heavy metals come
from that are inside our body wreaking
havoc how could heavy metals be in your
body how can it be possible first things
first medications all medications have
Metals in them all medications have
Metals in them they end up in the liver
that's where they end up let's go to
another one fluoride are we getting
fluoride treatments did you have 10 of
them did you have five of them did you
have one of them did you have a whole
bunch of them when you were younger
fluoride how about that one
what about our water cuz you got to
remember fluoride I'll just first of all
let's back into this a little bit so I
can clarify medications have Metals in
them yes they have copper in them they
have aluminum in them they got all kinds
of stuff mercury in them they just have
medications have things in them bottom
line fluoride that's aluminum someone
said to me and a trying to debate me on
this and said no no fluoride's not
aluminum it's a byproduct I'm like oh my
God can we be any more or whatever you
want to call that I don't know what that
is you know when I get done talking to
somebody like that I say you know what
they just don't know and then in back of
my head I'm like how can they not know
so what is it are they just fighting for
something just to prove themselves right
or something fluoride a byproduct is
methyl aluminum no matter how you slice
the cake look none of us are all
supposed to have the answers I totally
get that we're all working hard together
on the planet and that's not it I'm
talking about health professionals that
deem themselves at the top of their game
and they want to debate me purposely
because I hear a voice and they don't
like the fact that that's where it's
coming from and that's what I'm talking
about I'm not talking about all of us
that you know are just trying to find
our way and get through everything and
we're we're not supposed to know where
medals are or where they come from or
what they are we're just not we're too
busy trying to survive think about that
everybody's too busy trying to survive
and live their life and get through
their day and work their job and try to
and try to get through and and through
what struggle and whatever emotional
challenges we get that's what's going on
I'm talking about professionals that are
supposed to be on top of their game and
think they are or say they are you know
and and and look we're all learn you
know I told this professional I said
look if you don't know
fluoride in the end is a toxic heavy
metal to the body then then why don't
you learn about it you no big deal and
if you don't know about it fine but but
no this person was head head hellbent
really just to be like no it's it it's
not toxic to anybody first of all it's a
neurotoxin it's a
neurotoxin and it's you know it's
nobody's it's nobody's fault it's
nobody's fault but the big
Industries it's nobody's fault but the
big big
industry and so there's nobody to blame
there's nobody to blame on that level I
mean they're the industries to blame
what about our water too it's a whole
another thing I mean we there's Metals
in our water absolutely I mean how many
water guys have I talked to over the
years that are like you know any kind of
apartment I've ever been in or any kind
of different living situation I always
have a water guy come and just do a
little test of my water it's like oh
yeah you're you know what you're you're
doing good something pars per million
lead not actually perfectly agreeable
EPA safe and then you got no just very
little traces of arsenic totally in
range of what we're allowed to have I'm
like are you kidding
me and he was like okay yeah that's her
water stand standard that's like our
water standard there's all that stuff is
in our water I mean it really is it's
like yeah but it's not above the what
you know the APA caus dangerous TOS what
do you mean like this stuff goes in the
liver and builds up and how much water
are you drinking and not drinking I'm
sorry for giggling about this I'm just
saying that it's almost like so obvious
that it just it it hurts it just does um
and then our air I mean you know there's
Metals dropping out of the sky in
abundance in
abundance you know I mean I was talking
to somebody in the spiritual movement
and they're like yeah I believe in
abundance this person was telling me and
you I got a lot of respect for this
person they're like I believe in
abundance it's all about an abundance
and I said and they
said and they said to me and they said
to me this person said to me Anthony
like what's your whole Mantra like
what's your whole thing and I'm like
well I just just know that there's an
abundance of toxic heavy metals raining
out of the sky I know it's Doom and
Gloom but if I don't stay aware of it
and teach others so we can get it out of
our body because it's going to be there
I want to get it out of everybody's body
so they can heal you know I can't and
you know it was funny and the spiritual
person spiritual Guru was like you know
I never thought about that they were
like I never thought about that they
like I'm always worried I just always
want abundance to come to me like and
come to me that's what this person was
saying
and I was like I look that's amazing but
I just want the abundance of metals out
of people's bodies that's what I want
and that's what I live for you know it's
like it's you know because that's how
much we're up against aluminum cans have
you have you consumed anything out of an
aluminum can or aluminum foil have you
eaten anything out of aluminum foil I
mean right I I knew somebody that worked
at a restaurant and said the aluminum
foil they use was low grade and I was
like low grade that's right low grade
aluminum foil and they said yeah and
they said every time they would bake
like a macaroni and cheese in the oven
at this restaurant they would put the
foil over the top and they'd bake the
macaroni and cheese and stuff like that
and then they remove the foil and pieces
of foil were just they melt it off of
the foil into the macaroni and cheese
and so the bottom line is the bottom
line is so listen I'm telling you all
these things because we get exposed and
how many sticks of gum has everybody
been eating all these years you know the
foil and n it's really incredible what
about pots and pans you know it's like
even the stainless steel pots and pans
stainless steel pots and pans that we
deal with in the restaurants I've seen
pots scraped to the Bone a friend of
mine years ago at a restaurant people
were just scraping the pots with metal
utensils where do you think all those
metal shavings went they went in
somebody's meal and they went in lots of
meals I mean restaurants are like one of
the most toxic heavy metal providing
Industries for everybody and we fill a
lifetime of up in using you know those
those just feel a lifetime of eating out
in restaurants I'm not trying to keep
you living in a box I'm not trying to
get you guys to just live in a little
box and never experience the world
that's not what I'm trying to do I just
want to get the medals out of you faster
than we're putting them in how about
that I'm just going to repeat that I
know it's annoying I'm probably annoying
today but the bottom line is I want to
get the metals out of you faster than
we're putting them in that's the bottom
line and then let's keep on going a
little bit long I'm not even talking
about old metal fillings I'm not even
talking about those those silver
fillings of the old days I mean how many
how many times did the industry try to
protect those metal fillings how many
times have they protected those metal
fillings to the point where everybody's
getting ceramic right now but they stood
by it the industry stood by it because
Mercury was mandatory in the
conventional standard to get into people
how do you like that it's just
unbelievable we thought we were ahead of
the game long time ago with that one and
that's what I mean science of research
proves itself as a bomb every time every
decade it's always wrong but we heralded
is this unbelievable thing that's always
right I mean come on are you sick of it
yet and then what about and listen think
about the metal fillings and the Mercury
fillings what we had to deal with and
what people are still dealing with
that's not a problem that went away I
know people with plenty of metal
fillings in their mouth I mean it's not
like it's gone everybody's dealing with
it a lot of them have these little these
little metal fillings and big metal
fillings in today just plenty of them
copper pipes yeah copper pipes oh maybe
your house doesn't have copper pipes old
copper pipes pipes but maybe a friend's
house did and you stayed over and had a
couple tea 5 years ago yeah cup of tea
you know it's unbelievable how easy it
is to get all these Metals in us and
that's just one
thing pesticides herbicides fungicides
have you eaten organic since you were
born because pesticides herbicides
fungicides are ladened in Copper ladened
in Copper toxic
copper it it look I can fill the whole
show with all this fun stuff this part
right here
I really can't but let me go a little
further back let me go a little further
back than this let's go into Quicks
silver Quicksilver is a tonic from the
17 and 1800s that everybody drank when
they went to the doctor that's it you
wouldn't go to the doctor and leave
without Quicksilver Quicksilver was
Mercury heated up in a tube with a with
a a flame a candle underneath it in
water till the Mercury would kind of
separate itself just enough and out gas
into that into that fluid into that
liquid and then they pour it into a
little cup and you drink it that's what
that's what everybody did didn't matter
what was wrong with you you come in
there the element the the conventional
standard the conventional standard was
Quicksilver bottom line a Mercury drink
and all your forefathers drank it I
don't care what anybody says I'm going
to tell you right now I I don't care
what anybody says cuz somebody said to
me there's no way my my grandparents
drank that or my great-grandparents or
their grand great grandparents drank
that not in my life there's no way not
in my family line you're wrong I if they
went then they never went to a doctor
once in their life during the 1800s
that's what it means and I would say
that okay so that means that their whole
lifetime they never went to the doctor
once not even in their childhood not
even once for a fever back in the 1800s
because that's the only way they can
avoid Quicks over so if you can
guarantee that for me then I will
believe you if you can't guarantee that
I'll never believe you never because
everybody went to the doctor at least
once and drank that tonic children
included that's what was done that was
the that was the standard of science and
research you know what
happened no one would see the doctors
that the medical establishment was
running out of money and
collapsing collapsing down F the House
of Cards was falling by the late by the
mid
1800s no one went to the doctor anymore
and I'll tell you why because the word
quack was for the conventional doctor
not for the herbalist down the road not
for the chiropractor down the road that
believes in some kind of energy medicine
not for the naturopathic doctor that
have they have more respect now not for
anybody else not for any kind of person
not for any kind of healer quack wasn't
the word for any of them quack was the
word for the conventional doctor because
by the mid
1850s everybody thought that if you went
to them and drank that tonic you would
come home with Madness
Insanity so they called them the Quack
Like quack like a duck you'd come home
in Hyster like an hysterical manner from
the Mercury sometimes there logically
riddled in
Madness and that's how you would come
home and that's why they they deemed the
conventional doctor of the quack but
what happened
was it boomed a business that never was
thought of as anything it boomed the
Alternative Market for the first time
that's why holistic medicine started it
exploded Homeopathy
Chiropractic all of it it exploded
naturopathy
herbalism it
exploded it came to life because it was
where everybody went to by the turn of
the
century to stay away from the quacks
isn't it interesting right interesting
and then the quacks needed to take
control so they advertised they no
longer used Quicksilver there was a
massive funding and medical back and
funded campaign to save the conventional
model and it was a huge advertising
campaign by the late 1800s we no longer
use Quicksilver please come to us we no
longer use Quicksilver please come to
us that's what would happen the only
people the quacks would be servicing at
that point were the people at the
sanitariums people that were already
having problems with Madness even sane
people that were just stuck in the
sanitariums and that's the only people
that a conventional doctor ever worked
on anymore because no one would go to
the doctor they would go to herbalist
and every everybody
else so just a little history but here's
the problem we all have mercury in us
because of it we all have mercury passed
down to Generation generation through
utero all of it that's how we have it
and we still do and it's been building
up and we have mercury in other places
too so there's a little bit of History
just so you know it's important metals
are microscopic they can't be seen
they're they're smaller than
nanoscopic they can't be seen
and what you don't see won't hurt that's
what the industry always thinks we don't
see it you're fine Mr Mrs Jones you're
you guys are fine we don't see it so it
can't be a problem toxic heavy metals
are a particular type of toxin that
celery juices sodium cluster salts take
on so we're talking about celery juice
too celery juice helps with toxic heavy
metals we're going to go into that a
little
bit heavy metals have a destructive
active charge to them that causes the
metals to be Dam damaging to the liver
cells brain cells and other cells
throughout the body cluster salts sodium
cluster salts diffuse this charge
rendering them inactive and less
aggressive think about how powerful that
is when you're drinking your celery
juice all the sodium cluster salts are
in C juice that science of research
doesn't know about
yet that doesn't know about yet you
think science of research knows
everything you think they know
everything they don't it's so important
to know that and understand
that because you're going to need you're
going to need different information
because this world's not easy to go in
and people already are suffering to a
degree that's unbelievable from young to
old so you need Advanced
information and these sodium cluster
salts they diffuse the charge rendering
them inactive and less
aggressive they disarm toxic heavy
metals such as copper Mercury and
aluminum and there's other metals too
there's
nickel there's arsenic there's a lot of
different Metals there
cadmium and you know barium there's
different Metals celery juices
antioxidants is another thing that we
need really desperately one of the
functions of the celery juices
antioxidants not just not other
antioxidants is to remove fatty deposits
from the heavy metal CU this is what I
was talking about earlier we on these
high fat
diets we on high fat diets all the time
and high fat diets means we saturate our
bodies with with with fats that's how it
works metals that sit and oxidize inside
our body oxidize faster when our
bloodstream is filled with fat so we're
all told to be on these high fat diets
right now that's what we're told all the
vegans and plant-based people they're
just going all to high fat that's what
they do all of the you know the the high
protein people paleo people animal
protein people they all go to high fat
and this is what everybody's doing and
they're all mixing it all up they're all
mixing it all up the nut Butters and
everything else they all that nut
Butters are healthy but you know in just
in small quantities periodically because
we need more other things that are more
critical so we're all heading to the
keto land because it keeps you off of
processed foods it gets you exercising a
little bit gets a few pounds off the
belly for a lot of people not everybody
but for a lot of people when they first
go on it after getting off the standard
American
diet and so they're into the keto thing
and they think they found a Holy Grail
the the health professionals today think
the keto thing is a Holy Grail but what
it is it's just no
grains it's no sugar which is bad sugar
cuz no one ever ate fruit
anyway so it's just bad sugar staying
off of bad sugar staying off of
processed food staying off of Grease
staying off of um of high processed
greased fatty fast food and go for the
healthier fats
so that's what it means and everybody
does get a little bit better that's why
I don't even I don't even mind the keto
diet to some degree because if it'll
keep somebody off the standard American
diet and keep them from eating fried
fast food they're going to do better but
when we're chronically ill and we're
suffering and struggling we have
symptoms that won't go away that hasn't
fixed anybody that's not getting those
real real serious pathogen and toxic
heavy metal symptoms to go away in fact
it does the opposite when we have the
toxic heavy metals the more fat we put
into our body the more they oxidize the
fats cling to the metals and cause them
to rush and Decay and
oxidize and that's what they do and we
faster deteriorate later we age faster
in the brain we deteriorate later and
that's what
happens and those antioxidants and
celery juice help to separate the fat
deposits from the
metal they act like suction cups see
here's how it works fatty deposits cling
to toxic heavy metal deposits like SU
ction cups and when fatty deposits and
toxic heavy metals touch like this it
causes the metals to
oxidize byproduct of the metal develops
discharge that's what
happens a production
occurs toxic heavy metals possess a
destructive charge which is part of what
causes them to reative fatty deposits to
begin with and and other toxic heavy
metals aggressively so that means if you
have other tox heavy metals they mix
with other metals they
oxidize they they they discharge toxic
charges essentially we're talking about
heavy metals rusting in the body leading
to corrosive runoff that is damaging to
nearby
tissue think about that that's what
happens that that's what
happens so sure if we're on a really
really toxic high fat diet which is a
standard American diet we get we get the
Alzheimer's quicker we get um dementia
quicker we get memory problems quicker
we get all kinds of different issues
quicker in the brain we get
crystallizations in the brain we get
calcifications in the brain we get all
kinds of different spots in the brain we
age our brain
shrinks so taking people off the
standard American diet and putting them
on a healthy high-fat diet improves them
and slows all that down but by no means
means does it stop the process of the
metals causing dementia Alzheimer's
memory problems crystallizations
calcifications in the
brain it doesn't stop any of this or
liver issues or other toxic issues in
the body like feeding viruses and making
viruses get worse why do you think you
got people on all kinds of diets you got
people on clean paleo diets they're sick
they're sick with chronic fatigue I
thought that I thought the the Paleo
would fix them right wouldn't you think
so no people on plant-based diet sick
with chronic fatigue plant-based diet
didn't fix them people on all these
different diets chronically sick with
all kinds of problems different diets
everywhere whether they're on the you
know one side of it or the other side of
it animal non-animal whatever it
is and they still suffer everybody's
still dealing with their problems and
symptoms going to different doctors then
the doctors blame the diet like the
vegan diet or they'll blame this and
that and it's back and forth you go to
another doctor it's great when you're
young and you're not really sick and
you're exercising every day and you just
got like little problems like really
little ones but you take a mom who can't
get out of bed with all she's got just
to drive her kids to school because of
crippling anxiety or severe fatigue with
no answers abound and she's trying the
best keto diet possible and she's trying
the best plant-based diet possible she's
trying the best animal diet possible and
she's gone to 10 doctors already and two
functional medicine doctors and two
neurologists and two internists and
still can't get to where she needs to be
the keto diet's not going to fix it the
plantbase diet's not going to fix it you
need more than that you need information
because you can do plant-based high fat
and still keep yourself sick you can do
keto Paleo High fat animal protein high
fat and keep yourself sick even if
you're staying away from bad sugar and
processed
foods because the metals oxidize and
feed pathogens that's where we're going
next fatty deposits all throughout the
body
discharge because they're attached to
heavy metals that are oxidizing and
rusting so all of this just throws out a
throws out a problem it throws out a
problem as a result the fatty deposit
becomes highly
toxic and it can act as fuel for guess
what so those fatty deposits they're cor
that hold all that corrosive rust and
material and it's holding on to it
becomes this powerful food in a bad way
to viruses like gapin bar viruses like
the shingles human herpes viral 6 that's
hhv6 hhv7 undiscovered hhv 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 yeah that's how many viruses
are out there and their undiscovered
cousins and any other kind of pathogen
that may even reach the brain causing a
myriad of problems and conditions
undiagnosed and so
these
viruses they like to feed off of this
discharge that heavy metals create and
remember all this is happening while
everybody's asleep everybody's the food
Wars are going on everybody's throwing
their fake science back and forth
constantly this study here let's site
this but there's really no information
really in it in the end let's site this
let's site that let's keep on throwing
these theories around that are funded
and thumbed basically a thumb on the
scale all interest groups behind it
let's keep on let's keep keep the war
going you know let's the vegans keep on
fighting the paleos but no everybody's
sick though everybody's still
sick and so because there's more
information to be had there's more
information to be learned let's keep the
food Wars going let's keep the science
Wars going hardcore conventional science
in the in Harvard and and and yeah hard
you know hardcore science all all upset
at the alternative Sciences so
alternative science is all upet about
them they're all thrown or all kinds of
stuff around why everybody's sick
because everybody's too busy fting each
other and then your Metals they're
oxidizing no one cares no one gives a
heck and then our brains are still
shrinking our brains are still rotting
cells are being filled with Metals
pathogens are creating hashimotos
thyroiditis rheumatoid arthritis
fibromyalgia mecfs lime disease multiple
sclerosis that's just a name a few exmos
psoriasis that's just a name a few
that's nothing I mean I can go a 100
illnesses there's lupus there's all of
them them and that's I mean that's just
a few of
them if you if you know a name of one
then yeah it's that and in the book
celery juice book I cover almost 200
different symptoms and conditions and
there what what's happening what the
cause is and what celery juice is
doing severe mental and physical
deterioration such as Alzheimer's ALS
and Parkinson's metals can cause that
metals and
pathogens so this is all important
information it's critical to know how
does celery juice help celery juices
antioxidants help prevent toxic heavy
metals from decaying by removing the
fatty deposits from around the heavy
metal deposit and then coating the
metals to discourage oxidation that's
what these antioxidants do sodium
cluster salts attached to celery juices
antioxidant diffusing toxic toxic heavy
metals destructive charge toxic heavy
metals have a destructive charge in in
the body rendering these Metals much
less aggressive when you have the sodium
cluster salt involved so toxic heavy
metals have a destructive charge a
sodium cluster salt attaches itself to
the antioxidant and celery juice both of
these two chemical compounds diffuse the
top the Mercury and the aluminum and the
copper the destructive charge that
occurs from those rendering them less
aggressive this this isn't any any
information you can find out there this
is from the celeres book this is from my
source this is untampered with this
information it's pure it's clean there's
no agendas behind
it so this destructive charge is
neutralized celery juice is special
antioxidants can stop oxidation much
more
effectively and that's the difference
between those antioxidants and other
ones let's talk about Alzheimer's let's
talk about dementia let's talk about
memory issues a little bit these are
diseases we all fear of falling into as
we age and medical research and science
has no answers to them they don't have
any answers to them I know that in it's
really good-hearted people in the
alternative Sciences are actually trying
to get people to eat better with
Alzheimer's and try to reverse some of
the symptoms and then they they wave a
flag like oh my God we did it like by
golly we did it we did it we can do we
can do something now we can do uh series
or a documentary on this or maybe we can
write a new book or maybe whatever we're
getting people a little bit better by
getting them off of processed foods I
mean that's great that's great it still
has nothing to do with what's really
causing the problem how to get the
problem
remedied and not just being on the high
fat diet by just reducing processed
foods because it's not going to end the
problem it's not we are just victims to
these diseases that completely can they
strip us of the most precious
memories where we can't even recognize
our own family anymore sure and if we
could reverse that a little bit by E
eating cleaner it's it's a wonderful
thing but we got to do better than that
with all these different illnesses all
of
them because we can't just hang our hat
on that where we clean up some diets a
little bit we need this Advanced
information about how metals are rotting
and rusting in the brain and in the body
and in the tissue and in the liver and
other places of the body and how to get
those Metals out that's what we
need and people don't even know metals
are causing these problems out there the
industry doesn't even know they don't
even believe metals are really causing
these problems with the brain it's still
where no one really
knows and that's a devastating place to
be memory issues can occur in many
different ways whether in the form of
trouble receiving long-term memories
losing short-term memories or even
fluctuations or short-term and long-term
memory issues flip back and forth it's
important to know the bottom line is we
have to get the metals out so we're not
dealing with problems it's
critical you know we're talking about
more than those days when you're busy
and you're just misplacing your
belongings your car keys maybe even
forgetting where you parked at a busy
shopping center although celery juice
helps with that kind of problem
too you know it does weigh more than
that it does more than what we forget in
a day where we have so many different
tasks and so many things on our plate
when we talk about memory issues such as
alz Alzheimer's disease or dementia what
we're talking about without real
realizing it is toxic heavy metals are
inside the brain that's what we're
talking about without realizing it that
toxic heavy metals are sitting inside
the brain that's what's going on with
Alzheimer's disease and
dementia the most common being Mercury
the other one being aluminum close
Runners up copper nickel cadmium lead
and Arsenic and here's the thing you
guys like this is really important to
know right here if you want to know a
really good piece of information I
nobody knows everybody has a different
volume a different level of toxic heavy
metals in the brain in different
combinations with some metals directly
Crossing each other's paths which makes
them interact causing depression anxiety
anxiousness causing
bipolar causing
Mania causing schizophrenia causing just
regular mild depression that's
unexplainable causing unexplainable
sadness then we end up at a psychiatr
psychiatrist office went up at a psych
doctor's office and they're just trying
to like go through a childhood and stuff
when when are sadness and depression is
metals that are just basically fusing to
each
other and you know it's amazing how it
works we end up taking some you know
psych meds that we that we need to to
survive because some of these some of
the people some of these doctors they're
like I don't I don't know what else to
offer you and and the people they need
something to get them by so I don't
blame anybody for using anything they've
had to use but then the medications have
more Metals in them and then they end up
in in liver and the medications and the
metals end up in the liver it's just not
an easy path and I completely understand
I mean so many people struggle and
suffer it's
unbelievable memory issues occur when
those Metals oxidize when they Collide
when they cross when the paths are cross
oxidizing Metals lead to a discharge a
very potent one think about a patch of
metal rusting on an old car when cars
were metal I mean so many young people
listening to this podcast that you know
they just think cars aren't you know
they don't know what cars are cars are
plastic we drive around with plastic
cars now they're fiber fiberglass and
plastic so they're not metal anymore I
mean they're metal inside the frame and
the parts but the outside of the cars
are just basically plastic shells
fiberglass shells but think about the
metal rusting on a car becoming crusty
and bubbling
up if you're old enough to know that
this is essentially what happens in the
brain but on a microscopic or nanoscopic
scale and even smaller than that one
major cause of oxidative reaction is a
high level fat in the bloodstream so we
pound down the fats and we get ourselves
in
trouble sure though if you're on a
really bad diet and you're eating fried
greasy food with you know rolls with
butter on it and lots of you know wheat
gluten and you're eating lots of dairy
that's been you know melted cheese on
everything and fried in the oven and I
mean fried on the stove and baked in the
oven or whatever all these different
delicious dishes at all these different
fast food restaurants or whatever and
all this all this fair and you're eating
all that all this time and you switch
off of that and you're just eating
almond butters in your your in your
shakes almond butter and your shakes and
you're doing coconut oil and you're
doing Lots of avocado and you're doing
Freer range chicken and you're doing you
know some n different seeds and Seed
oils and you're doing all these things
and you're you know your your chia seeds
and you're doing the hemp seeds you're
doing all of this hemp milk almond milk
and you're just totally in the high-fat
diet you got rid of the processed foods
you got rid of the breads you got rid of
all of that it's a huge step and that's
where the world's going where it's going
all there all the diets are going to
lead everybody that there and we're
still going to be S we're still going to
be sick and
then basically the diet makers to these
diets are going to be like well you're
just you know that's just you something
something else you're doing you're just
doing something wrong if this diet
didn't cure you no it's not at all you
can only go so far when you remove the
processed foods because you're still
doing the high fats you're just doing
them in a healthier way and it may not
be enough for so many people who have
real real issues the Epstein bar and the
shingles tal neuralgia pler fasciitis
fibromyalgia you know all the problems
we get and the reproductive problems
women get PCOS and fibroids and all that
that doesn't go away with that we got to
lower the fats and then the metals don't
oxidize too I don't care I mean if your
diet's filled with high quality oils
nuts and seeds and avocados and and high
quality age cheese and and and organic
eggs and chicken and really good fish
and and and grass-fed beef it's all fat
all that was fat right there under the G
or the hidden hidden name of protein all
under the hidden name of protein all
somebody's going to think is there is
protein except for the word oils but
they're just going to think protein with
every word I just
said sure there's no hydrogenated oils
and cakes and cookies anymore in so of
these people's diets and donuts and
other fried foods of course there isn't
and both the vegan side and both the
animal pro protein side anymore the
resulting fat though in the bloodstream
leads to this oxidative reaction with
the heavy metals in the brain that means
all these other fats I'm talking about
the healthy Ones Still oxidize Metals
whether anybody likes it or not it's
just the way it
is and all these fats thicken up the
blood lower the oxygen levels in the
blood and get you in trouble with
pathogens like Epstein bar and some of
these some of these fats feed Epstein
bar like the cheese and the eggs
especially the cheese and the eggs they
just feed the Epstein bar
keep you sick it's why so many people
have been just Ring Around the Rosie in
musical
chairs I'm not trying to cause all the
fear around healthy fats a little is
okay too much can cause problems for
people that are really struggling look
I've always been the
person as the messenger as the person
The Fighter for the chronically ill that
have tried
everything and have been there for them
watching their back
or to make sure people don't get sick
and get
worse you know who've never been sick
before and end up getting sick and
getting worse because they don't know
this Advanced
information and they just fall they fall
prey to just a Ring Around The Rosy all
of all of the same old thing going on
and no one's telling them we got to get
the metals deep out of the tissue and
how to do it the right way none of that
I'm not trying to cause the fear around
it it's just basically your safety
you're protective protecting you making
sure I look out for you when these
Metals rust they change shape and form
they rupture they even grow they expand
they run together that's how it works
inside our brains celery juice has an
electrolyte Source the best one on the
planet nothing can surpass it it's
helpful it repairs damaged cells it
repairs damaged
neurons for one thing celery jues
complex blend of trace minerals for one
thing I'll tell you right now those
trace minerals are powerful they help
restore neurotransmitter chemicals this
is critical
information the blend offers complete
neurotransmitter chemicals that's the
blend in celery juice the blend of
electrolytes it's critical because it
helps to stop rusting metals from
oxidizing and running off that's how
incredible it
is
neurotransmitters it cleans them gets
them less dirty makes them more useful
rehydrates them because of electrolyte
power and celery juice for another
celery for another thing celery juice
does it stops the oxidative
runoff it protects the neurons from the
runoff the gleo cells in the brain all
this is critical I talk about this in
the celery juice book way more I cover
way more in the C juice book than I can
cover in a radio show like this
and the thing is you want to get these
Metals out that's why I've always
offered the heavy metal detox smoothie
which has always helped people I like
offering the celery juice as one of the
medical medium tools and then the heavy
metal detox smoothie the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie and that
Smoothie has the vimergy products in it
um I'm not sponsored by those guys
nothing of the sort this isn't an
infomercial I want you to know that
because that's what happens is every
single podcast I've ever just heard or
someone has talked to me about they said
there's like INF infomercials in
everybody's podcast now they're like
nothing but like radio shows of
infomercials left and right like
continuously all through the podcasts
it's unbelievable and this person said
to me you don't do that and I know I
know I've heard that out there I've
heard that myself I've listened to some
podcast I've heard
that now vimergy products are amazing
because I that's what I do to get my
medals out is I put their spin their
their their um I put their spirulina in
there their barley grass juice powder
their wild blueberry powder then I get
some fresh cilantro and throw it in
there and a little bit of
dols I put it in there with the Frozen
wild
blueberries and some other fruit that I
like I blend it up to get the metals out
I drink my celery juice before it you
know like a half an hour before then I
have my heavy metal detox smoothie and
that's what I do if you know don't know
the vimergy products it's vas inv
viictor i m e RG y best Spina there
there is to offer in the world today
that that stuff even helps to bring back
people's brain in so many ways and you
bring that into your
diet it helps and that's what happens
you I've had so many people come to me
over the years and they're like hey you
know aw it's like and I've had friends
come to me hey aw I just want to tell
you been on this really healthy diet no
processed foods No Junk Foods no fast
foods no anything whether you know it's
plant-based or vegan or someone comes to
me and whether it's you know a Paleo or
Hy protein animal and like I'm I'm off
all the processed foods but I can't
really get rid of everything alog
together I got these other symptoms I'm
still plagued with I got a little bit of
this left and a little bit of that it
helped me at first but I got a little
bit of that I'm like you got to get the
metals out where's your celery
juice where's your celery juice I I you
should be 16 ounces celery juice every
single day minimum they bring it in I go
and bring in that heavy metal detox
smoothie and get that spirulina the
right kind from VY get the barley grass
juice powder get the wild blueberry
powder
and put that in there and all of a
sudden they're doing the heavy metal
detox movie it's one powerful medical
medium tool that plugged into their
belief system whatever diet they tapped
into that's processed food free and they
brought in the celery juice and they
moved the needle those are two things
right there they also got rid of their
chicken eggs the chicken eggs meaning
they got rid of eating
eggs they don't have to get rid of your
chickens you just got rid of eating
their
eggs they you know I known people that
they they harvest their own eggs right
out of their
backyard and they have their own
chickens and I said just give the eggs
away they're like well what do we do
with all these eggs now I go those eggs
no matter how natural they are I know
how organic they are they're going to
feed Epstein bar they're going to feed
all your viruses you're going to stay
sick sick with chronic fatigue syndrome
they just they're going to keep the
metals in the brain they're going to
keep the metals in your body cuz they're
not going to let the metals out here's
the thing when you fill your bloodstream
with high fat constantly filling it with
high fat even if it's all healthy you
can't get the metals out anyway it's too
hard to get them out that's why you need
the heavy metal detox smoothie you need
some extra help it's why you need the
celery juice and if you really want to
go further go further with the Liver
Rescue 369 The Liver Rescue book learn
how to lower the fats it's worth it
you're worth it you are worth it you are
worth learning how to lower the fats and
what foods to eat and how to bring in a
little bit more fruit and leafy greens
and some sweet potatoes more of those
and bring in more of these and get used
to it a little bit so you can eat less
of the fat so you can thin out your
blood a little bit to not give your
heart so much of a struggle and to make
sure you get the metals out of tissue so
they can actually leave make sure you're
not oxidizing the toxic heavy metals
anymore make sure the celery juice can
go and reach the metals
easy really easy you can work on healing
that way and that's even more additional
medical medium information that's
powerful that can help you
heal I can only go so far
only go so far in the sense where I can
provide that information that's
untampered with that's pure I can
provide the information that's already
healed thousands and hundreds of
thousands of people and even more than
that over through the last three and a
half decades information that's Advanced
and ahead of science and research and
ahead of the best alternative science we
have now that can only go so far as to
give it to you hand it to you it get you
access of
it and uh and hope that you actually try
it because so many people have we got to
get the metals out the Mercury aluminum
the lead we got to get it out of our
brains got to get it out of our liver
got to get it out of our organs our
intestinal tract our colon got to get it
out of our reproductive system so we
don't have difficulties with
pregnancies we got to get it out of the
breast milk so you're not breastfeeding
your baby with all the toxic heavy
metals in
there that's why the heavy metal detox
movie is amazing for for women who are
breastfeeding they get the metals out
and the celery juice is incredible for
women it's for for breastfeeding because
you're cleaning the breast milk you're
cleaning it so the baby's getting clean
breast
milk I mean it that's doesn't get any
better than
that look I wrote the medical medium
celery juice book to help you understand
the root cause of almost 200 symptoms
and conditions and how celery juice can
help protect you and recover you I cover
brain fog and ALS and depression anxiety
OCD PTSD ptss addiction and so much more
in the
book so it's important to know if you
can't get a book go to the library if
you can't get a book at at Target or
Barnes & Noble Costco Costco has has you
know Costco is an easy place to get it
because you can pick up you can pick up
a few things you can pick up your celery
at Costco and that's what I like to do I
go to Costco I pick up my
celery that's what I do I pick up my
wild blue blueberries for my heavy metal
detox smoothie my frozen wild
blueberries that's what I do people
always say what do you do what do you do
well I go to Costco and I get my
celery and that's what I do I get my
frozen wild
blueberries yeah and so listen the
bottom line is I care about you guys I
want you guys getting better we can get
the metals out we can reverse anxiety
depression we can reverse these
conditions we can get different
neurological problems Twitches spasms
tingles numbness aches pains blurriness
dizziness balance issues vertigo we can
get rid of neurological symptoms we can
get Metals out lower pathogens like
Epstein bar we can clean up our diets a
little bit further we can do all kinds
of good stuff but most importantly just
start with some celery juice then if it
seems too
much just just do that let's do
that let's start with celery
juice and we can just go there I believe
in you guys I stand behind you 100%
always have always will and I'm always
proud of everybody for all that you're
doing everything from what you've gotten
through in your struggles we gone
through and how you've succeeding and
each day just persevering I love you
guys take one step at a time take care
I'll see you next radio show love you
much bless your heart bye