you'll hear out there the celery juice
is mostly water this humble herb is much
more than that people are missing the
most powerful points of celery juice and
what it knew he is celery juice is a
hydro bioactive liquid this is a
powerful healing herbal extraction
sodium cluster salts antioxidants plant
hormones vitamin C all of it suspends in
a living form it's not just water it is
a living mechanism that when you drink
it it becomes you and it starts to heal
the body I was once told that I had
fibromyalgia chronic allergies sinus
issues sleep issues hot flashes I
started going to a variety of different
doctors
no one knew it was wrong with me I had
other symptoms and nothing really helped
very much when you're drinking celery
juice you can taste the sodium cluster
salts you can taste the medicinal
qualities it has this is one aspect of
the power of the medicine celery juice
provides if somebody hasn't struggled or
suffered in the symptom or condition
that's chronic it's easy for them to say
celery juice is all water and it can't
be working it's knocking this remedy out
of the hands of those who really need it
and it's disrespectful to the growing
number of people that already recover
using celery juice it's telling them
that their hard work and healing
accomplishments never happened about a
month after that I came across medical
mediums book and decided to try the diet
immediately I started feeling better a
lot of my students have dissipated and I
am feeling great as time has gone on I
just keep getting better and better when
we get sick the first thing we're told
is to drink more water but water hasn't
healed
anyone who's been suffering with any
kind of chronic illness but celery juice
has I'm off all my medicine
no symptoms and it's just a miracle this
is healing you can all heal
[Music]