ranae's with the man who's helping
millions feel better daily with the
power of one vegetable he's taken the
world by storm with his books on helping
people overcome illness and disease with
me now Anthony William hi hey good to be
here good to see you again I mean every
time I see you I feel like a gazillion
more people are talking about celery
juice yeah yes this New York Times
bestselling author definitely has
Hollywood juiced up I am on the celery
juice train I really notice a huge
difference like your skin and your at
the inflammation in your body you have
more sustained energy Jenna Dewan
Gweneth Paltrow rub it to Nero and
Sylvester Stallone all fans it's getting
people better the man known as the
medical medium making a big impact round
the world with his powerful remedy it's
built up built up because of a storm of
people healing this is literally organic
the first organic movement of our time
what's been maybe the craziest story
that you've come across see people
transform their skin is so difficult to
deal with like the eczema or the
psoriasis being so out of control are
the acne they've tried everything and
then they're doing the summer juice and
it's reversing Kim K revealing she's
tried it to treat her psoriasis Anthony
revealing this about the drink it has to
be celery juice by itself that's a
mistake made all the time okay I wanted
to ask you cuz a lot of people are
putting lemon in it does that change
it's a message it stops it from working
you can't put water you can't put ice
cubes in it can't put lemon can't put
lime you can't mix it with things you
lose that pathogen killing ability
that's getting people better celery
juice one of the healing tools revealed
in his series of medical medium books
including his latest liver rescue so
many illnesses stem from the liver so I
needed a book that covered that in its
entirety so people can heal we age
because of our liver our liver ages that
we age faster okay thank you so much for
coming by you're welcome
be sure to pick up a copy of Anthony's
book live a rescue in stores now