right now
yeah
celery juice exposes
the frauds
that's what it does
celery juice not only knocks out
pathogens and viruses and bugs and
bacteria
unproductive
mold yeast
right not only does it do that
but it angers the frauds
it exposes
the frauds that's what it does in the
alternative and conventional movement
you know what's funny
you think that everybody in the
alternative conventional movement wants
everybody to heal
right
wouldn't you think that
doesn't everybody want everybody to heal
doesn't everybody in the profession of
health in any way shape or form want
someone who's struggling and suffering
who's on mattress island who's been
through hell and back don't you think
that they want you to heal
right
but then they hear a healing story
miraculous someone's healing because of
celery juice they get their life back
miraculous someone's having a baby now
that couldn't because they were drinking
32 ounces of celery juice miraculous
someone's skin condition went away
eczema psoriasis gone because of celery
juice miraculous but no no no
couldn't have been the celery juice
doesn't matter if nothing else moved the
needle but the celery juice
no can't be
i'm a naysayer
i'm a downer
you know no no no
practitioners doctors nutritionists
rd's whatever
anybody out there you think that they're
in it to win it for the patient for the
client get them better get them better
but you know what happens
there's a huge part of the alternative
conventional movement that doesn't want
people drinking celery juice doesn't
matter about the healing stories doesn't
matter about the incredible miraculous
things that happen doesn't matter when
somebody gets their life back
they
don't want the person healing and they
say no no no no no
don't you drink that celery juice
and celery juice
exposes
those frauds
because what that celery juice did
is it exposed that that person's not in
it to win it for the patient that
person's not in it to win it so that
person can heal that person that person
in the health movement that guru that
nutritionist that functional doctor that
md that nd is not really in it for the
patient because the because that
professional chooses to ignore
something that's changing the lives of
millions of people they choose to ignore
it completely
and say no you better just instead of
juicing it you better just eat celery
sticks it's a good vegetable just hot
eat it that's a good vegetable
yeah elizabeth says no money and healthy
patience elizabeth edwards good to see
you
right so what celery juice does you guys
it exposes all the frost fraud fraud
boom another one there fraud boom
another one boom another one
nutritionist boom some nutritionists
they believe in celery juice because
they believe in the patient healing and
want the patient to heal but some don't
frauds boom frauds boom functional
medicine doctors that don't believe in
it frauds boom
media people frauds you don't care about
people who are sick
you name it frogs everywhere
and that's what it does it exposes them
left and right front and center i can't
tell you how many times the media has
come to me and says we want to do an
article we want to do an article on
medical medium
and
we want to do something on the celery
juice because we don't believe it works
for patients and clients and all the
different people out there we don't
believe that seller juice works let's do
an article and i'll be like well in the
article i'll explain how good it is for
people and how many people are healing
and they write up the article and they
do a crappy shitty job and then they put
some dietitian in there and they put
some functional doctor in there and that
doctor says nope celery juice is not
proven by science and research to help
anybody so all the claims from all the
people healing yet the healing stories
aren't real
fraud
that's what you are a dietitian that's
what you are functional medicine doctor
that's what you are md that's what you
are whoever you are that doesn't matter
what angle
because the minute
you all of a sudden put a blind eye to
someone getting miraculous healing
getting their lives back getting rid of
their eczema there's getting rid of
their adhd getting rid of autism getting
rid of conditions left and right you're
gerd in your intestinal tract problems
and your colitis and your crohn's
getting rid of your ibs if you don't
want to hear that if you're a
practitioner if you're a doctor if
you're if you're some kind of health
guru and health professional and you
don't want to hear that and you just you
tell people don't drink celery juice
because it's going to give you a problem
you're a fraud man bottom line and guess
who exposed it celery exposed it
lorraine l hey loren l good to see you
today amazing the cashier that sold me
my celery today told me i was better off
just eating it
you can imagine my response laugh out
loud i was polite but i set her straight
he he lorraine because she heard it from
somewhere else she heard it from a
professional she heard it from an
article she heard it from a functional
doctor she heard it from a chinese
medicine doctor she heard it from a
registered dietitian she heard it from a
naturopathic doctor
she heard it from a western naturopathic
doctor whatever and what she heard
was a health professional being exposed
as a fraud because celery juice
exposes and angers the frauds
that's all it is
so whoever told that cashier
not to drink the celery juice and was a
professional in any kind of arena of
health doesn't care about the person
healing doesn't care which means they're
not in it for the patient to win it
angela gibbons my psoriasis is so much
better and healing a lot nothing else
moved the needle no matter how much
money i spent with a variety of
practitioners over the last six years
exactly
and if there's a practitioner that
denies it or denies someone's story last
five years unbelievable denies that
story denies what it can do and then
turns around after hearing that story
and says to another patient don't you
drink celery juice then they are a fraud
because what it is is they're not in it
for the patient to win it and get their
lives back and crawl out of that place
they're not in it to help people get out
of that get out of that hell from being
sick they're not they're not in it for
that
and that's what celery juice does it
exposes
all the frauds
green says i say if someone truly has a
scientific perspective they'd look at
all the evidence of people healing in an
open and curious way and they're not
paid for
are you guys paid
are you guys all paid to tell your story
you guys getting paid off
i'm just curious are all you guys
getting paid off we're live on tick tock
we're live on facebook we're live on
youtube we're live on clubhouse you guys
go getting paid who's paying you guys
right no you're not being paid
right
you're not
nope nope nope but guess what all the
other trends out there they are being
paid there's admin by the hundreds being
paid to push the new mlm product that
you guys are being that's being shoved
in your face 24 7.
there's there's there's
it's literally paid
paid that's all it is out there
incredible right
people are paid to tell their story and
then they hop on the mlm bandwagon with
the product they pretend they're not and
then six months later oh my god they're
selling it oh how did that happen oh you
told your story
it's it's crazy
but here's what's really annoying right
here
here's what's really annoying okay
celery juice
exposes
all those fraudulent products and trends
with all the investors and chairman of
the boards and and you know board
members and shareholders and everything
else behind all the other industries
pushing all those other products
right your apple cider vinegar products
and everything else and they're angry
over celery juice because celery juice
exposes their game
celery juice is like this light
light
it's like a light
in a ocean of darkness
and
that's what it is
and the farmers aren't making money off
of it
the media won't cover this but it's the
largest crop in the world
in the fruit vegetable herb and spice
world
the largest crop in the world they won't
cover it
no one will talk about it
because it means people healing more and
more they start talking about it more
people heal they start talking about
more people heal they've shut it down
they can't make enough farms and create
enough farms right now to grow enough
for how many people are drinking it and
it's not even spoken about
but what you will find
you will find
is a youtube doctor i am dr vinsberg and
now what i have to tell you is the next
study on green tea and buy my green tea
product while you're at it
there's a new study on green tea has
green tea pulled you out of bed i just
want to know if you got eczema psoriasis
aches and pains trigeminal neuralgia
vertigo dizziness you got the worst
brain fog you're suffering you've got
fatigue neurological fatigue green tea
and green tea extracts gonna fix you
it isn't but you'll still see it over
and over again hi i'm doctor
i have a new product a leptin product i
have a new antioxidant green tea product
i have a new apple cider vinegar product
go check out my store
[Music]
it's one of the most powerful healing
foods of all time that has moved the
needle and changed the lives of millions
and no one's talking about it besides
talking about it and talking it
down
no one's talking about it except to talk
it down
and to tear it down and the only thing
keeping it going
is that people knowing i healed from it
i'm gonna keep on drinking it because it
has saved my life
and then here's the really weird part
what i'm seeing out there is people are
closet drinking it
their closet drinking celery juice
because they don't want someone saying
medical medium
wait a minute you like the medical
medium oh no no i don't like that no no
i don't like the medical medium no no i
don't like the medical medium no no no i
don't like it i'm no no
no i'm drinking my celery juice in the
closet here i don't like the medical
medium
or they're just closet drinking it
because
you can't make money off of it uh you
can't say
you can't say oh uh
yeah um
i'm a youtube influencer and i'm doing
celery juice now uh
i don't know what to say besides um
check out medical medium who actually is
the originator celery juice uh
socket so what they do is they hide it
and they drink it in the closet
it's how it's done
anyway
celery juice not only kills the bugs not
only does it help people heal jason
mespas says it's cured my heartburn and
fix my digestion dot dot dot i preach
you all the time bro thanks bro i'm
honored man seriously
know that it does count
and it does matter and and truly it
matters
and i'm i'm grateful i truly am you guys
need to know that
um
yeah
seller juice is the guilty pleasure i
just saw that
people are at different levels of
sickness always remember this some
people they just need a glass of celery
juice and boom they change in one night
some people they need to have it
increased and they need to be doing
other tools but the celery juice is a
critical part of moving the needle and
getting people to where they need to go
so it's it's a major major tool
it's one of those most powerful healing
foods of our time
and it's an herb
it's an herb i gotta say that over and
over again because everybody still
thinks it's a vegetable a veggie
sue is celery force the same as drinking
celery no it's not there's no celery in
southern forest
celery force is amazing i just took some
so i'm going to try to slow the speed of
of i might a little talk so fast
i just throw a bunch of celery force and
send it down and
something just happens
but yeah it's not the same thing
you need your celery juice you do
so
anyway you guys
we're i'm gonna do some celery
that's what we're gonna do okay tell me
how much
and when to drink it well let's go into
it a little bit i'm gonna do some
juicing now
so
celery juice is not carrot juice
it's not carrot juice
marissa celery juice has helped me to
heal my severe digestive issues
celery juice is so amazing
this is the mm-900 hds
gene says does anyone know if i can zinc
sulfate being allergic like wine
sulfates it's not that's not a soul
that's a soul fight
in wine that's a soul fight
that's a whole entire different thing
that's not even that's not even you know
how there's apples someone's talking
apples and someone's talking oranges two
different things no someone talked an
apple and someone's talking like
cow manure
or
someone's talking apple and someone's
talking like juniper berry i don't know
like it's so hot it's not the same thing
hope that helps
[Music]
can't get sound
well somebody's saying can't get sound
so obviously not hearing me you on
youtube
go to youtube
facebook and instagram knock the sound
out
and kick people off so
just go to youtube i honestly i might
stop
doing lives on facebook
and instagram completely and never do it
live on there again and i might just do
it on youtube only
and if you're not on youtube then you're
not there whatever but i might only be
doing youtube lives and only that
unless me we unless miui has a um an
option for me to go live so when they
have that option i'll probably probably
be on there only for something on
youtube
tick tock too i might not be on there
live in the future either because they
don't notify anybody
[Music]
this is the mm 900 hps
it's 20 percent off at megajuicers.com
just so you guys know
it's a medical device
why would i
back
and support
a juicer
[Applause]
because it's a medical device that can
save you money
mj taurus doctors say that it's not
healthy to drink it daily oh really
where would they get such a uh piece of
information that would
science and research come up with that
no they don't do anything on celery so
doctors say that it's not healthy to
drink it daily because celery contains
oxalates
and these interfere with calcium
absorption okay
but it but doctors are okay with green
tea daily caffeine right
age you give you sun spots burn out your
adrenals
just burn you out coffee's okay daily
yeah chocolate's okay daily
those are okay daily by doctors that's
right because the caffeine industry
guess what is part of pharma
there's caffeine almost in every single
pharmaceutical even the ones they say
there isn't
so caffeine's in every single
pharmaceutical
it's a psychoactive drug but that's okay
to do daily
sure let's get our kids addicted to
caffeine too so they're drinking coffee
nice and early
then they're just addicted to caffeine
and espressos and everything else
burning out their adrenals
and oxalates that's a funny one because
oxalates are in every single fruit and
vegetable urban spice so don't eat a
fruit and vegetable again
uh
don't oxalates are in grass grass-fed
beef
cattle that's eating grass are ingesting
and consuming oxalates from the grass
their meat is filled with oxalates but
don't eat meat so you know what i guess
you just don't eat
don't eat meat
don't eat uh
we're going to eat turkey
just be on turkey
turkey has a little less oxalates in it
than anything else why don't you just be
on turkey
don't eat anything no fruit no vegetable
don't do celery don't do anything just
eat turkey
and then you can't poo
and then you'll get a hernia and then
you'll be getting a surgery and then you
know what they'll have you on insurer or
something in the hospital how about that
it's a bad theory the oxalate theory
isn't even real it's a bad theory
because nobody knows why anybody's sick
i remember
the oxalate theory came out of the the
the whole
like bloom of chronic illness where
nobody knew was that why anybody is sick
in the 1970s and 1980s nobody knew why
anybody was sick 1990s people suffering
and laying in bed nobody knew why
anybody has anything nobody knows why
people have ms nobody knows anything
oxalates was a theory along with other
things like that
you know i mean really that's what it is
meanwhile heavy metals and pathogens are
why people get sick viruses bacteria
toxic heavy metals
you know that's why we get sick and then
we get intoxicated from perfumes and
colognes and air fresheners and scented
candles and then we get intoxicated by
caffeine so doctors will support
caffeine i know because they are all the
chiropractors are supporting it you're
right all the chiropractors that's a
funny one right there it's like well i
heard it from dr so-and-so and i'm like
you mean the chiropractor
or the md because that's not an md
so every chiropractor and i'm not
against chiropractors they got
chiropractor friends and there's
chiropractors that support medical
medium information they're amazing and
but i say stuff about functional
medicine doctors chiropractors dentists
uh everybody you know anybody because
i'm about i'm about supporting the
chronically ill not making friends with
the next chiropractor making friends
with the next naturopathic doctor making
friends with the next functional
medicine doctor i could care less
[Music]
[Applause]
hope you're okay not burning yourself
out
with all the hard work you do god bless
you
i mean i burn the candle at four ends
[Music]
my candle's got four ends
okay that's what my candle has
yeah it's a suicide mission sometimes
and if i die
it's not because i didn't take it's not
because i didn't it's not because of the
celery juice i drink
if i die
it's not because of
you know all the fruits and vegetables
and wild foods i've eaten
if i die it's because yeah i did it to
myself i burned myself to the ground to
the ground
right
because i want to look out for people
you know i see the spirit of compassion
fruit of compassion tells me many times
like look
you're gonna have to you're gonna have
to slow down
you can't do 21-hour days all the time
i'm writing a new book right now it's
the best book ever
they're all best books ever but
this book
is so big
i'm worried about people being able to
hold it
it's gonna blow people's doors off
[Music]
but i gotta say i'm paying the price
cheese says i'm so excited i am finally
salt free yo
i never thought i could do it and i owe
it to you mmm
what's your heart
celery juice let's talk about celery
just for a little bit i'm i think i'm
just going off in different directions
on you guys and i want to keep it spot
on succinct whatever we want to call it
pertinent information
okay 16 ounces on an empty stomach right
you guys know the rules
so you can do less if you're sensitive
no problem do 8 ounces 4 ounces 6 ounces
try to work up to 32 ounces ideal if you
have to do 64 ounces or 50 ounces so
somebody left a
somebody left to come and i think on
youtube saying they did 50 ounces and
i'm like wow they did 50 ounces for a
long time if you're sensitive start out
slow though start out low whatever works
strain it don't add anything in it
but i love that right
lorraine it's unbelievable so you're in
the grocery store and checkout person
and sure it's the kindest checkout
person ever an amazing person and
they're like well yeah i heard it's you
know not good
should you should you know eat it
instead it's so sad when you hear that
carolyn says my husband had kidney
stones and he was he told me to watch
how many oxalates i eat and i put in his
food
you know what causes kidney stones
leaching calcium right calcium that's
leeched
how does calcium get leech let's go into
it right now
okay
so got a little friend here all right
and
let me give you guys a little run down
real quick
here's how
your skull shrinks
it shrinks from the inside out
letting you know
your skull shrinks and weakens from the
inside out
because of vinegar
caffeine
and too much fat
when you're 60 years old then you fall
on a sidewalk you crack your head open
when you're 20 years old your skull is
thick enough to not crack it open so
easily you will sustain some pretty good
confusions and blows but not have this
fracture across half your skull
unless it's a hit that just can't be
avoided it's a hit that's just so hard
then it'll crack anybody's call
the point is is our skulls
get diminished they get eaten away from
the inside out from caffeine
and vinegar and guess where the calcium
goes
in your kidneys and builds a stone
not from some phantom oxalate made-up
story that there's no science and
research behind
the high fat diets
are so acidic
fatty acid how should i say that
fatty acids
fat is acid
all the fat is acid your butter straight
acid
your dairy products your straight acid
your butter straight acid your eggs are
straight acid they're not alkalizing on
any level they're all acid fat fat fat
is acid and then you lose your bones and
then you add more acid to it you guys
pump the kombucha tea because it's being
pumped by money 24 7. kombucha tea
people hate the celery juice thing
because it people say well you know what
i'm going to spend my money on celery
juice i'm not going to spend it on
buying more expensive kombucha tea
celery juice exposes those frauds like i
said before
kombucha tea
literally dissolves your bones
vinegar dissolves your bones
okay
fat dissolves your bones and then that
calcium ends up in your kidneys and in
your gallbladder that's
a fact jack entirely different than what
people think they think they're wrong
misinformation out there and it's really
sad
if i had a kidney problem on any level
or kidney stones if i had anything like
that you know what i'd be doing if i was
an animal protein eater gone gone no
animal protein for me
and i'm not even against animal protein
eating for people
i'm pro-animal protein if that's what
your heart desires and i'm
pro-plant-based if you guys want to be
eating lettuce all day i completely i'm
on your side
but i want you guys to do it right
so that you can heal
but if i had a kidney problem man that
that animal protein would be gone boom
you think i mean i would i would get rid
of that stuff so fast it wouldn't even
be funny
be gone
so if i had a kidney problem or kidney
stones those meat patties
those meat patties toss them out
chicken chicken cutlets those chicken
breasts grilled gone if i had a kidney
problem that's what you that's what
you're going to have tell your husband
any kind of kidney issues tell your
husband it ain't the oxalates you got to
worry about you keep on eating that
chicken he's going to wind up with
another another kidney problem
even salmon
i'm not against animal proteins
i'm just telling you how it works
okay so let's talk about uh celery juice
i want to strain it you guys got to
strain it
you have to
now i just juiced this right the mm-900
hds
this is dry this pulp
this pulp is dry
it's dry
saving money
every celery stick that goes in
saves you money
you buy half the celery of what you used
to buy at least for me
that's what it is i used to have to go
and buy two cases of celery now i only
need one case of celery i used to have
to go buy a case of celery now i only
need a half a case of celery
this juicer has paid for itself dozens
of times at this point i can't count it
anymore it has paid for itself over and
over again
doing the heavy metal detox cleanse next
week giving you guys a 4-1-1 on it heavy
metal detox cleanses next week make sure
you're ready you got your juicer right
it doesn't have to be this juicer what
juicer do you have use any juicer
because the heavy metal detox cleanse
entails celery juice
and that's the mm-900 hds just so you
know okay so that's the megajuicers.com
the celery model mm-900 hds
that's the one just so you know do you
have the book we're going to do the
heavy metal detox cleanse next week
okay it's 20 off right now and it's only
running like that for a couple of days
i'm pumped it's a sale that's going on
for a couple of days
gives people a chance to get it way
inexpensive and then boom they're saving
money
that's the whole thing
and i'd rather have this medical device
than be hooked up to tubes
i'd rather have this medical device be
all hooked up to to oxygen because of
oxygen going up my nostrils
that omega juicer
is incredible
one of the best investments ever you
know why you know also it is incredible
and you know why it's one of the best
investments and you know why because
you're you're literally gonna save money
it's gonna pay for itself over and over
again i've never seen a juicer out of
all the juicers out there i've never
seen a juicer you guys pay for itself
and pay for itself and pay for itself
it's ridiculous it's almost stupid at
this point it's stupid
literally it's stupid it you know what i
counted like it paid for itself by its
10th time one time because i was keeping
track of all the numbers in the in the
usage and how much celery juice and all
that and how much i buy and it paid for
itself like for its 10th time and i said
at this point it's just stupid
that's how ridiculous that's how
incredible it is it just it got it got
dumb got stupid
what i love about the mm-900 hds
[Music]
you don't see metal gears rubbing
against each other
you don't see metal gears running
rubbing against each other
like someone tried to throw that at me
oh yeah this juicer company over here is
the best they even talk about how
they're better than the omega oh really
because i see metal gears in there so
unless i want a juice filled with tiny
bits of metal nobody sees
unless i want that
i think i took too much celery force
natalie question is it okay to juice the
celery leaves yeah it's okay
it's okay they don't come with a lot
normally but if you get some wild celery
like the wild crazy stuff like you know
a friend of mine grew a bunch of celery
and and i went to check it out and and
it was just only leaves right it was
only leaves i was like dude
you need to be careful on how much you
juice of that right off the running
that's bitter it's it's astringent
it's going to knock your socks off just
just do
some of that
you know at a time because that's
nothing but leaves it was only leaves
there wasn't even any stalks it was just
a whole bush of leaves
and he's like cutting the leaves and i'm
like oh dude you gotta like you gotta
chill on that
but yeah of course you do leaves when
you're doing stalks and you do some
leaves with it yeah of course you can
is there a special juice
it's look it's it's
the thing is with celery juice is
keep in mind that
it works it work its ability to work is
in it's in the fact that it's in single
herbal extraction
you know what you guys hear me out on
this
just check this out okay
check this out
nature
proof you can tell me i'm wrong tell me
i'm wrong it's all right you guys can
tell me i'm wrong just throw it at me
you can give me the comments to say
you're wrong aw you're wrong and it's
okay if you tell me that
human nature
doesn't like it simple
we think we like things simple right
but we really don't like we need to
think that a pharmaceutical is a
scientific
you know
invention of all these things in there
we need to think that this herbal
formula has 20 herbs in it that was
synergistically proprietary put together
for some we we think that
it's always got to be complicated
to heal
complicated
right that's human nature no it's got to
become it can't be just celery juice
that's too ridiculous it's too simple it
can't be celery juice
it's got to be complicated right right
because everybody everybody it's got to
be complicated always has to be no it's
got to be
scientifically tested and proven and 20
million things in there and and then
maybe oh that must be some mysterious
that must be the way the synergistic way
that was systematically all these things
put in there that works not just one
thing
and that's a grave mistake we make
simplicity is in
the power is in the simplicity the power
is in the simplicity
yep
jefferson says with plastic gears then
you get plastic in your juice
okay let's talk about that a little bit
right
plastic
is in every single thing you touch it
every day you touch your credit card you
just rub plastic and that's a bad
plastic on that
any kind of saran wrap any kind of
whatever whatever you know plastic wraps
any kind of plastics plastic this
plastic cups plastic everything right
plastic
okay there's plastic in petrofuel
there's plastic and gasoline you breathe
in plastic every day when you take a
walk on the street and a car goes by
there's plastic in everything and
anything
and plastic isn't the scary toxin
you know what is you know what the scary
attack toxin is it's metal
run from it for your life with your life
you don't want metal
metal does a whole bunch of bad stuff
okay and this isn't cheap plastic this
is bpa free plastic in here
but the point is is that even if a bpa
free plastic
right
even if some residue of plastic somehow
got into your body it comes out easy
because this not only takes out plastic
outside of your body but it takes out
plastic from every other thing inside
your body all plastic that's been in
your body this removes it this removes
celery just removes plastic you can't
get enough plastic in fast enough while
celery juice is pulling it out that's a
whole other thing too about why it's so
powerful and with detoxifying people
but metal
metals a
you want to play with metal gears
rubbing against each other uh-huh
you want more adhd you want more brain
fog you want more anxiety
keep on playing with metal
that's half of why everybody's sick is
because of metal copper aluminum mercury
cadmium lead nickel steel
steel
anyway guys just just a reminder like i
said this is 20 off
omegajuicers.com is the sale it's only
on this juicer it's only running for a
couple of days
just letting you know
saves you a lot of money and it saves
you a lot of money when you're juicing
because it's literally doing the dry
pulp the dry pulp okay there's no juice
down in here the pulp all the pulp
little drops come right off there's
nothing moist in here
it's not moist it's dry
i've never seen that with any other
juicer
so that's really cool
so
i just want to say one thing back to one
little topic right i support the animal
protein crowd is support the plant-based
crowd
both crowds right both crowds know they
get sick
both crowds do things wrong
both crowds are misled non-stop out
there
and
i'm not here to judge someone
because they're eating a piece of meat
and i'm not here to judge someone
because they think they're the smartest
plant-based person there is because they
watched all the plant-based
documentaries they talk to some
plant-based doctors
they think they got it all down and
they're indestructible
and i'm not judging them either
and then they think they're smart as
anything
and i'm not judging the keto person who
thinks they got it all down and they all
know what's going on and they think
they're smart and all the keto doctors
talking that
you know which brings me to and i'm not
judging anybody
but everybody gets sick
i've seen it over and over again you can
act like you got it down i think you got
it down and then you get sick and you go
down
and then you find out
that that keto or that paleo diet or
that plant-based diet something was
wrong you don't know what it is
hell you don't even know why you're sick
you don't even know you got pathogens
and
viruses and bacteria and you don't know
you've got metals you don't go no you
don't know nothing
because the plant-based crowd doesn't
know why anybody's sick and the animal
protein crowd doesn't know why anybody's
sick everybody's in the dentist chairs
all the same getting their teeth drilled
they're all doing apple cider vinegar
the plant-based crowds do an apple cider
vinegar the animal protein crowds do an
apple cider vinegar get this the
plant-based crowd they're doing caffeine
the animal-based crowds doing caffeine
the plant-based crowd are doing fat
fat robot
right that robot give me fat give me fat
fat fat fat fat that's good for you
healthy fat central fatty acids where's
my fat that's good for the brain brain
is made of fat give me fat give me fat
fat fat that myself to death that robot
that robot got myself to death that
myself to death that robot
fat robot
there's a protein robot
is the protein robot
there's a fat robot
and there's the chocolate robot too
anyway
which is fat
look
it's viruses bacteria toxic heavy metals
toxins the high fat diet
these are the things
that are taking out
the animal protein people in the
plant-based people but they're both
doing the bad stuff guess what
guess what
the animal protein people are doing
nutritional yeast every day and the
plant-based people are doing nutritional
yeast every day the animal protein
people are taking the nuts in the seeds
and the oils and the avocado and the ana
and the plant prostate protein people
are taking the nut seeds avocado in the
oils
they're both fattening themselves to
death
vinegaring themselves to death
they're both kombucha teeing themselves
to death
that's right fermented foods they're
both they're both they're just they're
just pickling themselves and they're
both over salting themselves to death
our body needs a certain amount of salt
when it's in the right form
the animal protein and plant-based
people just throw salt in everything
salt salt salt here salt here let me
drink salt salt they salt themselves to
death
kimwood says i have a food sensitivity
to celery juice what do i do
uh first of all you have to be your own
detective so let me help you be your own
detective
celery juice
swells up your throat you can't
swallow and breathe
does celery juice make you break out
with a big ration hives right away once
you just take a sip of it
the celery juice make you get oh son you
got a tight chest and you can't and you
got all since something happens and you
all these things break out on your head
and you're just all all just tears
running down your eyes because you're
having some kind of reaction
because if that's happening don't drink
it
or
is it a bs test
fabricated by the food sensitivity
people
when they tell you you're allergic to
this so this to this i got a phone call
you know what i got a phone call coming
through
because i actually did a blood test
and
my doctor the doctor that did it is
gonna read all the test results back to
me so i got a phone call scheduled
coming in right now let me just see what
time it is
just in time
dr chewie
yeah dr chewie
oh thank god you're here okay i want to
know what i'm allergic to i've been
waiting
so you did the food sensitivity test you
do the all cat too you did that one and
you did all the food sensitivities i ig
and all the other ones okay
what am i allergic to
peppercorns
okay what else
cilantro
i never remember having a problem with
what else
a nice
i'm allergic to a nice
okay okay what else
i'm allergic to what gluten oh you put
gluten on there oh okay i already knew
okay what else
i'm allergic to carrots okay
uh hemp seeds
all right what else am i allergic to
broccoli
really
okay broccoli broccoli rob i'm gonna let
you guys i'm allergic to broccoli rob
that's on my food sensitivity test
broccoli rob
zucchinis zucchinis i'm allergic to
celery
really i have a sensitivity to celery oh
crap then i better get nervous and
worried
yeah
i better start like thinking that um
yeah i better better be scared to death
the celery just this stuff is evil i
gotta feel my food sensitivity test came
out where
dr chu if you say that's what it is then
what else
um
oh i'm allergic to
parsnips
okay i'm allergic to potato all right
and i'm allergic to
sassafras with sassafras
wait that's not i'm coriander okay i'm
allergic to coriander and i'm allergic
to
cayenne
and what else i'm allergic to
i'm not allergic to turmeric because you
have a tumeric supplement you want me on
okay so that's okay though you want to
make sure yeah because you have me on a
turmeric supplement doctor
oh so i'm not allergic to turmeric
that's right you knew better okay sure
sure okay
um all right listen i i know there's a
list of 30 other foods oh my god you
didn't even go through the fruits i'm
allergic to apples i'm allergic to what
else
to mango to papaya i'm allergic to
grapes
okay i gotta
go that happened a billion times on this
planet the bogus food sensitivity tests
i always tell people
if you're eating a celery stick and your
throat closes up don't eat it if you're
eating a
piece of lettuce and your throat's
closing up don't eat it
if you're eating an apple and your mouth
goes numb
because then don't eat it tests are
faulty because they don't even know why
anybody's sick
so let's do food let's do food
sensitivity tests food sensitivity tests
they don't even know why anybody has
fibro hashimoto's
can i just ask you guys something
does it make sense to you
when all these years nobody knows why
anybody's sick with chronic illness they
just call it autoimmune now
and but yet they have all the answers
because i'm confused i'm scratching my
head a little bit on that one
they have all the answers but they don't
know why anybody's sick
yeah
see
tests are faulty
yeah
see innard uh brutal says i have heard
that you can develop an intolerance to
something you consume a lot
of over time surely not celery juice
i know a lot of alcoholics
they could just drink and drink and
drink and drink
and then they don't stop drinking
well i don't know they don't build any
kind of problems to it they'll drink
until they die down the road they'll
drink and they'll drink and they'll
drink and they'll drink i'm gonna get a
glass of wine you guys don't mind
i would love to just drink
i don't know they're building an
intolerance to it getting myself some
some white wine right now
so
i'm gonna have a glass of white white
wine
right when we get done with this live
i'm gonna have
white wine
five seconds after i finished my celery
juice
that's a terrible idea by the way
what happens is what people don't
realize is that
you can eat a healing food
for a long time
long time
there's no intolerance you get from it
right
i i don't know i've been drinking celery
juice since i was a kid every single day
i don't know what intolerance you're
talking about
but i do know this
okay
that
if someone has
some type of reaction and they think
it's because
of a food healing food they're using
that healing food could be cleaning out
yeast mold unproductive fungus viruses
bacteria
byproduct metals
the cleansing process gets mistaken
sometimes is intolerance
but you know and and that gets mistaken
when someone eats eggs they feed all
their bugs
they're gonna feel okay
they're gonna feel okay you know i ate
some eggs i feel good i made myself a
nice egg dish
a friend of mine tells me that they see
it on youtube all the time all the
youtube influencers are like making
their food
they toss their little salad of greens
with oil and vinegar with olive oil they
get their little soft-boiled eggs
and they put their soft-boiled eggs on
their salad
right goes down easy
but
the minute you get buggy and get buggier
those eggs will feed the bugs and feed
them and feed them and feed them to the
point where whether to the point where
every time you eat an egg you'll feel
fine or eventually you'll just get so
sick but not know the egg is feeding the
bugs
lorraine says i'm getting really
intolerant to bs but that's about it
mary fox says to think i limit it
limited my fruit potatoes and all but
green veggies for years
plus
um
got rid of i think you got rid of gluten
in dairy or you scarfed you scarfed
gluten and dairy with coffee and sugar
boy was i brainwashed
the brainwashing is real that's why i do
the whole robot thing is because we're
we're
we're considered a herd
you guys know that right
we're considered a herd by authorities
you're a herd you're part of the herd
that's what we are so we're we're we're
part of the herd you know that's what we
are right
okay we're just part of the her we're
part of the herd
that's what we are
right someone said in a comment the
other day that my goat is evil
i
i read a comment i think it was
yesterday's live
that my goat
was a sign of something scary
well i don't know that's terrible
is my sheep scary is my
cow scary
we're like we're like we're we're
basically supposed to be just part of a
herd i'm part of a herd heard part of
our sheeple
yeah chocolate chocolate chocolate
chocolate eat chocolate eat chocolate
eat chocolate paddle cattle we're part
of a herd hurt immunity hurt immunity
all about herd immunity you're part of a
herd you're not an individual soul you
are not an individual soul i am
brainwashed i am not an individual soul
i am part of a large herd we have no
souls hurt us hurt us
make sure we're part of the herd we do
not have a soul
did you guys know why they do that
do you guys know why
they
try to get us into this brainwashed
mentality
so that you're not an individual thinker
that's what it is
so you're brainwashed
with your caffeine addiction because the
caffeine industry wants you to be part
of that herd
the medical industry wants you to be
part of that herd
you're just a number
that's all you are
ain't nobody care about you
in authority land
you're just a herd
you're just a number you're a herd
how sick is that
you're not allowed to have a soul
you're not
you're just supposed to do whatever the
monies the money tells you to do all the
different studies that go for caffeine
and the studies that go for drugs you
guys would just be a herd listen to the
authorities and your health
professionals
well i want you to listen to your
doctors but i'm just saying there's a
bigger picture over that controlling
everything
kelly smith creepy never realized the
herd reference oh my god the herd
reference is insane they actually have
it brainwashed into us we're literally
that's what they use they say it all the
time esther
they brainwash us
to use all these chemicals too the air
fresheners oh my god do they ever
i'm going to give you guys a forewarning
right now okay
i'll give you a forewarning right
okay
um if you got
before i give you the forewarning
all right just want to give you a
rundown real quick we just used some
celery if you got here if you're if
you're late
this is the mm-900 hds it's got the dry
pulp because it squeezes every last drop
this is a medical device
i like saying it's a medical device so
you're not on a medical
device that's what i like about it okay
because i would rather be on this
medical device than other kinds of
medical devices
so that's what i would rather be on
hold on you guys i'm gonna
i'm gonna get on a
i got to get plugged in here because my
i just got a message
um
someone was at the door and said my
doctor's been trying to get a hold of me
yeah yeah
you want me to quit juicing
or why
it's it's it's not it juice juice is not
good for me the celery juice is not good
for him you want me to be plugged in all
right let me get the syringe i got to
get the needle and get me okay ow
all right i got him in right now it's in
my vein um
i don't want to be on this medical
device right here the mm-900 i want to
be on these medical devices right here
this is what i need to be on i need to
um
what's in that
drugs
really
okay
all right good and what's this plasma
and blood
blood plasma okay
all right this is what i need i don't
need this juicer
this is what i need here
huh
yeah i'm on my i'm on my medications i'm
on my blood pressure medication
yeah i'm on my cholesterol medication i
can the doctor yeah no doctors
prescribed this i could be honest i
could have this here there's nothing
wrong with that
okay
yeah
okay i i gotta go
what i like about this
medical device
is it keeps us
from the bad medical devices
and that's what i like i just pulled
this out sorry you guys
i'm gonna move this over i'll plug in
later
tanya says i stopped celery juice for
one week and felt so oh my god
well
this sale is running for a couple more
days the mm-900 hds you guys on tiktok
omegajuicers.com
this isn't just any juicer
i would never stand behind this thing if
it was just any juicer it doesn't have
the metal gears
which is a huge deal
huge deal for me in my book
and
squeezes the juice out so you save money
and it's the celery model see mmm 900
hds
okay
and you might want to have it for the
heavy metal detox cleanse because we're
doing the heavy metal detox splints if
you don't have it fine be there with the
heavy metal detox cleanse it's going to
be a three-day challenge next week
and i am pumped
make sure you have cleanse to heal
that's important if you want to be
involved in the
heavy metal detox cleanse
make sure
i'm heading off to ig i think i've
tortured you guys enough
you guys know i love you
so i'm heading off to ig you don't know
dr nesbitt
dr nesmet
dr nesbitt is
um
getting out of surgery
i think this is time he gets out of
surgery
uh dr nesbitt
you know what dr nesbitt says he's gonna
come on ig what
what dr nesbitt
he's gonna come on ig dr nesbitt's
coming on ig you guys that's what i'm
hearing over here
so
we're going to make sure caroline
are they going to have a sale on the
green
silicone o-rings because i need one just
just call them up contact one contact
them
tell them tell me you need an o-ring you
need the green thing
get a hold of customer service
just you know
you need a green green grommet you you
lost your green grommet just just get
one
i mean have them have them get you one
all right you guys
we are off
to ig
i'm gonna turn tik tok back on
go on instagram
and uh i'll turn clubhouse back on too
all right you guys i love you much
truly