There is a lot of land people do not see
or walk on. There are a lot of woods,
forests, mountains, hills, valleys that
people are not allowed on. government
land, classified land, land for testing,
land for mining, or just endless swaths
of land, vast amount of acres that
nobody has access to. And even private
land nobody has access to, but the birds
do. They have access to this land. And
the majority of the birds fly and die
over this land, die from chemtrails and
land on the land dead or dying. And no
one sees it. Millions and millions of
birds over the years have fallen into
these federal lands, into these private
lands, into these forests, these hills,
these valleys, on these mountains, and
the death is not seen. These birds are
not seen.
[Music]