[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
[Music]
medium hello I'm Anthony William the
medical Medium you're listening to the
medical medium radio show where each
week I bring the most advanced
information on health out there often
ahead of what's out there now and I'm
talking about conventional medicine too
and alternative medicine research and
science doesn't know a heck of a lot
about guess what chronic illness don't
get that confused with you know with
other life-saving medicine and
everything else that's involved in
technology that's different this is why
I often hear all the time young people
who have been taught and conditioned
that technology and science and research
has it all down with everything in life
they feel this safety they feel this
this control and all of it and all of a
sudden the the minute you get sick and
you all of a sudden have things that
just can't be explained by doctors or
that can be but you can't get resolv and
you're young it's an unbelievable
mindblower I'm seeing it more and more I
talk about this a lot now because I see
it every day now and it's really sad
back in the you know back years ago
decades ago doing this you didn't see
that as much but now we're just we're so
conditioned that science and research
knows everything about anything doesn't
matter what it is just go you know what
I mean just go to the doctor and if it's
not a cold which is really there are no
colds it's just flu there is no colds
there are no colds the cold viruses are
gone have been gone they've been killed
off overshadowed by the flu the flu is
what everybody gets some people get a
mild rendition some people react
differently some people get our worse
flu there's different strains of flu
that's just an example of what happens
here and we call it cold which is
actually not that's not how it works
there are no colds it's all flu now and
that's how it works when people get the
sniffles oh you got the sniffles oh you
got the sinuses and the congestion and a
little cough that's the flu it always is
and that's just a prime example of the
misinformation out there that's really
annoying but the point is if it's not
just something like the flu and then you
go and get an antibiotic for some kind
of chest cold or something meaning like
not chest cold you get some kind of like
chest bronchial spasms and cough and
everything else and you go to the doctor
and you get an antibiotic or whatever it
is you're on cough medicine and you just
you know you get better from the flu or
whatever even if the antibiotic didn't
have a whole lot to do with it cuz flu
are viral what happens is the whole deal
what happens is you think they just got
it all down you got it all down but it's
not it's not reality it's not how it
works it's unbelievable out there and so
we're talking about chemical
sensitivities and I'm drilling this home
a little bit chemical sensitivities is
what the show is about and I'm drilling
this home a little bit because it's
important to know this because people
with chemical sensitivities exactly
research in science they they're not
they're not like
they don't have it down with chemical
sensitivities people suffer they suffer
horribly terribly tremendously and and
this is a prime example a whole another
prime example and I'm not just talking
about illnesses that have names that are
common and everything else and that
people have every day like excus rasis
and Hashim Modas and everything else
restri science don't even have those
down either that's the whole point
that's chronic illness that's how it is
and it's always blamed on genes or your
body attacking itself which is
ridiculous cuz that's not how it works
it's how the body works so if you're new
to the show the information is Advanced
it's way ahead of what's out there now
it always has been and no one's talking
about it you can go online you can do
all this stuff you're not going to get
the medical medium information anywhere
else does it work put it this way
Decades of people getting better and
better and better just the celery juice
alone is changing the world in health on
all levels it's unbelievable and that
came from medical medium so that the
whole point is let's get all the other
gems and jewels we're talking about
rescue the book live a rescue this is a
book of all books that I've ever done
and and I say that because first of all
it's so huge it's such a big book it's
really intense it's packed it's
jam-packed it's a really serious book
and that's one thing all on its own and
and and it's so packed with so many
different conditions and illnesses and
everything else to understand and the
information about the liver and all that
that everybody needs but it's not just
that we're talking about CH chemical
sensitivities which chemical
sensitivities is there there's a little
section in the book
and it's important to know what's
happening how it works and everything
else around it very important show if
you don't have a chemical sensitivity it
doesn't mean you're not being affected
by chemicals chemicals that research and
science created funny how's that isn't
that
interesting research and science creates
all kinds of bad things and nothing but
bad things okay meaning like also some
good things of course but lots of bad
things chemical sensitivities well
everything behind them including the
chemicals that make people sensitive
including basic chemicals that make
people sensitive was some kind of
research and science behind it that
created it so it's just it's just
amazing how it goes I mean right no
irony I don't know I I definitely think
it is I definitely think it is so let's
go into chemical sensitivities this is a
big deal Big Show I'll tell you why
because people suffer they suffer with
these chemical sensitivities and I think
we have to be more more sympathetic I
think we have to be more compassionate
actually about it chemical sensitivities
are so frustrating for people who deal
with them it's no joke part of it is
physical suffering the physical
suffering is uh is extraordinary it's
really really difficult that's a big
part of it okay the other part is an
unsym athetic World an
unsympathetic world that's the other
part of chemical sensitivities that I
don't like the average person who's
never had to deal with a sensitivity
will view someone with sensitivities as
probably bat crap crazy most likely
that's what they would probably view
somebody like that or an ultimate
hypercondriac or Stark crazy or
something um so you yeah and that's
really hard I mean it's really hard it
really is unless there's this visible
allergic reaction unless it's like
somebody with a peanut allergy goes an
athlectic shock and they have to use you
know an EpiPen or whatever it is and you
know meaning whatever because there's
different kinds of there's different
kinds of injectors and different kinds
of um things that are out there being
offered right now thanks to science
exactly some of the good stuff to save
people's lives but peanut allergies in
general kind of came about because of
science and research too
so that's a whole another thing but uh
we can talk about that another time so
here's the deal it's yeah it's exactly
it's almost like oh here's a remedy not
a cure but here's a remedy to something
we created we created the the the peanut
allergies literally not the peanuts but
the science of research created it I
want to talk about it a little bit I
can't help it and yet we don't have a
cure for what we created classic classic
so here's a remedy to try to get you out
of like you know total total um you know
epilc shock so that's the whole bit so
anyway usually people who if it's not
something like that people think you're
crazy if it's not something where you
know you got close throats blocking the
Airways and it's hard it's hard for an
observer to think that there's anything
you know valid
validation about chemical sensitivities
right it's hard for anybody to take it
seriously it's hard for anybody to
actually care enough too really
difficult that's where I'm talking about
the unsympathetic world doesn't mean
someone's not a good person and they
just don't care it's that's not it it's
just it's just people don't care I mean
I don't know what else to say I mean
right so that's just one thing chemical
sensitivity
suffers reactions are very they're very
often
invisible that's what I'm trying to get
at here
invisible very important invisible to
the outside eye making it
challenging for people to find Advocates
making it challenging instead they're
often told that they're making up their
sensitivities you know looking for
attention that's brutal I mean that's
brutal seriously or that it's
psychological maybe see a psychiatrist
see a shrink see whatever they maybe
treat it with an ey roll right the eye
roll I just did one just now and they
may be treated like that I do that for
research in science with chronic illness
I always do that the eye roll like oh
here we go get another bogus another B
bogus junk crap study that's just backed
by investors to make something try to
have an outcome and just whatever put
the thumb on the scale and you know when
it comes an a chronic illness and
whatever it's just it's unbelievable I
do the eye roll all the time and and so
what happens is people do the ey roll to
chemical sensitive he sufferers and then
they may be told that they're
attracting their chemical sensitivity my
favorite annoyance of all is they may be
told that they're creating it
manifesting it yes you want to manifest
good things you do it's not a bad word
you want to do the best you can in every
way to generate the best you can to you
good energy absolutely you better
believe it good spiritual energy good
everything but but seriously it gets
used against anybody who has a hard time
not the part part that the word is there
not the part that the that the you know
the it's popular or trending whatever it
is everybody's trying to manifest
something that's not it that that
doesn't bother me what bothers me it's
it's it gets used against anybody who
has a hard time anybody who's doing good
should manifesting good stuff they're
all just the manifestation is working
anybody who's going through a hard time
you know you say you got a yoga studio
and you got 50 people in the yoga studio
and there's everybody's trying to
manifest something but if someone's
having terrible luck if someone's having
bad luck you know or someone's having
some difficult time yeah people are just
be like you're just not manifesting
right you're not you're not Greatful
you're not manifesting right and what
happens is it gets thrown on to people
chemical sensitivities you're not
manifesting you know whatever and you're
just you're just emotional what whatever
it is it's just not healthy I don't find
it healthy and creating your own illness
is a big topic I put in thyroid healing
for a reason because it's that obnoxious
because people think they're be they're
being told they think they're creating
their own illness and let me tell you
something that might be okay for
somebody who's 40 to think they could
probably handle handle it okay but when
you got somebody who's 15 and they think
they're manifesting their their illness
and you got somebody who's 14 or you got
somebody who's 19 and they're looking
into things and they think they're
manifesting their bad luck or their
illness or their or their or their
adversity it's
disastrous on a level you can't
imagine
disastrous it can tank someone it can
really get them to do something
absolutely stupid out of that alone not
good and not healthy I'm not I'm not
kidding around same same with somebody
who's in their 20s they think they're
not manifesting the right you're such a
like a vulnerable age everything about
it and if you think you're the cause of
why you got something going down like
that because you're picking up on that
whole manifestation thing it could be
damaging it's cute for the 40-year-olds
50y olds whatever they can kind of shrug
it and move past and if it's working not
working how they feel whatever I'm going
about the manifestation thing a little
bit too long I know and I'm going into
it a little bit but I have to because
I'm going to tell you right now chemical
sensitivity people they've been told
they're manifesting their problem
because they're told that a the problem
is not real B if their problem is real
and it's considered it then it's
something they're doing wrong because
there's no answers once again for
research and science about chemical
sensitivities anything there's no real
answers for it it it's it's it's it just
becomes like this that's why I'm going
into this a little bit I had somebody
personally who you know who came to me
and they said look I'm I'm thinking
about I'm thinking about just giving up
giving up because I'm obviously
manifesting it all wrong and and I don't
know what to do to fix it because I
still have problems coming my way and
I'm trying to deal with them and I got
the chemical sensitivities and I got
this and I got that I got this mold
problem in my house I got major chemical
sensitivities I got all this other stuff
I've been I've spent all my money I've
completely exhausted myself on all
levels and I'm just literally at the end
of my rope and I said just just just
forget the concern just forget the
manifestation thing just move that out
of your way you didn't create anything
you're not you're not manifesta things
the wrong way I said it's chemical
sensitive person it saved their life
they were literally contemplating
something grave and it saved their life
I'm just telling you right now okay it's
saved their life I've seen it happen
more than once where lives have been
saved by moving that aside moving that
over and saying here's the real problem
and here's what's really going on and
we're going to actually work on it and
we're going to get you in the right
place there are real answers there are
real causes just hang in there it's
going to be okay compassion compassion
compassion manifesting isn't about
compassion okay move on move
on and is that important so what we
really need is to do is to find
compassion the people who deal with
chemical sensitivities and other chronic
illnesses we need compassion for we have
to dig it out of us in any way we can
for others in any way we can somehow we
have to find it we got to dig it out and
we have to make it happen okay there's
nothing wrong with that there's nothing
wrong about being positive there's
nothing wrong with trying to create your
life in every way and your destiny and
controlling it and all that everything
don't get me wrong it's just there's
certain little laws in the manifestation
game that I'm was trying to tell you
about a little bit okay so we have to
dig out that that whole compassion we
have to dig it out for chemical
sensitivity people because they are real
they are real they're very very
difficult situations when sensitivities
are moderate to extreme individuals will
often confine themselves to home because
it feels like it's the only safe place
but there's a catch 22 so many people
are in just situations where they
feeling like their chemical
sensitivities are actually in the home
theirself or in their homes
that's really diffic difficult so
difficult and so they're in this Catch
22 right you guys you know when they
think their apartment you know there's
all kinds of things there's mold this
that there's everything else and
sensitivities and and you know whether
carpet cleaning fragrance outgassing
construction materials chemical presence
in the home they're always worried
people are like crap they're like
strapped in there and they're trapped
but yet they got knowwhere else to go
because they don't have where else to go
I'm serious this is really hard
and since the outside world has its own
threats often unpredictable ones like
these people feel like they can't go
anywhere you go into a department store
and you're just completely covered in
Cologne and and plugging fresheners and
God knows what things that actually yeah
things that make Chemical sensitivities
worse and worse and worse and worse you
better believe it yeah that's right you
walk through a park you get sprayed you
walk by somebody's yard you get sprayed
yeah you better better believe it and
depending on where you live they're
spring
24/7 literally spring the most dangerous
fungicides and herbicides 24/7
everywhere people's Lawns neighborhoods
oh you got 12 houses on a street I'm
just saying I mean that's a tiny Street
probably got 12 houses on a street and
six of them are just spraying stuff
meaning there's somebody coming and
spray in your lawn here you go here you
go Madam here you go Mr here you go here
you go Mrs and Mr Jones or whatever
here's your you know here's your service
we're killing you and we don't you don't
even know it and we don't even know it
we're just spraying it down you know and
then your neighbor who could be chemical
sensitive yeah
absolutely oh my God unbelievable or
become chem chemical sensitivity meaning
sensitive because of that kind of thing
I mean seriously look you know it's look
chemical sensitivities tend to vary from
person to person too and there's a lot
of reasons for that we're going to talk
about why and what it's all about why
it's even in the liver book the liver
book this Beast of a book if you don't
have it by now order it order it why did
I do all that I did if you don't have
it and you can't afford it whatever it
is I don't know what it is $15 $18
whatever it is $20 if you can't afford
it go to the library get it so I could
sleep at night so I could sleep at night
knowing that you got it and you're
helping yourself cuz that's all that
matters to me I'd give it out for free
all I could and would if it didn't cost
money for Printing and Publishing and
putting it out there so it literally can
get in somebody's hands from far away
places but get to the library if you
can't afford a book absolutely and I put
information out for free 24/7 on medical
medium and I don't charge it volumes of
it Medical medium.com blogs everything
else Instagram Facebook articles
everything and I kill myself to make
sure you get it so just please please
take part
partake and know you don't have to buy
into some program some crazy program and
SP spend money or buy you know a million
dollars and something okay so here's the
deal it's almost as if these
sensitivities move and shift for a lot
of people and the condition Alters out
nowhere you know you may need to change
yourself all of a sudden you may need to
change your perfume you're sensitive
perfume when you weren't next time it's
hairspray like oh my God I wasn't
sensitive to hairspray or aerosol some
kind of aerosol but now I am so that can
all
happen maybe you're you're you then
become sensitive to your allnatural
shampoo that you always that always did
you right this is how difficult it is
the inconsistency can make somebody go
crazy not because they're crazy to begin
with no they got the chemical
sensitivities but they end up going
crazy you can it's really difficult and
and and and we have to have compassion
for this this topic you know you may be
one of those people who finds your
sensitivity
manageable but if you don't take care of
something it could become unmanageable
there's something you got to learn to
take care of there's something you got
to learn how to do there's something you
need to do you guys in order to make
sure you don't run into that kind of
problem where it becomes
unmanageable
yeah because there's a lot to do with a
lot of things here we're going to cover
that so we got to be careful and you got
to make sure you got to make
sure that look for example to avoid a
plug-in air freshener when you can and
you get by so you feel like you can
manage it that's a mild sensitivity but
then there a person who has to avoid
multiple items conventional hairsprays
colog fabric softers Cleaning Solutions
and yes fresheners air fresheners of
course which many people can't tolerate
and rightfully so it's
toxic toxic because you're extremely
toxic because the enemy just a whiff is
a debilitating situation here
hypervigilance required makes it so much
more difficult to operate and manage you
know it's where are you going where are
you going today where are you heading
you heading to a store what's in the
store you going to the dentist office do
they have the plugins there what what
are you doing is the person at the
dentist office wearing cologne sit you
know is he wearing a cologne that's
sitting behind the desk is she wearing
some strong perfume and hairspray behind
the desk what are you going to do are
you wearing a mask today are you
surviving are you going to wear your
gloves your night trial gloves it's hell
for so many
people
yeah yeah I I don't hear anything like
this out there just so you know if
you're new to the show you're going to
get the you're going to get the truth
and you're going to get you're going to
get the information it's unbelievable I
did this liver book because I don't hear
anything anything the best experts on
the so-called Circuit of Health and
Wellness pedaling whatever kind of like
stuff they want to sell I mean you go
through their books and it's it's
unbelievable how there's nothing in
there there lower your carbs that's
what's in there lower your carbs
my God my God I can't even go into it I
talk about that in Liver Rescue there's
a chapter all about that how we got to
where we got to and how the best experts
in leading people in health and wellness
going around are literally just you know
pedaling their own platform stuff to
make money and then in the end what
information do they really have about
chronic illness it's not much it's very
little so you need to make sure you get
the information right look I have the
right to say any of this I have the
right to say all of it I've been been in
the trenches in the pits long enough and
I've helped a lot of people in my day
Decades of it I was given the gifted H4
if you don't know anything about me if
you want to learn about me get the
medical medium book one and and and um
and read origins of the medical
medium and I didn't just start this 5
years ago I've been doing this literally
for decades up all night helping people
with emergency situations people
bringing children to the front door of
my house slept barely anything in 30
plus years and more and just I'm at your
service
I'm at your service just like so many of
you are at the service of you know of
God and at the service of so many other
things that you're doing and At Your
Service to other people and whatever and
at the service of your family just the
same way so you think about what you're
doing and where you're at your Ser well
I'm at your service um so it's important
so cleaners are bad too these plug-in
air fresheners bad chemically treated
pulper can sneak up on you so how are
you going to function when you don't
know where you're going like you're at
the dent office wherever you go and you
got to worry about all these things
things
nonstop and there's an activator around
every corner an instigator around every
corner for god sakes every
corner yeah
exactly
exactly and even Christmas trees are
sprayed with some kind of concoction to
keep them looking green as long as
possible or as fresh as looking possible
and even fake fake Christmas trees are
treated with nanotechnology now and
solutions that can set somebody off so
Christmas becomes a bummer a bummer if
you celebrate
Christmas you
know those who are chemical sensitive
are forced to become experts they're
forced to become an
expert they're forced to become an
expert and you know it it it's difficult
and it doesn't mean there's still an
expert they're an expert at maybe what
could be triggers but they're not an
expert at what the heck's causing it cuz
science and research once again leave
everybody hanging leave everybody
hanging all that research money goes
into just whatever investors are putting
it into at all the time thumb on the
scale leaving everybody hanging in
chronic illness like you can never
believe
unbelievable and you know you can have
all the best technology you want and
still someone has chronic UTI with no
with taking antibiotics once a month
with no like no sight no sight in front
of them of it being like the light
coming yeah that's just one little thing
I talk about that in Liver Rescue a show
thousands of things the um so they
become experts they're forced to become
experts and be mindful that's what
people are do with chemical sensitives
are forced to do that's that's how it
works they see things in a different way
they have their eyes and a Different
Light they have to see things in a
different way chemical
sensitivities that you know chemical
sensitivities make it so you have to
leave your rosec colored glasses
behind it's such a bummer you know
because yeah those Road those Rose
Colored
Glasses do tend to get people through
life in many
ways they also get you in trouble too so
maybe those rose colored glasses are not
a good thing they must dedicate an
immense amount of energy that's that's
what these people have to do that's what
you guys have to do in reading labels
have you ever done that done the label
thing but you really have to read the
labels right not just a little bit and
you got to figure out what's in really
what's in every product how they come
across everything ingredients you name
it pets and pet stuff too all of
it it's
unbelievable and you're all about
hyperallergenic that's what we got to
all be about so that's another thing too
it's
endless and and even clothes you know
saturated with multiple synthetic
laundry chemicals you know and air
fresheners that go on clothes and
leeching out oils doesn't have an effect
unknown effect meaning it's unknown
effects on humans it has real effects
see here's the thing if everybody thinks
they're escaping all of this they're
wrong they're wrong just cu the canaries
just because the
canaries are being affected first
doesn't mean you're not being affected
now now and later never forget unless
you do something and take care of what
your liver that's what we're going to go
into pretty
soon those who are newly chemical
sensitive and you guys will probably
ring true on this you'll tell me you'll
be like yeah he
knows those who are newly chemical
sensitive have a very tough time of it
oh man is it rough new chemical
sensitivity for a new person a new be on
the Block whoa it's rough it's rough and
maybe I'm look I just think it is but
maybe I'm wrong you tell me am I wrong
about that one when you were brand new
at it with chemical sensitivity was was
it was it's was it extra difficult that
me my wrong I don't
know I'm not right about everything
spirit is but I'm not you know you know
the story in the book Origins medical
medium I stepped on a rake smacked me
right in the
[Laughter]
face
um even though the person I was talking
to could walk again because it's Spirits
information I do stupid things though
personally separate I'll say something
stupid step on a rake smack it in my
head cuz I'm not looking at where I'm
going so those who are newly chemically
sensitive have a very tough time of it
first there's a process of becoming
aware that's brutal that something's
even wrong that's really hard it can
create a tremendous amount of confusion
stress headaches for the first time
funny taste in your mouth runny nose
it's always happening tingling tongue
certain settings you tingling tongue in
certain settings of your life getting
tired easily while walking through a
department store and breathing in
thousands of synthetic chemicals or
starting to feel a tight chest in the
workplace that's really annoying from
fragrances or other air day-to-day stuff
yeah these aren't fun symptoms you think
they're fun
no
newbi have a difficult challenge they
have to find a doctor who doesn't say
it's all in your head or maybe some some
kind of motivational person to say
you're not manifesting right that's why
I mentioned it
earlier yeah or you'll be shoved into
the Lyme disease trap oh my God if you
know listen if you want to know the
truth about lime get medical medium book
one read the lime chapter and try not to
bring a torch or shovel or pitchfork to
to to you know to my apartment building
because when because when you learn the
truth of Lyme disease it can anger
people that's what I've learned even
though there's all these there's there's
actually at this point now hundreds of
thousands healing from Lyme disease when
they learn the truth from the
information from medical medium but
still it just still angers people
because when you're conditioned a
certain way and and to think a certain
way and the labs they train you and
condition the doctors and train the
people it gets frustrating it gets
frustrating but there's just you know
it's unbelievable how things work but
you might get thrown into that whole
thing you know that that whole lime trap
can easily get thrown in there so you
got to remember that can easily happen
and it does it does it gets a lot of
people and it's really difficult and you
want to be careful you don't end up like
that because it happens now you know
anyone with chemical
sensitivities anyone with any kind of
chemical sensitivities has a challenge
on their
plate really a big Challenge and you
need to you know in finding support from
a family member or friends is difficult
too they may be bewildered or become
sick of it all easily and come they
could get sick of it quite fast there's
no question since everything was fine
before you know your body reactions
aren't easy they're not easy for anyone
to deal with it happens it happens all
the
time it's not and you know and people
you know they got the perfumes and the
makeups and they got the clones and the
aftershave and you know they're at the
Sal the salon or breathing in car
exhaust and shopping at the mall and
they got no complaints there's a lot of
people that go through that they can do
anything they can breathe and all those
things throw after after shave is just
horrendous cologne is by far one of the
I can't stand I can't stomach cologne it
makes me sick and that has nothing to do
with a chemical sensitivity the smell of
it just makes me like it gets me
nauseous gets me nauseous cologne's a
bad one it's like anytime I run across
somebody and they got clone on their
hands and they got clone all over their
clothes and they shake my my hand or
they give me a hug and it's covered on
me I have to go and I have to change my
clothes because the cologne is brutal it
just it sits there and it gets caught in
your sinuses and it stays in your
sinuses and you get tasted and it ruins
your meal I've had that happen where
I've actually I've actually been in
meetings with people loaded with cologne
where I was inhaling it for hours and
then literally tasting it my sinuses in
my mouth and then we went to go get
something to eat and my food taste it
like cologne I'm like oh my God how do
people live like this how do they live
like this imagine somebody who's
actually chemical
sensitive imagine that situation how
difficult it is you know I just hate it
but they're actually chemical sensitive
just imagine and I'm aggravated enough
when I run across that where I'm like so
put off I'm like oh my God I just can't
stand this imagine somebody who's
actually getting affected by it in all
these other ways oh my God it's
unbelievable so so you know look someone
can develop a fresh sensitivity and when
they do the reality is
limiting limiting versus what other
people can do and live in their life
they say why can't I be in the real
world why can't I live my life like I
used to why can't I live like everybody
else that just does what they want
living in moderation eat in moderation
just so you know that's all bold that'll
just get you that moderation talk will
just get you that'll just get you
moderation doesn't work when you're
actually dealing with chronic stuff
internally and I'm not just talking
about chemical
sensitivities you know I've been you
know the thing is is I've been a little
bit more I guess sarcastic or annoying
and and and I want to apologize for it
just look listen just I might have just
gotten a little bit more difficult maybe
you know it's like each decade goes by
and you think that you know I live by
the Hope and Faith thing you know that's
how I live is hope faith and um and I
live by that and I always keep you know
faith that you know research and science
is actually going to you know do
something that's just not about the
money they're going to actually really
like help people and I keep on thinking
it's going to happen any minute because
people who work for all these different
situations venues or whatever and
institutions they're all good people but
they're trapped in whatever kind of
bureaucracy that's involved with every
bit of it so I get it so but I always
have this faith that it's going to break
through that all the truths that I bring
in the medical medium series and
everything else to help people with
chronic illness is going to break
through more and more and it has it's
helped Millions around the globe
actually at this point but but still
it's not enough and what happens is I
have this this hope and this faith that
the new trendy doctors or the new trendy
people that want to hang their hat on
stuff on stuff that have a whatever and
they put their books out on their
internet information I always think
they're going to just come around a
little bit and they just don't and then
I realize I'm alone I realize I'm alone
and but but then I realize I'm not alone
I got you guys you guys are experts you
guys know you guys are practitioners you
guys are doctors and I and I and I know
that I know that but then I I I I also
but I like I said I get can get
irritable and I'm really sorry just take
you just listen just you know please
accept my apologies if you can when I
get sarcastic I get a little bit of
whatever Brash I get a little bit of
abrasive whatever it is it's not towards
anybody it's just it's towards the
industries is what it is it's towards
the industries and maybe a little bit of
the people involved in some of the
industries you like a can't it all right
so here's the deal so I'm on the Hope
and Faith game you know the Hope and
Faith thing is I got faith
I got faith that you know some someone
else is going to actually you know
start start a good fire yeah in the
industries in the industries you guys
are already starting the fires the good
ones you guys are already you know
starting to fires and it's helping out
die out bad fires starting good fires
and you're helping out to die out bad
fires bad fires that become bad Trends
and bad situations that bring people
down so you guys are really doing I'm
just blown away I'm actually just blown
blown away all right so and then you
have people who they have to become the
experts they're already an expert they
discovered their sensitivities years ago
then you got those people right you guys
know who they are you're probably one of
them and they know what they can handle
and what they can't afford they know
what they can afford when they're
exposed and they know what they can't
afford that's right they also know what
kind of boundaries to push up and put up
there it it even could be predictable
for them and and they can go through
times of feeling better and handling
more than waves of being able to
tolerate less it's a game of chance we
can't confuse chemical sensitivities
with
reactions to harmful chemicals though
we're not talking here about highly
regulated highly regulated and
unregulated chemicals like those to
visibly burn your skin we're not talking
about those substances we we you know
we're talking about substances that we
can't see or feel ones that many people
even can they they can't even smell how
about that you can't even smell it
how does someone develop develop a
sensitivity that's invisible isn't it
interesting how does it even happen what
occurs right did you ever ask that
question I'm asking that question I got
the
answer it all stems from guess what the
liver the liver l i v e r the
liver and that's one truth that not even
chemical sensitivity people know about
yet the best chemical sensitivity
experts who are affected by it or
so-called experts who say they know
what's going on don't even know that
that's what it's about they don't even
know that's what it's about and if they
did for some reason they got it from me
and they got it from me long before this
book came out cuz I've been talking
about this for years and years and
putting that information out there
see all sufferers of chemical
sensitivities have their guesses about
why it happened to them you know they
often have a landmark they play with you
know got sprayed by a pesticide walking
through a condominium Park some people
think it started the day they ate a
certain food some say it was the day
they had their house painted yes these
experiences can be triggers and the
realization that something's wrong can't
occur at these times they aren't the
whole story though they're not the whole
story what about the other person who
got sprayed walking through the park or
condo or whatever it is and they're not
affected and they're just fine what
about them how about that how about them
apples you know he went to the hardware
store or she went to the hardware store
purchased her own pesticides on top of
it sprayed them on their own
lawn and didn't develop a chemical
sensitivity maybe it could maybe it
could happen down the road for him
absolutely or her you better believe it
can though not yet that wasn't their
Landmark for the person who did develop
a sensitivity it was about what was
going on internally it was about what
was happening internally the timing of
the day in the park was random the Sens
was going to happen anyway it had
already begun somebody who did get
triggered by walking through the park
and they got triggered by a chemical
that was sprayed or whatever it is
walking through you know through
condominium Park they got sprayed yeah
and that seemed like the Treck that was
that was just a random occurrence it was
already going to happen it was already
on its way let's go into chemical
sensitivities let's go into chemical
sensitivities baby let's go into that
let's talk about that a little bit it
all starts with the liver as I was
saying it's your big sponge whose job is
to collect catalog and check in
thousands of what I call troublemakers
in The Liver Rescue book that's right
chemicals you name it liver's job is to
try to protect you and shield you you
know it it it that's its job it even
Shields you against toxic substances
your body creates it's natural for the
body to create that for example when you
experience fear the adrenals pump out an
adrenaline that helps you survive at the
moment but it's highly abrasive and
toxic and dangerous to your brain and
central nervous system it's so potent
though that the liver must clean it up
and absorb it all up and it's doing its
job to protect you the rest of your body
so it doesn't get in danger so the the
rest of your body doesn't get in danger
and then we also eat foods with bad
ingredients that's hard on the liver and
we eat high fat diets which is hard on
the liver we all eat high fat diets I
don't care how clean your diet is I
don't care if it's the best vegan diet
it is it's high fat unless you're really
really really really doing a lowfat diet
and you're probably not even doing that
right you're not even doing that right
unless you get enough celery juice and
how many years have you been doing
celery juice not long I bet if you have
even done it celery juice by itself not
even the best plant-based raw diet
that's low fat is even getting done
right doesn't mean you're getting enough
leafy greens not even the best paleo you
know low animal protein diet that's got
a new fancy name to it that I won't
answer I mean that I won't mention cuz
the names are just getting stupider by
the minute out there not even that diet
has probably enough leafy greens in it
and enough say celery juice and other
things too and mineral salts and allone
that so we you know we get we get
exposed to all kinds of stuff grease we
eat and grease on our skin exactly we go
to we go on cruise sh ships and all the
food on a cruise ship is sprayed with
the preservative how do you like that by
law and our livers must tend with it and
deal with it so as we're dancing on the
cruise ship and having a great time and
breathing in everybody's and perfumed by
the truckloads and all the insecticides
and all the carpet cleaning chemicals
that are all in the carpets and we're
having a blast we're inhaling all that
the liver's got to take it all in suck
it all up and take it all in and then on
top of that we're eating all the food on
a crud ship I'm not ripping apart crude
ships everything has its toxins and then
all of a sudden you're eating all the
cruise ship food forget it it's all
laced it's all got chemical
preservatives on it from chemical
companies and then what about drugs we
take oh I got a bad migraine let's take
a drug or whatever it is that's going on
that we we have to survive with and all
kinds of things that happen when we
don't know the cause of all our problems
we have to do things we end up at the
doctor's office taking drugs we ingest
everything like
that all of it going all the way back to
antibiotics in their childhood they all
the liver has to suck it up has to suck
it up that's what it has to do just like
your coach in high school at track or
your coach at high school at lacrosse
are you coach at high school at soccer
or you coach at High School in in in um
football or baseball suck it up walk it
off that's what the liver has to do suck
it up and walk it off that's what it has
to do pathogens that's a real pain in
the book cuz guess what that plays a
real big role in chemical sensitivities
I hate to drop this truth but it does
EBV is one of the big ones they find
their way inside the liver they make a
home in there and they create a mess all
on their own releasing waste like
dermatoxin and neurotoxins it's the
byproduct see all these troublemakers
and more your liver is constant
constantly at a ratio game how do I let
what I got to let out how do I release
how much I got to let out how do I got
to control how much I got to control to
protect them how much viruses inside of
me how much everything else is going on
that the doctor has no clue about on any
level
yeah how many germs can I come across
right now how many Road toxins can get
back into my bloodstream the liver is
watching all this how many medicines are
being ingested how many all these kinds
of things how much alcohol are in herbal
supplements that I've been shunning for
decades
decades yeah I've been
shunning that for decades for real yeah
for real and you know and I'm telling
you right now that's a bad one all on
its own doesn't mean your practitioner
is a bad guy or your doctor's a bad
person or Bad Gal it's not it at all
they just don't know that the alcohol is
bad in supplements always remember that
protect yourself
um and then maybe you'll teach them
something So eventually they won't use
it that's all so they can do their
beautiful work and help people like they
want
to how much can the liver afford to let
go or eliminate from your body that's
the whole point when you're going to
bathroom or anything else that's that
all that's critical to know every every
last bit of this you know when the liver
is sluggish and the colon is already
dirty which is most people and yet more
poisons keep coming in from toxic food
sources fresh paint a visit to a store
with sent candles air freshers plugged
in at dentist office waiting room
delivery truck spewing out exhaust and
idles your driveway I'm trying to talk
as fast as I can cuz I know I run out of
time every show and I hate running out
of time with you
guys cuz I love you guys so all this
stuff the liver has to deal with it work
with it in a whole bit toxic weed killer
that we run across everything we get hit
with the liver gets hit with and over
time the liver has grown sluggish for
everybody everybody with chemical
sensitivities even if it starts younger
the liver is grown grown tired sluggish
and problematic the final triggers are
not the
cause here this is what I'm trying to
say the final trigger of what you think
triggered you to chemical sensitivity
whether it's mold in your house or
something else is not the
cause is not the
cause you can have a viral situation in
the liver since birth you could have a
viral situation like Epstein bar in your
liver for years and that's one of the
true causes is like the Epstein bar
virus sitting in there along with strep
sitting in there
absolutely percolating eating stuff the
whole bit and then finally you get one
last trigger and you think it's that
trigger that did
it a sensitive central nervous system is
behind chemical
sensitivities it's behind it it's
another big part of it all and why
because when you have Epstein bar
releasing neurotoxins because it's
eating tons of toxins lots of toxins
inside your liver and spewing it out of
your liver and it's floating around your
body it affects the central nervous
system and guess what chemical
sensitivities are all central nervous
system that's right toxins that the
liver can't neutralize or contain get
overloaded and the ner nervous system
pays the
price this can take in the form of all
kinds of things funny feelings in the
mouth sense that you can't breathe
deeply or right blurry eyes yep chronic
headaches migraines fatigue tingles and
numbness insomnia dizziness anxiety
depression and
more yeah and more some of these
symptoms can happen independently for
example as a result of Epstein Bar's
neurotoxins going after the nervous
system chemical sensitivities also can
cause it and that's all part of it being
viral
too yeah big thing to know that's how it
works often neurotoxins and dermato
toxins from Epstein bar combined with
certain toxins stored inside the liver
create chemical Cent sensitivities
messing everybody up and causing trouble
that's the big one I'm I'm telling you
right now for a person who has
EBV without the right kind of toxic
heavy metals pesticides and Li and
chemicals inside the liver may
experience a different kind of chemical
sensitivity or not even experience it at
all
yet there's a lot of different things to
learn you guys should saturate yourself
in the medical medium book series so you
really become that expert get the
thyroid healing book just get all the
books I mean just get them get the
books I you just need to you really do
and this one right here is my God yeah
the liver book you have to
get you know I was proud of spirit with
this book when Spirit gave me every bit
of the information that was put into
this book I was proud I handw wrote the
whole book it was a stack of paper
almost the height of the ceiling to
begin with cuz I had to sit there day in
and day out and take that information
from Spirit until it was finally done
that's been my job my whole life
this you know what happens
is unknown combinations Factor that's
what happens too in medical research and
science when they try to figure out the
cause of chemical sensitivities doctors
and other practitioners need to keep an
open mind and learn that in most
chemical sensitivity patients the
central nervous system is the is
weakened and a viral infection could be
playing a very large role in all of that
not every chemical sensitive person is
dealing with an active viral infection
but they must have had one at one point
without a doubt at one point even if
it's not active in the moment that's why
doctors get confused too because it can
still make you sensitive if you was
active at one point if you had Mono a
long time ago if you had a scratchy
throat in college and it was actually
mono but didn't know it was mono cuz it
just went dormant and went away and went
to the liver all these kinds of things
and everybody has Epstein bar in their
system
so all of
this all important to
know so the bottom line is many people
have a chemical sensitivity for a long
time realize what's going on but when a
chemical sensitivity makes itself known
an emotional component kicks in that
makes physical suffering harder than
ever and that's a part I want to touch
apart Right Touch with right now what
could trigger
it what could trigger it next is it
getting better is it getting worse am I
dying are all questions that happen with
people with chemical sensitivities it's
really difficult many people can't put a
finger on what they're dealing with
and they can't and it's a mystery fear
heightens and OCD happens obsessive
compulsive disorder can happen freedom
from knowing what it is or the trigger
or not is and everything else is what
people need it doesn't happen overnight
it's a slow build getting freedom from
chemical sensitivities takes time that's
why I put it in the liver book so you
can work on this so you can get the book
and work on it and figure out what you
need to do healing from chemical
sensitivities is possible I've helped
thousands do it over the
decades it is possible it is
possible without a
doubt I'm not
blind I'm not blind to the fact that
chemical sensitivity people have a
difficult detox you know situation where
they have difficult detoxing I'm not
blind to that at all no way many can't
even take a single supplement in order
to try to sooth the nervous system or
detox the liver because they're so darn
sens of the poor things and you guys
might be one of
them if this is you don't think you're
stuck food is the answer in this case it
is and you can take care of your liver
and nervous system carefully with food
it's why I got The Liver Rescue book out
this is just one reason why if you're
not dealing with chemical sensitivity
but you're interested in the show look
into the book there's dozens and dozens
of conditions that the liver is involved
with that you probably have or deal with
are dealing with and one one of them is
not knowing that your liver is breaking
down over the years so you become sick
down the road so you may as well take
care of your liver now and get the book
it's
important
so trying to get it all out as much as I
can but it's a fraction of what's in the
book so we just do the best we can
you're not the problem if your nervous
system is really sensitive you may still
react to certain exposures after you
even
heal it takes time you'll still have to
follow certain boundaries work with the
rules work with the foods be careful try
not to get too much exposure while
you're
healing but here's the thing you have
the right to react to the world that's
toxic you're not the problem and never
were toxic chemicals and constant
stressors are the problem
sensitivities are are not the problem
it's just it's a valuable thing have
being sensitive being sensitive is
valuable not not not valuable it's
valuable yeah even if your sensitivity
goes away completely with your liver and
nervous
system okay even if it went away
completely you're gifted a heightened
awareness of The Perils of our world
makes you
gifted so that you can better protect
your family yourself and your future
remember that it means you're
gifted knowing
truth I can't even tell you it's that
powerful
the information from the medical medium
radio shows and the series and the book
series and everything else and the
articles is information that's not
contaminated it's pure it's
clean and it's not it's not persuaded by
belief systems it's not persuaded by the
thumb on the scale and investors
lobbyists that are in the medical field
and everything else it's not persuaded
by all of
that it's not it's clean information
it's independent and it's an independent
Source take advantage of it while I'm
still here take advantage of it wherever
you
can and um I just know I really care
about you guys it's not regurgitated
information that's out there in books
every single day it's not regurgitated
recycled remanufactured information it's
trying to sell something or whatever it
is and there's no info
infomercial okay in front of every
podcast
sure I want you to get the book to heal
you better believe it and I stand strong
by that and if you can't afford it go to
the library I don't care if a million
people go to the library and get the
book doesn't matter to me just get it in
your hands help your family help your
friends and get yourself
better persuaded belief systems don't
run this information it is an
independent Source that's given to you
and it's for you for a darn good
reason take advantage of it take
advantage of me with everything you got
got and
um and just know I love you dearly you
take one day at a time I know so many of
you suffered and it's not just chemical
sensitivities he suffered from all kinds
of different chronic conditions and I
know science and research and chronic
conditions has left everybody pretty
much
basically in the dark and I get
it take one day at a time and uh I'm
with you I stand behind you I believe in
you and never forget it and uh my
apologies if I sound
annoying and I sound obnoxious even at
times you know one thing Spirit told me
are you ever going to lose your
snappiness when I was a kid if you going
to lose your sarcasm and I said no it's
who I am so I'm going to keep it but I'm
going to definitely keep my compassion
strong just like you guys are and let's
do this together and get everybody
better I love you take one day at a time
God bless you as always and uh talk to
you soon bye