and we're going to talk about some great
stuff i'm going to make a salad
number one number two we're talking
about lyme disease
talk about autoimmune and we're talking
about blood draw
really important things to know things
that can keep you safe
things that are really critical to
understand so we're covering a lot of
stuff you guys this is an avocado in my
hand by the way
i got three avocados right here in front
of me so i'm excited about that got some
avocado
um making this salad
it's called the chop salad pretty basic
right chops out it's got avocado in
there it's got red bell pepper in there
got cucumber okay so hey guys good to
see you glad you're coming on
um i want to read you a little quote
from the medical medium
secrets behind chronic mystery illness
and how to finally heal this is the
revised and expanded edition of you guys
did you guys get this yet have you guys
had do you have this in your hands yet
this is really exciting powerful
information
it's out and you don't want to miss out
you don't want to miss out
okay you're making dinner i see that
right there
um cool you guys doing a little
experimental thing with tech today and
see how things work and so if i'm moving
around or doing something
uh anya you're loving the book amazing
right there on facebook on facebook and
youtube live by the way
so i'm both uh valerie you love the new
book
incredible isn't it a mind blower it's
such a mind-blowing book it really is
it's an amazing book so i'm glad you
guys are on
just order the new book that's it right
here it's in my hand
i can't wait for you guys to get it
making the chopped salad inside the book
so it's just showing you right here
right
so i'm gonna make this if you guys don't
mind
right yep
i'm glad you guys you know you're
waiting for the book in germany
thanks for being here that's incredible
um
germany's a great place i'm honored
you're here
amazing you guys so you guys today i'm
doing something i'm testing out the tech
and
something might be a little messed up on
youtube or facebook but just
bear with me trying a new system
trying to make it work for you guys
trying to get the best
so you guys can see the most but we'll
see what happens
all right so i'm talking about blood
draw today i'm talking about lyme
disease talking about autoimmune
and i'm making a salad i'm glad we're
all here
um take a look
i mean seriously it's just it's it's
great to have you in my kitchen
i love having you guys in my kitchen
okay that's a very special thing
um
so you guys got the new book
love the new book ordered cleanse to
heal too cleanse the heel
is a mind-blowing book as well it's
you know i mean the opportunity to heal
is in these books
that's what's incredible and so many
people are healing and have healed
really is amazing hey guys on youtube
you're waiting for me to come on sunny
valley i'm here
and i'm honored you're here your book is
coming tomorrow
great i'm just reading the comments you
guys can't put the book down it's so
detailed it
is insanely detailed this book
is detailed um
yeah yeah it's great hey uw can't wait
for this conversation
i saw that
um lemon balm love you healed because of
these books
incredible incredible robin hi
w from new hampshire great book thank
you for being here i'm honored
guys i got youtube on reading youtube
comments going to be reading facebook
comments
this is just a special time with this
book coming out right now
um yeah
it really is a great time really is a
special time
so um doing a little reading for you
guys is what i'm doing
just reading some comments
robinson i've had a post of yours fact
check today
my friend did too yeah i mean we post
and
i think i think what happens to the
system doesn't realize that
medical medium information is medical
medium information
um all of medical medium information in
all the books
is original and unique and comes from
the source
and you guys know because if you read
the first chapter origins of the medical
medium right here
in this book new edition you'll read
about the source
in which the information comes from all
the information in this book
okay and in the medical mean books is
advanced and it's
decades ahead of science and research so
medical medium information
is going to be fact checked because they
don't realize it but it gets fact
checked back to me
because it's original and unique and
that's why millions are healing around
the world
so you can't just take medical medium
information
type it in and try to find it somewhere
else unless someone else has
taken it and they're not citing it but
it's the original from the source so
you're gonna see that you're gonna see
you're gonna see a post that will be
like fact check
this isn't true well that's kind of
funny because
it is because it's this is the source so
they just don't realize that and medical
science research is taking all my
information
now so they're taking the information
and
using it out there and it was published
first here
in this book published first that says a
lot doesn't it when you really think
about it
what does that tell you so i put unique
original information in the medical
medium book
and then years later science and
research steals it out of the book
right plagiarizes it and then they start
to use it
even though it's already been published
so legally
it is here published and documented
first
and years later science research they
can't come up with their own answers to
why everybody's sick so they had to
steal medical mediums
it's actually incredible when you think
about it it's also really insane too
like
i mean are they that desperate where
they could just knock on my door and say
hey well you
obviously you've healed so many people
your information so can we use your
information
good to see you guys um
we choose truth michelle l we choose
truth over studies
i mean how many studies get people
better none
that's what's really demented about it
all right
i mean you could be sick for 30 years
with thyroid problems fibromyalgia
multiple sclerosis symptoms seen 20 30
specialists
and the study on matcha tea is not going
to fix you
they're busy with studies you know
they're busy with studies with all kinds
of stuff
they're studying wine they're studying
alcohol they're studying wine
just give you the stress benefits that's
what they're studying meanwhile
people are sick all around the world
with autoimmune in all kinds of ways i
mean
dying sick and they're studying
wine they'll pay for studies on this
group of people drinking wine
seems to have a lower reduced stress
level
paid for by the wine companies this
group here
who's not drinking wine seem to be a
little bit more uptight
and upset maybe because they're not
drunk
all right
okay thanks to the readers who went into
action
with the information here in this book
this book has prompted medical research
and science to recategorize
lyme disease this book prompted medical
research and science to recategorize
lyme disease i mean talking about
powerful what a powerful book
it's unbelievable while labeling lyme as
autoimmune
because that's what they did because of
this book still does not represent a
full understanding of lyme symptoms
this recategorization is a way for
medical research and science to admit
we don't understand this as well as we
thought we did
so medical research and science doesn't
understand lyme disease
or anything else in chronic illness as
much as they thought they did
especially lyme disease and that's a
major shift toward progress if you think
about it you guys it's a testament
to the people who read here in medical
medium
that lyme disease is viral eureka
viral not bacterial
okay who brought that information to
their doctors and who applied
the healing protocols here and got
results
it's also thanks to the doctors who have
educated themselves with this material
as they work to help their patients
many doctors have even applied the
healing protocols in their
own lives with their own lyme disease
symptoms all right
i wanted to read that
yeah it is i mean jeanette right that's
powerful
it's life-changing um
so yeah
so anyway you guys i'm on here we're
live youtube and facebook i want to make
you some food
and we're going to read some stuff in
here that's really cool
um thanks for being here with me we'll
read together
right and let's do that now let's read a
little bit before i start
chopping up some salad good to see you
guys
you got the few you got the book a few
days ago
um have you done you have you tapped
into the book
i hope so hope you got a chance
ariana why is everything viral epstein
barr
well science research believes
everything's genetic
your genes anya so that's what they
believe
so the question is why does research in
science
medical research and science believe
that every single thing is
is genetic so that's the question you
have to be asking
like why is research in science thinking
it's all genetic so every single disease
you have now
out there every single symptom every
single condition is genetic now
so it's not like why is everything
epstein-barr
anthony no why research in science is
everything genetic
that's all they have as an answer so
think about that right
when you're functional medicine doctor
or your practitioner a natural
practitioner
when they they do all their magic spells
we'll try a little this we'll try a
little apple cider vinegar here take
these fish oil capsules hey take this
supplement here
let's do this test maybe we can do this
whatever they do and in the end they
still believe
it's your genes in the end
if you really beat them down on the
ground enough about it it's your genes
so it's not about and plus i don't say
epstein-barr is everything
i don't say everything fc bar is
everything simplex one
i talk about a lot hhv-6
the shingles virus has over 30 varieties
of mutated strains
the epstein bar is not one virus the
epstein-barr virus is over 60 varieties
of mutated strains and they do different
things
toxic heavy metals i talk about a lot of
the books
radiation okay toxic heavy metals
talk about that and
pharmaceuticals causing problems like
all of it so everything's not
epstein-barr
but a lot of stuff is epstein-barr
so yeah so you guys
i'm gonna read a little bit in here and
then we're gonna get making a salad i'm
glad you guys are on here i'm excited
i got youtube live right here which is
really cool
i also talk about high fat diets being
harmful too so it's not just epsom bar
it's high fat diets beating down your
liver giving you a stagnant sluggish
liver
doing harm i talk about all the trends
that are bad
like all the bad trends that cause
trouble
i talk about a lot of stuff and then i
talk about the emotional aspect
not just epstein-barr i talk about the
emotional aspect the trail
happens with your adrenals what happens
when you're in fight or flight
what happens when you're when when
you're you know somebody breaks your
trust
and betrays you stabs you in the back or
you get a broken relationship
and a broken heart and a divorce and
all kinds of stress that people go
through i talk about that medical medium
information is really vast with a lot of
information
pam question there on facebook do you
think epstein-barr is part of your
genetics
wow 65 it's here it's not part of
genetics viruses have nothing to do with
genes at all at all
nothing to do with genes so
a virus just so you know
okay a virus is a microorganism
it has nothing to do with your jeans
it's
absolutely nothing to do it's a bug it's
on its own
it's it's a bug um does a fly flying
around a room have anything to do with
your genes
does it when you get food poisoning from
a foodborne
microorganism a bad parasite on a piece
of meat or a piece of
raw fish and you get the food does that
have something to do your genes
i don't i don't think so right it
doesn't at all
the virus that you can contract okay so
say you've got
mono which is the epstein-barr virus and
you kiss somebody
right in a relationship that person
then catches mono is that their genes
why would that be their genes they just
caught mono from you
so when you go into a public bathroom
and you sit on a toilet after somebody
has fecal matter on the toilet and in
that fecal matter
the poop on the toilet there's viruses
all in it because they're sick with the
hhv-6 or epstein-barr or shingles and
you sit on the toilet and you
catch the virus somehow
is that your genes
and kiss somebody with a cold sore and
you've got
the simplex one virus and you got a
fever blister
and you kissed them and now they have a
is that their genes no they caught a bug
that's its
own microorganism and that's how it
works
i you know it's the thing is is that
but they'll tell you though that it's
your genes
so do priests as viruses can integrate
gray integrate
into your data no they can't
they can't so they can't mess with your
dna
they can't become your dna they can't
that's all theory and there's no science
behind that
there's no study that can actually show
that that's theoretical
but you know it's theoretical
theoretical
um that's how it works virus
is on its own you got the herpes simplex
one
and you got your fever blister and you
kiss somebody else and
then you give them your fever blister
they just caught herpes simplex one
that's not your genes or dna that's you
catching the herpes simplex one a live
virus
it doesn't kind of get any more clear or
easy
breezy or understandable
okay um how did so many people get it
um all you gotta do is eat in a
restaurant
more than a few times in your life and
you're gonna get something
you just are the amount of
microorganisms
viruses like epstein-barr and strep and
shingles
you can get from restaurant eating is
unbelievable
unbelievable you've got chefs in a
kitchen with 100 degrees
dripping sweat in your salads and in
your food
tripping drenching sweats sweat just
drops right
you got that okay you got chefs cutting
their fingers
they constantly cut their fingers they
got band-aids all over their hands
as they're preparing your food that's
just one thing
you got public bathrooms public
bathrooms
if you go to bathroom and you don't
flush the toilet before you go
to bathroom because sitting on top of
that bowl is remnances
of somebody else and it splashes back in
you and then you can get it from
relationships relationships is the big
one
such relationships that's how everybody
spreads all the bugs
that's why it just goes around decades
of just spreading bugs it's just normal
life i mean normal life i'm not saying
anything
good or bad or bad whatever i'm just
saying that's a big piece of it
and that's just some of the stuff i can
go on and on and on let's look a little
bit here it's just great to answer
questions you guys
glad we're here so i'm making the salad
but i'm going to read a little bit
out of the new edition right here okay
so medical medium secrets behind chronic
industry illness how to finally heal a
new admission
this is called a look back this is in
the lyme disease chapter you guys
bear with me all right let's travel back
in time for a moment to november
1975. when multiple
children and young adults were
developing symptoms
which alerted doctors to launch an
investigation
in the area around lyme connecticut
that gave lyme disease its name right
first let's remind ourselves of the
technological back
technology back then let's remind
ourselves a little bit right
rotary phones do you guys remember the
rotary phones it's like i got to call
somebody but i gotta call somebody quick
let grab the phone
[Music]
um there's a lot of young people here
that don't know what a rotary phone is
or am i getting that old or what is it
which one is it
um i got to get a rotary phone prop i'm
going to get a rotary phone prop
i'm going to order one tonight that's
going to be good
that's gonna be fun i could do a tick
tock with that one
and you're like right
okay i just dialed half the number there
it is
uh seven four two
uh
[Music]
okay that's when they're deciding your
fate
back then with your lime now
that's the technology we had back then
right
so let's travel back in time for a
moment to november 1975 when multiple
children and young adults were
developing symptoms which alerted
doctors to launch an investigation in
the area
around lime connecticut that gave lime
disease's theme if you guys just came on
watch the replay of the facebook live
watch the replay of youtube the youtube
live
please if you can first let's remind
ourselves of the technology back then
rotary phones on the kitchen wall the
rotary phone was on the kitchen wall
this is important to know i'm trying to
tell you guys
why this is important okay and it's part
of why
everybody was so injured by treatment
for lyme
and how tens of thousands hundreds of
thousands of women
lost their health and their lives their
families fell apart
many died because of stupidity in the
medical system
keep keep that in mind so the rotary
phones on the kitchen wall
no such thing as voicemail voicemail
didn't exist back then
and sony was just releasing its first
vcr do you know what that is
anybody too young in here christina
laughed with an
lol christina elizabeth
right sony just launched their first
vcr i mean
right okay for sale in the united states
in the medical world kids were getting
their tonsils plucked out
as if they were apples on trees every
kid that had a scratchy throat
had their tonsils ripped out of their
throat
okay this is dark ages this is just 1975
but it's dark ages
and we're still in the dark ages that's
what's sad and when i talk about blood
draw in a little while you'll know what
kind of dark ages we're talking about as
you guys get sicker and sicker getting
your blood taken from you
i gotta kind of get your back on that
help you
hey terry just said no answering machine
either
right terry we the same age
or what nancy said i remember that
all that as a young child
all right kids were getting their
tonsils plugged out plucked out
as if they were apples on trees with no
understanding of the underlying cause of
tonsillitis
science research is so smart you guys
they don't even know what causes
tonsillitis and guess what
they still don't know what causes
because medical medium tells people what
the cause of tonsillitis is
and puts it in the books medical
research and science are going to steal
that
next just like they stole all the other
information in here and started
publishing
with no studies behind it but started
publishing it after the fact
plagiarized plagiarity plagiarizing
if you're somebody who doubts medical
medium info and you're a big science
person you're all about science is
everything medical medium is crazy
well then this might give you some
relief to know that medical research and
science is
hijacking all of medical mediums books
and information stealing it out of there
yeah the medical means looking into it
because that's really screwed up they're
hijacking it
taking it and using it they're not
supposed to it's a pup this is
this is a publication that was before
all of their
them knowing all that even today there's
no clinical understanding of what's
behind tonsillitis they still don't know
what's behind tonsillitis
so smart my god they're so smart
while technology has made leaps and
bounds
yeah with phones and crap like that and
car like radios
technologies made leaps and bounds to
computers phones and car radios
that's it pretty much pretty much that's
it
think about that right but
the cars still have rubber tires we're
so advanced but all you got to do is run
over a nail
and your your ass is stuck on the side a
highway
we have so much technology now but we've
had a rubber tire since 1902
i'm trying to think about that one like
that that's a head scratcher to me we're
so advanced in technology
but we've had car tires since 1897 or
something like that but we
we still have a car tire which is a
rubber tire
with air filled in it since 1902 or what
is it 1904 i forget
1890 this is crazy right
so where's that advance we're advancing
car radios and
cell phones and and computers
while technology has made leaps and
bounds advancements in chronic and
mystery illness has been
at a freaking standstill
fibromyalgia still cause unknown they
think it's just overactive nerves
and if a functional medicine doctor
talks about pathogens it came from
medical medium books
and lectures the most advanced
information we have in chronic illness
comes from medical medium books only
you can have the best functional
medicine doctors practice in all their
stuff
the best naturopaths practicing all
their stuff and anything that they
that they talk about that's
microorganisms or comes back to anything
like viral or anything bacterial
comes only for medical medium books
before the medical medium books
and medical medium lectures and
everybody thought
candida was the cause of everything and
that was it
it's actually demented when you think
about it like why does it have to be
spirit of compassion that has to
solve medical mysteries why does it have
to be me at
four years old like you guys read in the
book i wake up one morning
and i'm hearing a voice perfectly clear
that's giving me all this information
like why does it have to go
that route and science research still
can't figure out why everybody's sick
that's why i wish it didn't have to go
that route because i would have had a
really
fun life or a peaceful life right
the symptoms that children and a few
adults in the lyme area started to
experience
chronic fatigue headaches joint pain and
so on were symptoms
that had been seen for decades in every
other town
in that state not to mention every state
throughout the entire country
so lyme disease symptoms were nothing
new
these symptoms children were
experiencing were nothing new it was
just that a few doctors had some
compassion and wanted to look
into it that's all it was they made a
few phone calls
yet somehow in this area around lyme the
illness was treated as something new and
unrecognizable even though everybody
around the world children were suffering
from this
for decades it's most likely because
compassionate doctors were trying to go
above and beyond their role
taking these symptoms more seriously on
a personal level
on a personal level doctors researchers
and townspeople began
looking for a culprit they went looking
for a culprit everybody
and landed on the deer tick they landed
on the deer tick
talk about lyme disease here they landed
you guys just got on well i would i
would advise you guys to
recommend at least to watch it from the
beginning
later on so they landed on the deer tick
because one of the patients reported
seeing a
d a tick a few weeks before he fell
ill that's like a train derailing
the reasons unknown
and a passenger mentioning a deer
he saw grazing 50 miles back
the clues don't add up in either
scenario
even though no one could explain why a
tank would give someone lyme disease
a 17th century style witch hunt began
don't put those two words together
it'll it'll happen based only on a rumor
deer
ticks those two words
that lived on deer became the targets
so what happens you guys
what happens is the deer tick took the
blame
that's what happened it took
the blame right so
it's only because a deer tick
was seen a few weeks back
crawling on someone crawling on someone
and that is how it happened
okay nancy says oh my gosh so ridiculous
yeah so nuts right
so that's how it happened you're dying
here
so am i i'm laughing hard too the new
book is incredible
viola so you guys
that's how it happened so so when we go
back
into history into lime okay where it all
started
and you think about all the science and
research and technology
that we have in medical research and
science that we have
okay when you think about it
right really the conclusions were drawn
from symptoms children were having that
we're having
all around the world in places there
weren't even their ticks
or ticks of any kind not to mention
they only brought the deer tick in
because
one of the families saw a tick
crawling on someone weeks before
you see how how bad all this went how
terrible it all went
that's why research and science also
knows that i blew the ceiling off with
this one because millions
and millions of copies of this book sold
around the world
and doctors learned about it and they
realized
being sensible that research and science
and the
story and how it all happened with lot
in with
lyme disease was all bs yes people were
sick
yes they get sick with neurological
symptoms but it wasn't
really what it seemed to be
so patients reporting seeing a tick a
few weeks before
he fell ill that's like a train
derailing for reasons
unknown and a passenger mentioning a
deer ticky saw grazing 50 miles back
the clues don't add up in either
scenario like i told you guys
so in 1981
so you guys i'm gonna make a sell in a
minute you hang it in there
so i'm doing some reading for you guys
tonight i am i'm at your service
that's my new thing now at your service
of course i want to be at your service
you guys always know that
in 1981 okay
all right a doctor announced he
discovered the missing link
a bacterium named borrelia
that the ticks passed along the humans
through their bites so
he thought he found something he thought
he found a bacteria
that must be passed from a tick to a
human right
1981. it's the missing link
okay he was lauded for his discovery
which led to a series of bacteria focus
tested treatments for lyme disease
it was the perfect out for medical
authorities
we solved your problem you guys your
problems solved
it's all solved it was a tick
bite that's what it was a tick bite
and we found the bacteria um
we everybody only had am radio
everybody had rotary phones on the wall
right no 9-1-1
probably didn't exist right
you had to call the town office to get
an emergency vehicle to your house
or you had to call the police department
number with your rotary phone
but they had the answers for lyme
disease just like they have them now
it was a perfect out for the medical
authorities no one liked ticks anyway
you guys like ticks
you guys like ticks crawling on you do
you guys like when you have a tick
crawling on you
i didn't like seeing those roaches run
across my counter did you see those
roaches run across my counter in the
tick tock video
i'm still still laughing here cracking
myself up no one likes take
ticks anyway and the theory of a
tick-borne
illness fed into the fear of nature
already present in society we hated
ticks everybody hates tickets
medical authorities felt they could give
up on digging for the answer all done
don't have to look for any answers
anymore we figured out it must have been
that little tick
that was you know found on that patient
weeks before they fell ill no other
ticks were found on anybody else but it
must have been that tick
reading out of medical medium new
edition if you guys want to know it's a
mind-blowing book
it's a mind-blowing book amazon.com it's
on sale right now
it's just it's just a mind-blowing book
i can't say it enough
unfortunately all these discoveries were
wrong
they were wrong and wrong
this is what you won't hear anywhere
else lyme disease is not
caused by ticks i broke
the back on that with this book
incredible what happened it freed so
many people
and lyme disease is not caused by
borrelia when the research was taken
place in the 1970s and 1980s you'd
suppose researchers would have realized
the problem was happening nationwide
and globally and today
you think someone would wake up and
realize that hundreds of thousands of
people who have never
been near a deer tick receive lyme
diagnoses
um so i'm gonna start making some food
real quick
guys isn't it interesting i'm just going
into that a little bit right there
um i just don't believe what i'm doing
the chopped salad right now so i'm gonna
start
i'm gonna start getting some lettuce
going can you guys see this
facebook right here facebook live right
now tonight youtube live right there
you guys are awesome let me get some
lettuce in this chopped salad so let me
just
put some lettuce down in here i mean
so i can just run by a couple little
things with you guys is here's what
happens
here's what happened with lyme disease
so because they thought it was bacteria
or it was on purpose to sell billions of
dollars of antibiotics
let's say trillions of dollars of
antibiotics let's just say that how
about that
trillions of dollars of antibiotics okay
let's just say that
worldwide worldwide worldwide right
so
and that's what happened there it was
about selling antibiotics because there
was no treatment for the disease or
condition there's no
there's no treatment now unless
someone's doing an epstein-barr protocol
for medical medium other than that it's
all guesswork
but they had to they had to
sell it because they needed they needed
to sell a drug
for this thing and so they had to say it
was bacterial and they had to say it was
a tick it was the perfect way out
it's the perfect way out so doing a chop
salad here
so what is behind lyme disease xena it's
a viral condition
viruses such as epstein-barr that cause
a lime
they release a neurotoxin that causes
neurological lyme
neurological lyme disease
that neurotoxin affects the nerves
bacteria
can't create a neurotoxin and can't
cause neurological problems
but i can tell you right here the
history of lyme disease is grave
grave so many lives destroyed
see even some podcast doctors out there
and
health gurus out there that gave a lot
of antibiotics during the during the
90s
to their lyme patients put them in bed
forever
lyme disease okay
if you want to say it's bacterial
borrelia and bartonella are not super
bugs you can kill them off with the
mildness of
antibiotics but what happens is the
antibiotics makes lyme patients worse
neurological line worse and worse and
worse and worse
unless you got a doctor now that gives
you just a little bit of a mild
antibiotic so they're not
killing you with the antibiotics and
then they're giving you cat's claw and
all these other supplements
like i've talked about um
the cats call here like i've talked
about not sponsored by the way
the cat's claw from vimergy and i've
been talking about cat's claw for
decades
and so now lyme doctors use cat's claw
their integrative
lyme doctors they use a little bit of
antibiotics and they see that they see
the patient get sicker and sicker and
sicker from the antibiotics so they back
down they get off the antibiotics real
quick and then they start using cat's
claw and natural subs and stuff it's all
medical medium information they're using
now
but they do a blend so that people think
they're not getting killed or
literally losing their lives from their
lyme treatment that that thank god
that's what medical medium information
did it's
literally turned things around so people
don't get killed off
by their medical lime treatment
making a chopped salad
so we got the lettuce let's start
chopping some other stuff you guys
do red bell pepper let's do that
red bell pepper i cut it at the top like
that like you see
i know i showed you these guys guys this
100 times
bartonilla barnella
babesia borrelia get killed off easy
with antibiotics
they're not superbugs mrsa is a superbug
and you can
and the cure rate for mrsa
is is incredible it's better than lime
isn't that funny how's that possible
because lyme disease is viral that's how
it's possible
and viruses create neurotoxins and make
people really sick
viruses such as epstein-barr are the
cause of lyme disease
why do you think now right doctors have
used so much medical medium information
they now test for epstein-barr
every time they actually work with
somebody with lyme disease
what why are you testing for
epstein-barr no one gave a crap about
epstein-barr before
why are you testing for epstein-barr
with everybody who has lyme disease
like why are you doing that you're
testing prep scene bar now
everybody's testing for reactivated
epsine bar you guys reactivated epsom
bars medical medium information nobody
knew it
it reactivate it and now you can go to
your doctor and they'll test you for
reactivated epstein-barr
and just so you know the reactive babies
medical medium information
35 years a lot of work
but remember i'm 28 years old
they're always writing all the articles
and
and hit pieces on me and everything else
and the internet everything
everything everybody has all the
information right
i have it all wrong
morgellons i'm going to talk about more
gel in some day you know what i'll do a
podcast over jones okay
how about that i'll do a podcast on more
jealous i'm gonna cut up some tomatoes
right here you guys let's cut these up
real quick
you can get an infection from a tick
bite
you can get a bad rash from a staph
infection from a
tick bite because the tick can leave a
little particle of its body inside your
arm
okay that little particle is either the
tip of the tick the head
if it's not totally taken out all right
or
a leg of the tick can be left in your
arm
when a foreign body is inside your body
you will start to get an infection and
you'll get an infection on your arm and
that infection will
turn into a really nice staph infection
right there
and yeah if you need an antibiotic for
that i i'm totally on board
totally on board but that's not lyme
disease
can i talk about collagen
absolutely you can't build your collagen
by taking a collagen supplement
can i save you money by telling you that
yeah years worth of bogus collagen
supplements
can only build collagen like medical
medium information has always said and
now that's being stolen out there and
used
influencers are actually talking about
it now uh you can't build collagen
unless you're doing leafy greens
you have medical medium information
leafy greens that's a way to build
collagen
wild blueberries that's the way to build
trace minerals it's a way to build
collagen
let's talk about a way to destroy
collagen do you want your collagen
ruined
do you want your all your collagen to
disappear do you want wrinkles fast you
want skin all saggy and hanging early in
your age
then make sure you keep all your
caffeine products going
if you want to destroy your collagen if
you like it you like your collagen all
ruined and you want
sunspots make sure you have a lot of
chocolate because the caffeine and the
chocolate will age you quick and destroy
your collagen
don't believe me fine stay on all your
chocolate
but that will destroy your collagen
caffeine coffee products
i don't care if it's mushroom coffee
with real coffee in your mushroom coffee
blend i don't care if it's that mlm
thing that's going around now
i don't care if it's the best chocolate
which makes it even worse because it's
more caffeine
i don't care it's gonna it's it's gonna
cause collagen problems collagen damage
another thing that hurts your collagen
is viruses
viral loads releasing viral toxins
dermatoxins epstein-barr
dermadermatoxins that's another thing
right there
you guys how you doing if you just got
on here watch this whole thing
yep chocolate two people michelle
michelle clayton
thanks for saying that on youtube um i
got some beautiful tomatoes here with
these red bell peppers
and i got some butter leaf lettuce
sugar selena what about it
talking about processed sugar i don't
think anybody should be unprocessed
sugar
but sugar is not the problem that's not
why people are sick
sugar's not white people are sick that's
a cucumber you guys
cucumber so sugar is not why people
are sick it's fat that's why people are
sick it's fat
so that's why people get sick all the
fat in their diet
but i don't think anybody should be on
processed sugar i don't think that's
good xenon looks good
on facebook how you guys doing on
youtube
is technology working out okay tonight
you guys see me
i'm skinning this uh cucumber down a
little bit
so what what really hurts collagen is
all the cookies and cakes and
even vegan cookies just fat anything
that's fat
lots of fat and diets you know i'm gonna
have avocado tonight though
but you can overdo it you can eat too
much avocado because it's not avocado
really that's the biggest problem it's
avocados plus too many nut butters plus
too many oils plus milk cheese butter
plus chocolate it's all the fat
and then then things are getting really
out of control and then now your diet's
just fat every day it's like oh my fat i
had fat for breakfast i had peanut
butter smoothie
i had peanut butter on my uh acai bowl i
had
chocolate on my oatmeal i had chocolate
cacao nibs on my oatmeal i'm having all
that fat
um i had oil on my salad i had eggs in
my salad i had tuna in my salads fat fat
fat
we fat ourselves to death that's what we
do it's constantly it's all the time
just lots of fat then
i'm gonna have some bacon too or maybe
pasta with oil maybe cheese
cheese is fat it's just non-stop it's
just constantly fat
everybody's fatting themselves to death
and then it builds up in the heart is
what it does
it always builds up in the heart later
on i don't care who you are yeah you
could live older and not have it
take you down but you can also have it
take you down to 50 years old you're on
your treadmill at 50 years
old you drop dead happens all the time
out there you know
and that fat just builds up and builds
up and builds up
and it gets inside your heart gets
inside the valves gets inside the veins
and the fat just builds up and builds up
and that's a problem all on its own so
it's not sugar's not the problem sugar
doesn't build up in your arteries and
your veins
sugar can't build up in your arteries
and veins it just can't it can't can't
but fat can i like healthy fats hemp
seeds avocados tahini
sesame seeds i like healthy fat but you
can still overdo it if you're sick if
you've got
health problems if you've got some kind
of autoimmune going on if you've got
acne if you've got problems
that's not even going to help even the
good fats
so i got a cucumber right here let me
chop this up i'm going to chop the
cucumber
in half i just want to tell you guys the
book the medical medium book the new
edition you're seeing right here
new edition revise and expand it okay
all right i talk about autoimmune
disease depression anxiety lupus
i talk about ptsd autism i talk about
adhd i talk about gut health problems
um i talk about fatigue chronic fatigue
syndrome fibromyalgia
i mean lyme disease that i'm talking
about now i mean the book is loaded i
talk about colitis i talk about shingles
causing colitis
i talk about menopause menopause
symptoms in here i mean seriously i got
meditations in here
i talk about angels too and i have even
the story about my life talk about
adrenal fatigue that's another thing as
well
the book's so loaded it's so loaded
cutting a cucumber right now
so
cucumber pieces going on top of chopped
salad
i'm going to cut some of these a little
smaller so i have some smaller ones too
there we go
yeah angels kathy got angel's chapter
it's it's mind-blowing so let's talk
about blood draw a little bit
you guys ready for this fashion your
seatbelts i know some of you already
know i've been talking about it already
but just
you might need to sit down for this i
might need to sit down
so when you get your blood drawn the
doctor's office
or at a place you get your blood drawn
or phlebotomist comes to your home some
people get that done that way
um what happens is as they're drawing
your blood
they're removing something from you
that's really important
that shouldn't be removed from you so
and what they're removing from you
is your white count and everybody needs
their white count desperately right now
especially now you guys know why
especially now you need your white count
especially now
so every time you get the blood draw
they take way too much blood than they
should
and they keep on doing it they keep on
doing so when you go back they do it
again when you go back
they do it again or the doctor orders
for more tests and you do it again
if you're chronically ill or chronically
sick
you're gonna get blood drawn from
another specialist or somebody
else but they'll take four vials full
vials they'll take five full vials six
or seven
pretty much on any given day it's six or
seven
sometimes it's ten and in your blood
is your weight count there's your white
blood cell right there
there's your red blood cell right there
yeah your cbc
your cbc your cbc see you later
out the door see you cbc bye cbc
yep six files seven files bye cbc see
you later cbc
um whoa a white blood cell on top of red
red blood cell going out going out now
see you later
and what happens is when you lose your
white blood
count your red blood cells they take a
long time to come back
so after they take your blood it takes
easy 12 weeks for your red count to come
back
your red blood cells will come back you
leave
the doctor's office empty empty
you're still walking you're still
talking they give you some apple
juice maybe maybe they give you a cookie
and
you leave you know they might take 10 14
vials out they might take 18 vials out
but you end up losing your immune system
so if you've got chronic illness of any
kind
you end up you end up
losing precious reserves precious
reserves you need
there's a reason so i'm in the lyme
disease section
which is also a trigger section which is
interesting
triggers to lyme disease and really
triggers to a lot of different
conditions right
so extensive blood draw when a larger
number
of blood vials are drawn
it can be stressful on the immune system
because the very immune
system the very immune defenses that are
keeping the viruses behind
lyme symptoms fibromyalgia hashimoto's
any kind of chronic fatigue syndrome ra
lupus whatever it is
the very immune system that's keeping
the viruses behind that are keeping them
at bay end up being drawn out of the
body so your
white count gets drawn out of the body
when your blood is taken large blood
draws tend to take away a substantial
portion of a person's immune system that
day
and it sometimes takes weeks
to rebuild these portions of the immune
system
within those weeks that the full power
of your immune system is not present
anymore to monitor your blood
you don't have your white count
monitoring your blood like it should
it's not
it's not present viruses can get
a window to strengthen and proliferate
infections can travel from organ organ
with ease because there's no account to
protect you
because they're not being corralled by
your white blood cells it could lead to
flare-up symptoms
more fatigue more problems whether a
week later
a few weeks later or months later i
recommend doing smaller blood draws
over more visits i recommend doing
smaller
blood draws over the more visits
if you're struggling with lyme symptoms
or any other condition
labeled autoimmune so important you guys
so important
i recommend no more than four vials of
blood
at a time and even consider
fewer if it was me i wouldn't even do
four
if you're strong and you feel good maybe
you can do four
a mistake made by well-meaning doctors
is to draw a large number of blood vials
with sensitive people
and i recommend if you're sensitive
to do less so
why is this important because it could
take you down
one of the greatest holes in the medical
system right now which i had to drop the
bomb
i had to let everybody know because it
always starts with medical medium
with the you know these incredible
pieces of information
and it's not me in the end it comes from
my source is that
there's a serious serious crime
happening
and it's a crime of bloodletting where
people are losing their immune systems
to all these blood draws
and if you're sick with chronic illness
and you get five six seven vials taken
away from you
and your immune system leaves and then
your viral issues creep up and you're
getting sicker then guess what the
doctor wants you back into the office
for another blood draw and now it's
another seven eight vials
and then as you get sicker again the
specialist that he recommends for you to
go see wants a whole new blood panel
and they want to see your metabolic
panel they want to see your you know
hormone panel they want to see
everything
and now they want to see a cbc they want
to see all of it and now you're getting
a whole nother round of blood work done
and then you never get out of your
sickness
they keep you in your sickness for years
and years and years
that's how it works lisa says what about
donating blood for blood drives
probably the most dangerous what i would
say is
if you're donating blood for blood
drives see if you can talk to them about
donating less at the time and going back
again if you really want to that's
something you want to do i'm not saying
people shouldn't donate blood we need
we need blood donations but if you're
sick with chronic illness
the person who there should be some some
system changes where
people who donate blood should be the
people who aren't dealing with any
chronic illness you're not dealing with
an
autoimmune label no one with autoimmune
should be donating blood
but people without the autoimmune label
they can donate blood they should be the
ones donating blood so people who
you know are at the top of their game
they're in good health they don't seem
to have any problems they're not
diagnosed with autoimmune they should be
donating the blood
if you know if they choose to
but you know took 30
30 bikes bikes at a time you mean 30
vials at a time
30 biles at a time so
what happens is that um we lose all our
blood
and then that's a scary thing so it's a
hole in the system
a really bad hole in the system where's
your blood going
because here's the problem they only use
this much so
they only use
that much they throw your whole violent
blood away
what i recommend is asking for half
vials that's what i recommend
asking for half files ask your doctor
can you do half files we're going to
take about seven vials
of blood can you do seven half vials
which will end up being around what
three and a half full vials
i would want to keep it if it was me to
two to three vials so you tell the
doctor it's either two to three whole
vials
or two to three half vials one or the
other
now the nurse or the doctor might say
well the blood lab won't receive it or
accept it that's not true the blood lab
will accept it
the doctor just has to send it as half
files and the blood lab takes it and
uses it because the blood lab knows
they only use that much
they throw all your blood away that's
what they do
it's probably the most dangerous
negligent
unreasonable deceiving
disturbing broken part of our system
and when we're dealing with times like
these
on top of it and we're dealing with the
fact that chronic illness is on the rise
to such a degree
it's critical to know how it works and
now i'm not giving you all the
information on blood draw
i'm doing a podcast pretty soon i'm
hoping next week
it comes out is what i'm hoping i'm
doing a podcast on this
and the information is going to blow
your mind wide open it's medical meeting
podcast at apple podcast i'm just
preparing you guys now
that medical medium podcast at apple
podcast that's the uncensored version
because
if you hear it anywhere else at any
other platform it's not going to be
it's going to be censored even though
you're hearing it it's going to be
missing pieces i'm letting you guys know
and they take crazy amounts of blood
from pregnant women can you imagine
how hard that is on the baby
it's just unbelievable and they take
crazy amounts for people who have cancer
so when you have cancer you desperately
need your immune cells you need your
white count when you have cancer
and they take all they take your blood
they take your blood they take your
blood and they take your blood and you
don't even have an immune system because
they're taking so much blood
you ever you know come across somebody
that's
has cancer i mean they're taking all
their blood
and they're not using it they're
throwing it all away
they don't even tell you why don't we
just take a quarter of a vial or a half
file or do a real tiny tube and take
half file they're throwing every bit of
it away except for
the smallest percentage there is
you know what they used to do years ago
i'll just cover this for a couple of
minutes you guys they used to bloodlet
everybody right when you got sick they
would cut your arm open you bled in a
pan and then if you didn't recover they
cut you again if you didn't recover they
cut you again if you got sick or from
bleeding in a pan they cut you again cut
you again
cut you again and then you're dead they
didn't stop bloodletting it's still
happening now but it's under everybody's
noses
they completely fooled everybody every
doctor every nurse they fooled everybody
in the system and they fooled all of you
everybody's fooled i had to drop the
bomb
i'm the only one to do it but i had to
do it
i'm gonna put some green onion on the
salad
i'm not saying don't get your blood
working don't see your doctor i'm pro
doctors i talk to doctors every single
day
i've helped doctors all through the last
30 35 years with their patients
i was known as the bizarre symptom guy
doctor sent people to me
to try to find answers because i was the
detective of all detectives because a
spirit of compassion
and i would find out what's wrong with
people i'm telling you that when you go
get your blood
drawn you got options you tell them to
reschedule another appointment come back
another day and get another two vials
you keep your immune system so you don't
lose it so you have a chance to heal and
you don't
lose your life lose your health or stay
sick
for 20 years as they do regular blood
draws and you stay sick for 20 years
because your immune system can't even
work on cleaning things up so you can
get better
from your epstein-barr shingles hhv-6
cytomegalovirus streptococcus bacteria e
coli
the staff and everything else all right
let's put some avocado on this
guys which avocado should i use did you
ever come across that were you like you
don't know which avocado you want to use
is it this one or this one you know like
some look better than the others
meaning in a sense they look like they
might be tastier
i like the ones that are more firm this
one feels a little
softer i like avocados that are more
firm that's what i like
you guys you guys open avocados probably
all the time right
whoa that's a nice one whoa whoa whoa i
like that
you can squeeze that pit out that's
an option you can do the knife trick
trick right where you hit the knife into
it and then you twist it like that
but you can also squeeze the pit out
right like this
a lot of times it doesn't squeeze out so
you end up crushing your whole
half avocado so you didn't know you can
also spoon it out
a fork you can use a fork to get it out
too right
let's get some avocado pieces in this
salad
so we're youtube live right now we're
facebook live we covered lyme disease a
little bit we're covering blood draw
um we get some avocado in here
so i'm taking some nice beautiful pieces
of avocado and i'm just putting them on
right here
i still got to put a few dates on there
so just bear me bear with me you guys
all right there we go
just want to get some avocado on that
salad
can you see any of that
how i got the avocado pieces right got
the cucumbers got the tomatoes
yeah they draw a lot of a lot of blood
out of pregnant women
it's really sad i'm going to put some
[Music]
some little tiny bit of dulls on the
salads a couple little pieces of dolls
it's really great for toxic heavy metals
getting them out of the body
guys good to have you on youtube if you
missed this
youtube episode please watch it from the
beginning if you can putting little
dolls pieces on here
what can you take for cholesterol it's
getting liver better first is lower the
fats if that was me if i had a
cholesterol problem i'd be lowering the
fats
that's what i would be doing i mean that
you can ask your doctor what you need to
do your doctor can tell you what
whatever how you want to do it but i'm
telling you how i would do it and i
would lower my fats that's just what i
would do
learn how to lower the fats maybe do one
of the medical medium cleanses and
cleanse the heal
maybe get the medical medium
revise and expand it new addition and do
the 28 day cleanse
start changing things around i'm putting
some some dill
chopping up some dill you guys fresh
dill right on to this salad
a little fresh dill
you know what and i got a little parsley
here
i want to put a little parsley on top of
the salad do you guys mind do you like
parsley are you okay with parsley
our piece is loving your content i'm
honored truly
i hope you didn't miss you're always
you're always going to get
um unique original content here that's
life-saving
that has a history of getting out there
and then people
they run with it they take it meaning
like the industry takes it
some people cite it back some people
don't but you wouldn't believe the list
the exhaustive list i can give you a
huge list of all the medical medium
informational uh accomplishments that
have changed health in the last 30 years
it would blow your mind you'd be like he
started that
what he started that what wait a minute
he started that what
i'm gonna have like a show on it and
talk about that
just so people know what happened
it's unbelievable really i mean the list
is just
it's unbelievable but the information
starts here with chronic illness as far
as
information that's classic timeless and
has saved lives
so you guys i got a couple of dates here
so i'm gonna chop up a couple dates
what am i gonna do
you're in my kitchen right now medical
medium
thank you for sharing the information
deb it's to protect you
totally it's it's to protect you yep
it's critical to know what they're doing
and how the system's broken
somebody at the top knows they know
they're taking your blood from you
and they know it weakens everybody and
they know it can even lead to an early
death
with your illness
it's about being proactive telling your
doctor to take less blood
tell them to take half vials and you
know what that will change the entire
system you know there'll be less less
deaths
worldwide when that happens
they drain your blood they take your
immune system you get sicker and sicker
and then you die sooner than you should
that's what they do and if you're strong
and you're young you can keep on getting
your hormones checked and keep on
getting your blood tested
and keep on playing the game when you're
got resilience and everything but
eventually catches up to you and at
least can give you chronic illness
cause the immune system cause the immune
system to break down
and you can get your your chronic
illness and your autoimmune putting a
little dates on here
takes years off your life is what it
does the blood draws that are happening
is taking years off of everybody's life
you know those people that live to be 95
years old nobody knows why or how or
what one of the reasons is they didn't
catch a lot of bugs
had one of those lives where they didn't
get a lot of different viruses bacteria
the other reason
is they didn't go to the doctor because
they weren't getting sick to begin with
to get them to the doctor
they took less blood draws a lot you
know i've known so many older people
they're like i don't get blood taken
from me
but now i am i'm kind of sick i'm 89 i'm
getting a lot of blood taken from me i
hate them
damn vampires
so i'm going to squeeze some orange on
here
this is a red orange
all right i'm gonna squeeze a little and
then we're good
this salad is so good you guys i am so
pumped
i hope you had fun tonight we covered a
lot of good stuff
thank you for sharing the truth with us
you're amazing thanks trisha murray
you're awesome you know that on day
seven lillian of the 369 on facebook
michelle l says old people fear
hospitals yeah the blood let them to
death
give them a quick death always have fun
watching the videos i saw that on
youtube
always been uh fun spending time
you guys are awesome i'm heading to tick
tock at the same time as ig
and i think i'm gonna nibble on a little
bit of salad for two minutes before i go
on
and i think i'm gonna get fired up
because
i don't know i think there's a lot of
cool stuff to say i don't think i said
it all
so we got to go to instagram
and tick tock live which one do you guys
want to come with me and remember if you
go to instagram if you get kicked off
because there's a glitch
go to tick tock live catch me there
i love you guys i really do