they have chronic illness they think
that one or two symptoms that they're
having chronically isn't an illness of
any kind because maybe it did not make
them bedridden maybe they're in a place
where their symptoms aren't setting them
back maybe they're in a place where
their symptoms aren't
stopping them from working and being
productive maybe they're in a place
where their symptoms they just push
through they're not really in the way
but when it gets to a point where your
symptoms get worse and worse how about
you like have you ever experienced this
where you have the fatigue and the brain
fog
and the acne and the body pain and all
kinds of other symptoms with it the
dizziness or the vertigo or the tinnitus
and then it's getting to a point where
more fatigue more brain fog and you're
visiting doctors and you're getting
blood drawn left and right and now
you're just declining and declining
chronic illness right that's where
people think well then maybe that's a
chronic illness but no it's not just
that it is any symptom that is
persisting that's not going away that's
just staying there day after day or
intermittent where it's like it's here
for a little while then a week later
it's gone it's here for a little while
then a week later it's gone
but chronic illness is all of that
good to see you guys
q a we're just
we're talking about symptoms conditions
that's why I'm here you see I got the
books in front of me by the way vimorgy
has a sale going on right now then
Reggie these in Victor i m is the Mary e
r g y did you ever
did you ever know something know
something
that you know could change somebody's
life
did you ever have that happen where you
know a piece of information you know
something that can change somebody's
life but they don't know it they have no
idea but if they only knew
if they only knew good to see you guys
too I'm going to tell you something
about propolis something I take every
day
I don't know if you guys experienced
this but the sad thing is how many
people in the world who are chronically
sick have not a clue or no idea that
this stuff exists right here not just
talking about any propolis but the
vemergy one right they don't have a clue
people who are struggling with all kinds
of symptoms if they only knew
what this was that's in my hand right
now I mean if they only knew and it
pains me it pains me
Sienna Lions just took advantage of the
Bemidji sale and got extra B12 and
goldenseal incredible
this golden golden
incredible what I call medicine it's
medicinal
this golden medicinal propolis right
there
no additives no [ __ ] put in here
nothing
polytheanols are sustaining themselves
in here natural quercetin that's in this
propolis all intact right there you guys
know I endorse them memory G and
and dang right I do it's the best stuff
I've ever seen anywhere but this
glistening golden Jewel this is the
immune system
builder in my opinion of like all time
and people have just they just don't
know and all the crap I see out there if
people only knew
the right tools
the right kind of tools if they only
knew and that's the sad part because
most people will never know no one so
many people out there will never know
what this is right here and what is in
my hand they will never know and and
that's the sad part right there it
really is but anyway I'm just showing
you guys this is just incredible stuff
of course
um I dripped it right there all over the
place but that's fine
that's why we're live
and said it'd be like oh let's edit that
cut the video now edit it can't look
like a fool you guys were doing symptoms
conditions
q a chronic illness q a that's what
we're doing Vitiligo right there I don't
know if you read in the medical medium
books about vitiligo
I think cleanse the heel cleanse the
heel where have you been
you've saved thousands upon thousands of
lives in fact hundreds of thousands of
lives in fact even over a million lives
out there in the world with your blessed
knowledge cleanse the heel the
monocleanse the morning cleanse the 369s
the protocols you name it that is
cleanse the heel right there
love freaking love that book
um you got that book Incredible
tinnitus
tinnitus right so we'll talk about
tonight for a second little lie though
something we can talk about too
villago is a combination of the
Epstein-Barr virus inside the liver
okay this is important
feeding off of
toxic heavy metals like aluminum
releasing
a neurotoxin
that neurotoxin damages the melon in the
pigment
in the skin
creates
vitiligo
Liver Rescue
cleanse the heel both these but there's
Liver Rescue cleans the heel right there
talk about vitiligo
detail
so you have to understand
inside the liver
lives a bug
the bugs happy happy is a clam inside
the liver feeding off of garbage and
[ __ ] and junk and junk and garbage
feeding on all that toxic crap and then
it runs across a Wellspring of aluminum
that Wellspring of aluminum
feeds the bug the virus the virus eats
it eats it eats it then it shits and
pisses that toxin out and that toxin is
a dermatoxin that dermatoxin is lethal
to pigment
and that's how you end up getting all
the white spots in the middle eye going
it starts going crazy Linden Forrester
propolis have done at least five to
seven bottles and I just keep getting it
getting in a better place and the sad
thing is people don't know this Linden
over there on YouTube
uh four times a day you're saying
incredible
that's amazing
Pure Living on I jesus how often you
take propolis
do what your doctor says but I take it
by three times a day
I take it I don't have an illness and I
take it three times a day
right
that's what I do do what's right for you
your doctor and everything else
but it's it breaks my heart saddens me
when people don't know what is in my
hand it's like having an answer having
something that's so valuable but
nobody's gonna know
it's like okay it's just it's painful
uh Nivea green Navy green good to see
you on here on IG I give it to my kids
also amazing that is so good to hear so
good to hear
so anyway I just want to tell you that
can you please explain why Bemidji is so
much better okay the four things really
quick you guys just bear with me for a
second we're going to talk about
symptoms conditions I'm here I'm here to
help I want to go through stuff with you
guys
four reasons why energy is better you
know how you hear high quality or
quality good quality
and supplements are like good quality we
got the quality control no there's
different levels of quality there's
different tiers vmrt they do something
no one else does they go to the top tier
where no one wants to spend their money
and supplement companies don't want to
spend their money they don't want that
option you can get like for instance
just ashwagandha you can get
um okay you can get a good quality
ashwagandha you can get another good
quality ashwagandha you can get another
good quality ashwagandha you get another
good quality
but they're not as good as the quality
at the top and you keep on climbing up
right the bottom quality is not as good
as the top quality this is so important
to say memory goes to The toppest
quality and the tapest quality is
expensive and some little companies
won't do that they don't need to they'll
just buy
you know ashwagandha put it in their
supplement and Bank on the bottom line
right remember she says no we won't do
that this is huge huge Bemidji goes and
asks for the highest quality and if they
don't have the highest quality of energy
we'll go and find it somehow no one does
that
that's one thing let's go to another
thing ready no alcohol no natural
flavors no citric acid no
titanium dioxide no all that junk no
gluten obviously no soy but better than
that they knew better at the start not
to put natural flavors natural Berry
flavor which is all MSG they knew not to
put any of the flavors in this stuff so
you know what other supplement companies
will try to copy them and they'll leave
out natural flavors I can actually
mention one that's actually out there
like yeah man ours is the best yeah dude
you had natural flavors in yours and
citric acid in yours forever until you
copied themergy so
they're the only ones though it has none
of all that stuff in there none right so
that's that's the next thing so let's go
to the part three which is incredible
into three points okay
they don't put hidden stuff supplement
companies are allowed to legally keep a
secret from you guys they're allowed to
legally put a certain percentage of
hidden ingredients in your
supplementation and I can guarantee you
if you're doing other supplements out
there you're eating hidden ingredients I
can freaking guarantee that
will not put that undisclosed hidden
ingredient in their supplements dude you
can't get that and I don't care who it
is they're all putting in binders anti
whatever or binding agents they're
putting all kinds of stuff in there
that's how insane that is that sounds
insane
and so these alone are reasons why and
the list goes on there's so many other
reasons too I could talk about it but
I didn't want to make it about this I
just I want to talk about symptoms
conditions I want to talk about tinnitus
next we'll go into that we'll go we'll
dig into the book right
take advantage of the sale while it's
happening though okay so vimergy.com
these in Victor I am as Mary
ergy.com all right because people ask me
about when they're having a sale over
and over again how many DMs I get about
that it's insane they're having a sale
now but like I said even more than that
it's what this is right here that I
think
so many people will never have an
opportunity to understand or experience
it or to know how it moves the needle
they will never ever experience that
but what is in my hand is something
extremely special
and I live by that propolis right there
How It's Made has specific bees they use
everything
it is no joke no joke anyway all right
let's cook
let's cook with pork
no and don't you pork don't do pork
unless your doctor's telling you to do
pork don't get don't go against your
doctor's advice your doctor wants to do
work
um skin says skin Couture says what's
the best thing for migraines so it's all
about like learning about why you have a
migraine so let's go in here medical
medium new addition right here
let's just hit migraines for a second
I'm all over the place come on
what is going on here
let's find out where you are
I'm gonna put this up here too
and I'll show you what this is you guys
so you even know right
so that's the propolis pure so you guys
can see this
that's it right there because I saw it
somebody actually saying like what are
you even talking about
that's the purpose if you're from
Bemidji there's nothing like it out
there
I can't even tell you
honestly the stuff I want to say about
it is off the charts
and
I mean the things I want to say about it
like for real
all right so I just want to get to the
migraines part migraines can be a lot of
things keep that in mind people need to
know migraines are neurological one way
or another migraines are neurological
page 123
right here
my migraine section so let's cut into it
for a little bit
I'm at your disposal I am at your
service
please have patience for me
okay if you can
large part of the global population
suffers from migraines or reoccurring
headaches Bavarian type types some
people experience migraines in the back
of their head except where you get it
right here begin the back of your head
if you get migraines back here
because I know a lot of people
throughout the years they get the
migraines back here
back of the head
some at the temple do you get the
migraines here by the way
on the temple where where are your
headaches it's what I want to know where
are yours some on the top of the head
who gets the headaches on the top of the
head
top of the brain
right
cranial
who gets those top of the head how about
behind the eyes you guys get the
migraines behind the eyes which ones do
you get
that's what I'd like to know which ones
do you like
nevy green said you scared me now with
the pork
you're eating pork
all right migraines can also be
experienced as intense pulsing or
throbbing focused on one side you can
have that throbbing intense pain right
migraines can feel like it takes over
the person's entire head and neck do you
get the migraines where it's your whole
head and your neck
you guys actually get those kinds of
migraines just wondering
the majority of migraine sufferers are
women
at any age even children migraines can
make life very difficult to navigate
those familiar with migraines know well
that the pain may be accompanied by
extreme sensitivity to light or sound
or smell blurry vision seeing flashes of
light nausea or vomiting difficulty
speaking lightheadedness lightheadedness
that can result in fainting spells a
migraine can last anywhere from a couple
of hours to several days how many people
get it for several days they get the
migraines
and it may rob you of the desire to do
anything but lie down in the dark
in a quiet room until it's over
so let's talk about it a little bit
The Usual Suspects right here
let's get into that
okay there are certain conditions that
are well known for creating migraine
symptoms concussion
right
meningitis stroke
Tia
brain aneurysm brain tumor brain sister
microcyst impeded cervical nerves those
are things that medicine can find things
that many times
MRIs can find many times doctors
Specialists can help patients find find
and but if your migraines are not caused
by those and you're just dealing with
migraines
then we got some other stuff going down
this is about making you an expert of
your own health having this incredible
information comes from above
if you've gone through the battery of
tests reviewed your medical history
with your doctors and rolled out the
elements on the list above then you're
in the mystery realm if you hear me
yelling
because some people are like I can't
hear you speak louder
what follows are explanations of
migraine triggers that medical
communities don't fully yet understand
unless they stole it poached it taken it
from the medical medium books
long ago along with triggers that I'm
disclosing Here For the First Time
Epstein-Barr virus and shingles doctors
don't know that millions of people
suffer from migraines as a result from
Epstein-Barr virus or even a shingles
virus
and I go into that alternatively
shingles can inflame your trigeminal or
phrenic nerves which go into it a little
bit so trigeminal and phrenic nerves
herpes simplex one the virus behind the
common fever blister
the virus behind the common fever
blister
I don't know what I'm doing I'm just
pointing to something
I don't know what I'm pointing to
my arm just won't stop pointing stop arm
stop stop pointing stop stop playing
it's funny herpes simplex one
the virus behind the common fever
blister can also Nest within the
trigeminal and phrenic nerves elevating
their inflammation ever so slightly just
enough to be a trigger
to learn if you're being afflicted by
the Epstein-Barr virus read these books
this one's incredible all on its own
okay
here's another one for migraines that
people don't know about micro Tia attack
and Trigger micro tias it's a big one
right there people have no idea they
have let's just go into the sinus
related migraines
some migraines stem from chronic
streptococcal infections that sit in the
Linings of the sinus cavity
strep sitting in the line line I'm sorry
sitting in the sinus cavity linings
craving headaches all the time for
people chronic strep creating chronic
headaches chronic strep creating chronic
migraines oh it's just allergies
allergies
I just
got a strep infection it never goes away
that nobody knows about
right there
show this is book one there's protocols
in here
you can take a look at these protocols
they're incredible so it's not just
information there's protocols in this
book this is medical medium new edition
book one
some migraines stem from streptococcal
and these K in these cases ears nose and
throat specialists offer often recommend
sinus surgery to remove scar tissue
because they don't know it but strep is
difficult to remove they don't know
that's why they're doing it people get
scar tissue removed out of their sinuses
surgeries
out of the sinus Linings but then it
comes back again because they had strep
this whole time
if these surgical procedures work at all
then the relief they gave patients is
only temporarily until the strep comes
back a better way to address sinus
related migraines is to strengthen the
immune system so that the body can
naturally fight infection
um okay over there on uh Instagram my
brain was the first thing that's gone
after following your diet thank you so
much God bless you
my choice of foods good handle great
handle
all right so let's move it into a little
bit of other permeability trigger that's
really cool
while blueberry dreams says on IG I used
to get chronic sinus infections and was
on antibiotics twice a year until I
found medical medium information no
doctors could help me now I haven't had
one since starting medical medium it was
the strep all along
incredible
[Music]
another major migraine culprit is
burning gut
medical communities don't know that when
your digestive system isn't working
properly ammonia gas can drift out from
your gut to your vagus and phrenic nerve
and trigeminal nerves ammonia can cross
the blood-brain barrier and find its way
into all parts of the central nervous
system
as the gas deprives the brain of some of
its needed oxygen tension can arise and
you end up going into spasm and you're
in a migraine so it's ammonia
permeability
medical meme information by the way and
I see somebody stealing it out there a
couple of people stealing the whole
ammonia thing and now you see
influencers like ammonia
yeah it's like yeah yeah okay you got it
from the medical mean books and then
you'll see a couple of bigger
influencers with their stuff trying to
sell their stuff like yeah ammonia
permeability in your liver and your HCL
it's like dude you never spoke like that
that's mm info
ammonia gas
all right let's move on there's tons of
info here just talked about migraines
and triggers let's see what we can do
electrolyte deficiency trigger
boom to remain healthy your body must
maintain a certain level of electrolytes
these electrolytes are used to maintain
neurotransmitter strengthened neurons
and send the electrical nerve impulses
that run your body and your brain
so here's the thing
people are they don't have the
electrolytes needed to sustain what
they're up against the stress are up
against
lots of things in their life they're up
their current diet all of it though and
they don't have that so that's another
section there stress I talk about how
that happens
menstrual cycle trigger
for migraines that's incredible
information right here menstrual cycle
triggered
can we run into that for a little bit
let's go
many female migraine sufferers notice
that their migraines come on right
before during or after their menstrual
cycle because when the menstrual cycle
happens the immune system drops
and when a woman's immune system drops
men don't have to go through the
menstrual cycle so their immune system
doesn't get
challenge
at all it doesn't get challenged at all
when a woman's going through
menstruation menstrual cycle the immune
system is focused on the reproductive
system leaving
all these other places alone without an
immune system and so streptococcus
Epstein-Barr other impedements toxic
heavy metals whatever it is
can easily bring on that
that headache
the Divine Lilith says can you also
explain why hot weather triggers
migraines
expansion of nerves nerve tissues
so hot weather
creates swelling if you have any
inflammation you're going to feel it
like no other
so you're going to see one person it's
like I love hot weather
I really love hot weather I could best I
could bask in it all day long I could
lay out in the sun I don't care how
humid it is I can work in the garden I
could go out and shop I can do all kinds
of things in the hot weather you've got
another person that's suffering in the
hot weather they feel so sticky and
swollen and don't feel good and they're
swelling internally and the heat also
puts pressure on the nerves there's a
combination of all that the same goes
with really really cold weather it's
hard for somebody too who's struggling
for a lot of reasons
Barbara Carbone on YouTube yeah the
propolis is good for immune system
definitely you guys if you just got on
here I was talking about how I wish
people knew what this was in my hand I'm
not insulting anybody I'm not saying
that they don't know what propolis is or
ever heard a propolis that's not it so
if you're somebody and you're like well
he's insulting me because he doesn't
think I don't know I've never heard
about propolis that's not it this
product propolis pure what it is and it
people only knew what was in my hand the
quality the the process of how this is
even made and how incredible it is and
how I live by this look live by this
propolis
anyway Germany has a sale you guys don't
endorse these guys
um but I the reason why I endorse these
guys is because stuff like this
stuff like that
that's why huge huge reason
okay so let's move into some other stuff
someone was talking about tinnitus
tinnitus you can you can get tinnitus
information all through these books
and here's the thing you guys
I don't want to see this disappear
it would be
a sin
a true sin
if this disappeared if the company
didn't make it anymore if this wasn't
available anymore
it would be
devastating
because people
it's an opportunity
for good health and people don't know
this but yeah it's just anyway so
um
anyway Bemidji vimergy.com these and
Victor I am as in Mary e r g y.com
uh their their customer services unlike
any other and propolis
p-r-o-p-o-l-i-s this is propolis pure
I'm gonna hit tinnitus because I I
bypassed it earlier
so I'm in medical medium right here book
one New Edition
I'm assuming you have the books but you
may not have the books you may not have
this book
no hard feelings you don't have to have
the book so I'm just looking through
here
this isn't this an amazing book right
I mean you can well I have tinnitus
inside medical medium book one I have
tinnitus in brain saver as well
we can we can go to either book but I'm
looking here well
um and I wanna I wanna read about it a
little bit too
let me see
I could also read about it in brain
saver too
these are medical textbooks
if you have these you know how hard this
hard is I mean there's so much
information it takes a second is what I
mean
that's not one of these thin books these
thin paperback books these you know
there's not much in there there's just
some weird marketing plan in there along
with some Diet that's trying to be
trendy you know that's not what this
stuff is
Robin over there on YouTube why do
symptoms get worse before they get
better while healing
so why do symptoms get worse before
getting better while healing okay
a lot of people it goes like this
your healing you go three steps up two
steps back three steps up two steps back
three steps up and you get stronger and
stronger and stronger right
a lot of people
okay
they start taking advantage of their
healing so they start doing more than
they have in six months more than they
have in a year
and they push themselves kind of off the
cliff
because they're getting better and
they're able to do more I can't tell you
how many people are they're starting to
heal and they want to go back to life
the way it was
when they weren't sick many years ago
and they just start doing all kinds of
stuff
physically emotionally mentally and they
get a setback because they went
all of a sudden went into full speed in
life because they were like woohoo
I'm getting better and they got full
speed so there's a bunch of them that
are out there it happens
and then there's a group of people too
that get exposed but don't even know it
they're working on their healing process
they're doing good and then they get set
back because they got exposed to
something something somewhere don't even
realize it
and they're set back for a little while
because of it maybe they're taking
something that's tough maybe they're
taking charcoal which is really toxic
maybe they're taking you know sodium
bicarbonate maybe they're doing apple
cider vinegar maybe they're doing
something and finally it tips the scale
and it sends them backwards so I'm just
giving you a few options maybe they're
doing the alkaline ionizer water
machines which literally is destructive
to it just sets people back maybe
they're doing something that's setting
them back maybe they're doing the Rife
machine which will set people back
so
um so that's the whole thing too people
that had bad symptoms coming on already
and by the time they started working on
healing they was already coming on so
there's that group of people too let's
hit that for a second there's a bunch of
people that we're going to get so darn
sick it was heading there and they
started working under healing process
when they were already going downhill
fast
and as they started the healing process
it could not catch up to it enough to
bring it back do you guys know what I'm
saying this is huge right here they
couldn't get enough done with their
healing process in enough time to stop
the bleed and literally
send themselves backwards to stop it
right
instead they were going down anyway
it's like
[ __ ] I'm getting sick I better try this
I better try that I'm getting sicker
they're just going down anyway and it's
going to take time for them to do the
right things to do the right protocols
and heal and climb back up because they
were already heading down there boom
they're already going down
there's that group of people
and then there's a group of people that
aren't doing what they need to do
they're dabbling they're inter mixing
things they're doing sodium bicarbonate
tearing up their intestinal tract
weakening their immune system while
doing celery juice and something else
they're doing charcoal and fish oil and
probiotics that are probably a toxic
variety versus
doing enough of the other things
right they're getting blood drawn they
think they're working on their healing
process and then they just had five more
blood uh vials of drawn they're working
under healing process and I know I
showed you this before but I have to
show you again because I think it's
important
so
and they get five more vials four more
vials
10 more vials
they're working on their healing process
and they just had 15 vials of blood
drawn from a specialist and then a month
later they tank and they're like what is
going wrong I'm working on my healing
process I'm doing the heavy metal detox
I'm doing the celery juice I'm watching
now I'm not eating the pork I'm not
eating the you know the tuna I'm not the
Mercury and the tuna I'm not eating the
cheese I'm not eating the eggs
and they go downhill because they just
had 10 vials of blood drawn and their
immune system was removed and their
immune system was cleaning up the mess
trying to keep them healthy there's that
group of people and there's a ton of
those people a ton of those people
and then there's those people that get a
bad medical treatment it just happens
boom now it's about fighting
to stay alive or fighting to get better
another another group of people get food
poisoning they should get food poisoning
there's a whole food poisonings every
day it's out there rampant out there
and there's you know and that's another
thing too they get food poisoning or
something it triggers off their
pathogens or they get a bad medical
treatment or something else
relationships uh um mental emotional
abuse a loss and that lowers their
immune system either way people are up
against a lot of different things think
about how many different triggers there
are I'm giving you a lot of different
scenarios but that's how many there are
because people in their lives and what
they're doing there's a lot of things
going on
so I don't know if I've given you 10
scenarios really common or whatever five
scenarios that are really common but
that's what happens with people as
they're trying to heal
and just quick reiteration here
there's that person who's healing but
wants to now go back to life 100 and
jump into something and just go full
force and they get beaten down
I mean there's just there's so many
that's just one out of so many I just
gave you and I could reiterate the rest
of them but I think you guys got the
point and I'm missing some too
I'm actually missing some I know I'm
missing a few that's how many things
tinnitus
said there for a little bit
when decibel damage has been rolled out
you haven't been to a lot of rock
concerts you don't play the bass super
loud
you're not somebody that's working
around construction and stuff like that
and you haven't worked around heavy
machinery for many years worked in the
music industry around live concerts or
had physical injury to the ear where
something happens here here and it was a
physical slam and hit
right and then when you receive a
tinnitus diagnosis because you have
ringing or humming in the ear you're
someone who's living with something else
than if you weren't injured if it wasn't
something like that when you were
injured it was an obvious thing you were
in the music industry you were in the
construction industry you had a reason
to have decibel damage in the inner ear
and this little bones in the air right
nerve damage and so forth if you don't
have any of that and that's not
happening
you're talking about viral inflammation
now we're talking about viral
inflammation
tinnitus you guys say tinnitus or do you
say tinnitus
tinnitus someone said tinnitus the other
day and I was like huh what that's right
tinnitus what tinnitus tinnitus doesn't
have to be ringing in the ear it could
be humming buzzing vibrating popping
fluttering crackling is yours crackling
is your fluttering is yours buzzing is
yours humming is yours wishing is there
a wishing in here whoa whooshing
w-h-o-o-s-h-i-n-g whooshing
when someone has the high-pitched
ringing in the ear
[Music]
right the high [ __ ] see if I can get
higher than that I don't think I can
higher than that it can change and alter
and dance about when a fan or an air
conditioner is on it's like
right
all right
let's see
when someone has the high-pitched
ringing near it's not funny if they do
I'm just for some reason cracking myself
up
um can we edit that out no we can't
because we're live
when someone has that high-pitched
ringing in the ear it can change alter
and dance about what a fan or air
conditioner is on or when music is
playing some people experiencing the
experience with sounds like air rushing
through their ear
some people experiencing popping
like they're they're popping popcorn in
their ear tinnitus can vary from mild to
extreme often people get small moments
when they hear a ringing in their ear
and then it goes away like
is somebody talking about me I think
somebody honey is somebody talking about
me
is my friend talking about me
right is that an angel that was speaking
in my ear my ear rang is that a spirit
guide like what is that ringing the ear
this has been passed off as someone
speaking about you or Angelic forces are
speaking to you what most of these
people and you'll see what most this is
important this is why the words in the
medical medium books are so they're
detailed in their meaning
they're detailed in their understanding
this is incredible information right
I just said this has been passed off
as someone speaking about you when your
ear rings or Angelic forces are speaking
to you if you get a temporary like quick
earring
what most of these people why did I say
most
because it's possible
that an angel
is communicating it's possible that
someone is talking about you it is and
it's possible that could actually create
some frequency to your ear
but what most of these people who
experience passing tinnitus discovers
that eventually the ringing sticks
around a little longer and a little
longer and a little longer and a little
longer and then permanent Boop
and the whole time I thought someone was
just talking about me when it was
intermittent
and the whole time I thought it was an
angel trying to communicate because it
was intermittent once in a blue moon I
got a little ringing in the air but now
five years later hot damn I got tinnitus
it's ringing all the time
they get to a point where they're past
the whole phase of it must be a ghost or
a spirit or an angel or someone talking
about me and they realize they're
developing a condition
sometimes it takes years of intermittent
ringing in the ears to be diagnosed with
tinnitus many times hearing loss can
occur with tinnitus because the ringing
is so dominant in many situations even
if the ringing isn't dominating hearing
can also be lost I've seen bar is the
number one reason why people have
mystery tinnitus I talk about how it
occurs yes I'm just trying to cut
through some of this
yep
Lorraine now says mine is like a random
movement in my left ear but has improved
lately
good good if your body's healing
and you're doing things to heal your
body they're really powerful
other things are in the works of healing
and sometimes some symptoms are left
high and dry for a while
important critical piece of information
for anybody who's got chronic illness
here
anybody you know who has chronic illness
Dr fine good to see you
MD
this is critical to know
when your body's healing your immune
system is taking care of business
if it's given the tools it needs
especially it's taking care of business
if it's given tools it needs especially
it's taking care of business right
and when your immune system is taking
care of business
it's working on things you may not even
know exist inside your body that are
symptom or it's working on two or three
symptoms and problems and sometimes some
symptoms are going to be left alone for
a while and high and dry or your immune
system is fixing the problem fixing the
ear ringing issue but the nerve has been
injured by the Epstein-Barr virus and so
now the Epstein-Barr virus is gone
out of the ear
because your immune system gobbled it up
and your protocols killed it off
but then you still got some tinnitus
left over because the nerve channel has
to heal the Damage Done to the nerve
channel the inflammation that damaged
the nerve channel from the virus has to
heal so now it could take a long time
for the body to repair repair the damage
and what if you don't know the medical
medium information good enough and you
don't know other tools to use within it
to repair damaged nerves so that's
another reason why it takes longer for
some people to heal because there's it's
in here the secret sauce is in here in
these books
so yeah
all right
keep on rolling
we're rolling
okay anyway the protocol for tinnitus is
inside brain saver protocol so I just
want to get to that to the moment there
it is what's that brainstorm circles
juggling some books around right now
there it is
so
I got a surprise coming up for you guys
not going to say anything right now
because I just have to make sure it's
actually happening but I got a surprise
that's gonna be cool
it's gonna be something fun we could all
do together
that is
incredibly life changing
some of you are familiar with it already
and may have partaken in it in the
medical medium book series but I want to
do this with you guys
and so I'm gonna be making an
announcement coming up I'm hoping I'm
hope
I'm hope I just got my team working hard
on it
I got
things in the works but I can't wait to
announce it I'm hoping because it's
gonna be so powerful
life-changing emotionally
spiritually life-changing and it's
coming up stay tuned stay tuned to the
medical meme newsletter you don't want
to miss this you don't want to miss this
seriously
today
we were working on it trying to make it
happen
in some so I want to talk about this for
a second in some instances there is die
off from pathogens that people feel
you need to have a decent High viral
load
right and I see a lot of people out
there that have
um they don't really know what's
happening they don't know they're really
having a die off they don't know
what's going on so that's something two
I saw a question pop up about die off
if someone is extremely
viral
right
and people overuse the word detox so
we're back on detox a little bit
because I've been working on this detox
podcast episode that eventually want to
get out to you guys I'm just I'm not
done with it but
and you're gonna need some patience for
that one because that one ain't no one
hour podcast episode that one is gonna
be like a three hour I don't know like
it's insane
so because anyway but the word detox is
so abused and so misused
and I told you the last time we did
write this get-together right here in
the Q a
it's so misused
because people don't know why people are
sick and they don't know what's going on
inside their body so it's the perfect
out for a lot of people too oh you're
detoxing oh you're getting much sicker
and sicker sicker oh you're detoxing
right and so and then the whole detox
pathway thing oh you just don't know
about the detox Pathways that you don't
know about the detox Pathways either
like you'll hear that out there
but people have to understand that
it all depends
like you won't you'll rarely ever hear
me use the word detox because I use the
word cleansing because what you're
really doing is you're cleansing out
those impurities
and you're doing it in a way that you
can feel the least amount of symptoms if
it's done properly and correctly and
medical medium information does that
because it's not man-made
it's not like someone's saying take this
take this I Got Dirt in here and I got
geophobic in here and I got and I got
probiotics in here and I got you know I
got bentonite clay in here I got clay in
here and I even threw a little bit of
Ayahuasca in here for emotional detox go
ahead and take that down oh you're sick
oh you're detoxing that's why we're sick
from drinking that you're detoxing
there's so much stupidity out there
it's it's incredible so the whole point
is is that is detox is thrown around as
if it's just like this answer to
everything no one understands and that's
the sad part about detox but if you're
really toxic in the sense where you're
high viral load
you're loaded with poisons and toxins in
a sluggish stagnant liver
if you do like protocols right cleansing
right
you might get some lethargy
and I talk about that symptoms in the
medical medium books
but you're not going to get so sick and
develop all of a sudden some crazy rash
or some other thing that's
because you were getting sick you were
actually getting sick people don't
realize they got a lot going on inside
of them they're already heading to a
place where they're getting sick they're
already been sick
and it's ketchup time and it's hard to
catch up with a lot of people fast
instant and overnight
so that's a whole nother point that I
didn't mention the other day
here's something you never want to
forget
and I've seen this information used
and it's not correct
right is
the medical medium cleanses are hard on
the adrenals they're not hard on the
adrenals that's misinformation what is
hard on the adrenals
is water fasting
I'm not against and I talked about this
short term
short-term water fast if necessary
for crises I've talked about that in the
medical mean books but water fasting
hard on these renals
straight juice fasting only hard on the
adrenals
not getting enough calories
okay is hard on the adrenals that's why
medical medium information has the
adrenal stacks
that's why eating regularly
is critical to sustain the adrenals
that's why medical medium cleanses don't
take away food
because you take away food completely
from somebody
especially for so many reasons and boom
that's hard on the adrenals
so medical medium cleanses are designed
from above
to protect the adrenals that's the whole
point to protect
the adrenals
and it's critical to know that
chocolate
destroys adrenals
cacao hurts the adrenals caffeine hurts
the adrenals
Ayahuasca destroys and annihilates the
adrenals
I'm just saying these are some things
right there okay
high doses of apple cider vinegar hurt
the adrenals by burning out the stomach
glands and into and and in turn killing
off your HCL which makes your adrenals
work harder like there's so many things
that injure adrenals Every Day High high
fat diets every single day hurt the
adrenals
betrayal hurts the adrenals
emotional losses hurt the adrenals being
stabbed in the back hurts the adrenals
being emotionally triggered hurts the
adrenals
so
these are all important things to
understand MSG hurts the adrenals
MSG
hurt so these are all important things
to know because what you'll see out
there you'll say oh 369 cleanse it's too
much on my it's too much in your
adrenals it's designed to protect your
adrenals restore that
so when I hear this this is a little
tough
a little tough
the monocleanse restores someone's
damaged and burnt outage renals the 369
protects and restores adrenals it's a
big part of how someone recovers the
heavy metal detox cleanses helps restore
adrenals they're adrenal Savers adrenal
restorers
bring your backers
but somebody might feel high and happy
for a bit when they start tanking fats
again where was where was this my whole
life I was on the 369 for two months and
I was just feeling lethargic
what you're doing is you were healing
deep deep deep inner core stuff your
body was in the healing mode you're on
the 369 if you do it correctly your body
was in the healing mode
chipping away at all those things that
are freaking wrong inside the body and
you're you're in the healing mode and
then when you shut off that cleansing
healing mode you were cleansing and
healing and when you shut that cleansing
and healing mode down that's a new move
when you shut in that cleanse and
healing mode down
what happens is
you get high high as a kite you're
flying oh my God I had a slice of pizza
I'm bringing in two avocados a day I
just had some beans I just had beans and
avocado I just had some oil I just had
and what happened was you're hot
freaking high as a kite buying Hezekiah
because your adrenals were restored so
much they were restored they're so
jamming strong that when you dumped fat
into your bloodstream
or cacao into your bloodstream your
adrenals were loaded and were like boom
and you were like oh my God I'm euphoric
I'm high you know screw that diet what
the 369 was hard what meanwhile the 369
restored those adrenals it did deep
cleansing and deep healing
and then
you threw in all the fat
and you threw in the cacao and your
adrenals just freaking released a ton of
adrenaline because the whole time you
were burnt out all these years and
you're doing the 369 and you're doing
the cleanses in the 2018 cleanse because
you're so freaking burnt out that your
adrenals were fried
and they restored and they restored
Weeks Later months later they restored
six months later they restored they
finally restored and so when you went
off the wagon and jumped into that slice
of pizza that vegan pizza and those
avocados heavy avocados and that tahini
on your salad and those bean burritos
and when you went into that you were
high as a kite and you were feeling the
effects of what you did for yourself
healing and restoring yourself
I'd be able to do that forever
you might be somebody that needs more
healing and you can only do it so long
before father time or father Christmas
says Ah you were really sick years ago
and you better get back on your
protocols and your and your you know
cleanses and you better get going
because yeah you still got more to go
can't tell you how many I see do that
and they even hide
what's going down because they don't
want to be embarrassed so they can't be
honest about stuff I'm not saying that
no judgment it's just I've seen a lot of
different stuff out there
nerves need time to restore and heal
central nervous systems need time to
restore and heal
adrenals need time to restore and heal
but no way and nowhere
our medical medium cleanse is actually
there to harm an adrenal it's there to
restore them and make them Rock Solid
and I've witnessed it myself throughout
the decades
for a lot of people that literally were
on steroids
because they had no adrenals left and
they had to do the 369 day in and day
out and restore their adrenals until
their doctor was like you don't even
need injections anymore and boom
so it's the opposite when people are
immobile and lose a lot of their
Mobility it can be harder to come back
because they can't get
they can't get you know where they need
to be fast takes time
when someone is bedridden or stuck in a
wheelchair they can lose a lot of
mobility and muscle and connected tissue
and have a lot of problems
from not being able to move much
and that's something that happens to a
lot of people so it takes time to heal
and cleanse and rebuild nerves and get
them strong enough to to rehab physical
therapy and very sick people and when
you do the medical medium stuff because
medical medium stuff is for the really
sick people so they can rehab and
restore it takes time
well anyway
I'm speechless
speechless
so Susan says mystery throat tightening
neurological symptoms let's head into
here and see if there's anything in
brand saver
protocols let's try to find it here
curious very curious
look
a lot of times I you guys I I try to
keep up with everything and I try to
keep up with everything the best I can
but there's so much going on
you know to try to bring the information
to you guys and and put these books
together with Spirit of compassion's
information of one human being
trying my best
seriously
um
and um all right so let's get into it
right now
and I'll apologize for flipping through
me
Pages here
this is one chapter right there
you guys have to read supplement gospel
so I'm going to look into neurological
symptoms like chest heightening throat
tightening throat tightening okay we're
going to go into that a little bit
but
um
it there's another thing that pains me
out there when someone says you don't
need supplements
dude
there are people out there walking right
now and living their life because of
supplementation added to their protocols
without it
baby screwed
totally screwed
there are people that if they didn't
have the right tools
they'd be riddled in pustules in their
mouth their throat their vaginal area
like if it wasn't for supplementation
if it wasn't for supplementation
forget it
I don't
appreciate blatant
ignorance
on the matter out there
just because someone or somebody out
there doesn't personally like me
they don't like
my tude or
me as a person or they heard rumors and
stories that aren't even real and
they've convinced themselves they are
whatever it is
there are supplementation that freaking
turn people's lives and it's critical
so
it
biased personal
vendettas or whatever and influencers
all through social media or wherever I
don't like medical medium whatever it
has whatever it is
that don't
actually say that it's not all
supplements that are bad
there's so many that have all this red
dye and all this garbage and gluten and
soy and everything else and that's just
some and there's some that just have all
the gelatin and all that garbage in it
whatever then there's some that are just
that don't have that in there but are
just straight out bad like bentonite
clay and charcoal and all that other
stuff but no one's no one's kind of like
breaking that down so people can learn
these are all supplements are bad you
don't need it you just need food really
you just need food because yeah there
are people out there that just need
celery juice and their acid reflux is
gone forever
but then that's that person there's that
Mom that's bedridden that has kids and
they they and the kids are like Mommy
why are you in bed for eight hours a day
and there's those moms that if they
didn't have the right tools they'd still
be bedridden God forbid
so
the whole kind of like misunderstanding
the attack on supplementation is
completely the confusing process of that
is just unbelievable
so
there are times you need it time Stone
I'm going to read a little bit of this
if you guys don't mind
you guys know why I'm this pumped up
today some of you guys are you're not
complaining but you're talking about
like you're talking about like why I'm
acting like hanging because I haven't
taken this in a while
maybe you don't like how I am right now
but some of you guys are like what
happened to him and why is he going into
what he's going into why is he talking
like I'm just saying it's because of the
celery Force I haven't been taking it in
a while
I ran out
and then I took a bunch before I came on
this live and it kicked in I took it
right before I came on and it finally
kicked in I don't know about you but for
me it makes my brain go into a different
place
say no more
okay
because of the vagus nerves size and
reach
when inflammation occurs in the brain
stem that affects the vagus nerve Great
Vine the vagus nerve Grapevine going
through
you guys vagus nerve grape vine
important to know I'm in brain saver
right now
Legendary Legendary unbelievable classic
Timeless book already helping so many
listener of Grapevine the Vegas nerves
can exhibit a wider range of symptoms on
the whole than other cranial nerves
these vagus nerve symptoms that result
from an inflamed brain stem could
include tightness of the chest
tightness of the throat
I feel bad for anybody going through any
of this
just kills me mild dizziness and
imbalanced feeling a sense of not
digesting well anxiety pressure in the
chest difficulty swallowing
even if mild a hard time taking a deep
breath pain in the throat nausea and
sometimes erratic heartbeat
all with inflammation of the vagus nerve
grape vine
when vagus nerve inflammation is
stemming from higher up like this from
the brain stem itself
from the brain stem itself
[Music]
maybe I didn't have to take you apart
from the brain stem itself
it could be a little bit of everything
if the inflammation is in the brain stem
itself it could be a little a little bit
of everything difficulty swallowing
digestive problems anxiety pressure in
the chest imbalance feeling mild
dizziness tightness of the throat
tightness of the chest
I shouldn't have taken that much celery
for us before coming on
I just threw an extra bunch in
who's counting
when vagus nerve inflammation is
stemming from higher up like that it can
do that
as inflammation Ebbs and flows in the
brain stem from mild to more severe some
of the inflammation will lessen are
intensified on the Vegas they're a great
fine inflammation can come and go based
on whether someone was getting more
sleep or lacking sleep
because when you sleep
your vagus nerve calms down it calms
down
just so much Vegas Urban I'll do a Vegas
nerve show
or a podcast or whatever eventually but
yeah so back to that question
someone's dealing with tightness of the
throat tightness of the chest
yep
information that's critical you guys
oh wait we got another question here IG
how to stay a little positive and
motivated to keep healing after breaking
some rolls in bad conditions that you're
bringing some rules
you mean breaking protocol
breaking cleanse
um
first of all critical to know no
judgment ever ever
no judgment
okay life is hard
life
is hard if it
if someone doesn't believe life is hard
they're either totally bullshitting
themselves
or
more money than God they have
with very little stress if any
either or life is hard there's a lot of
Temptations around us there's peer
pressure there's hard times we're up
against
a lot of people go through a lot
and that's that's on all accounts
for anyone and everyone
I've seen spiritual gurus throughout the
decades
that anyone would think they have it all
down and nothing could ever harm them or
happen to them meanwhile
the crap they go through as they keep it
quiet is unbelievable there's
life isn't easy
but that's okay
we Forge ahead we stay strong and fight
for it the key the key is to be
compassionate and realistic about what
happened
don't be upset don't get upset if you
get a little set back from it get right
back on track when you get a chance but
the keys to be compassionate
and easy on yourself
look
let me get right back on it
look I I look I'm guilty of a lot of
things one of the things I'm guilty of
is if I'm working too hard on something
for too many hours I won't
get something I need to eat
so that's kind of like a mistake that I
make even with SOC in my ear saying you
just passed another two hours without
getting some glucose in your bloodstream
for your brain because you're thinking
like intensely you're you're working on
a project and you're so involved in that
project you just literally it's four or
five hours later you didn't get any
glucose in you you had a little bit of
coconut water you had some celery juice
but you don't have anything else in you
you better do it and I'm guilty of doing
things like that but then I I tried to
say okay okay okay I'm not trying to be
hard on my adrenals I'm not trying to be
hard on my brain I know my brain needs
glucose I will do better tomorrow I will
do better tomorrow
comes and I screw up again and I do it
over again
the medical media
Anthony William aw a dubs he does it
again the next day because five six
hours I'm working so hard I don't go and
get myself a piece of fruit I don't do
any of that and then it's like SOC
saying it all over again and so the
third day it's like finally I'm back on
track or something but yeah so
whatever protocol is what I'm saying you
do or however you're doing it or
whatever cleanse you're working on or
whatever Foods you brought in
incorporating is it just the wild
blueberries you brought in it's wild
blueberries and celery juice whatever it
is you did and you fall off the wagon
it's okay get back on discipline is
important and it comes it comes
and it goes It goes
and then it comes it calms that
discipline and then it goes It goes then
it comes it goes and comes and it stays
there and stays there and stays there
and stays there and stays there and it
goes
but
we're all doing the best we can and keep
a light hard
all right
love you guys
many blessings God bless you
I will put my blood back into the
refrigerator
um get on the newsletter
um
by the way I put out an environmental
disaster air quality tools
PDF
which is so incredible
information and tools it's worth it
it's worth
the download
go to medicalme.com
download this
you might see the link of the profile
and in the description newsletter fun
things come in fun things coming get on
the newsletter medical medium.com
newsletter please get on there I'm
telling you guys
I am offering
something by the way this is free I'm
offering something really exciting
and if everything goes right
it's going to be
freaking incredible
follow me on telegram Twitter and tick
tock there's something I want to do
I want to do
something really powerful with you guys
that's going to be life-changing
spiritually emotional
can't wait I can't wait to announce it
I'm just I'm just hoping I'm hoping
medical medium podcast new episodes
coming soon by the way
medical meme podcast said Apple podcast
medical medium podcast
right
God bless you
if you don't believe in God that's okay
light bless you if you don't believe in
the light create or bless you if you
don't believe in the Creator
then Earth bless you if you don't
believe in Earth was you Moon bless you
if you don't believe in the book then
son bless you you don't believe in the
Sun in the sky
then Angel bless you if you don't
believe in angels
then that's okay
you don't have to believe in anything
anyway God bless you guys truly
see you soon