[Music]
find out what's making you sick and how
to heal Anthony William is the medical
medium hello I'm Anthony William and
you're listening to the medical medium
radio show where each week I talk about
the most advanced healing information
and secrets about health much of which
is not found anywhere else and is
decades ahead of what's out there now as
I've always said who has 10 20 30 years
to wait for answers because when you're
sick and you don't feel good regardless
of whatever whatever the diagnosis is or
non-diagnosis or wrong diagnosis or
misdiagnosis whatever it is if you're
sick and you're not feeling good whether
you got an answer that could almost be
right maybe it's not right maybe it is
doesn't matter you don't feel good and
when you don't feel good that's not good
me what I mean by that is for people who
have problems and they're more than just
a sniffle more than just you know they
catch a cold once a year you know twice
a year more than just that you know
that's the whole thing I mean people get
miserable when they catch a flu they
catch you know they catch the flu so
there are sinuses their throat at your
sore throat sinuses are running they get
the cough they're coughing they go to
the doctor just you know they're
miserable for a little while they're
getting bad night's sleeps getting
postnasal drip for a while and all that
is miserable what about the people what
about the people who are chronically ill
and chronically ill they got they got
you know uh chronic fatigue syndrome me
they got you know they got all kinds of
different things going on what if it's
not just that what if they got um a
goiter what if they got uh different
symptoms dizzy they got brain fog severe
brain fog and they live with it every
single day what if it's more than that
what if they have physical pain in
random strange places in the body that
too I mean I've seen it all out there
and I know it's out there now people
hurt in different places it's not just
the knees not just the feet I mean they
hurt in the most you know random places
in the body no no information to what's
going on what's really wrong been
through all the testing been through
everything seen dozens of doctors and
professionals you name it and what about
the people that are dealing with you
chronic infections and things like that
too that actually you know skin
infections and all kinds of stuff um
just chronic s sinusitis but really
debilitating kind chronic migraines
migraines headaches everything eye
problems ear problems people out there
they're you know you guys know you guys
know and it's not an easy life when
you're not feeling good it's not easy at
all compassion is not something that's
just out there so easily to grab on to
and get so you know compassion towards
the sick is doesn't isn't really out
there I hate to say it but it's it's
it's kind of not it's kind of not yeah
there's there's a lot of Charities and
you know there's fundraisers for
different things out there for for
diseases and illnesses and good causes
of course but you there's not a lot of
that hey look we're going to do
something about this hey there's not a
lot of that kindness for how many people
are sick if you really want to know how
many people are sick what's something
that's more than just a headache once in
a blue moon from a little stress or
whatever if you want to know it's most
of the country it's most of the country
at this point guess what it's going to
get a lot worse a lot worse we're
talking about COPD today so just hang in
there we're we're getting there just
we're we're we're there's a reason why
I'm talking about this because we're
heading into COPD hang in there this is
the only show just so you know where the
information here doesn't come from
medical interest group groups it's not
repackaged reg garbled it's not
repackaged recycled Theory constantly in
every single book out there right now in
the medical realm alternatively and
conventionally it's not recycled it's
not repackaged and just Rewritten and
thrown back out there with bogus studies
and everything else and citations of
bogus studies this information is free
from all of that thank God because
that's why I've been able to get people
better over the last 35 years and even
more since I was four years old so it's
not backed by you know medical funding
with strings attached it's not it's not
attached to this information it's clean
there's no botched research interest
groups and investors investing in
something so the outcome comes a certain
way news flash it's like that in all
fields of chronic illness and medicine
at this point Sorry but it is and so it
doesn't have that contamination that
botch research it doesn't have the whole
thing with the medical lobbyist behind
it internal Kickbacks yeah internal
Kickbacks you wouldn't believe the money
that's constantly changing hands all
through alternative medicine alternative
medicine and conventional medicine
persuaded belief systems which poisons
everything persuaded belief systems is
like this whole thing where it becomes
you don't want to know the truth because
you're saturated in a belief system
someone doesn't want to know the truth
someone doesn't want to be open to the
truth cuz they're saturated in a belief
system I can't tell you what that does
and gets in the way and this is why
people are still sick and not getting
better and it's why people are getting
sicker and sicker and sicker private
panels of influencers yeah they're there
health field payoffs and trendy traps
those trendy traps oh my god look out
for them there's a new one each year and
you'll get sucked into it you'll get
funneled into it you'll get pulled into
it you'll get tricked by it that's right
you better believe it whether anybody
likes it or not it's just a fact Jack um
this is the only show where the
information here is pure untampered with
Advanced Clean source so I work for you
I work for you I'm not sitting here
trying to be sarcastic and mean about
everything I'm not sitting here trying
to say oh ho ho ho ho my information all
the other information out there no it's
from a pure unclean source and don't you
want that don't you want that because I
would I would if I was just out there
and and I wasn't Anthony William and I
wasn't given this gift at age 4 and
spent my whole life getting people
better including the thousands and
thousands and hundreds and hundreds of
thousands of people now we're at the
point right now where in the millions of
people that have the books and have the
information in the millions globally and
they're healing hundreds of thousands of
people are their lives are being turned
around in they're healing unlike
anything seen in alternative medicine
ever before in history is what's going
on just so you know that's happening
right now thanks to Spirit and thanks to
you thanks to everybody involved here
it's incredible so so here's the whole
point wouldn't want wouldn't you want
that pure un tampered source of
information that's not dirtied up by all
that other garbage I just mentioned yes
so we're I would want it I'm sorry but I
would want that so we're talking about
COPD now what I was saying earlier is
that everybody's getting sick yes
everybody's getting sick they're getting
a diagnosis you go into I'm not just
talking about people that are in their
40s and 50s and they got some
hypertension and they got some heart
disease you know cooking or they had a
stroke which is still most Strokes are
actually mystery to all doctors all of
this would it I'm not just talking about
that I'm talking about people in their
20s I'm talking about people in their
30s I'm talking about people in their
teens teenagers talking about little
kids and little ones getting sick like
never before in human history just so
you know never before in human history
I'm letting you know I'm letting you
know the truth I'm letting you know I'm
just I'm I'm giving it to you there I
said this in one of the other shows that
years ago I knew that life expectancy
was declining I knew that it was all it
was all you know it was all declining I
knew how long you live was declining but
it was ignored no one was doing any
studies no one was doing I knew I knew
of course and doesn't mean the studies
would even come out right because if
they want to hide that that everybody's
getting sicker and not healthier if they
want to hide that they can easily all
you have to do is have somebody invest
into the study and boom it goes the
direction they need to go or an investor
will never invest in it again and a
study will never happen for that person
who wanted to do the study career over
done so what happens is they all come in
you know so they've been saying oh we
live longer we're living longer I've
been watching it decline since the 80s
been watching it decline since the 90s
been watching the health decline in in
in the US since the 2000s and now just
recently recently it got out because it
was it was impossible to hide it or
starting to drop they're starting to say
well no life doesn't go as long as we
thought it is now it's starting to drop
the numbers are dropping you you don't
live you know life average isn't this
number anymore it's coming down because
you can't hide it you can't hide
it there's millions and millions of
doctors offices globally being filled up
and filled up and filled up and it's
like it's never before in history have
been like this and the young people the
young people I've said this before I've
written it in the book One medical
medium okay
17 roughly around this number 17 out of
a hundred college students go home and
don't come back not because they're
disinterested in their work not because
they don't want to be interested in
their studies not because they don't
want to be in school not because they
want want to change course or Direction
in their
life roughly around 17 out of a 100
college students go home because they're
done they're done they're in bed can't
function barely Confunction and talk
getting diagnoses left and right of Ms
and Lyme disease and everything else and
nobody knows what's going on being told
they're just being lazy being told that
they're brain foged maybe they just need
a drug going to different doctors and
they're done
that's it not going back to school and
most of them women most of them women
young women that don't end up going back
to college and then all the other
reindeer just moving forward they watch
all the reindeer moving forward they
have to sit back watching their old
friends move on with their careers and
it's not that they're not getting sick
either most people are in this day and
age getting things wrong with them
constantly non-stop no one wants to
check into that on how kids have to go
home because they're getting vertigo
chronic
vertigo and they're they're getting
dizzy balance problems severe severe
severe debilitating brain fog fatigue
neurological fatigue that I talk about
all the time and that's it gone home no
finishing school no one cares no one
cares in the industries no one cares the
parents care the parents care no one
cares no one else the parents and the
families of these children most of them
care of course and whatnot but I'm just
saying the industry does
care whatever whatever and so that's how
it works so is is things getting better
no I've been watching it it's not I used
to be in the I used to sit in the
nursing homes to visit clients all
through the years and I I see younger
people filing into those nursing homes
like never before younger younger
younger people younger people younger
people it is
unbelievable and that's what we live
with now and that's what we're living
with now but hey whatever and I say
whatever because you know what
the industry the industry just doesn't
care they'll just pass it off to
genetics pretty soon completely every
single disease is genetic if it's not
your body attacking itself which is bull
it's going to be the genetic theory
another theory this is how it's done out
there they're not going to go into
viruses really deep because you know
what's going to happen if they go into
viruses really deep if they understand
the 60 varieties the over 60 varieties
now of Epstein bar that I talk about in
thyroid healing and book one medical
medium if they start actually trying to
figure out any of the information that
been been providing all these years if
they even go into it there's going to be
hell to pay and I'll tell you why
because every mom out there every mother
and every grandmother is going to want
something done about it because they
know they would know what's going down
because these viruses are out here and
being ignored and there's going to be
hell to pay Mama Bear Mama Bear with her
children knowing that her children have
been affected by a virus like Epstein
bar and no one cares and they're not
doing anything about it and they want to
pass it off as all this other junk
medicine and junk studies and everything
else you wouldn't believe the hell to
pay if the information really got out
there and really got out there somebody
would have to be held accountable and
that's this is the prime example so
anyway we're talking about we're talking
about COPD and and you're probably
wondering well he's not getting the COPD
yet I'm talking about this because copt
COPD has doubled since the 8
as far as
cases now they say out there it's
doubled since the
80s it's more than doubled okay so my
source says it's way more than doubled
it's not doubled it's tripled since the
80s tripled since the 80s COPD so
because there's a lot of levels of COPD
that are not diagnosed properly of CD
and it's also the they don't when they
when they look into those things they're
just averaged out they're not even done
right but there's so many cases of
beginner
COPD and they're not even added into it
and also you know they also do this
weird thing where they just don't throw
every COPD case into the
numbers they throw the smokers in and
they leave others out that's what they
do so they say well it's doubled since
the80s actually you know it's tripled
and even going past that so how is that
possible how's that possible I thought
we're getting better in medicine I
thought we're getting better I mean we
are we got laser surgery we got
different you great techniques we got
Great Brain surgeons even though hey
we're still we're still like you know
like a grain of rice compared to a silo
of rice is in knowledge and brain
knowledge but we still got some great
brain surgeons we can transplant a few
different organs I mean you
know we got a lot going on
on and we got a lot of good going on but
why are we here with everything getting
worse to the degree it's getting worse
what's my predictions what's my
predictions which always come out true
what are they it's going to get a lot
worse than this it's going to get a lot
and a lot worse because when you look at
where the experts are going including
the Alternative Health experts with
their books and everything else and you
look at what they're doing and what
they're putting out there and what
they're writing we're not we're we're
not getting anything done we're not
going anywhere we're not going anywhere
and then you look you look at you know
the information that's out there in the
internet and like okay we're not going
anywhere there you you look at I mean
it's not in conventional medicine we're
not going anywhere there we're not
cleaning up the mess we're not cleaning
up the viral mess that's taken over the
world and the country here this country
here we're not looking we're not
figuring out what the real cause of
Lupus is we don't no one cares no one
cares what the real cause of Lupus is we
do no one else does in the industries
meaning nobody doctors care but nobody a
lot of doctors care but nobody above
that the people that pull the strings
and pull the pull the strings and make
the moves up there so you have to
understand you have to understand that
this is this is a serious thing going on
where I predict sickness to come even
more and more and more and when I see
the genetic stuff coming out where it's
all oh it's your genes let's do you know
let's theorize about it's your genes
that's why you're sick that means we're
getting nowhere because nothing's going
to be fixed nothing nothing's going to
be fixed sure you know we could do the
high fat trendy diets take away
processed food and people can get better
with some of their symptoms and call it
an autoimmune diet when they don't even
know what autoimmune is that's what I
love here's here's here's something
that's really really disturbing and I
love to talk about it because I I try to
I try to get people to know and
learn and you got the whole autoimmune
thing going on out there so you get all
this information you get all these books
autoimmune this autoimmune that and they
don't know how autoimmune works or what
causes it or what causes any autoimmune
diseases that's what I'm saying so do
you think we're going to get healthier
no get outside of pulling out processed
food and cleaning up your diet and
people improving their lives a little
bit doing more exercise and you know
those kinds of things can help but we're
still getting sicker faster younger ages
rampant Pace going forward like never
before in that and what you're seeing in
the literature out there now and
everything is not even close and here we
are in this year it another decade going
to go by another decade's going to go by
and no one still knows what even
autoimmune means except for spirit and
ie it's
disturbing it's disturbing so what's my
prediction lots and lots of sickness
like never before with bogus theories
such as the autoimmune Theory which is
completely wrong such as the genetic
theor which is completely wrong I'm not
not denying we don't have genes and how
important they are and the Mysteries
involved in it but it it has nothing to
do with the chronic illness that we're
seeing with people suffering today and
it has nothing to do with
COPD because they're passing off
nonsmokers with COPD into the genetic
category that's what they're
doing you you see how it's going you see
what I mean how it's going in what
direction it is they're passing that off
to the genetic theory because if it's
not somebody who obviously smoked and
puffed all those all those heavy duty
cigarettes their whole life if it's not
that person and you didn't do that H you
know you go to the doctor I how can I
have COPD there lug problems I thought
it was just asthma and how am I having
this
COPD I never smoke
and they're just no well science and
research and studies say w it's it's
genetic now you got to it's your
genes oh my God dear Lord we're so going
nowhere to decades to come and decades
to
come it's really sad it's really sad not
not well you know this is what's going
on with your lung sex this is the virus
behind your lung sex this is the
bacteria behind your lung sax this is
this is your lymphatic system condition
this is what's going on inside your
liver this is what's really happening
here none of that no you won't hear any
of that you won't hear any of
that there there nothing like that it
won't even exist it won't even exist
instead it to be like no it's it's look
we just got to get you on all the
medications and look some medications
sustain people's lives when they and
that's the that's the good part of
conventional medicine Sometimes some
medications do help and sustain people's
lives with COPD oxygen 10 TKS you name
it but it's like it's like okay it's
just no it's genetic if you didn't
actually damage your lungs with some
kind of chemicals or
whatever so and that's where we are
we're nowhere it's called nowhere
absolutely nowhere is what it's called
and what year is it you think we're in
modern times you think that we're you
know where it's going on the BET look it
is amazing what computer technology can
do and Tech and the Tech world can do
it's absolutely astounding and
amazing absolutely but that goes ahead
that's moving ahead of what we do for
sickness and chronic illness that's just
moving way ahead in a different
field versus understanding what's wrong
with people in their sickness and their
diseases and illnesses and all their
symptoms that that that's enti that's
not even you don't you don't get fooled
by that when you think look look where
the tech world is going when you're
young and you feel indestructible and
you don't have symptoms a lot of
symptoms that are you know in the way of
your
life and and you're you know using the
tech world you're like oh yeah we have
science down pat right now we got
genetic technology down we got
everything down pat we just just listen
to your doctors listen to science when
any peer reviews out there let's listen
to it you think you think it's all there
you start getting sick you learn fast
you learn fast after you've been to your
fifth doctor you start learning quick
when you start giving that oh your G ADC
or well we don't know what it is oh no
you you got lime even though you were
never exposed to a tick oh you got this
oh you got that it it you start learning
quick oh wait what's my treatment it's
just antibiotics wait a minute what's my
treatment it's just it's just
immunosuppressive and antibiotics so
what's wrong I've been sick for 2 years
what do you mean I was doing great I was
on top of the world a little while I'm
28 years old what what's my treatment
isn't there better knowledge out there
than this I've been to five doctors
eight doctors 10 neurologists what do
you mean my my my my my phone my
computer phone does everything it's got
every Emoji there is in the world and
it's got every ability to Tech this and
do this and talk to this person and live
chat this and do all this and look you
know what I mean I work at this you I
work at this company and they got the
best everything and you wouldn't believe
it you just they they scan your retina
and you walk through the door you don't
even need a card hanging off your neck
and you can't you and I'm chronically
ill and I got fatigue and I can't
function anymore what's wrong with me I
got sio what I got bacteria in my
intestinal track what's going on I got
what what's wrong and I can't function I
can't think and I got brain fog why
aren't we fixing all this how is this
possible and that's what happens to
every single
person who believes we have it all sewed
up when they're feeling pretty good and
they're young and they believe and they
don't have a lot of life experience and
they believe we have it all sewed
up and then
bam and it's happening more and more
years ago was just you know was just so
many people in the in their 20s and
their late
teens now it's truck loads and bus loads
and train
loads and they're
learning a hard hard way Hard Knocks and
they're learning wait a minute there's
no
answers and and I've been to the best
functional medicine doctor I've spent 50
80,000 50 60 70
$80,000 and I don't have
answers you know it's it's it's it's
unbelievable the amount of information
Spirit and I gave people that came to me
over the
years was more information than they can
get anywhere else even today right now
anywhere and they had not only the
answers but they recovered if they
applied themselves to What Spirit wanted
they recovered and thousands have and
thousands are now just with the books
alone and everything else
and I've had to dedicate my life to
these books and now I can't I can't work
with with anybody anymore and it breaks
my heart that it can't but I put it all
in the books and if you read them
carefully and you bring them to your
practitioners or you bring them to
people that can read it for you if you
can't read it you will find your way and
heal you will find your way and heal and
and if you have to bring it to
practitioner to interpret it you bring
it to a practitioner to interpret it and
whatever you need to
do but things are getting bad out there
and the answers have to come and people
have to get the answers and Tech and
Tech and computers and everything we got
going out right now and genes and the
theories in the medical world and the
technology we have and the best cars we
have isn't providing the answers in the
health realm for people it is the wild
west out there in the internet and is
the Wild West in the books out there and
it's and they're still avoiding trying
to even look into what's going on and
when they do try to grab a little tidbit
because it gets popular because because
a popular
popularized can't say that word some of
the things like epine bar and other
things they take a little piece of it
and they don't want more than that so
people still get confused and go down
the wrong road and down a trap it's
unbelievable
COPD reminds me of this because when you
have
COPD and you're told it's genetic and
you didn't smoke and if you had it when
you smoke too I mean that's there's
people out there that smoke their whole
lives and don't get
COPD and then there's people who
smoke and get it quick with with a
fraction of their life smoking and
there's a reason for this everybody's
different everybody's different to what
degree or what can trigger it what how
it can get to the point it gets to what
happens and it it's unbelievable how it
works the uh you know so the whole point
with
COPD is that people they struggle they
get beaten down by it there's no answers
out there and we're going to cover that
right now that's what we're going to do
so let's talk about bacteria and viruses
because that's that's where I'm heading
now COPD is not only tripling but in in
about I'd say about another decade 10
years maybe 15 coming on 15 it's going
to quadruple but it's going to hit the
youth it's going to hit the youth it's
going to hit the young people and it's
going to hit the people in their 20s and
30s and it's going to be the first time
the first time in history I mean there
there is some random rare cases of
already that happening but it's going to
be a wave of hitting people in their 20s
and 30s COPD something that we think
about for 80y olds who smoked their
whole life that those days are gone
those days are gone the 80-year-olds
that smoked their whole life meaning
those days about COPD are gone it's not
also the 58-year-old either you know the
young 58-year old or the young
50-year-old which is you know happening
all the time with COPD it's moving it's
going to move into the 30s and 20s
that's why I'm doing the show I'm doing
the show for all reasons you know for
people that are older people that are
but the people that are younger to come
so what's going to happen it's always
going to be blamed on the genetic Factor
because people are smoking less and less
and less so we're we're phasing out the
smoking crowd we're phasing out
that crowd there's always going to be a
crowd that also you know they they
breathe in a lot of smoke they they have
fireplaces running all time they live in
certain areas of the world they have you
know their wood burning stoves but W
wood burning stoves you know also
release still a lot of smoke when you
have to open it throw more wood in it
and close it there's always the smoke
Factor going on um if you live near an
industrial area or an industrial city or
something like that and you're and
you're living in that you might be on
the downdraft some serious you know some
serious um gases and smoke and toxic
fumes and stuff like that that can
happen a lot of that that can be a big
part of CPD for a lot of people so that
you got all that going on too you got
the whole environmental thing and then
like I talked about in the environmental
show where in the Agland conventional
Agland all across the country all over
the country conventional Agland pick a
state pick a state and it's it's
happening there they there's there's
something called row covers if you've
gardened and you buy a row cover if you
ever garden and buy a row cover row
cover goes you know on your garden bed
and your plants can grow up through it
so you know you get a hole in there and
the area and the plant grows through it
keeps the weeds down well row covers are
used in conventional Agriculture and and
and and not when you see conventional
agricultural um photos and everything
like that you won't see the row covers
but they're there in conventional
growing they're there I noticed that
they you usually see the field when it's
all green and you know all the different
cabbage heads are sticking out you know
as far as like Green Revolution stuff
and conventional farming and you know
you see broccoli going miles and miles
and miles and you you just you you know
you see it but you don't see any row
covers you don't see any row covers but
but they were there they were there and
most likely removed or um some don't use
them but for the majority they are used
these row covers and what happens is
here's what goes on the fields all get
sprayed with pesticides Mercury Laden
pesticides copper Coop dangerous copper
Laden pesticides neuro antagonists All
chemical neuro antagonist chemicals all
in the pesticides Dangerous Ones or
skull and crossbones on all the
pesticide herbicide rodenticide
fungicide larvicide um containers so you
got the skull and crossbones you got the
it's literally that mean means death if
you go near that thing and you don't
have a hazmat suit on and you're loaded
and you're opening that can you can die
that's why that's on there like that if
the can rolled over and dumped the big
can rolled over and dumped and it hit
your legs you're dead that's why there's
a skull and crossbone on there so they
have to take that dilute it with water
fill it into all the tractors and the
big and the big you know um containers
on the tractors and they got all the
sprayers in the op you know all the
hydraulic sprayers and everything and
they're spraying the fields if they
don't do it by planes they don't do it
by planes as much and and they do it
mostly by
tractors and all that pesticide is going
on the row covers it's all going on the
row saturating the row covers saturating
the row covers all year long or all
during that growing period whether it's
three months or two months or five
months depending what they're growing
and what they're
doing and then they get when they when
they harvest after they harvest they
gather all the row covers it's all
plastic and they pile it up in gigantic
m s in every state in every part of the
country and they burn it they throw fuel
on it and they burn it and this is one
reason why COPD is worsening at this
point it's worsening at this point
because of this reason right here and
this is like a like an
unbelievable
illegal way of doing things but they all
do do it and it's usually protected by
hands you know people passing money
along under the table but it's it's far
worse than any car pollution it's far
worse than some of the factories that
are spewing out crap out of the top of
those factories and Industrial sections
of the world it is actually worse it's
it's these massive plumes of smoke and
why wouldn't anybody see this because
it's called the white smoke so it's it's
just the burning plastic
and the Plastics are mostly white mostly
white so it's a white smoke that goes up
in the air and it just burn and they
burn it everywhere all over the country
and what are they doing they're making
us sick and no one's allowed to go near
it no meaning no one's allowed to learn
about it no one's allowed to understand
it no one's allowed to do anything it's
a it's it's a practice that it it makes
the GMO thing look
ridiculous look ridiculous you couldn't
even
imagine and you know and and when they
it's unbelievable it's unbelievable and
that's what's happening in the country
that's actually part of why COPD is on
the rise so we have to protect ourself
so we can get around that it's it's why
asthma's on the rise like never before
it's part of why asthma is on the rise
like never before and other lung
problems are on the rise like never
before like never
before so what happens here is that that
we have these lung problems and
different reasons why and varieties of
why if you have a bacterial infection
that's chronically in the lung which is
Strep strep can get in the lung all
these different varieties of strep all
these different varieties so many
mutations at this point and we take
antibiotics and it mutates it more and
take the antibiotics it mutates it more
makes the strep stronger stronger
stronger stronger that could lead to a
COPD case we can have underlying thing
is Strep they'll never know they'll
never they can't tell they can cut a
piece of your lung out they're still not
going to find it
because no one cares so the study and
the the money is not going there the
money is going into genes medicine is is
at a drought point right now it's at a
drought point that means that anything
productive in medicine to move people
forward in chronic illness is dried up
the Ws are dried up and money can't be
dumped into anything anymore unless it's
bogus
alternative interest groups wanting to
fund a trendy concept to confuse people
more and then you know and that that's
that's that's a different situation
those aren't drying up they come out all
the time but in conventional medicine
the well has dried up it all has to
funnel to genes so any money involved
has to go into genetic
technology cloning and everything else
and just but you know whatever it has to
just all be genetic no matter what the
case or what the direction is and so you
know there's no money in cutting out a
piece of lung and figuring out what
bacteria teria is what's causing the
problem or in a case of viruses there a
lot of different herpetic viruses they
get also into the lung area through the
lymphatic system so there's a lot of
Epstein bars different varieties of
Epstein bar not everybody with Epstein
bar is going to have one thing or
another just so you know a lot of people
with Epstein bar they'll have chronic
fatigue a lot of they'll have Hashimoto
thyroiditis they'll have ra there's
different varieties of Epstein bar
something that medical science research
has no idea about whatsoever until I
came out with the information there's
over 60 varieties of Epstein bar and
so and there will be more varieties as
they mutate and they grow so move
forward so anyway the bottom line is I
say so a lot sorry about that the bottom
line is that we get we can get a viral
infection inside the lymphatic system it
comes out of the liver the viruses sit
inside the liver so your Epstein bar
will sit inside your liver hhv6 will sit
inside the liver
hhv7 hhv7 um undiscovered hhv1
undiscovered hhv1 undiscovered hhv 12 13
14 undiscovered hhv 15 undiscovered
hh16 and and their subgroups meaning
their
mutations so what happens is these
viruses sit inside people's livers they
move into the lymphatic system over time
over the years it's different kindes of
types of herpetic
viruses they create mucus in the
lymphatic
system and when they create mucus and a
backlog of mucus
continuously it causes oxygen problems
meaning the whole thing with oxygen
switching off with carbon dioxide just
to get the oxygen and carbon dioxide
Exchange in the lung in the lung tissue
in the lung sack so you got the oxygen
carbon dioxide exchange it it it creates
mucus mucus gets in the way of that
exchange so then you get this these
viral these
viruses that produce a lot of Gunk and
junk and byproduct not necessarily
neurotoxins because there's different
varieties of viruses you got the hh10
like said you got different ones and you
got H6
and and so what happens is and some of
these people with COPD now they do have
neurotoxic symptoms too that I always
talk about from Epstein bars and
everything else so they're getting
multiple symptoms they got the
neuropathy they got the neuralgia
neuropathy they got different things
going on they got fibromyalgia and they
got COPD they got aches and pain so it
it all does come out in the
end but the whole point is you got this
viral stuff that's never going to get
researched
ever and then you got the bacterial
stuff like the strep strep aacle and
strep cacus and you got that going on so
the streps and the different kinds of
streps sit in the lungs itself and sit
in the lung sacks when they sit in the
lung sacks they're they're they're
actually creating the lung
damage and then and then also Epstein
bars tend to also get into lungs too
they leave the lymphatic vessels and
they they get up into the lungs they
create lung
scarring you know the scars and lungs
and create little cysts and little
pockets and little scars and they do
lung scarring it's all a mystery to
research and science they don't know how
all that scarring happens they don't
know how all the lung cysts happen
happen you know the non-cancerous ones
and everything else they don't even know
how the cancerous ones happen but it's
like and and what happens is that you
know all this is from viral and
bacterial stuff so when you're when
you're breathing in these white plumes
of smoke environmentally that are in
just are they're everywhere and no one
knows about it no one knows about it
it's just blowing
around that can trick because there's
pesticides in that white plume of smoke
coming off those rad covers all those
skull and bone pesticides I was talking
about that are saturated on the rad
cover so when they burn them they're
they're creating new
chemicals new chemicals through burning
those pesticides on the
Plastics and when you breathe that in
and you got the
viruses and you got the lymphatic mucus
and everything else it just it just
feeds it those chemicals feed it because
you breathe it in and it's going into
the lung just like somebody smoking a
cigarette going into the lung and then
feeding any kind of bacteria virus or
pathogen and then more more Scar Tissue
occurs more lung sack
damage and then not only that mucus lots
of mucus forming everywhere then take
the
foods people want eat dairy they want to
eat cheese the new longevity food
cheese it's a new longevity food sure
yeah I'll buy into that one cheese feeds
every virus and pathogen in the
book and this is the bottom line I don't
care how you know how it was raised how
the animal was raised or anything like
that or harvest it the che I mean the I
don't I don't care how everything was
done but the bottom line is so you got
the cheese you got the milk you got the
dairy you got all that you can't do that
with COPD so one thing you have to do I
would even go plant-based with COPD I
wouldn't even do an animal protein
because when it comes down to your lungs
you don't want to mess around you just
don't want to mess around it's a lot of
people that will they'll give up a
certain thing they'll give up they'll
give up something they'll give up
something but there are people now with
COPD because it's a new generation of
COPD it's a new generation it's a
younger generation and they tend to give
up more in the older days remember in
the 80s and the 90s early 2000s in the
older days people with COPD they they
you know the chain smokers and really
old and all that was going on and they
would smoke to the end it would smoke to
the end even with COPD it doesn't matter
you have an oxygen tank at the same time
you're smoking while on oxygen that was
that that's that's how it was done
that's how it was done now we got a lot
of younger people now and the world's
Chang a little bit better for the all
kinds of reasons and you know and and
younger people are like well I'm going
to quit smoking so they do throw their
cigarettes away and then you got the
young people that are told it's
jeans because they don't know anything I
just described to you just earlier about
COPD so they don't know anything about
it so they so they just throw the Jean
thing at you and those people they tend
to they tend to you know they they will
change something if you tell them to
change something they will eat better
I with COPD I wouldn't even mess around
I would go 100% plant-based 100%
plantbased is what I would
do even if it means you're high fat
plant-based even if it means you're
eating too many avocados too many nuts
and seeds too many oils you're eating
you're eating you know even if it
means you're eating something you know
you're eating quinoa even if it means
you know which is actually isn't the
worst grain at all and somebody out
there is going to say oh it's not a
grain it's a seed everything's a
seed so here's the thing so here's the
here's the deal here's the
deal um everything's a seed even if it
won't grow even if a seed won't grow
it's a seed even if it won't grow just
so you know don't get that confused that
was something that's been going
around but um quinoa like even if it's
quinoa even if it's millet even if
you're eating Millet every day and
oatmeal every day you're better off
doing that than eating an animal product
with COPD I'm not trying to rip down the
Animal product world or ripped down I
know many of you you're doing animal
proteins that's not what it's about if
you have
COPD you just want to get rid of the
animal proteins way too heavy on the
liver way too heavy on the
liver because the more bog down the
liver is the more lymphatic system is
going to get bogged down the more mucus
is going to be caused the more mucus is
going to form and go up through the lmag
system push up into the lungs and it's
just not going to help that's one reason
the other reason is the more animal
products you eat I'm just saying like
meat
chicken even fish turkey whatever the
more you eat of that or pork the less
room you have for the foods that we're
going to talk about next that restore
lung sacks here's here's how it works
here's how it works um you know I'm not
on anybody's side with the food diets
but I'm going to tell you what happens
here with animal protein it doesn't fix
things it doesn't hurt things in many
ways and some ways it does but it
doesn't fix things just so you know
what's fixing anything is everything
else you're eating so when you got all
these different autoimmune diets and
they're all filled with animal protein
and everything else what's helping the
person what's helping them at all is
they got rid of all the garbage number
one number two if they're making room
for a green juice they're making room if
you know they got rid of so much garbage
that they have room for a smoothie even
if it's not the right kind of smoothie
they got room for a green juice they got
room for more cucumbers they got room
for salads green salads they got room
for these things those are the things
that heal damaged lungs I'm not saying I
have something against the animal
protein for you if you're really sold on
it I'm just saying I would get rid of it
100% one if that if if it was me I would
get rid of it 100%
gone gone if I had if I was somebody
eating animal protein with
COPD because you know what it is when
you're take you got to take your lung
serious you need every antioxidant every
antioxidant you can possibly get in any
way shape or
form anthocyanins undiscovered
antioxidants there's hundreds and
hundreds of undiscovered antioxidants in
foods that aren't animal products that
you need to restore your lungs you need
melons to restore your lungs you need
melons you need papaya to store your L
restore your lungs foods are critical
you need berries you need wild
blueberries to restore your lungs if
you're busy eating an egg breakfast or
you're busy having a turkey sausage
breakfast healthy turkey
sausage and you don't have your wild
blueberries you just lost an opportunity
to restore your lungs just lost an
opportunity to restore your lungs plus
it's just too it's too much high fat on
top of it way too much high fat and that
doesn't help your lungs either because
it burdens down your liver here's the
thing the higher fat that's in your
bloodstream so if you're going to do all
animal products when you have
COPD when you do high fat which is
animal products if you do really high
fat and if you're vegan or vegetarian
you can do high fat too if you're
vegetarian you could have tons of oils
you I've known vegetarians they dumping
all the sesame oil they're just C
they're cooking their vegetarian dish
and they dump a whole you you know like
ounces of sesame oil in there and it's
filled with sesame oil and they got they
got lots of tofu in there which is which
has a lot of fat in tofu there's a lot
there's a high volume of fat soy oil in
there soybean oil in there so they got
that and then you know with with all
that with all that they even have you
know they even have dairy they even have
they throw goats milk in there and they
throw whatever and so just a large
amount of fat and that's not good so
when you're talking about animal protein
eaters too meaning just we're all big in
animal protein so much fat what happens
is it gets rid of your oxygen in your
blood what I'm saying is it minimizes
your blood oxygen the whole
point is keeping that oxygen getting
into your blood and having that carbon
dioxide
transfer that's the whole point so when
your diet is high in fat you can't do
that anymore you're losing oxygen so you
go plant-based 100% even if it's higher
fat plant-based it's still it'll still
give you more oxygen in the bloodstream
plant-based 100% And you need room for
the right Foods you need room for
peppermint tea ginger tea garlic onions
you need room to be hydrated with a
little coconut water you need room to be
hydrated with lemon water you need the
melons the berries you need lots of
apples you need the papaya you need the
mangoes to help with the the the
keratinoid to help restore the lung
tissue the antioxidants the amount of
beta carotene carotenoids and anti an
oxidants all of that and the pigments in
there that are loaded with antioxidants
that they don't even study yet because
you can't break them down they're not
they're it's not something you can
separate and break down easy you need a
lot of money and a lot of science and
research and a lot of real honest
hardworking people trying to figure out
what's inside these things it's really
difficult you need the celery juice cuz
the mineral salts are critical to
restoring the lungs and knock down
viruses and bacteria you need the
cucumbers lots of cucumber juice when
somebody with COPD they on cucumber
juice if you're sitting there eating an
egg and sausage breakfast you're not
going to get the cucumber juice in you
there's no way and if you do do a
cucumber juice after having an egg and
sausage breakfast what's going to happen
is it's not going to help as
much so you want to go 100% plant-based
if it's too hard for you with COPD I
understand completely then keep your
animal products to one a day and start
bringing in some avocado to try to
offset it try to do some different
things I'd rather have you on quinoa I'd
rather have you on Millet I'd rather
have you on oatmeal I'd rather have you
on things if it means it gets you kind
of off more of the animal products with
COPD it's just one of those it's one of
those illnesses it's one of those
diseases illnesses dysfunctions
disorders it's one of those where you
have to have your blood fat a little bit
lower or a lot lower so oxygen really
gets into the bloodstream helps you heal
on all kinds of levels it's a big deal
I've been able to reverse COPD in so
many people and very easily and there's
different stages of COPD depends on what
stage somebody's in too you want to
catch it earlier you don't want to be in
stage four but you can still keep
somebody in stage four alive and going
if you do the right things so you can
keep somebody in stage four here on the
planet alive and that's what you want to
do here's here's here's something that's
really good spirits always us used for
people with COPD to help them is chop up
fresh Rosemary you chop up fresh
Rosemary throw it in your salads you
chop up fresh Sage fresh Sage go to the
store get fresh Sage Sage leaves chop it
up throw it in a salad go to the store
get fresh rosemary leaves chop it up
throw it in the salad time tea you start
drinking the time tea that I have on the
blog and in the books that's really good
for COPD time tea kills the strep that's
in a lot of people's lungs that cause
COPD the younger people all have strep
in their lungs the people that are
getting COPD and Asthma and they don't
get diagnosed with COPD yet because
they're just they're just told they have
asthma at the beginning those people in
their 20s that's that's strep in inside
the lungs do the time tea vitamin C lots
of vitamin C I would be doing a whole
bunch of vitamin C every single day 3
4,000 milligrams every single day 5,000
milligrams if you can coenzyme Q10
really good for restoring the lungs ala
that's alphal opic acid good to restore
the lungs netal cysteine that's good to
restore the lungs talk to your doctor if
you're on any medication if you're going
to do any of this stuff and interact
with them make sure you talk to your
doctor
practitioner um zinc zinc deficiencies
are rampid people with see OPD young and
old have zinc deficiencies make sure
you're doing the right zinc go to my
directory and get the right kinds of
things don't get the wrong things people
if people get wrong things they don't
heal and they don't know why you got to
get the right thing go to the directory
the um Mullen Leaf that's a great one
you get a Mullen Leaf tincture I got one
on the directory you just use it you
know send it down a little bit of Mullen
Leaf every day lomatium root great for
the lungs mullen's great for the lungs
lomatium Roots great for the lungs Leaf
very good nettle Leaf every single day
including nettle leaf tea olive leaf in
a capsule is really amazing or just in
in liquid form but nettle leaf tea very
important peppermint tea every single
day you got to do if you're somebody
sensitive to garlic and onions then just
you know don't use them but if you're
not sensitive you do garlic and onions
it helps move the mucus around so that
the exchange of carbon dioxide and
oxygen occur hydration is important like
I said before you got the coconut water
you got the lemon water you got you know
and and that's why I like melons it's
really good that's a good one for people
celery juice incredible for C COPD what
kind of foods can you like you can eat
the sweet potatoes the winter squash
it's a great one so all the different
delicata sweet dumpling a spaghetti
swash all the different squashes you can
get all that is if you're living off of
butternut squash every single day your
your COPD will improve believe it or not
if you got your celery juices and you're
living off of butternut squash and sweet
potatoes your COPD will improve you take
the Animal product products down because
you want the fat down low even if you
did avocados in between at all your COPD
will
improve so you want to have the right
Foods if you have to move to grains you
do the like I said the quinoa and the
Millet and the oatmeal if it's too hard
to do all this you go into hummus just
do a little hummus if you feel like you
can hack a little bit of hummus
chickpeas garbanzo bean hummus you know
there's even low there's no fat garbanzo
bean hummuses out there and there's
lowfat you know hummuses out there you
can use those you can make your own
where you only put a little bit of
tahini in there or something like that
or a little bit of olive oil oil in
inside there or you can make a hemp seed
chickpea hemp seed garbanza meat bean
hummus where you take garbanza beans you
throw it in the blender and you throw
some hem seeds in there now I know you
know I know you don't have to look if
you're somebody who wants to go plant
Bas you do want to do that you don't
have to have hummus you could just go
you can go potatoes potatoes are even
amazing for somebody with COPD you do
the celery juices in the morning you do
the fruit smoothies maybe even the heavy
metal detox then you move on to lunch
you have potatoes for lunch with a salad
you have some Yukon Golds you have some
red potatoes you have some rusted you
have some um you know uh some purple
potatoes steam them up throw them on top
of your salad for lunch in the afternoon
you eat some apples after that you you
know you have another celery juice or a
cucumber juice it would even be good
cucumber juice maybe some coconut water
the end of the night have another salad
maybe throw in two one two avocados on
top of your salad maybe have some
butternut squash on there maybe have
something like that you can do that you
can do that and be 100% %
plant-based and while you're plant-based
like that you'll get higher oxygen
levels in your blood because your fats
will be
lower and then you'll be able to start
getting your life back eventually even
doctors end up taking you off of
medications when you start getting
better if you're stage one stage two
stage three uh COPD if you're stage four
depending on what's going on and all
that you're up against and and
everything else it could at least keep
you there and maybe even reverse it a
little bit I have reversed stage four
COPD and a lot of people where they've
moved them to Stage you know I moved
them to stage three moved them to stage
two so you know yeah and you go to your
practitioner you say I want to do all
these things so bring all these things
in if you can that I mentioned I
mentioned a lot I threw a lot at you but
bring them all in that's really
important um so listen I love you guys I
hope we covered you know a decent amount
of this to get through it and uh I stand
behind you 100% you know that and look
you got me I'm yours I'm yours all right
I'm yours all right I'm staying with you
I'm sticking with you we're going to do
this together one show at a time let's
just keep on doing this get the books
because I I can't cover what's in the
books and the shows all right I love you
take care God bless you all right
byebye