we're live right now you guys
i released two new episodes the medical
medium podcast you gotta check it out
link is in the description link is in
the profile you don't wanna miss it one
episode right
lemon water is it really that bad
that's really killer it's awesome
another episode supplements do or don't
you don't want to miss these two
episodes they're highly detailed packed
with information i'm excited it's a new
season going for it man each week coming
out with one every single week wait do
you see next week's but check it out
last night release the lemon water one
you have to check it out we're gonna
make some lemon water we're gonna do
this you guys had a tech problem earlier
so i'm back all right
good to see you guys coming on so i'm
just showing you how simple this is
right i cut a lemon
got a pitcher of water
okay
really easy you can do this and just
leave it in the fridge that's what i do
i leave it in the fridge i'm gonna
answer questions about lemon water
lemon water is a critical medical medium
tool to flush the liver cleanse hydrate
get electrolytes to the brain
that's one of the great reasons to use
it every single day i'm going to answer
some questions about lemon water too
now you don't have to put the whole
lemon in if you don't want you can just
do a half a lemon like that now this is
a lot of water this is more than 32
ounces of water
so i'm gonna be
putting in a whole lemon in here
caddy says i was listening to your
podcast incredible honored
medical meme podcast it's out check it
out right link is in the description you
guys
all right lemon water is it really that
bad because you know what i'm talking
about
right
how many people are like lemons are bad
for your teeth
when my dentist said lemons destroyed my
teeth that's what did it it wasn't all
that other stuff i did it wasn't all the
garbage and the chips i've eaten all
these years
and it wasn't anything else wasn't the
candy i had well candy doesn't really
kill teeth depends on what's in it
that's a whole nother story all the
additives and all the garbage and all
that right but it's like yeah no it was
the lemon water that destroyed my teeth
and ruined them that's what you hear all
the time the dentist is like whoa you
you need five cavities here and
how much lemons are you doing well i had
a lemon like a year ago what do you mean
lemon right
another thing too is if you're doing
lemon water you're actually helping your
teeth and i'm going to go into some
details about that too look i just did
some lemon in here we're all set now
that's a powerful pitcher of lemon water
right there okay now look
16 to 32 ounces is the best way to do it
so you can just take a glass right there
that's like probably 12 ounces
right but 16 ounces just do a half a
lemon right in the glass every single
morning don't do hot water good to see
you guys coming on here we're live right
now
we're talking about the two new episodes
that came out the medical medium podcast
you guys i'm not kidding about this
podcast
you're going to want to see
for yourself you're going to want to
hear for yourself okay i got episodes
that will blow your mind
the lemon water episode will blow your
mind
it's just gonna blow your mind i just
saw lemons and all kinds of stuff and
spit and everything just fly everywhere
just now
you guys i'm not kidding okay
so
for real you got a lemon water right
there every single morning just like
this jennifer says yay hello i can't
wait to listen to it jennifer seriously
when you listen to the lemon water
episode in the thoughts of the
supplement episode that was before there
supplements do or don't
clear done says oh i just squeezed a
slice in a cup i need to do much more i
guess well
yeah
but look i'm not picking on you
if you just do this right here
if you just do a slice
right
okay let me get this glass right here
i'm at your service
look
if you just do this
i'm proud of you okay no judgment here
no judgment if you just do this and a
little bit of that lemon juice just
falls off of that slice right there just
a little bit and goes in that water
i'm proud
very proud if that's all you do
i'm okay with that every single morning
this is what you do i'm not gonna pick
on you i'm not gonna judge you okay
it would be better if you did this right
see the juice come out that would be
better and it would be even better
better if you do this
right you squeeze more of it out and
then
it'd be even better if you took the
other part and you did that
that's better
much better there you go now you got a
glass of lemon water do that first thing
in the morning and flush out that poison
and toxin load which we're going to talk
about
jojo i see a question right there why
not hot water number one question that's
sweeping the nation right there it is
and i'll tell you why because people do
it in hot water now
you're allowed to do your lemon juice
from your lemon in hot water
but you're not gonna get the same
results you're not gonna get the
flushing action now you want a cup of
hot tea in the morning
or you got you got a flu
or something and you you want to drink
lemon and honey hot tea and you need it
hot on your throat right you can do that
and that's fine you're still going to
get medicinals
from that lemon if you do hot water but
this is what's going to go wrong
if you do it for flushing the liver and
flushing toxins it has to be
raw alive and living you go wrong when
it's hot or in hot water when you put it
in hot water like a mug of hot hot tea
when you do that you don't get the
flushing action that you need in the
morning you guys to drive the toxins out
of the body critical to know right there
guys on tick tock just want to let you
know medical medium podcast will blow
your mind i promise you this give it a
shot listen to an episode listen to the
supplement do or don't listen to the
lemon water is it really that bad
episode the medical medium podcast link
is in the profile you guys it's in the
description
right at apple podcast right or even
spotify
but when you listen your mind will be
blown because you're going to do so many
great things for your health once you
learn that vital information it's a
different experience than the lives
right here because you guys know when i
do the lives it's a whole different vibe
right when i'm doing this
but when you hear the podcast
it's an entirely different experience i
want you to check it out when you can
and then make sure you got your
notifications on so you you get each
week that new episode every single week
of the medical medium podcast
i promise you won't be
oh all right hold on you guys hold on i
got it i got a dentist
he's coming in he's going to talk to you
guys he he's got his opinions on lemon
he wants to be helpful so i got a
dentist coming so he's already at the
door so let me just let him in so just
hang on just give me a second you guys
because
i gotta make sure he
gets a chance to talk to you guys
because he's got a lot of cool things to
say
which is really awesome
so
hey dr joey
how you doing
oh good to see you you coming in
are you going to talk to everybody
fantastic
well this is dr jovi
dr joby
this is the dental office
oh no it's not
this is aw's phone
i thought it was my office
i'm here to talk about
lemons oh
lemons
oh it's bad
this is why all my patients
they're losing all their teeth
it's because of these lemons
[Music]
oh oh
oh this is good for your teeth right
here
what's this
this looks like vinegar
vinegar is good for the teeth
oh yeah
lemon's bad for the teeth
oh wait a minute here i can't hold my
pipe in i'm having my own teeth problems
myself
i have to get my veneers fixed soon
yes
i had a dental friend do veneers on me
yes but i have a problem right here it
needs to be fixed
i recommend
i recommend everybody do plenty of
vinegar for their teeth
it doesn't harm the teeth
oh lemon
citrus is bad
very bad
yes
yes yes yes
this looks very good right here a cup of
coffee is what i want
coffee is great for the teeth
yes
okay let's take a look and see what else
we got here oh yeah
this is very good
indeed
every morning
yes dr joby here dentist dds
a dds
um yes doctor of dentistry
every morning i have a cup of coffee
every morning
and i have a bagel yes the bagel's good
for my teeth i floss
after i have the bagel yes
lemons
no wait a minute i brush after i have
the bagel that's what i do i brush when
i have the bagel i just don't floss my
teeth
oh you thought i was a bad dentist did
you
yes yes okay what else do i have here
yeah
hmm this is very good over here
oh
when did this arrive
yeah i have one of these for lunch every
day
i drink make sure
you drink your lemon water
with a straw so you don't damage your
teeth
uh-huh
but i'd rather have you do vinegar
oh yeah do vinegar with a straw no you
don't need a strawberry vinegar
yes
have a cheeseburger
okay
i think
i have to get back i have a patient that
i'm drilling their teeth
i better get back to them right away
okay
i'll let you go
why do i have a stethoscope
i don't know
i have a stethoscope in case my patient
has a problem in the chair and i need to
listen to their heart
let me go back here and find a way
so we're talking about lemons we're
talking about damaging teeth you guys
we're talking about that
you guys medical medium podcast at apple
podcast check it out you'll be blown off
your seat the lemon water episode
okay so it's lemon water is it really
that bad you've got to check that out
i'm proud i promise you you will be
blown away now there's a lot of
misconceptions
about
drinking through a straw right
everybody's like protect your enamel
protect your enamel drink through a
straw that's the way to do it and what
people don't realize you don't have to
protect your enamel with lemon i go into
it in detail on the episode okay
lemons don't hurt your teeth they help
your teeth they help prevent gum disease
they're
antibacterial so that's a key right
there people are loaded with bacteria in
their mouth
multiple kinds of bacteria the bacteria
is eating away at the gums the bacteria
is eating away at the teeth
and so lemon water helps to get rid of
that bacteria helps to clean
the palate it helps to clean the mouth
clean the teeth that's important all in
its own and the misconception out there
is well you can't do lemon on your teeth
but how many people really do lemons how
many people do that much lemon water i
know the medical medium community uses
it as a healing tool you guys you drink
your lemon water 16 to 32 ounces on an
empty stomach and you're using your your
lemon water tool every morning
and then you move on from there and you
do your celery juice right but you're
doing your lemon water but in the world
of dentistry in the world of patients
seeing their dentist there's millions of
people in there in the dentist chair
getting their teeth rolled getting root
canals getting implants getting bridges
getting fillings getting crowns right
getting veneers because their teeth are
so shot
so shot and a big part of their teeth
being so shot is mineral deficiencies so
people don't realize when you're doing
your lemon water you're putting minerals
back into your teeth you're not hurting
your enamel you're not messing your
teeth up you're helping your teeth
because you're actually putting calcium
back into the teeth so that's something
that's really important to know right
there
jeanette says i've been drinking lemon
juice first thing in the morning per
year instructions i have not had any
cavities or teeth problems for a few
years and jeanette the reason why is
because it's helping to stave off
cavities now a lot of people they may
start lemon water and their teeth fall
apart because they were already falling
apart because teeth are like time
capsules and i go into this in detail on
the medical medium podcast you guys on
this episode you got to watch got to
listen to this episode what happens is
our teeth become these mineral deficient
time capsules that through life because
of our deficiencies
and all the acidic foods and all the
vinegar we do right
all the vinegars in our food
all of that we break down the teeth we
destroy them over time vinegar not only
corrodes erodes the enamel off the teeth
but when you have vinegar go into your
body and it's in your bloodstream it's
so acidic that your your teeth throw the
calcium out of it
your bones throw the calcium out of it
and this is really important to know so
here's how it works
the more acidic we are inside our body
the less alkaline we are inside our body
and the more acidic we have to take
calcium from the bones to neutralize it
so the more vinegar you do even if it's
just in a dressing every single day or
in a salsa or something else what's
happening is the calcium inside your
bones is starting to deplete as you're
doing vinegar another one is coffee
right if you're doing your coffee every
single day
what's happening is your body has to
throw calcium reserves into the
bloodstream to buffer it a straw is not
going to save you so if you drink your
coffee with a straw you drink your
vinegar with a straw you drink your
lemon water well lemon water you don't
need a drink with a straw anyway
regardless but if you're drinking with
the straw thinking that's your best bet
you're not going to save your teeth
because it's about what's going into the
bloodstream it's not about what's
touching the teeth so much
vira good to see you let's see i noticed
my teeth get sensitive after drinking
lemon water for a while so let's cover
that right now that's important all of
its own
okay
so what happens elvira is that when
people have sensitive teeth they already
have sensitive teeth lemon water doesn't
make it sensitive it's already sensitive
so if you have a nerve problem a gum
problem a tooth problem any kind of
issue with your teeth mouth trigeminal
neuralgia or just just a nerve that's
had it's been jabbed too many times at
the dentist so it becomes sensitive
because you had the novocaine the
numbing agent the needle went into your
nerve in the jaw right and it just made
it it made it sensitive over the years
so if lemon water you feel it with the
lemon water
you're probably feeling it with other
things too so it's not like you're
living your life and you never had a
tooth sensitivity and all of a sudden
you have lemon water and now you have
one it doesn't work like that i'm sure
that you have sensitivity somewhere
around your tooth with other things that
you either eat or drink because
everybody does right now
the other thing too is people get
sensitive teeth they have sensitive
teeth automatically they get sensitive
if it's cold water going down or if it's
really hot and no ha that'll ring the
bell on a sensitive nerve but lemons
don't make a sensitive nerve lemons help
heal a sensitive nerve susan broon says
i use limes in my water which i have
right here susan cool i use lime in my
water do they work the same as lemons
yes they do incredible if you love lime
that's the way to go
that's a great way to go wendy says my
teeth actually stopped being sensitive
with medical medium protocols amazing
and that i hear that all the time that
people's nerves get stronger in their
mouth because medical medium protocols
so they end up healing so that they're
less sensitive in their mouth which is
incredible all on its own you guys if
you just got on here we're live right
now but i just wanted to announce which
i'm really excited about the medical
medium podcast just released two new
episodes
and it's gonna be mind blowing all right
i'm just letting you know you've got to
hear it one episode is about supplements
do or don't another episode is lemon
water is it really that bad you don't
want to miss it it's mind-blowing you
want to actually have your notifications
on at apple podcast medical media
podcast at apple podcast so that you
know each one that comes out each week
you want to get on my newsletter too so
you can be notified through my
newsletter because i'll send out a
newsletter before also as well so make
sure you sign up to the medical medium
newsletter medicalmedium.com link's in
the descript description already too
so
and sunday videos that are actually
incredible on sunday you guys videos
that i do exclusive on the newsletter so
you've got to check it out
so when it comes down to
acid versus alkaline let's hit that
really quick this is important
information that you might want to know
right
lemons
yes
it's got some citric acid the natural
kind the right kind right so it's got
the acid in here but it's alkaline the
lemon is an alkaline fruit lime two for
the ones that like lime right these are
alkaline what happens is that when those
minerals those alkaline minerals enter
in
okay when they enter in the body these
alkaline minerals an amazing process
occurs
they go alkaline
everything in the lemon goes alkaline so
if it feels like it's not
alkaline because it's acidic that's the
fruit acid that you're experiencing
right
but the minerals in here
turn alkaline because they are alkaline
they change the chemistry of your body
immediately so lemon water is alkalinity
so first thing in the morning you're
getting an alkaline flesh
that's critical to know
so lemon may seem acidic but it's
neutralizing acids it's making you
alkaline internally which is a game
changer for people who are sick and have
problems and all these other issues
so when it comes down to restoring
minerals back into deficient teeth the
lemon water brings alkaline minerals
like calcium because it's high in
calcium back into your teeth to help
restore your teeth
that's
where the money's at right there
because you're actually bringing your
teeth back when you do lemon water
that's how it works i've had thousands
of lemons in my life thousands upon
thousands and i still have every one of
my own teeth
okay
which is incredible
so that's important to know right and
yeah okay they're not perfectly straight
but i never had braces or anything but
whatever i don't have veneers i know all
the podcast doctors they all got veneers
they all got implants you know but you
know who cares if someone has implants
or veneers or some people that have
crowns and root canals i get it and i
totally understand but what i'm saying
is with the podcast doctors is here they
are they're the ones saying these days
watch the lemons watch the lemon on your
teeth meanwhile these guys are just been
drinking coffee all their life
doing whatever vinegar everything else
all their teeth are gone they all got
veneers
you know and at my age
i got all my teeth every last one of
them they're there and they're in top
shape bottom line
and i've done thousands of lemons
thousands upon eaten lemons do the lemon
water
clearly nature says my teeth are so much
stronger with medical medium no more
thin chipping teeth exactly so many
people have the thin chipping teeth
because teeth crumble from the inside
out they are the time capsules manual
says does fermented food also have the
same acidic effect like vinegar
fermented food it all depends on what's
going on with that fermented food a lot
of fermented food has it is acidic okay
it is acidic naturally fermentation
becomes that but it doesn't have the
same effect
kim miller says my teeth were falling
apart
doing acv regularly
doing your protocols have saved my teeth
and they've never been healthier now
here's the funny thing
exactly so you'll see professionals and
health professionals and dietitians and
podcast doctors or whoever out there and
they're promoting the acv they want all
their people to buy their acv brand
right apple cider vinegar meanwhile
they're just promoting people to lose
and destroy their teeth
there's a big difference right there all
on its own you know how much confusion's
out there
um by the way in the fermented food
question that was there earlier actually
just so you know
the kombucha tea right kombucha tea that
is
highly acidic that's got the caffeine in
it that re and it's really acidic that
fermentation process that does hurt
teeth bad so kombucha tea does hurt
teeth really bad
so kim miller says my teeth are falling
apart doing acv regularly doing your
protocols oh you said that incredible
and they're healthier amazing um smokey
mountain paradise i've healed a cracked
tooth
split right down the middle on medical
medium
drop the mic
that's amazing that's incredible
incredible um
gina says
my broken enamel grew back i consume
around 10 pounds of lemons each week
yeah
right and people don't know this
they're in fear every day out there
jeannette says citric acid is not citrus
correct citric acid in supplementation
is corn
it's a byproduct of corn
it's not good either and it's always gmo
citric acid this is different this is an
entirely different kind of citric acid
entirely different sabby says i heard
the episodes they are boring and the
same repeat of the information you have
already mentioned in your lives books
and blogs that's interesting sad because
i'm wondering what episodes you heard
then i think you were listening to
somebody else's podcast
because it was all new information
the whole episode is is like cranking
with info in detail
so i'm like confused i recommend you
read my books again and i recommend you
listen to the episode again or try to
find the episode because i don't think
you heard it okay so but thank you for
listening
nicholas said the podcast episodes are
truly mind-blowing and not at all a
repeat of previous info best podcast
ever nicholas russell thank you
nicholas russell i am at your service
i'm going to deliver another good
podcast as soon as i can
next week there's going to be another
one i am at your service at your service
all right so anyway
all right
let's gather my bearings here we look we
got some comments here i want to read to
you guys
tracy lynn lemon and lime water ghost
thing
i'm the morning's game changer and no
more erosive esophagealitis and all
these years the doctor said to me stay
away from lemons and tomatoes no pain
and teeth are great
incredible well that's what happens
right doctors don't know why we're sick
i want you guys to have doctors but
doctors don't know why we're sick with
chronic illness they don't it's sad but
they don't because scientists don't know
why we're sick with chronic illness so
medical universities don't know why
we're sick with mysterious chronic
illness we know that right
and at the same time they're like
telling you what to do or don't do or
not do meanwhile they don't have any of
the real teeth i know because i know so
many doctors
they don't have their teeth right and
next thing you know they're doing all
the chocolate and they're doing
everything else they're telling people
lots of chocolate that's a great way to
lose your teeth too
so
my teeth have been getting strong so
nisha says my teeth have been getting
stronger with medical medium information
i can actually see how strong my teeth
are now they used to be transparent the
transparent teeth look exactly now they
are solid
boom you're getting all your minerals
back
lamb tails says the sarcasm used to put
me off because i was too serious
and heavy-hearted and you taught me to
lighten up in many ways my inner light
is brighter than ever and getting
stronger
you're actually you're actually getting
me emotional because to think that you
you know that you're okay with my
sarcasm i am honored i'm not kidding
around right now i'm not joking i'm
honored and thank you because i get it i
do have some sarcasm stuff going on i do
joke around a lot because you know i've
had it hard in my life and you know and
i haven't had it easy with hearing
spirits since i was age four and writing
all these medical books these brain
saver books nearly almost killed me i
got to tell you guys incredible brain
saver books that when you when you get
these brain saver books in your hands
though yes it's all worth it it's all
worth it so yeah so i appreciate you
being here for seriously travis
where is the peer-reviewed study saying
acv is bad for you all peer review
studies that know why everybody's sick
the peer review studies that get moms
out of bed that are actually dying
because they
can't even feed themselves they can't
lift up their arms the peer review
studies that have people all healed and
better with multiple sclerosis oh wait a
minute or do you mean how science took
medical medium information that fcmr
causes multiple sclerosis so just so you
know when you say peer-reviewed studies
to medical medium please know science
takes medical mediums information
and they use it and they do it illegally
and we know that because it's already
been published in all the medical medium
books and science takes it later so try
that for your peer review
you guys this is great susan says i love
your podcasts they are so informative
and i feel very relaxed listening to you
phew
phew phew it's nothing more worse than
than feeling like you're annoying
somebody so to know that you're relaxed
and listening makes me very very happy
seriously you guys incredible so we're
talking about lemon water i want to give
you a couple of really killer things to
know about your lemon water flush that's
happening in the morning you guys right
now we're live on all the platforms
practically
and uh we're streaming we're streaming
live on medicalmedium.com right now
and that's why i'm back because we had a
little tech glitch on it but we're
streaming live
on medicalmedium.com right now
which is incredible i'm blown away that
we were able to do that i just want you
to know kim miller says your poems at
the end of the podcasts always bring a
tear to my eye
i never knew i was a poet
i'm honored i'm honored i'm not a poet
but i'm totally honored incredible thank
you thank you spirit spirit gives me
information and i use it on the end of
those podcasts
so i'm i'm excited to know that it's
touching and it actually brings a tear
to your eye and i'm i'm truly honored
truly honored
so yeah elena says dear anthony i am
doing your protocols for more than three
years god bless you
everything like my stomach and thyroid
issues got a lot better but my teeth not
my dentist wants me to use fluoride and
i don't know what to do okay
so okay
look
i've always listened to your doctors but
i would nev me personally would never
touch fluoride ever in a million years
okay
fluoride's a neurotoxin doesn't
strengthen the teeth it destroys teeth
my opinion fine so so i always tell my
family and my friends when they're at
the dentist you avoid
that fluoride treatment
always tell my family and my friends
don't let them put that poison in your
mouth
teeth are time capsules you can be doing
medical medium for three years and
medical medium during those three years
could be stopping your teeth from really
falling apart
see your teeth
all these years being a time capsule
already had the deficiencies already
been damaged by vinegar all along the
way maybe even caffeine chocolate
products coffee products already damaged
along the way you might have come into
this world mineral deficient so your
teeth were already on the trajectory of
falling apart for the future right
then you got onto medical medium and
it's slowing the process down it's
slowing the teeth from really collapsing
and falling apart
because the medical medium information
is like putting on the brakes like
it's like putting on the brakes of a
real problem happening
but you still got work to do lots of
work for restoring and re-mineralizing
and that's important to know you're
doing the celery juice what protocol are
you using medical medium are you doing
the lemon award the cellar juice the
heavy metal detox movie people who have
a lot of heavy metals
in their body
have teeth problems
are they getting all the metals out
you know are they getting the metals out
of their body are they getting the
metals out of their liver
all these things matter
because those time capsules
are a historic history of the past in
your life from all kinds of toxins
poisons coming in here mineral deficient
having toxic heavy metals in your system
all of
this so when you're doing the mm
protocol and everything else is getting
better your thyroid this that your
stomach everything's getting better
everything's getting better think about
how many problems you got right well
your your body's using all those
reserves man your teeth they're just
like time capsules that are deficient
from you being sick all these years too
so it matters that you're even doing
medical medium protocol because not only
are things getting better but you're
halting you're stopping the teeth from
getting worse and worse faster until the
breaks can hit and then it's about now
the teeth are getting better
so you guys we're live right now i
wanted to tell you if you just got on
here you're going to be mind blown when
you listen to the medical meeting
podcast
okay medical medium podcast at apple
podcast go listen to it at spotify2 all
right you got to check it out i just
want to tell you
right now okay when it comes down to
lemon water i'm going to give you guys
this run down really quick
what you're doing in the morning every
morning you do your 16 to 32 ounces you
guys
you're flushing your liver every single
morning when you do your lemon water
you're flushing your liver
keep that in mind all the toxins and
poisons that build up in your liver i
know i showed you this earlier but i'll
show you again okay
because this is important right here
see these chicken wings right here okay
so when we have our chicken wings
because a lot of people have chicken
wings right they'll go out be like i'll
have some chicken wings
okay
they think that once they've gone to
bathroom the chicken wings are gone
yeah that was that was
yeah that was the dinner i had when i
went out to the restaurant with
everybody
that went out into the toilet that's
gone i got a clear you know i got a
clear path now tonight i'm gonna have
pizza is what i'm gonna do tonight
so tonight i'm gonna have pizza that's
what i'm gonna do tonight right
but the good news is tomorrow i'm gonna
poop the pizza out i get a fresh start
a whole fresh start
because it's gone i could poop the pizza
out so that's gone the next night
maybe i'll have something oh yeah
i don't know
maybe i'll have some eggs and some bacon
some hash browns with oil and grease on
them right with lard on them and some
butter and toast but that's okay because
i'll poop that out gone fresh start man
i got a fresh start that's all how i ate
last week i don't have to worry about
anymore
i shed it all out it's gone man
all right wait
and then
i'll have this
the next night but guess what it's gone
too it doesn't work like that
yeah you might be going to bathroom
that's what's happening
but what people don't realize
there's parts of that still in here
that liver over time gets stagnant
sluggish builds up
and then we've got to flush it one of
the tools the medical medium
16 32 ounces lemon water
mm info made the connection to flush the
liver with this guys i'm going to ig
check out the medical medium podcast at
apple podcast when you can two new
episodes right the supplements do or
don't lemon water is it really that bad
they're going to blow your mind i got an
episode coming out every week you guys
want to be ready for them you got to
fasten your seatbelts i'm telling you
right now sign up for my newsletter
because i'm doing exclusive
videos every single sunday on my
newsletter medicalmedium.com make sure
you sign up to that link is in the
description okay
and uh you guys check out tick tock and
everything else we're live on tick tock
we're going to be live back on tik tok
live on telegram and live on ig in just
a few minutes you guys i love you