always want to start out fresh it's a
new year coming on we want to start out
fresh right we want to wipe out the old
we want to clear the past away we want
to forge ahead in the future we want to
clean up things our relationships and
problems we have we don't want to take
them into the next year we try to start
fresh with it all right that's what
everybody tries to do and they start
making different things like what do we
all talk about we're like we start
making different claims of I'm going to
do it right this year I'm going to make
myself better this year I am going to
stay committed I'm not going to smoke
I'm not going to drink I'm not going to
party I'm not going to do some Dangerous
Drug I'm not going to do that I'm not
and everybody's just going like it's a
whole bunch of noise out there in the
world right I'm gonna drop my addiction
I'm going to back off on my addiction
I'm going to lower less coffee I'm going
to back off on chocolate I'm not going
to eat as much I'm not going to eat fast
food I'm going to stay away with crazy
fried food I'm stay
away it's like noise out there of
all of that and everybody is trying to
say say no I'm going to start fresh but
the same time we try to do that we bring
something into the new year which is all
the toxins and garbage and crap and
poisons and crud that are in our body
from the year previously right so we got
all that sitting in us from what
happened last year and we bring it right
into the new year so we take the past
with us we take the Christmas past we
take the Thanksgiving past we take the
holiday past of whatever we ate during
that time we take it right into the new
year we take everything all the poisons
toxins all the toxic heavy metals we
gathered all the different cologn and
perfumes and air freshers we breathe in
and all the different cans we drink out
of and all the metals in different areas
and aluminum foil and everything else
that we've ever been in touch with from
deodorants and everything else we use we
bring it all in to the next year all the
different pesticide spray herbicide
spray and all the gardens and all the
people's properties and yards all the
different Lawn Care around buildings and
apartments all the different fragrances
we breathe in and all the different
detergents and fabric softeners and
everything from After Shave to just all
kinds of stuff and body lotions and
essential oil products that have
fragrances in them which is toxic like
you name it we bring it all into the
next year that's it we take it with us
but we can mentally say I'm starting out
fresh I'm working with this new um you
know like coach that builds up your
confidence I'm working with this new
fitness coach I'm working with this
person and that person I'm starting out
fresh but you're bringing in all your
garbage from the past you're bringing
all that junk and crud and poisons and
toxins you're bringing it right into the
new year and that's what you're doing
but that's just the reality that's just
how it works here on planet Earth I
don't I don't expect anything different
I don't I don't expect anything
different we bring in all the stuff into
the New Year we're doing the morning
cleanse that's what we're doing we're
talking about the morning cleanse but
I'm making a lot of different stuff and
we're going to talk about all the
different toxins we have inside of us
that we take into the next year you name
it you guys doing the heavy metal detox
smothie you better believe it heavy
metal detox smoothie that's what we're
going to do I'm excited about that heavy
metals does anybody have heavy metals
yes we do depersonalization anxiety
depression eema
psoriasis all kinds of other things that
people have
bipolar ups and downs emotional
struggles that are
unidentified mystery sadness mystery
guilt mystery everything all the
different emotional struggles we have
toxic heavy metals OCD does anybody have
OCD out there at all any kind of OCD do
you know anybody that has OCD or
struggling with OCD toxic heavy metals
that's what they have and so we're going
to make a lot of different stuff I have
some Millet in this pot yes Millet I got
steamed potatoes right here I'm going to
give you an
introduction introduction please oranges
mangoes bananas cilantro lemons wild
blueberries till this day I see it out
there I'm making blueberry with ever I
got a blueberry smoothie I love
blueberries in my bar I love blueberries
and they're all regular blueberries
cultivated blueberries we got wild
blueberries that takes it to the next
level we got some raisins over there
Believe It or Not raspberries
blackberries which are actually pretty
close to the wild blueberry to some
degree pomegranate seeds over there
apples and pears in the front you can't
see mangoes am I missing something
oatmeal watermelon right there
nothing like a delicious watermelon here
we go and we got so much more so giving
you guys The
Rundown we're giving the liver a chance
to breathe we're giving the liver a
chance to heal so I want to bring this
little guy over
here so our liver gets filled up with
all kinds of different junk garbage free
radicals all kinds of different toxins
our livers get toy they get filled with
yellow crud they get swollen they get
inflamed they go and we don't
even realize it our livers malfunction
every single day they become fatty our
livers become fatty you can see someone
who's like they look like they're cut
they don't got a scrap of fat on them
they're in the gym and they can have a
liver where it just starts to
malfunction and it starts to become a
fatty liver and then they're they go to
the doctor and their liver enzymes are
up and the whole bit they got
cholesterol problems and everything else
cuz their liver's malfunctioning you
don't have to be somebody that's
overweight have a sluger stagnant liver
you can be someone who's built someone
who's got muscle someone who's in the
gym and their livers have problems I
can't tell you how many workout guys
lose their liver they still lose they go
into liver failure happens every time
you can if you actually did a search
through all the different hospitals
around the world you'll find somebody
getting a liver transplant that was
bodybuilding and looking good no fat on
their body and they're getting a liver
transplant it just happens to people
that are overweight happens to people
that are actually you know fine-tuned
and toned or built so the liver is
something that gets a break when we do
the morning cleanse so you guys do have
the book cleanse to heal it's a great
book right there to actually to really
to really work with
so cleanse the heel cleanse to heel has
the morning cleanse in it it is an
incred incredible incredible powerful
cleanse and it's really really helpful
for so many people who use it people
live by it they do it every day it keeps
people alive it keeps them strong it
keeps them healing and healthy so we're
doing the morning cleanse so that's what
we're doing and I want to get some other
stuff too I want to get some props and
I'll be right back really quick and take
a
look
for
you know that's why when you do I forgot
my props that's what happens when you're
live right here so what do we have we
got Burgers we got these right here who
has Burgers all the time a lot of people
still eat them every day who has the
pancakes who has the ice creams who has
the chocolate cakes who has all of it so
many people have these things all the
time I'm going just get some props out
here you guys and it's not about
punishment it's not about guilt it's not
about we shouldn't be eating something
and now we need to punish ourselves it's
not about that at all it's about the
reality that so many people still eat
things that are not healthy for them
still eat things that are not productive
for them they still eat things that
actually can even hold them back or set
them back it just happens every day it's
a hard world out there and we have
emotional attachments to food this is an
ice cream right here that I'm going to
have after the show I can't wait a
Triple Decker chocolate espresso ice
cream I'm excited about this it's so
high in caffeine I'm going to be
bouncing off the walls killing my
adrenals and killing my liver but I
don't care because I want to indulge and
have a cheat day so I'm definitely going
to have this right here you guys going
into the new year a lot of people don't
start doing good things for themselves
on the day one of the new year it
usually takes to be like January 15th
everybody's like I'm going to do it on
the 15th it's January 15th that's what
I'm going to do it another person is
like I'm going to do it by the end of
January I'm going to start February 1st
and there's this thing that happens
where people are like know I'm going to
do it in 3 days 7 Days 10 days next
thing you know it it's like February 1st
it's February 15th and then they're just
like screw it I can't do it and a lot of
people end up like that but we can start
January 1st January 2nd we can do that a
lot of people are just getting over
their their hangovers and they don't
want to start anything because they're
still filled with alcohol and all kinds
of other stuff and fun Foods in their
blood streaming
system so the whole thing with the
morning cleanse is just so great because
if you do it every single day you're
protecting your liver even if you're
somebody that's just eating whatever
like if you're having chicken if you're
somebody that eats animal protein and
you have chicken every day if you do the
morning cleanse and then you have
chicken at the end of the day you're
still doing incredible powerful things
for your liver especially if the heavy
metal detox smoothie is in your morning
cleanse if that's in there you're really
working on getting the metals out
getting the junk out the garbage out
it's really powerful so so many people
they'll have like you know grassa beef
or some kind of animal product have it
at the end of the day do the morning
plans in the morning keep the fats out
in the morning the first half of the day
that's the key right there so how does
this work if you like salmon if you like
fish if you like chicken if you like
meat if you like avocados if you like
nuts and seeds whatever it is that's an
overt fat keep it out until after 12
then I actually prefer if you keep it
out even longer than that maybe till 3
keep overt fats out till 3 if you're
going to have the over fats you can even
go later keep them out till 6 if you'd
like but but I'm going to go into the
morning cleanse a little bit and what
that means to start with lemon water
that's one thing right there so let me
start getting some things out and then
we'll talk about what this morning
cleanse does for the liver what it does
for the body and we go into that so I'm
excited all right so I'm going to crack
open a lemon right here you
guys this is how easy it
is the morning cleanse is so hard I
can't do it it's just too hard I just
did it just did a piece of it right
there for you simple is that 16 to 32 oz
of water squeeze a half a lemon right in
it and you're
good
okay not hot
water don't do hot water so it's really
important to know all right cold water
is fine luk warm water water is fine
room temperature water is fine don't do
hot water you just destroyed the lemon's
ability to give you a liver flush in the
morning to flush out the toxins and the
poisons you took the lemon and you
cooked it once you cook the lemon it
does something different now you can
cook lemon you can put it in food you
can prepare food you can put it in
dishes and stir fries and cook it down
it's fine but when you put lemon
in hot water you destroyed the
mechanisms phytochemical compounds that
work in a specific way with the Living
Water built inside of that lemon and the
calcium that comes deep within the clay
of the earth that goes in the lemon
roots and up into the lemon tree and out
into that fruit you just annihilated all
of it basically you have yeah still some
nutrients and still some good stuff in
there but you destroyed the living Fresh
Fresh Living power that it has from the
traes minerals and phytochemical comp
compounds that have to stay floating in
this suspension of living water inside
of the lemon you destroyed it when you
do hot water keep that in mind so and CU
I see it every day I'm doing my my hot
lemon water I'm doing my hot lemon water
aw I'm like great that's good glad to
hear that it's not doing what it needs
to do it's doing something else it's
good for you it's great for you it might
help you go to the bathroom a little bit
that does happen right so if you do that
it might help you in a different way but
it's not going to help you with what
you're trying to do flush out the liver
flush out the toxins and poisons so the
first part of the morning cleanse is you
take water 16 to 32 ounces right there
you take a lemon cut it in half you
squeeze it right there if you want to do
the whole lemon do the whole lemon if
you want to do half do half if you want
more fine if you want less fine you can
be somebody that doesn't like lemon then
just do this check this out ready 3 4 5
6 7 8 nine 10 drops just do that
just that I hate lemon aw I don't like
it medical medium then just do this you
ready one 2 3 4 5 6 7 that's it or 1 2 3
4 that's all you can do that I prefer
you do a whole half like this boom done
you want to do a whole one do a whole
one okay your liver is working hard
overnight it's Gathering up poisons and
toxins it's working for you so that's
what the liver does
all night long while you're sleeping
your liver's awake a lot of times people
can't sleep good cuz the livers are
spasming because they're working hard
they're malfunctioning they're having
difficult difficult abilities to work
difficult difficult time functioning so
what happens is as your liver is working
all through the night cleaning out the
toxins and cleaning out the poisons and
getting them ready to be packaged up to
go out the door to get to the kidneys
and go out the door the lemon water
comes in first thing in the morning and
starts to grab onto the garbage and
flushes it out that's the key but once
again important information get a piece
of paper out get a pen okay no hot water
with the lemon it just doesn't work it
won't give you that flush it won't help
your skin it won't help your body detox
it won't help your bloodstream clean up
it won't help your lymphatic system so
you go into a spa and you go in there
you know what they give you now in the
spa besides cucumbers on the eyes you
know what they give you they give you a
cup of hot lemon water why thank you oh
fantastic I'm glad I'm spending $75,000
in this Spa right now can you give me a
hot glass of lemon water that sucks it's
not going to even flush or cleanse me on
any level that's how it works and that's
what they do they give out hot lemon
water you want it lukewarm room
temperature I just have to say I have to
say say a thousand times and guess what
5 years from now I'll be saying it again
because there going to be a whole bunch
of people that are putting it in hot
water it's like crazy okay so that's the
first part of it right
there let's go into the second part what
I like for the morning
cleanse is celery
juice celery
juice do you guys remember in the celery
juice book I put something back there
somewhere deep into the celery and Juice
book how they're going to try to take
down celery juice knock it down out
there say it's not really helpful say it
doesn't do anything just eat a celery
stick that's still going on out there
there's also a bunch of rumors out there
celer is bad for your skin celery's you
know bad for this bad for that they're
still doing it out there the truth is
though they can't keep enough celery in
the world in stores they can't keep
enough in stock it is the biggest
produce crop herb crop there is on the
planet right now the largest there are
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of celery Farms because of medical medum
information everywhere on the planet
growing celery there are trucks that
deliver it just filled with celery not
apples and celery not apples and
cucumbers and C celery that's how insane
it is it's in every health food store
worldwide you can go into every hotel
and order a celery juice right now
that's how serious it is
and so there's a reason for that because
it really does help people heal whether
they know it or not in in the sense
where they you know whether they feel it
or don't feel it it's changing their
lives it's why they keep on drinking it
because they know it's doing something
one way or the other it might not do
something within a minute but it might
do something within a day it might not
do something within a day for one person
but then it does something in a month
where it changes their life everybody's
different I see acid reflux go away in
one week for people I see skin problems
go away in one month for people celery
juice is one of these incredible
Miracles that we have an herbal medicine
Miracle that's at your fingertips it's
the second thing I would recommend for
the morning cleanse right here is celery
juice I got mine I'm excited here it is
so you got your lemon water you got your
celery juice the next is you can go
anywhere with this okay you can just do
plain fruit you can cut up some apples
you can do that you can do a lot of
different things you can do apples you
can do pears anything you want to do
grapefruit I was doing some grapefruit
juice I have it right here I'm going to
have another sip right now if you don't
mind so
good you can do apples you can do a
fruit plate you can have pears I'm
cutting up a few right
now all
right you can just have plain fruit is
what I'm trying to say
just plain old
fruit you can make a nice fruit dish you
can put assortment of apples and berries
together I got blackberries right here I
got raspberries right there and
blueberries so what I love about the
morning cleanse is that you're not
fasting fasting taxes the
adrenals that's what taxes the adrenals
I hear out there a bunch of
different rumors that started by
naysayers and haters and critics and
they say oh cleansing too hard on
medical medium cleansing too hard it's
hard on my adrenals well that's funny
because it's not hard on your adrenals
it's impossible to be hard on your
adrenals unless you stop eating if you
stop eating for a complete day if you do
a water fast for seven days if you do a
water fast if you do intermittent
fasting if you don't eat all day but you
drink coffee that's hard on the adrenals
that is what hurts adrenals right there
another thing that's hard on the
adrenals if you're eating too much over
it fat over it fat takes adrenaline to
actually help disperse okay so what
happens is when we eat too much
overfat the overfat doesn't get broken
down too easy because the bile reserves
are low in the liver it's not dispersing
the fat well enough the fat ends up in
the bloodstream
too high in the bloodstream you end up
getting insulin
resistance the body then calls for
adrenaline and your adrenals are now
pumping out adrenaline the adrenaline is
to thin out the blood it's kind of like
gasoline turpentine it's a thinner a
blood thinner so that's what adrenaline
is for us it thins out the blood
adrenaline is used for all kinds of
things like if you're exercising what
happens if your blood is too thick and
you're exercising Ing and your heart
starts to struggle cuz your blood is so
thick cuz you're it's all filled your
bloodstreams filled with fat while
you're exercising while you're running
or doing something what happens is that
after your exercising your adrenals will
release more and more adrenaline to get
into your bloodstream to try to thin out
the blood so you don't die of a heart
attack while you're
exercising so our adrenals are always
that blood thinner for us keeping the
fats dispersed keeping the blood thinner
so we don't have a heart attack we don't
have a stroke and that's what our
adrenals do but what happens is when
we're eating over fats in the morning
now our adrenals are boom all on if you
have chocolate if you have cream in your
coffee if you have something like an
avocado in the morning your adrenals are
now releasing adrenaline to try to
disperse it and thin it out I'm not
saying avocado is bad that's not it
something you can eat later on in the
day but people are used to running on
their own adrenaline they're addicted to
their own adrenaline that's what people
are
they have
adrenal addiction epinephrine adrenaline
addiction that's what they have they run
an adrenaline all day long and they like
it it feels good gives them energy feels
like they got energy they're on caffeine
they're on chocolate they're on coffee
they're on espressos they're on Macha
tea they're on green tea and they got
that caffeine pumping and so their
adrenals are just constantly pumping so
they're on adrenaline then they hop on a
treadmill or their EX exercising they're
exercising trying to use up all that
adrenaline right and then they go and
they eat something where I'm going to
eat a whole bunch of high protein or a
whole bunch of protein they end up
eating a whole bunch of fat with that
protein because it's mixed in it's
naturally there and when they do that
their adrenals are now doing it again
they're just releasing adrenaline
adrenaline so we live on adrenaline
we're Adrenaline Junkies most of us walk
around like that the morning cleanse
protects your
adrenals adrenal glands medical medium
cleanses bring your adrenals back so
much so so much so that when you go off
of a medical medium
369 you go off of a medical medium 28
day
cleanse you go off of a medical medium
mono eeding cleanse your adrenals got so
strong and so preserved and so reserved
that boom you can go eat your vegan
pizzas you can go eat your chocolates
you can go eat your gar garbage you can
go eat your stuff and you're like oh my
God I can eat again I'm feeling great
I'm doing great and your adrenals are
just strong and they're and they're
releasing adrenaline and you're feeling
better because you did all the work you
re you basically refurbish them all
throughout the time you're doing the
medical medium cleanses you restored
them all throughout the time you're
doing medical medium cleanses and so
what people don't realize is that
medical me cleanses bring back the
adrenals now
intermittent fasting is not a medical
medium cleanse it destroys the
adrenals water
fasting long term for reasons that are
not
emergency is not a medical medium
thing it's not and that destroys the
adrenal
glands so there are lots of different
things that hurt
adrenals and medical medum information
doesn't do that it's not about
that it's about preserving the adrenals
keeping them strong keeping them healthy
I got some Millet in the pot right here
I think it's done turning this off right
here for a
moment you look for this right here I
take a look you guys oh yeah that's
nice that is definitely good let's make
some banana oat breakfast cookies let's
do
that all right let's move some of this
we're going to talk about adrenals a
little bit more and the liver a little
bit more
too I want to make sure that whatever
you're taking into the new year poisons
toxins junk garbage that's inside of
your body I want to make sure you get
rid of it this is the year coming up
where you cleanse to heal this is the
year here you cleanse to actually heal
and get over the finish line and the
morning cleanse is a protective measure
so that if you mess up and you're this
like I'm at a fast food restaurant
there's nothing I could do I just gobble
down a double cheeseburger that your
morning cleanse is helping to protect
you that it's actually helping to
protect you through the process of a
hard year or a hard day or a hard month
or whatever it is a hard emotional
moment that we end up doing something
where eat a chocolate bar will you know
my morning cleanses help to protect me
whatever it
is you start your day with something you
can accomplish something you can get
done if it's simple as just lemon water
boom get your juicer out make yourself
some celery juice
boom maybe do the heavy metal detox
movie and drive Metals out of your brain
and your liver and your body boom we'll
do that this year why
not and if it means starting January 1st
we start January 1st if it means
starting another time we do it but we
will do it because this is about
cleansing to heal this time and that's
where we're going I want to start making
a couple of things you guys I got a lot
to do all right and some roll Nots right
here you can take a
look okay and I am going to before I do
anything with those roll rops I'm going
to take a bowl right here I'm going to
mash up four bananas let's go four
bananas is what I
want start your day with something you
can accomplish in the morning every
single day some lemon water some celery
juice but I'm going to give you a lot of
different options okay I'm just
making what you see right here is some
oatmeal cookies banana oatmeal cookies
because guess what you can do it and
still be on the morning cleanse if you
want to eat this at some point in the
morning you can still do it and be on
the morning cleanse how insane is
that it's
incredible so we're going to make also a
millet porridge that's something you do
and we're going to make hardboiled eggs
so you guys want to stick around for the
hardboiled
eggs I'm making hardboiled
eggs all right I feel so bad for eating
chocolate for the past 10 days it's okay
we can do the morning cleanse we can do
the morning cleanse is what we can
do don't feel bad we'll do the morning
cleanse I'm excited it's all right
there's a reason why you're eating
chocolate for the last 10 days there is
a
reason it could be anything emotional
emotional reason you're having a tough
time maybe a difficult time maybe you're
under stress maybe you're going through
a lot maybe you're just addicted and
you're having that chocolate because you
feel like you need it that the addiction
maybe you're running on adrenaline
because of that chocolate it's it's
cranking your adrenaline it's keeping
you functioning for the moment maybe
it's helping your brain where you're
thinking a little better and clearer but
it's it's kind of a vicious cycle
because you're thinking a little clearer
and then all of a sudden you got to come
down from it it's like a roller coaster
ride the chocolate brings you
up tread every on the roller coaster is
going up you're going up and then
everybody goes
down get the chocolate back in there
chocolate bar okay okay that's enough
chocolate it's going screaming screaming
it's more
chocolate and it's over and over again
it's like a vicious
cycle that's what it
is all right
I'm just mashing up these bananas right
here I'm also going to put a couple of
other things in here
too put some cinnamon in here and I'm
going to put some raisins in here all
right don't feel bad that you're eating
chocolate instead what we're going to do
is we're going to change some things
we're going to bring in something like
the morning cleanse and then it's going
to help us and it's going to empow and
then we're going to be able to let go of
the RS of the chocolate demon because
the chocolate demon is brutal it's a
brutal demon a chocolate demon it's got
the world trapped putting cinnamon in
here if you don't mind excited about
that a little touch of that in there I'm
going to pop some raisins in here do you
want to see these raisins look at these
golden raisins going in okay nice you
guys see these raisins right there
incredible
chocolate is something that has really
got a lot of people trapped I'm going to
put a cup in here roughly a lot of
people trapped there we
go and you can't get
out can't get out and then we're going
to do four cups of gluten-free oats
we're going to do that right here we
have it this bowl we're going to
flip we're going to knock the bananas
four bananas in here like
that now oatmeal cookies I happen to
like them is that okay or is that bad or
is that good are you guys all right with
that are you guys judging me on these
oatmeal cookies I hope not don't judge
me
please you can judge me if you want I'm
okay with that everybody does don't
worry everybody's like wait what's he
doing now he's doing oatmeal cookies
what you'll find right here is there's
no oil there's no butter there's nothing
like that in these oatmeal cookies
there's no overt fat in these oatmeal
cookies keep that in mind you guys these
are fat free fat free now there's a
little bit of fat a little bit fat in
every single food there's a little bit
of fat in lettuce keep that in mind
there's a little bit of fat in kale
there's a little bit of fat and
everything but there's not overt fat
we're not adding oils in here vegetable
oil or anything else like that Sophie
Norr says I could cry I'm so glad you're
here supporting us CW December has been
such a rough month thank you love you so
much Sophie I'm glad to be here I'm
honored to be here truly okay I believe
that I am blessed to be here talking to
you guys right now truly am blessed and
I am honored for sure okay I'm just
mixing this up really nice right now I'm
getting the
bananas and the oats all nice and mixed
there we
go and we're going to make a bunch of
things I'm making the heavy metal detox
smoothie as well and I'm making
hardboiled eggs do you guys want to
stick around for that I hope you're okay
about that but these hardboiled eggs are
going to be so
good so good you
guys I can't
wait do you believe your ears right now
I'm going to make hardboiled eggs
I can't believe I'm going to make
hardboiled eggs all
right but are they really are they
really hardboiled eggs what's he talking
about all right so what I did was I
mixed
up these and now I'm going to actually
turn them into
cookies I got my little pan
here I'm going to put it right here you
guys you see that yep okay the recipe is
in cleans here right here now listen
we're doing the morning cleanse you can
actually still cleanse while eating
gluten-free banana o cookies right there
there we go you guys see them you can
actually still cleanse while eating
this I mean and that is
powerful powerful to know all right
let's start getting these
going guys I got a lot of moving Parts
going on today let's just hope I don't
mess something up how big do you like
your cookies you like them small I like
them a little bigger popping that one in
there I don't really like tiny
cookies I know that like sometimes
people make them really small I like
making them bigger but you know what
that's a little too big right
there I'm going to make
these
nice you make a smaller cookie you can
eat more of them right people do that
they're like they feel like they are
less guilty if they eat a bunch of small
ones but you don't have to be guilty
about these I'm
excited all right make some different
sizes here so what happens is if you
keep the overt fats out of your diet out
of your way in the morning your liver
can actually clean this means that if
you've eaten fat in the morning most of
your life your liver never got a chance
to ever cleanse cleanse as far as things
that are deep deep inside your liver
never got a chance to cleanse out
poisons and toxins that were deep in
there maybe a few surface toxins escaped
a few surface
toxins but not the Deep stuff definitely
certainly not the metals for sure no
metals are coming out toxic heavy metals
sit inside the liver inside the organs
in the brain for a lifetime until you
wake up one morning you're like who Am I
who am I until you wake up in the
morning and you're walking down the
street in your
underpants and you're actually
jaywalking in your underpants
and there's a alert out on you because
you're
missing that's what
happens when the metals build up and the
metals build up and they build
up they build up until you're at your
psychiatrist's office on four
anti-depressants and then on four anti-
anxieties the metals build up and build
up until your OC CD is so bad that you
are just totally freaked out with
everything that's happening in your life
and you're suffering and this is not a
joke you're
suffering the metals can build up so
bad where you know your eczema and your
psoriasis and your skin problems are
really really out of
control metals can build up so bad that
your autoimmune and your chronic
fatigue can get just so bad because
viruses like the upsteam bar are feeding
off your metals and you're really
struggling and then people don't realize
they can get so bad that you can get to
the point where you don't you have like
delusions you actually don't even know
who you are or where you are anymore
dementia not just
Alzheimer's and so Metals create a lot
of trouble in so many people all right
we got some cookies right
there can I rinse my
hands is it okay can I ask permission
you guys can I rinse my hands for a
second you okay with that all right
let's go this is going in the oven take
a
look guys take a close look if you can
I'm going to show you right
here those are quick banana oatmeal
cookies going right
in yep here you
go
all right it's baby Z at
350 so what's incredible about this
let's uh let's maybe make the heavy
metal detox let's do that all
right going to bring this blender
over going to pop some stuff in
it first of all I'll do it this way
first all right two cups Frozen wild
blueberries
that's what I like to put in I don't
have any blueberry juice in the
moment but I'm going to
put two cups of these babies in right
now all
right can put more you can put a little
less if you really want but two cups is
really what you should do that would be
better let's pop a couple of bananas in
here
okay this heavy metal detox Smoothie has
saved lives it's got people out of
wheelchairs all around the
world it's got people's minds back it's
reverse brain conditions it's reverse
cranial nerve inflammation they didn't
even know they had it's gotten rid of
everything in people from tingles and
numbness and aches and pains and
depersonalization and panic and
anxiety it's gotten rid of skin
problems the heavy metal detox
smoothie is the most powerful there is
out there in the world is the healthiest
the mildest on the body gentle doesn't
give people side effects and it's even
helped people who were cutting
themselves the
hmds has literally stopped many people
from cutting their arms and their
legs that's how powerful the hmds is
okay I never wanted underestimated
because it is unbelievable it is reverse
suicidal thoughts and so many people out
there in the
world it has
reversed suicidal thoughts for so many
people this is
huge it's a big deal it's revers
depression anxiety crippling panic
it's reversed
depersonalization OCD it's reversed
autism
ADHD that's how powerful this is it has
a track record this isn't about let me
just throw in a couple of things in here
and try to become an influencer and get
out there in the circuit and be like
well I'll put a little zealite in here
I'll put a little Bentonite in here I'll
put a little something in here let me
make my own heavy metal detox blend that
has no track record hasn't healed people
and brought their lives back but let me
just make something because I hear
metals are so popular now this one is
worldwide known for a reason because of
what it's done for people it has the
track record for a long time reversing
people's conditions and bringing their
life back and that right there is
incredible cold White Springs says I
know I got rid of my
depression that's what the medical
medium hmds has done for
people brought them back to
life brought them back from the grave a
lot of people broughten back from the
grave broughten back from mattress
Island couch
Island this should never ever be taken
for granted that's what s so tells me to
me all the time because I've said the
hmds a zillion times I have made it
thousands upon thousands of times for
family and
friends I've talked about it
forever and spirit has always told me do
not take this thing for granted because
it is the most powerful tool there is
right now in this day and age with what
what's happening with people and their
diseases and their symptoms and
conditions it's one of the most powerful
of all is the hmds anyway we got bananas
in there let's pop some cantro in there
one cup of
cilantro coming right
up all right I'm going to put the douls
liquid dos
here in I'm going to put two dropper
fulls of the liquid dou in there nice
you can put the regular do if you want I
got that one I'm going to pop in the
barley grass cheese powder I'm going to
pop in the spirulina okay so let's get
these
in
teaspoon of that in
there teaspoon of this spiruline in
there all right I'm going to pop some
oranges I'm going to squeeze some orange
in
there okay move this over for a second
let's cut
these all right Anna Dominguez says I
got rid of my debilitating migraines
that I suffered from for over 25 years
thank you aw and
so all right let's squeeze it you guys
sorry about the loud noises from banging
stuff
around there you
go I can be much more gentler I can be
like
this and I'll put the knife down like
this
and
then then we'll never get done all right
look okay I'm just squeezing some orange
in here juice from one orange I'm
putting two little oranges in you guys
don't
mind all right let's blend this
up you can add a little bit of coconut
water in there you can add a little bit
of water in there too to get it to spin
you can do it a couple different ways
like that you can add a little bit of
liquid that's
okay I might add
[Music]
some we
go metal detox
withing worldwide
no Kyrie says you're super L super L
what you
do
[Music]
nice we did it you guys we did
it
incredible all
right I'm going to pour this in here
there it is guys could take a closeup
too on that and see what you think there
you there you go that is medical medium
heavy metal detox
movie the one that has changed lives all
around the
world the one that
has help repair the nervous system in so
many that has removed Metals you know
what I love I love hearing this he
doesn't know about
binders medical medium doesn't know
about binders
ERS he's he's he doesn't get it he
doesn't know you should listen to me
I'll give you the binder talk really the
wild blueberry is the ultimate
binder the ultimate ultimate
binder okay I'm just going to be
straight out here the reason why you
don't hear me talk about
binders because the ultimate binder is
actually in the drink that's why I I
don't need to talk about binders but you
guys need to talk about binders out
there that are like naysayers are like
he doesn't know about
binders all
right anyway there it is right there the
pectin from the wild blueberry by far
one of the greatest ultimate binders the
wild blueberry and the anthocyans are
the ultimate
binder and so have you noticed something
have you guys noticed something the wild
blueberry what it does have you noticed
something about what happens here it
gels up have you noticed that it starts
to gel take a look right here give it a
little time how many of you guys made
the heavy metal detox smoothie and it
gelled up to the point where it was like
jello where you're doing this like clunk
clunk clun clunk clunk and it was like
jell give it a couple of minutes it's
congealing right now as we
speak why is it
congealing that's the
binder that is is the wild the
blueberry that is the ultimate binder
right there that's what it's for nobody
knew that the wild blueberry had
anything to do with removing toxic heavy
metals that's mm info right nobody knew
that ever okay because a berry won't do
it a just a plain old Berry won't do it
a cultivated blueberry won't do it
people don't know people didn't know it
did it they had no idea what could even
take out of metal and now worldwide
right now people are talking about oh
the wild blueberry and the other things
that are in here and and the key is
you'll see like it's starting to now gel
right there it is it's starting to turn
into Jello-O so it's now getting thicker
and thicker right it's congealing right
there in front of us that's what it's
doing so it's getting less liquidy by
the minute how many of you guys have
left your heavy metal detox smoothie
somewhere like on the counter or
something in somewhere in the kitchen or
maybe in your office or in your car and
it basically turned into almost like
jello where if you dump the glass over
it would it would come out almost in one
piece how many people have done that
that's the
binder it's why I've never talked about
a binder because it is a
binder that is one of the things that we
need to understand
but it's amazing any anywhere someone
can get away with anything they can
they'll be like okay let's throw that at
him let's try to chop him down a little
bit let's try to chip away at him a
little bit more let's say he doesn't
know anything about binders let's start
talking about all the bonite clay and
all the other stuff and all the other
garbage that we're putting in the smooth
let's talk about that dude you missed it
you missed the boat it is a binder sorry
anyway and there it is heavy metal detox
smoothie it is the ultimate nature B
says oh my God I think I have the wrong
blueberries European ones they don't gel
it's because they could be calling them
the wild blueberry but they're not a
wild blueberry I noticed in Europe they
do that so there's a there's there's
they use like bilberries and stuff like
that and they call them a wild blueberry
but they're not a wild blueberry and
people just don't know this so all
through Europe right now that's what's
happening they're not using the wild
blueberry they're not they're using a
different Berry and that different Berry
might have a different makeup of
antioxidants it might even be higher
than an antioxidant but that's not the
key that's not how it works for removing
Metals it takes the wild bluebery to
remove metals because there's a
difference because of its binding
properties are unlike anything else and
unmatched and you can't measure that
good luck go ahead and try The Binding
properties in the wild blueberry
supersede anything in the European what
they call a wild blueberry that's a
billberry or whatever supersedes
it
and that's how it works it's not about
how much antioxidant you have that
doesn't determine how like if the metals
leave or not that's only and there's
different antioxidants you can't just BL
do a blatant thing where you're saying
antioxidant and there all every antiox
there's antioxidants in coffee does that
take out Metals no instead it kills your
brain there's like you you have to
understand you can have an antioxidant
in something there's antioxidant in
psilocybin
but it doesn't mean it's good for you on
any level there's antioxidants in every
Berry but it doesn't mean it's going to
be the one to remove the
metals so what I noticed in Europe and
it's just no no disrespect on any level
but I'm noticing they're packaging up
different berries out there and they're
telling people that this is going to do
it this is going to remove your Metals
this is what you use in the hdms this
here's what it is and what they don't
realize is it may have a different
composition of antioxidant it may maybe
maybe even a higher composition of
antioxidant doesn't mean that's the
antioxidant that helps in guiding Metals
out and it doesn't mean that's the one
that has the high enough gelatinous
binder that doesn't mean any of that and
that's the difference and that's the
difference with s so and why things work
and what they don't they also haven't
discovered all the antioxidants that
they're able to even measure in the wild
BL to be to begin with they haven't even
measured them and looked at all of them
and that's a whole another thing on its
own it's what works it's not about
waiting for science every second it's
about what works and what the track
record is the track record of people
getting out of wheelchairs the track
record of people getting rid of
depression that's the track record I'm
talking about not some article somewhere
that's going to chop up a bunch of
studies that never really happened it's
about what is going to work because when
you're Downing out and you're on your
hands and knees and you're praying to
God and you're like I'm going to die if
I don't get better I am literally think
I think I'm going to die my I have 50
neurological symptoms no no one
understands me no one gets what I've
gone through and what I'm going through
and I think I'm dying and I have no hope
left it's about what works that's when
it counts boom it's about what works and
that's where it is and I'm noticing out
there I get it there's a lot of people
that are like just like no you can put
this Berry inside of a canister you can
put this Berry inside of a glass jar and
look or whatever you want to do and
Market it the way you want doesn't mean
that's a wild blueberry they may call it
a wild blueberry you can call anything
yeah okay sure here's a wild blueberry
everybody here it is this is a wild
blueberry I'm going to put it in a
package now that's a Blackberry but no
I'll call it a wild blueberry that's
what people can do and it's crazy point
is is the wild blueberry what you see
right here that's the one and it's
getting actually starting to really
congeal right now and get actually to a
point all right you guys I'm just saying
this because there's a lot of people
that they don't
know they may not know why they're
healing as fast as they want to heal and
that's that's part of it too so it all
matters every little bit matters The
Details Matter so we just made the heavy
metal detox smoothie boom we got that
done let's make a porridge right now
okay let's we can get on to
that all right
so if you want something harder if
you're one of those people that are like
you like bacon and eggs in the morning
we still got to make hard-boiled eggs
hang out for that I'm going to make the
hardboiled eggs
last but they're not
least but I'm going to make them last
but they're not least all right look
we're going to make the porch it's
something more heartier for people that
love bacon and eggs and sausage they
love that Canadian breakfast they love
that English Old English breakfast where
they're eating kidneys and sausage and
blood sausage and all this other stuff
that will give you a heart attack you
know and you know what happens is we're
going to instead we're going to do
something hearty that doesn't do that
we're going to make a millage porridge
real quick okay so I'm going to take
this little Bowl right here and I am
going to scoop out some
Millet right and here we
go all right I'm going to mix this
Millet
up yep there you go about that let's not
block that there you go I'm going to mix
this Millet up with some maple
syrup maple syrup high and trace
minerals all right let's open this up
let's get a little bit of maple syrup in
here too going to mix it in so what I'm
going to do
and there we
go all right got a little bit of that in
there we're also going to mix in a few
wild blueberries if you don't mind into
this going to mix a few of these in
all
right let's bear with me for a second
here I'm going to mix those in
here
and
all right so I got the maple syrup I got
the wild blueberries right
here there we
go and I'm going to put a few more
blueberries in here like
this this is a simple Millet porridge it
doesn't take much to make TimeWise
really not much there you go look at
this a little bit of maple
syrup serve it right in a bowl just like
this
nice I'm going to put a few blueberries
right on top look at this you guys it's
incredible and I'm going to drop just a
few sprinkle them right on top like
this all right
there we
go what you have right there is a millet
porridge fat free no oil no
Crisco no vegetable oil no canola oil no
soy
oil right no oat milk which is high in
fat no almond milk no almond butter no
peanut
butter none of that how many of you guys
you know see that like you put that in
things right but you don't want to put
that in things in the morning this is
the morning Cleanse This is a hearty
option for a morning cleanse breakfast
right there there it is
millet with wild blueberries and a
little bit of maple syrup incredible
we're going to I can't wait to try a
little later let's check out those
cookies they're
cooking cookies are just about done I'd
say a few more minutes okay now we're
going to make a hardboiled
egg that's next now what I like about
these hardboiled
eggs is they're not like the other
hard-boiled eggs that we're talking
about these are much
different and much more fun to make I
think I think they're more fun to make
so you can have somebody that like
really wants that hearty flavor that
hearty taste something hearty inside of
them I recommend this so so let's start
making these hard-boiled eggs so what
you see is a rusted potato right there
now it takes a little creativity
so in the sense where you're going to
make these I'm going to cut a piece
right off that potato just like that
take a look you guys okay all
right and I'm going to peel this potato
in the shape of an egg this is so simple
and so easy it's ridiculous okay see
peeling this and I'm even going slow
instead of fast so I do like to do
things quicker but I'm taking my time on
this one there we go I'm going to make a
few of these right here there's one
hardboiled egg look at that I'm going to
grab a little
bowl what I'm going to
do okay is I'm going to use that bowl in
a
minute it's one hardboiled egg right
there I'm going to make another
hardboiled egg out of the same potato
check this out okay now you can save
those little potato pieces you're ready
we're going to make another one it's
going to come out really nice I can tell
already right so there we go okay I'm
going to shape this one all good going
to get this one done another hardboiled
egg two hardboiled eggs sitting right
there now I got the rest of this potato
I might be able to get a couple more out
of that one I'll I'll switch I'll try
another potato as well here we go I'm
going to cut this piece off make another
hardboiled egg right out of here
there we go I'm going to make a few of
them these can go anywhere on salads if
you want you want that hardboiled egg on
a
salad these can go on anything but
you're thinking like why is this a
hardboiled egg you can make it taste
real good cuz we're going to do
something with this we're not done this
one's got a little spot in the center
there we go I got three hardboiled eggs
let me make a
fourth I'm GNA cut this piece back we'll
make a fourth right now okay there we go
all
right all right here we go I got some
hardboiled
eggs all right let's get some black salt
out you guys ever do the black salt okay
now what I'm going to do is put black
salt in this
bowl
what I like about what what I like about
black
salt is it's not as high in
sodium well it depends on which black
salt it is don't quote me on that
because there's different black salts
out there all right there we go put a
little bit of that in
there
okay all
right now I'm going to take
that hardboiled egg and I'm going to dip
it in the black salt just like
this you can do less black salt you can
do more of it you want to just do a
little touch to sprinkle it on it like
for example see these three that's the
way I did it right there for guests for
family that's the three three hardboiled
eggs just like that with the black salt
you might want to do it this way you
take some black salt and you just
sprinkle a little bit on you don't need
much that's it just like this little
sprinkle right there and that's that's
the one right there that's a hard-boiled
egg you might desire
okay now if you're somebody that's kind
of laughing saying that's not an egg
that's not an egg don't knock it till
you try it do not knock it until you try
it I'm going to be straight up on that
okay because these are unbelievable
these ones I'm going to put it now in a
little on a little
plate okay leave in a little bowl
like this four hardboiled eggs coming
right
up nice there we go that's
them now if you're somebody that's
addicted to addicted to eggs and you
have to have them every single morning
realize this that your liver cannot
cleanse it will not cleanse out the
toxins of the past it won't cleanse out
the toxins of yesterday it won't cleanse
out the toxins of 10 years ago 15 years
ago it won't do that you cannot cleanse
the poisons and toxins out of your
liver out of your
liver unless you get rid of the overt
fats an egg that's an overt
fat avocado over fat almonds over fat
almond milk over fat chicken fish meat
over fat oils over fat right you got to
keep that out soy too fat you got to
keep all of that out in the morning
you're doing the medical media morning
cleanse you do your lemon water first
thing we talked about
that you do your celery juice after give
it a little time you guys
know in the cleans of heel book you can
learn about that and the you know what
you do also in a Brain saer book
too you get these going you can do
something heartier if you want something
heartier like a millet porridge
it doesn't have any oils in it there's
no fat in there there's no peanut butter
there's no almond butter in there think
about how incredible that is you can do
that right there and the oatmeal cookies
pulling them out of the oven now boom
those babies are done all right you guys
let me get these cookies out I'm going
to move the eggs I'm going for those
eggs though I am before I pull those
babies out I wanted to say one thing
watermelon is something you can do as
well look at this beautiful
watermelon so what you do is you do your
lemon water you do your your celery
juice a little later in the morning you
have watermelon that's an
incredible medical medium morning
cleanse option right there you can do
apples you can do pears you can do
mangoes it's another option too I'll
make a little fruit plate a little
bit let me just get out
the cookies if you guys don't
mind
we have this physical body we have this
Temple I hear it all the time out there
you
know leave my temple
alone this is my temple you can't enter
my
temple you can't affect my
temple don't touch my
temple
right well we want to keep our Temple
clean want to keep our body clean we we
want to get rid of the industrialized
junk and metals the Mercury the copper
the lead the Arsenic the aluminum the
cadmium the nickel we want to get rid of
it we want it
gone all
right that is one hot hot plate right
there here we
go what you see right there oatmeal
cookies that could be a great medical
medium morning cleanse option right
there and it really is ooh these are
really done nice too can I just give you
a little closeup here personally I like
them when they got a little bit of that
brown when they're browned a little bit
that that look do you see that look you
guys right there you guys see that look
right right how amazing is that look at
these
cookies these are oatmeal banana cookies
there's no ins the resistance going on
with this there's no blood sugar spikes
going on with this because there's no
oil oil in here to battle the sugar so
when you're eating this this isn't this
isn't about having that oil or that fat
in here there's no peanut butter in
these cookies there's no almonds there's
no chocolate chips in these cookies
that's the fat right there that will
stop your morning cleanse so if you make
your oatmeal cookie with chocolate
chocolate chips there's no cleansing
your liver is not going to cleanse it's
not going to happen because the overt
fat is going to make your liver go into
overdrive and it's going to produce a
lot of bile and it's not going to be
able to actually cleanse it's going to
be busy producing B
so the whole point of the medical
meeting morning cleanse is to not have
to have your liver go into production
and start producing too much bile to
break down fats and when you actually
stop that process where you stop your
liver from having to break down for
having to worry about breaking down fats
and producing too much bile once you
stop your liver from having to do that
you give your liver a break where it
could its only focus from there on out
is cleansing out the poisons the toxins
and the junk you want your liver to only
have one Focus every morning and that's
to clean out the
poisons that's the Focus right there you
want your liver to have one job one huge
job yeah it's got a bunch of other
little jobs it's working on too but you
want it to focus on that one big job and
that job is to release poisons and
toxins and get them out of the body and
it won't do that if you bring in an over
fat in the morning you have coffee with
cream done
liver's not going to cleanse you have a
smoothie with peanut butter in it done
liver's not going to cleanse you're not
going to move forward right you have
oatmeal with a little peanut butter in
it almond butter in it done your liver
is not going to cleanse sorry you have a
piece of chocolate before noon you piece
of chocolate at 10: in the morning done
your liver is not going to
cleanse it's not going to cleanse if any
of that's happening so this is critical
to know you got almond milk in the
morning done your liver is not going to
cleanse you got oat milk in the morning
nope your liver is not going to cleanse
that's how important this is how easy
though is
it if you do this any of this even if
it's just lemon water celery juice and
an
apple that's it lemon water celery juice
watermelon lemon water celery juice a
mango lemon water celery juice and if
you want something harder these options
right here the Millet porridge the
oatmeal cookies the hardboiled eggs that
I made so let me get these on a plate
talk a little bit more
too for a
plate let's get these cookies on here
you guys take a
look what do you
think am I going to eat these
yeah
I saw somebody leave a question there
sing are you going to eat them I am
going to eat them let me get rid of
this put this
down okay showing you the options right
there we got the hardboiled eggs you
guys when you try these hardboiled eggs
you're going to be like that's the
craziest thing they are literally so
close to that it's unbelievable I got
the Millet porridge right here
these three things all on their own I
got the heavy metal detox smoothie right
there and there it
is the Smoothie is getting more geloy
and more geloy that's the binder effect
right there so good so
good I like to drink it fast so I'm not
scooping it in that's what I like to do
like to drink it quicker okay so here we
are I'm going to make a little bit of a
fruit a fruit medley really quick let me
do that
I'm going to move these
over I'm dying for one of these hard
boiled eggs though before I do that all
right
nice don't knock it till you try it I'm
serious that's not a hardboiled egg I
don't know what
is
just close your eyes close your eyes
when you try
this close your eyes and then have
one it's insane so good it's going to
have to finish this
piece let me make a little little fruit
uh fruit plate for you
guys all
right
depends on how big we want the
plate all
right now you can do like an assortment
of
fruit
yep got a plate right here let's do that
get some
watermelon
okay so put a couple slices of
watermelon on
here start
with put one more slice this watermelon
looks
amazing you guys you can do
this I have faith in
you you can do this I have lots of faith
in you you guys know I do you guys know
I
do you already know that though let's
get some apples on this fruit plate real
quick all
right can do apple
slices you can cut them any way you
want you guys the eggs are made from
steamed
potatoes I see somebody on there that
just got on that said aw's eating eggs
for the first time what is
this what is he doing is he
flip-flopping like everybody else does
in health no he's not these are steamed
potatoes you notice that in health have
you guys seen that I'm going to knock
another Apple down in here you guys seen
that out there it's like year
one of a health author or influencer
they're doing one thing year two they're
doing another thing what happened the
first thing didn't work year three
they're doing something else did you you
ever see that out there now they're
doing something else they're selling
something else what happened year four
they're now into keto year five they're
now into carnivore oh year six they're
back into keto year seven they're vegans
now all the health experts and authors
to included right year eight they were
eating tons of fat year nine they're
staying away from fat for some reason
cuz they heard about it from
somewhere and I'm just saying year you
know year one year two year three heck
they do it every 6 months it's another
change to change to something else let's
take a look at this nice mango right
here we'll see what we
have I'm going to pop this on the
plate okay you guys you ever see that
you guys know what I'm talking about
right but you know what's funny the
medical medium information is consistent
because guess what
I'm not in charge of the medical medium
information that's
why if I was in charge I'd probably be
doing the same old stuff everybody else
does out there they're keto one minute
then there's something else the next
minute then they're like you could eat a
little fish then they're like don't eat
any fish they learn about heavy metals
year two and they're like don't eat any
fish but your first book said you could
eat fish then year three they're doing
something else then year four they're
doing something else I would probably do
the same thing the same stupid
stuff if if the information was wasn't
coming from above when it's coming from
above it's it has to be what it has to
be that's why there's no
contradictions that's why you see
consistency in the message for years and
years and years 15 years 20 years going
all the way back you see that
consistency is there in the
messaging it's just always there I'm
going to pop in a few berries on this
fruit plate
it's like
this I got some mangoes on here I got
some
watermelon and I'm going to pop in some
orange some oranges if you guys don't
mind what I'll do is some orange slices
take a look at this just like
this some orange
slices
okay get some orange slices on this
which is going to be really
nice
okay get a couple more oranges and then
we're going to make a nice we'll have
this nice fruit
plate and that's something you can do
you can just just do that every single
morning even if it's a small fruit plate
and not a big one and you're cleansing
your liver you're cleansing your brain
cuz once your liver is cleansing your
brain gets to release a little bit more
poison everybody has old Pharmaceutical
stuck in their brain even if they didn't
take any they still have them because
you can get them in you through so many
different Avenues it's
unbelievable okay I'm going to pop one
more orange on this fruit plate for you
guys you see it out there right even
with health influencers they're doing
something they're doing something
different one month and they're like
doing something different a month
later next thing you know it they're
saying all kinds of stuff like like you
don't have to worry about your food at
all you can eat what you want and next
thing or or hey be carnivore just meet
only only meat meat and then next month
later it's like you can eat meat and
honey now it's honey oh wait you can eat
meat honey and now have a
berry it's Insanity out
there and I would probably be part of
that if I didn't have the information
coming from s so to keep me in check and
that's how the books are so consistent
these eight medical Bibles quic heel is
the one right there that you should take
into the new year look into it do the
medical meeting morning cleanse there's
a beautiful fruit plate as we
speak right here so we got the fruit
plate we got the oatmeal cookies take a
look you guys the Millet porridge the
wild blueberries all fat free and then
we got the steamed potatoes which are
really steamed potatoes which are really
hardboiled eggs but they're not
hardboiled legs and for some reason I'm
going to have another one of
those because you're that freaking good
that's insane all right
guys I love you guys medical me morning
cleanse check out the books get the book
if you don't have it go to the library
get it for free don't even pay for it if
you don't want to just get the book
start the medical meeting morning
cleanse do the heavy metal detox
smoothie when you can that's a big deal
get on the medical me medium newsletter
go to Medical medium.com link is in the
descriptions if you can and check
out heal withth Amber okay on IG on
Instagram so heel h l with wi and then
Amber a m b r um you know there's some
intense stuff going on check out her
stories if you can and that would be
great so go to heal with Amber check out
her stories and so forth um that would
be wonderful you guys are incredible
check out my telegram get on my telegram
make sure you're on there for my
exclusive messages that I leave on
telegram a lot of them are healing
messages inspirational messages many of
you guys might have heard those already
check out cleanse to heal if you get a
chance get on the medical media
newsletter so you can you can get the
emails that show you what you missed and
also to keep up on things too that's
another reason to get on the email list
but either way you guys incredible take
care love you guys