before I start talking about cleansing
and emotions what happens when we're
cleansing cleansing out toxins and
poisons out of our bloodstream out of
our organs
and all that poison and all that toxin
comes out how it can trigger us
emotionally how we can feel things
before I go into a little bit about that
and other things regarding cleansing
because I'm reading
out of cleanse to heal one of the most
powerful books in the world in health
where Millions have already gotten their
lives back from this very book I don't
know if you have it before I go in there
and start talking about that I just want
to make an announcement tomorrow's the
big day
tomorrow is the first of the collecting
Stones meditation Journey it's a free
Journey have you signed up link is in
the profile link is in the description I
am more than excited about this because
I can promise you this
without a shadow of a doubt you're going
to have an experience
it's going to be an experience you'll
never forget by the seventh day
of the collecting Stone's meditation
Journey
you are going
to have an experience and you are never
going to forget
that experience
from the seven day collecting Stones
meditation journey I just want to tell
you so before we go on to cleansing
and emotions
cleansing out emotions
make sure you sign up
make sure you sign up to the collecting
Stones meditation Journey it's free
seven day Incredible Journey that's free
link is in the profile link is in the
description you don't want to miss this
seriously it's where you get the three
stones
you pick and choose your three stones
you name the stones
and you're just gonna have an amazing
time an amazing experience
something you'll never forget
something you you'll be so blown away
at what happens including results
this is definitely something that you're
going to be moved by
anyway let's get into it now and all I
just wanted to tell you though that
tomorrow is the first day sign up today
sign up today if you can because each
day the Link's in the description the
link is in the profile because each day
you're going to be getting a video
she don't want to miss you don't want to
miss this collecting Stones meditation
Journey
everybody has a different set of
experiences is that true can we all say
that
by the way link is in profile and
description or go to medicalmedium.com
to sign up to the free
collecting Stones meditation Journey
it's mind-blowing
I promise you'll never forget your
experience I know you guys are all
signed up you're enrolled you're signed
up three stones that's it
serious I want to just talk about that
but I do want to cover some cleansing I
want to talk about that I don't know if
you have this book I'm just reading a
little bit of about that here
all right
so
Heather says so do we pick out our own
Stones ahead of time
I would pick them out tomorrow on the
first day of the collecting Stones
meditation Journey you can pick them out
before tomorrow you can pick them out
today you can pick them out yesterday
if you have to if you have no choice and
you're available like you're available
to do it like you have the option you
have the the time whatever you can do
that but tomorrow is the best day for it
but I understand if you had to do it
earlier you had to do it today
everybody has a different set of
experiences the Betrayal one person went
through might have been substantially
different from someone else's
not everybody's betrayal is the same not
everybody's pain suffering and
experience from being betrayed is the
same
everyone is different
the Betrayal that you may have had in
your life is different than what someone
else has gone through
keep that in mind it's so important and
yet maybe the negative impact it had on
their lives could in some sense be equal
someone could be betrayed
in one way
and somebody else can be betrayed in
another way
they won't seem equal when you hear
about the Betrayal
but yet it could affect us equally like
we can still feel that experience I you
let me down you broke my trust you
betrayed me
you stabbed me in the back
sometimes people experience much more
hardship more losses a lot of people
experience hardship on planet mess
more breakups as they look for love in
their life how many people have
experienced a lot of breakups a lot of
relationship issues divorces
relationship breakups separations
so many people go through that and
they're hurt and it builds up and it
gets stored up inside
hence why it's so important to do the
collecting Stones meditation journey to
pull that stuff out so it's not sitting
in there and it's not festering and it's
not in there and it's not rotting and
festering because our hurt can actually
sit in ourselves and just fester in
there
and so we want to get that drawn out
like a Venom
business relationships that are hurtful
rather than fruitful so many people
partner up with people going to Biz with
people try to start something with
people and instead of it being fruitful
it becomes hurtful
and as people find their way find their
true calling they crawl out of the
depths of a hardship they thought was
their fault and in reality was the
depths of Darkness
some people see Darkness for what it is
and many don't
many people choose to kind of like
put the blinders on they don't want to
see the darkness
they kind of just don't want to admit or
have the realization that
there was something dark going on there
with that person or however and they
just don't really see it so they don't
they put the blinders on they don't want
to drop the blinders they don't want to
be able to see
they have different ways of handling
difficult memories and experiences
that's a whole other difference between
so many people
so many have difficult
way they have difficult experiences
Korean says what book are you reading
from please page 458 if you don't have
cleanse the heel you're missing out
it's one of the most powerful books of
all time in health
millions of these books got around the
world and have changed people's lives in
such a way like getting like getting
them out of the darkest situations with
their health pulling them out of hell
that they were in and suffering and
struggling and taking them into such a
great place of healing
the information in this book is just so
powerful by the way
so this is a really
powerful piece of information I'm
reading right here
so many people have different ways of
handling difficult memories and
experiences
we have a glitch I see on IG it looks
like the connection is just going and
going and going
but so many people
they handle memories and experiences
differently some people just wall It Off
it's like a mechanism that occurs where
they can wall it off they can put a wall
up some people are in in a place where
there's so much PTSD and they're
struggling so much they can't put that
wall up
it's not possible for them
there's they feel so vulnerable they
feel so exposed with that experience and
that memory
Walling off Walling it off becomes very
difficult and they're trapped in the
PTSD of whatever that experience was or
is
they have different different ways of
handling hardships memories and
experiences releasing as much as they
safely can while some memories become
buried in the subconscious so this is
what happens with people you go through
an experience you move forward
and it's buried in the subconsciousness
that hardship
that hard time that struggle something
they went through
it's now buried
in their subconsciousness
well we're all different our experiences
there is still a Sisterhood and
Brotherhood to what we go through in
this life so even though we all have
different experiences
some of us can bury it into our
move forward some of us are trapped in
the PTSD in in the moment and just can't
seem to shake it can't seem to push it
off anywhere but regardless We're All in
This Brotherhood and Sisterhood as we go
through life
if you're having problems on IG head to
Telegram
the chronically you'll often find power
in numbers when they connect over their
shared suffering and that's the thing
the chronically ill have been swept
under the carpet they've been beaten
down through the generations
they've been treated like lepers even in
the world of health and wellness and
what you'll notice now with chronic
illness
is that chronic illness is getting some
more respect the medical medium books
the last decade of putting information
out there for the chronically ill
information that's been life-saving and
moving them forward and validating the
real symptoms and conditions has changed
and shaped the health and wellness world
right now
where now it's becoming a little trendy
for people in the health and wellness
and influencers to acknowledge the
chronically ill a little bit even if
they don't understand
or know
the one thing about doing going live
when it happens and you can't avoid
anything else but I think we're here
so the chronically you'll often find
power in numbers when they connect over
they're shared
we're having a tech problem
check one two
this is when you're not live you can be
like let's edit this out
even if some of these physical symptoms
vary with one person experience
migraines anxiety or depression in
another person going through back pain
and neck pain or insomnia
everybody who's chronically sick who's
really suffered and struggled and
understands what it's like to go through
what they're going through
can relate to another person who's going
through it
that's what's incredible about
the chronically ill about people who
have struggled and suffered and been
through a lot
they can relate
to someone else who's struggling and
suffering and I think that's what makes
the medical meme community so powerful
and that's what people don't understand
out there
including the haters and the critics and
stuff like that they don't know why
there's such a strong bond in the
medical medium Community with people who
care about each other
because when they've been through
something
they
understand
and they recognize that someone else
could be going through the same
someone else
could be going through something similar
and it's this connection
it's really powerful
it's being able to understand what the
other person is going through
we've all experienced relationships
whether with friends family members
spouses or others that became difficult
or even harmful in some way many of us
have had experience physical injury that
went along with emotional injury we've
all been let down
either way physically or emotionally
even when the details are different we
can find enough similarities to one
another's hurt to identify with each
other
if you've been hurt emotionally
and you know somebody else who's been
hurt emotionally
there's a way to identify and connect if
you've been hurt physically or you're
sick physically with chronic illness and
you're really struggling like
neurological problems
and you have all the different
neurological symptoms and you've been to
50 doctors
and you talk to somebody else who has
neurological problems
there's this similar experience even
though they're different
that's what makes the chronically ill
truly like bond in numbers
especially if they're people
who have been sick and they've gone
through so much not being validated
being told they're crazy being told that
it's all in their head being told that
it's their fault of why they're sick
being told that they maybe manifested
their sickness being told that
it's their fault they're a faulty person
being told that it's their genes or
genetic
makeup of their body
all these things
if we're not isolated from those who
have gone through similar situations
sometimes we feel completely alone
especially when the experts we consult
or the people in our lives imply or
outright tell us that we've imagined or
created our illness do you know anybody
that's ever been told they created their
illness
do you guys I don't ask you guys enough
like questions around that do you know
anybody
that they were told they must be
creating their sickness
they must be creating their illness
I'm not sure if any of you guys have run
into anybody like that or you know
anybody like that
because so many people
are told they created it it's their
fault
they're the reason
they're thinking
their thought process
they haven't figured out how to correct
to stop it
there's still a stigma Around The
Chronic suffering a result of how little
it's understood it can be hard to find
true help from someone who gets it
that's another thing too is how many
people have been seeking help for their
chronic illness seeking help
for their pain and suffering
and they can't find a professional that
gets it
they can't find a professional that
understands it
maybe they do and maybe it takes 10
professionals maybe it takes 15 20
health professionals
maybe it takes 30. but finding someone
to understand what they're going through
and that gets it is
so
so hard for so many
it can be hard to find true help from
someone who gets it rest assured even if
you believe that you are the only one to
know the particular pain of fighting for
your life well those around you look at
you with skepticism that your muscle
stiffness or brain fog or fatigue is
really that bad
others who Bend through near nearly the
exact same struggle are out there and
that leads us to this whole thing
even if you can't find someone that
truly believes what you're suffering
with and what you're going through even
if you can't convince someone
that what your symptoms are are real
like the chronic fatigue that you have
all the twitching and the Tremors and
the pain and the panic attacks and the
anxiety and the headaches and the
migraines even
if you can't find someone or you don't
know someone that really gets it that
really understands your struggles and
your suffering and the pain you're in
and your symptoms
just know there's somebody out there
that's going through it as well there's
somebody out there that understands
that's going through
what you're going through
the emotions that went along with
fighting to be heard are some of what we
release when we cleanse so this goes
into the cleansing a little bit I wanted
to
head to the cleansing aspect
of this Courtney says the
the migraines are brutal for you the
margarines
so I'm reading out a cleanse the heel
right here
migraine I see that
I'm reading out a cleanse the heel I'm
talking about cleansing And the emotions
involved a little bit
so that's where we are
the emotions that went along with
fighting to be heard are some of what we
release when we cleanse
so when we start to heal and we start to
cleanse
emotions
are releasing
Trish on Facebook it's page 459.
so 4 59.
we release
a lot of our old hurt when we cleanse
we release information that's in our
cells that's in our organs when we
cleanse
those struggles also lead to emotional
based adrenaline that flowed through our
veins and got stored in our cells and
this leads to something that's really
important anytime we go through an
emotional experience an adrenaline surge
occurs
a surge of adrenaline
fires up
if you hear bad news your adrenals start
to pump
and they're releasing all of this
corrosive adrenaline
and all of that adrenaline is flooding
every cell inside your body it's going
through your bones it's going into your
bones the cells of the inside your bones
the cells inside your organs your
connective tissue
it's going it's rushing through your
lymphatic system it's going into your
nervous system it's going into your
brain it's going throughout your body
so in any time we go through something
any kind of experience
we get this
surge of adrenaline
firing up into our bloodstream
and all that adrenaline has to find its
way either out of the body or it stores
itself into fat cells
it stores itself into organ tissue
and that adrenaline harbored information
because when we go through a difficult
time like fear or betrayal or some kind
of chaos that happens in our life
whatever that is
or we're just upset about something
that information
this gets transmuted it gets transmuted
into that adrenaline and infuses itself
into cells and it sticks around into our
fat storage in our body into our fat
cells in our body into tissue and organ
tissue
so struggles that we have lead to
emotional based adrenaline that flowed
through our veins and got stored in our
cells now get ready for this as we detox
as we start to cleanse and detox to heal
some of the feelings may come back up
that were in that adrenaline going all
the way back
so if you had something happen to you
last year or six months ago
or two years ago or ten years ago or
even further in your life if you went
through some abuse if you went through
some kind of hardship
some kind of
difficult time a relationship a
situation
and it created an adrenaline surge
throughout your body
that adrenaline was released during that
hard time
so adrenaline is coded it's got
information in it
it'll have information of that hard time
that you went through information
of that difficult time that betrayal
that hardship that loss in there
and then it stores deep in your cells so
as we detox
we might get some feelings that come
back in different ways
so when you're cleansing those poisons
and toxins and you're restoring your
physical body and you're bringing
yourself back and you're working on your
healing
you may experience
some sadness some different feelings
some different experiences and different
emotions that are coming out of
the cells coming out of the fat cells
coming out of the fat storage bin
coming out of the liver
coming out of the spleen
if you guys want to know I'm in cleansed
Hill right now I'm reading about detox
and cleanse and emotions
sharianna says on YouTube no wonder I
can't lose weight yes struggles from a
death of the family dealing with family
members
actors ship
detectorship
one person may find themselves with
nostalgia
that's almost uncomfortable in a way
where they feel like something's going
on what's this nostalgic feeling the
sense I'm getting what is this
so some people will have that come over
them
when they're cleansing and detoxing
Pearl said wow I'm always amazed by the
information thank you for being here
Saints who says
might want to try the anger shifter
brain shot works better than any calming
medication it has changed my life I used
to be told I was born angry not anymore
so one person can find themselves with
that nostalgia
another may go through intense dreams so
when we're cleansing and detoxing
we can go through some serious streams
dreams of running away from people
dreams of
being chased dreams that don't make
sense on any level dreams that are a
little bit scary a bumpy ride dreams
that
that feel unsettling but we may dream a
lot when we're cleansing and detoxing
the reason why is because when you're
cleansing and detoxing adrenaline is
loosing up in those fat cells adrenaline
is loosening up in the organ tissue and
the cells in the organ
and adrenaline is starting to leave and
get into the bloodstream and it floats
around and it's got these messages
inside of it which is you hurt me a long
time ago you didn't understand me a long
time ago you didn't validate me a long
time ago I was suffering I was going
through a hard time
and you didn't understand no one
understood I had a loss I had a hardship
something happened to me I had a breakup
I had a bad divorce whatever it is that
adrenaline is floating through the
bloodstream in the veins and just
swimming around and that adrenaline has
information in it for when you had a
difficult time in your life or a time
that you didn't think was difficult at
the time but it was difficult
you were just in survival mode you might
have been someone that was in survival
mode
and when you were in survival mode you
didn't really know at the time and that
moment how difficult things were you
didn't know in that moment or at that
time how hard it was
it was really hard but you just were in
survival mode and you had to move
forward and Forge ahead but adrenaline
was occurring during that time and it's
stored inside the cells of the body it's
stored inside the cells of your tissue
your organs in your bones and then
you started cleansing and detoxing you
started doing it
the right way
that's safe for the body
you started doing it in a powerful way
that actually really does detox and
cleanse and purify
and you started doing that
and then lo and behold
something was being released
something toxic something that was there
for a long time something that was there
when you were living your life years ago
may not even realize how bad things were
in that moment in your life
maybe it was just a quick Moment In Time
someone texted you something bad 10
years ago whatever it was and it gave
you a surge and boom it soaked into
those cells and then it's coming out and
some people have a lot of that inside of
them they have a lot of hardship
betrayal emotional
distrust from broken trust and as
they're cleansing
that toxic
information that's inside the cells that
were stored there deep there from the
adrenaline being so toxic started to
release and dislodge and break out
of its catacombs and start to release
and go into the bloodstream and as it's
circulating in the bloodstream you're
having strange dreams
you're having dreams that don't make
sense you're having scary dreams
uncomfortable dreams
and then when you're awake you feel like
some kind of nostalgia some kind of
sadness comes over you you're thinking
about things you haven't thought about
in years you're emotionally detoxing
emotionally detoxing
is what you're doing
that makeup chick over there in IG says
I wonder if my friend's murder and all
the grief has anything to do with all my
health issues
so sorry to hear that
but when we go through something
so intense
where you go through something so
catastrophic where a friend gets
murdered or something happened in your
life
or a friend
lost her life in a car crash or however
it is if you've gone through something
like that and it affected you
emotionally then that means an
adrenaline surged occurred
and it was the fear
the loss adrenaline it's the blend and
that had to go somewhere and it tends to
store inner cells especially if we're
doing Comfort Foods at the time because
we are we're doing Comfort Foods
we end up doing comforting foods and we
capture it in the comfort food it soaks
up that adrenaline and then it stores it
deep in her liver into the fat cells
deep down in there
Edith C on YouTube yes I just finished
369 cleanse that's aim here actually
and had a lot of weird dreams now I
understand
Margaret Hurst says wow my dreams are
crazy I have forgiven a lot of people
after messages in my dreams
this is the kind of healing that occurs
when you're taking care of yourself when
you're doing some cleansing Rachel Jones
says I do the morning cleanse every day
since February and have healed my gluten
intolerance psoriasis nerve inflammation
and I am so much happier as a result
incredible
it can be hard to find true help from
someone who gets it out there
and that's what I love about the medical
meme community
because people get it
they get it here
they get it now I know there's a lot of
posers that come into here that pretend
they get it they just want to take
advantage of the medical meme Community
I've seen this over and over and over
again
or they were really never that sick
they don't understand that
what real struggles are with their their
health yet they're just not there
they're just
had a little bit not so sick stuff going
on
but man when you've been there you've
been there and you know what it is and
you know how to identify it Kim Miller
says my mom said she never used to dream
when she was on caffeine for years she
got off the coffee and started dreaming
again
all coffee is another thing that
suppresses emotions and berries emotions
we walk around we spend a lifetime
suppressing and suppressing and
suppressing we spend a lifetime burying
and burying
goes into the old trash bin
we spend a lifetime pushing it down
shoving it down shoving it down
right deep into the cells in the organs
right down deep in there
Diana
says what is the best thing to do when
you're detoxing this old adrenaline
did you sign up to the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
it's a free
incredible seven day healing Journey
that starts tomorrow link is in
description link is in a profile
and when you recognize the emotions and
you recognize the adrenaline
if you recognize
what these emotions are and where
they're coming from they're coming from
that Old adrenaline storage it's
surfacing and coming out that's one way
to help see you later alligator bye and
have it leave the system and leave the
system
we spend decades in our life shoving it
all down
but when we let it out we can let it
pass
if we do a medical medium cleanse we can
get it out and have it leave instead of
recirculate
and that leads me to the next thing I
wanted to say
if you're somebody that
has a lot of toxic emotion stored from
toxic adrenaline deep inside your cell
tissue in your cell walls deep inside
your connective tissue every part of
your body
deep in your liver what happens is that
if you're not
cleansing it out properly it recycles
and recirculates and goes right back
into fat storage or right back into
liver storage
so it kind of taunts you for years to
come there's something in there that
never was let out there's something in
you that's been trapped in there for so
many years and never got out
and then it just kind of like haunts you
and haunts you and you relive it a
little bit not really unsure not sure
what you're reliving but you're reliving
it you're feeling it it's giving you
that sense of like what's wrong with me
what's wrong with me emotionally I must
see another therapist I'm gonna have to
see another therapist and another
therapist
a therapist shopping
educating myself
nothing like waking up to a bitter
poison of utter and total betrayal
educating myself
yes indeed
I concur greatly as you would probably
know from the information
and fall cities that are always swimming
around out there
Melanie Foss survival since 2013
greetings from Germany at the moment
I'm in the Netherlands incredible
greetings
Gina says if we have OCD is it okay to
wear gloves when collecting and cleaning
Stones until they are cleaned indeed it
is
indeed it is
even if you believe that you are the
only one
to know the particular pain of fighting
for your life well those around you look
at you with skepticism
that your muscle stiffness and your
brain fog and your fatigue
an experience where they're just
bringing their lives back from so much
they've been through
this means that even as cells release
old adrenaline
that carries difficulties from our past
it's not a reckless process
your brain is getting critical glucose
and mineral salts to give you grounding
that you need
you don't need to engage or process the
emotions or feelings that come up on a
cleanse and that's another thing too and
need people to understand that when
you're cleansing
and emotions are coming out it doesn't
mean you have to process them for them
to leave and go
that's something that's really important
because when you're cleansing it's
usually not the time or space to go deep
into emotional grit you want it to pass
through and go you want to you want it
to leave the system and Purge out
it's usually not the time or space to
deal with emotions that are really
intense when you're cleansing or
detoxing
but what I love about the medical medium
cleanses Spirit of compassions cleanses
is that it allows it to leave
and that's why so many people are
getting their lives back too because
they feel they can stay on the cleanse
everyone is different in how or when
they need to process life sometimes
mirror sometimes
Miracle states of emotion or healing can
happen actually during one of these
cleanses
and I see that a lot a great lifting of
energy could occur a sensation of weight
off your back
I see the tech demons are after us today
by the way they're just messing up our
Tech in any way possible the tech devils
Tech betrayal too laugh out loud
educating myself yeah let's not forget
that
I think they just wait for me to go on
and go live
there's nothing better than a sensation
that was so heavy Weighing on your back
getting lifted
lift it for good
there's no rule about how our emotional
processing is supposed to happen by the
way
everybody's different everybody
everybody processes different
usually the shift that they can have
occurs after the cleanse is over when
we've had enough time to gain insight
into what's surfaced during the cleanse
after the cleanse we become wiser in the
emotional area in so many ways that
leads me to this
you're sick
you find the answers
you do one of the most powerful cleanses
there is to heal that has a track record
of people healing
you get better
and you get better and wiser for it
and emotionally stronger
you get sick
you cleanse
you heal you become wiser
as we release poisons and toxins that
were deeply embedded into cells of all
kinds including fat cells that are now
bursting and draining while we cleanse
you know when you cleanse you guys fat
cells are bursting and draining
no one talks about that
been talking about that for years
we cleanse and fat cells are bursting
they're bursting and draining while we
cleanse those poisons and toxins that
are now flowing through a bloodstream
are on their way out of our body and it
can affect our taste and smell as well
sometimes while cleansing someone will
taste a manufactured food they ate when
they were a child they wanted to ask you
guys that question do you ever
experience that
do you ever experience when your cleanse
isn't when you're doing a cleanse in any
way
that you all of a sudden like I remember
the taste that food when I was a kid
that's a cheeseburger
that I used to eat at this restaurant
that's a chocolate cake I used to eat at
this restaurant or
that's just some candy I used to like
years ago whatever it is there's
something that comes up maybe some
cookies that used to eat some packaged
cookies from a long time ago and they
surface and you can taste you can
actually taste
those cookies yes you've had dreams and
chowing down on Fried Chicken Hannah
totally understand you're on YouTube
yeah you can have dreams
and experiences where you taste it or
you dream you're eating it
how about that
manufactured food that you eat when you
were a child yes with every cleanse
see Andrea
Andrea missed on IG says with every
cleanse
yep
a cheeseburger for example from a chain
fast food restaurant sometimes they'll
taste smoke from cigarettes anybody was
a smoker were you guys smokers
at all
smoking cigarettes
how did you smoke a cigarette did you
hold a cigarette this way with these two
fingers and go
did you smoke a cigarette this way
or that way you put the cigarette
between
how many of you guys smoked that I would
like to know I don't know you guys many
of you guys probably smoked right me
okay so many of you guys have
sometimes you'll taste smoke from
cigarettes from 20 years ago from 10
years ago
secondhand smoke Pearl yeah
I bet a lot of people have had
secondhand smoke
definitely
sometimes it's a type of ice cream
sometimes it's cheese
I got a friend that I finally convinced
to cleanse
Jesus let it out
and he said all he tasted was American
cheese like American processed cheese
that's all he tasted
he said he used to live off of those chi
in American craft you know like whatever
it is different singles or whatever
American cheese
yes I smoked my mm healing lifestyle
over there in IG you smoked
here with Haley I used to smoke but I
quit
over there on IG
Alex amulet said weed
no loose says yes I smoked
everybody said yeah and I quit a year
ago you quit a year ago
incredible 25 years ago Sarah Hughes
says on YouTube my God you guys all
smoked funny you did too I got the
smoking gang here I got the smoking
group here is that what I have
everybody smoked everybody smoked
Kim over there one four four one four
four on IG says smoked a lot when I was
drunk double whammy
that's like smoking and drunk it's like
yeah what what yeah I know all right
yeah I'm gonna drink give me another
vodka
double whammy
sunrid said only for two years many many
years
many many years
someone what
wait a minute
only for two years
many many years ago
so sorry for not reading that right
double whammy is very interesting with
that one too because you know what I've
known people yeah drinking and smoking
at the same time
bottle of beer
yeah
sometimes while cleansing will actually
taste manufactured food like
American cheese
fast food chain stuff smoke from
cigarettes sometimes it's a type of ice
cream or cheese or donut or cookie they
used to consume sometimes it's a
familiar flavor it's like a flavor you
remember it's some kind of cookie or
donut or anything like that it comes out
you don't want to be toxic I saw that on
IG
and I don't blame you one bit
do you guys have this book please tell
me you have this book
because if someone says a whole bunch of
people say I don't have that book it's
like really
what
come on go to the library get it for
free it's on Amazon too right now it's
on Amazon it's on sale on Amazon
Alexandra Sophia said smoked a few years
and then my adrenals went out and I quit
Ms perio says I quit almost 10 years ago
my God you guys smoked
wow
Sylvia smoked on and off but have it now
for 13 years incredible
I got the smokers group
or the cool were the Cool Cats no
question we're the cool cats right no
doubt about it Andrew says I smoked four
packs a day at one point how to withdraw
only this year after five years off
baby boom
I'm proud of you it's not easy
I smoked way too long and drank Carrie
smoked and drink
filterless cigarettes I smoked a pack a
day as a teenager
you guys this must be the cool crowd I
always knew
I always knew the medical medium
Community was the cool crowd I always
knew that
I stopped smoking 30 years ago
sometimes it's a chemical Essence we
sense sometimes it's a pungent and
rotten ammonia sulfur like medical
medium books have been talking about
ammonia for years
talked about it even before the medical
medium books a decade ago and now people
the influencers that are trying to Pawn
off supplements or whatever they're
doing out there they're talking about
sulfur they're putting it in posts
sulfur sulfur in here sulfur ammonia
ammonia ammonia
and they're talking about ammonia
that's medical meme info
I did drugs 32 years now
32 years now because of medical medium
I'm clean so you did drugs for 32 years
and now you're clean lobbying
I'm proud of you I know that's a massive
accomplishment I actually understand
that I do
Alexander said stop smoking in 2010.
okay okay I just have to say something I
have to say something first of all I'm
beyond proud of all you guys I'm not
kidding that's not a joke
it takes some serious strength to stop
the smokes serious strength
you got my respect you got my respect
for a lot of things she got my respect
hands down
you got my respect
uncle uncle
I call Uncle
okay you got me down in a Chokehold
right now I'm on the ground respect
respect
keep the hope today says in IG 46 years
smoked 21 months clean 21 months nice
nice nice
yep
they can all connect to feelings the
smells and tastes can change over the
course of the cleanse too if you're
cleansing this stuff's going to come out
and you're going to taste it you're
gonna feel it you're gonna detox it out
of your cells and out of your
bloodstream out of your body
when you're cleansing and you're
cleansing it right and you're doing it
right old adrenaline stored in those fat
cells and the fat cells are bursting all
those old toxins from all those old
Foods stored in the cells deep down in
your liver and all through your body all
through your entire body are going to be
coming out
wow incredible
Danny says stopped coffee and alcohol
and one day clean since 2015. boom
you release a certain amount of toxins
your senses can even become more
fine-tuned you get fine-tuned senses can
you imagine
the more crap you get away from your
senses the more fragrances you get out
of your life you get rid of those
plugins you get rid of that air
freshener you get rid of all the stuff
that medical medium broke to the world
because once again in health no one
talked about all that stuff now they're
all acting like the pros at it it's
crazy
once you get rid of all those fragrances
all the clones and the perfumes and get
rid of all the fresheners air fresheners
and the scented laundry stuff and the
fabric softeners and the and the lotions
that have tons of like chemical scents
and whatever all kinds of different
fragrances in it which is all mysterious
garbage and chemicals once you get rid
of that and you get rid of the smoking
and you're cleansing old toxic
adrenaline out of the cells and you're
cleansing all this out of the cells then
your your senses are gonna be fine-tuned
fine tune
Susan says I'm still I'm still smoking
now I'm calling on Angel of addiction
completely understand
are you going to be are you signed up
for the collecting Stones meditation
Journey
can I would name one of those stones
smoking and send that baby into the pond
on day seven
that's what I would do Jamie yep up to
two packs a day quit over a night 12
years ago 33 years ago 12 years 33 years
ago
you notice that what won't come up on
the cleanse is the taste of a grape or
an apple or a celery stick or a
strawberry or a berry or a Blackberry
these are foods that fight toxins they
aren't toxic foods themselves you'll
notice that it's only the toxic food
that surfaces during a cleanse you'll
notice it was those cupcakes
that were packaged when you were a kid
those donuts that were packaged or donut
at a donut place
a creamy donut place or whatever and
whatever
it is it's stored into your cells deep
down there
W green
on YouTube I was a smoker and my dad was
a smoker I tasted the smoke while
detoxing
your emotional well-being can become
more fine-tuned as well that's that's
the thing I want to tell you guys that's
the thing you can read the [__]
you can see the [__]
yeah
you start cleansing you start healing
you start removing all that junk and
that garbage inside of you and then you
can you can
smell out [__]
a mile away
some of us have been through so much we
have to have compassion for our bodies
while
we heal and while everybody heals we've
been through a lot we have to have
compassion Irena Park says I smoke too
got it
I understood understood understood thank
you for actually telling me because I
got to tell you something
I'm proud of you guys like you don't
even know I'm not kidding used to smoke
cigarettes in high school
Jackie B's got a laughing face
Relic speaks as I just quit yeah
nice
when you get fine-tuned and you get
cleaned up you guys
you can smell horse [__]
from someone from a mile away
you want to get your Intuit abilities up
you want to get Keen
you want to be able to sense who's got
demons who doesn't you want to know
who's got Devils around them you want to
know if their Fork tongue is legit or
not you want to know if you're a good
person bad person you want to know
anything you want to know what the lies
are and the [__] is you clean up and
you're going to be more able to use your
intuition your senses all those senses
and you're going to be able to smell
horseshit from a mile away
it'll definitely be more keen on it
Brandy says yep I smoked and drank until
three years ago so glad I quit
Michelle gray says I quit four and a
half years ago very happy celery juice
juice helps me to stay off of it
it's amazing I could say celery juice a
million times over the last 35 years and
I can still mess up the word while we're
live
this is who would have known
seriously
old hurt
okay ready this doesn't mean that you
become more emotional emotional after
cleansing rather that you can become
more emotionally protected and
emotionally sound
you cleanse properly you cleanse with
powerful cleanses
and you become emotional sound
emotionally sound
George news over there on
George Hughes over there on YouTube
cigar smoker still once a month
and I don't judge you for it I'm not
going to judge you I'm not going to
shame you no way am I going to be
throwing that at you never in a million
years I got your back I got your back
smoking is tough on the body it tips the
scale in the wrong direction
it's hard on the body but I do not shame
or blame or
judge anyone
who's still burning coals
old hurt can create such a brain fog
allowing us to make the same mistake
over and over again I read that wrong
let's do it again old hurt can create a
fog
that's what it is not a brain fun
allowing us to make the same mistake
over and over again just as when we're
in pain from burning our hand on the
stove I got to tell you something so
many people if we don't get old heard
out of her system join the collecting
Stones meditation Journey please please
please link is in the profile link is in
the description I'm serious you guys
it's a seven day free Journey your mind
is going to be blown I'm talking about
that right now because I want to get old
hurt out of you guys and I want to let
it go and get it out of your system
because once it's out of your system
man
Life Changes
many of us dealt with secondhand smoke
trust me many of us have dealt with
secondhand smoke
old hurt can create such a fog allowing
us to make the same mistake over and
over again just as when we're in pain
from burning our hand on the stove we
may turn away in fear and inner haste
accidentally back into the fireplace
when we aren't filled with poisons and
fear-based betrayal-based harm-based
adrenaline
when we're not filled with all that crap
anymore all that adrenaline and
fear-based and harm-based adrenaline
when it's out of our cells and out of
our fat cells and out of our organs and
out of our body and our bloodstream the
door opens up old hurt can leave it can
leave and you do the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
forget it wait till you do that
we're going to be able to see the
momentary pain clearly rather than find
ourselves in a fog of old percolating
hurt and that's going to let us take
care of ourselves properly rather than
hurt ourselves even more by making
mistakes out of desperation
you know your decision making
comes clear
you're cleansing you're getting the junk
out you see the truth you know what's
going on your healing your body's
healing and things come clear and more
clear and more clear Clarity happens and
that's incredible Saint Suey says I
can't believe I'm still alive after so
many decades of abusing my body I'm a
walking Miracle to be able to heal now
drop the mic
so many don't realize that out there
so many don't realize that
after cleansing the right way you often
become wiser beyond your years
after cleansing the right way
we often become wiser
beyond our years
Becca Johnson said 369 cleanse made me a
lot wiser
you may find yourself a little more
guarded in a good way
you may find yourself a little bit more
guarded in a good way you're more
cautious about when to be vulnerable
make better decisions about whom to
involve yourself with and whom to
confide in
and you're more intuitive about when to
drop off your guard and open the door
for a healthier friendship or
relationship you become more keen
you clear out the junk and garbage in
the old emotions that have been sitting
there rotting and festering and you
don't recreate the same patterns over
and over again you break the patterns so
you're not a slave to those patterns so
you're not stuck in that so you're not
getting in another toxic relationship
that takes you down so you're not
getting into another bad friendship that
takes you down so you know make another
Wrong Turn you get clarity you cleanse
you get rid of the junk the old crap
that's stored inside every cell and
inside every every organ in your body
and you clear that out you get rid of it
and you open the door you open the door
to Clarity and what happens is you
become more keen less reactive more
mindful because when you rid yourselves
of enough toxins and poisons and viruses
and unproductive bacteria and old
adrenaline that harbored past emotions
you become better able to avoid
repeating mistakes
those are my words
those are SOC words right there
I could never ever
in a million years come up with the
information in these eight Medical
textbooks
then healing textbooks
here with Hannah says I am way better at
handling stressful situations than ever
before so definitely we become wiser
with medical medium cleansing thank you
you're on IG
I mean this information just blows my
mind every time and I can't take credit
for it totally yes I was the messenger
I heard the information from above
I took my pen and paper and wrote Every
Word
and it blows my mind to read it over and
over again I haven't been in this book
in a while this is just an incredible
book from from SOC
once you've released old hurt and fears
from broken relationships your
adrenaline
passageways become clearer
did you hear that adrenaline passageways
that's in here and cleanse the heel
adrenaline passageways
to come mind-blowing
your own deep understanding of what
you're truly feeling and who you truly
are can Surface who are you
who are you truly surfaces
in the end
what this all amounts to is freedom from
the old chains of toxins and bugs and
hurt that have been holding you back
throughout a lifetime
it's this incredible book do you have
cleanse the heel amazon.com us
it's like 48 off or something I don't
know I just don't quote me exactly on a
percentage but it's on there get it
take initiation
take some health responsibility what you
guys already do so I can't say that
because you guys do
you guys are more responsible with your
health than I've seen anybody
on the planet go to the library get it
for free
if you don't want to spend the 20 bucks
or whatever it is
Lucina says I become so much more
intuitive it's incredible
incredible
you guys sign up
if you can
sign up to collecting Stones meditation
Journey it's a free seven-day Journey it
starts tomorrow I am very excited I
don't even know what to say
I don't even know what to say
ing Saints who says I'm so fired up
right now
empowered Souls chapter 26 right there
empowered Souls
read that chapter
you won't be disappointed me too
787. I got something you wrote
me too hang on me too
me tube787.
low battery let's let's hope I can get
this
okay me too 787
you said this you put this comment on
YouTube
I actually screenshot it
regarding pro athletes and chronic
illness sufferers
yes 100 percent
on point aw
I can attest to that
as a former professional downhill
mountain bike racer
by the way me tube787 that blew my mind
former professional downhill mountain
bike racer no Training Day
no Sprints no physical injury no
completion can compare with the struggle
and challenges of chronic illness it's a
whole other level in my case brain fog
neurological fatigue chronic fatigue leg
pain Etc if I didn't have the experience
of competing at the elite level I would
have thought and believed that I was
just weak and I've definitely thought
that many many times as I was going from
Doctor to sport doctor to Alternative
doctor to Alternative sport doctor etc
etc etc
all training and competition seems like
a walk in the park compared to the
torture of chronic illness your word 787
I often think how easy a heavy gym day
is
yeah people right
I often think how easy a heavy gym day
is or Sprints or com competition in
comparison to the constant chronic
illness suffering
I'm definitely not as impressed as I
used to be with the athletic
achievements as I am with the
achievements of the ones that are
struggling with chronic illness
and their strength to keep going and
going forward and healing regardless of
what the world around them might tell
them
I'm going to read that last line because
I kind of messed it up are definitely
not as impressed I'm definitely not as
impressed as I used to be with the
athletic achievements as I am with the
achievements of the ones that are
struggling with chronic illness and
their strength to keep going and going
forward
and healing regardless of what the world
around them might tell them I'm finally
healing with the medical medium
information thank you for caring for so
many aw and of course thank you for
sticking around much love God bless
you guys
when you get a chance
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
when you get a chance make sure you own
this book
or go to the library
it's mind-blowing information
this has been
an incredible experience today just
hanging out with you guys and seeing how
many of you guys smoked
Katie says how to cleanse yourself after
years of smoking
that stuff comes out
it comes out of your cells Katie
when you're doing
the stuff comes out
Veronica says do your book want do you
do you book one-on-one appointments I
haven't booked one-on-one appointments
and almost a decade
been very long time
um but look out for imposters
because imposters are actually
pretending to be me
and trying to book appointments with
people
they're saying they're aw they put a
picture of my profile
they make it look like I'm them whatever
they're me
and they might even be using a y
I call it y
you know what I'm talking about a
y
is that it
is it you know the two you know the two
letters I got it wrong right it's a y
do you guys know why I do that do you
guys know why I'm not saying a
do you know why I'm not saying that ah
a y
cause you say that
then that brings it to you that's how
crazy ay is Chrissy chaos says thank you
I feel so much validation that's soc's
information by the way
of that a y thing
thank you I feel so much validation
after hearing that question for the
longest time if I was weak or not you're
definitely not weak you're definitely
not weak
no one's weak here
no one
me too true thank you for all your work
aw
you guys I could stay on here
I could stay on here all day
it's how much I love you guys
cold cold white spring you just said you
don't get it you don't get what I was
saying
you don't get it
a
but I'm saying a why
because if you say Spirit tells me
anyway
that if you say a
then it comes to you
because that's what SOC tells me and I
believe it because SOC
doesn't let me down so it's yes that's
what I'm trying to tell you you don't
get it either wanna you don't get it
come on
seriously
oh you ready
a
a why
a what's this an eyeball right
i ball I
a eyeball a uh
okay
all right guys
Jenny Mack you got it
all right this concludes
this concludes another medical medium
live
until next time
and hopefully
the haters keep hating because it's the
best part
of doing this work
because right now
God you do incredible things out there
try to help people you put information
try to save lives hate her scream bloody
murder even more and more
it's like Venom coming out of like
Devils coming out of their cells forked
on coming out of them the more and more
good you do the more and more and they
scream
like it's insane like they're just poor
it's coming out of their pores their
hatred and their
crap coming out of them the devil's
coming out of them they're like
definitely possessed right coming out of
them the more good things you do the
more they get crazy it's actually funny
Priscilla H best book ever loved it it
healed my joint pain I'm always grateful
to you Anthony and to Spirit of
compassion from Switzerland my loved
Switzerland
incredible
Jackie B haters will never stop this no
falsities are insane at this point
tomorrow's day one collecting Stones
meditation Journey
do not miss it
I don't know what else I could do
love you guys I love you guys quite
spring
uh-huh cold white spring exactly
huh exactly I read that
I hear you all right guys
love you