here the moon meditation episode six
the moon meditation have you done the
moon meditation
it's a powerful healing meditation for
the soul so
episode six the moon meditation
is out today it came out like last night
and i'm hoping you did the moon
meditation for healing
it helps get rid of the poison inside
the soul i'll talk about that a little
bit and i'll also talk about how
that poison has a color so when you do
the moon meditation
you can visualize and see that color and
i'm noticing
people are seeing the color even before
i talk about the color that they see
you know that that's in there so it's
really powerful so the moon meditation
episode six hey guys hey glad you're all
here
um and so this is a powerful healing
meditation
on a whole nother level so i hope you
guys experienced it okay there's the
brain meditation that was the other
first meditation um
in the episodes now now the moon
meditation is a whole other level for
healing
you don't have to do the moon meditation
when the moon's out if you don't want to
you can use it to go to sleep at night
you could do the moon meditation any
time
but it's a powerhouse to move you
forward and heal so great to see
everybody tonight
um and the and the link you know the
link is in the description so you have
to check this out you have to check
the moon meditation out as soon as you
can the link is in the description
and the power this has to heal
and i want to talk about why and how and
i even want to talk about the brain
meditation so you guys got questions
ask me any questions as well with these
meditations regarding them
and have you heard the egg episode too
so eggs eater
eat eggs eaters lose all and
you know i know they got a lot of people
upset the egg episode but it's a
powerhouse all in its own
information never known out there so
this is this is powerful
information that's going to be really
helpful so so you always fall asleep
so you always fall asleep during the
brain meditation yes well the moon
meditation you may be able to do that
too fall asleep during it
um so dr faun md's here hey
he's got the shades and the emoji uh
mary says i can't wait to do the full
move we'll do it with the full moon
tonight incredible
incredible robbery you're amazing um so
you're rhonda says i'm loving these
meditations i'm so happy can you share
them if you guys can
please share these meditations share
them with others so people can heal
margie says hello anthony hello and
kathleen says you love the moon
meditation
incredible so i want to talk about that
a little bit the power it has and what
goes on the moon's magnetic power
can identify some hurt
some poison some emotional wounds that
are deep in our soul and body
where do we get these emotional wounds
struggles hardships
losses breakups divorces broken
friendships broken relationships
difficult circumstances difficult trials
and
tribulations and injustices in our life
we collect these wounds along the way
emotionally
and it can just sit inside our soul how
do you know it's sitting inside your
soul post-traumatic stress
syndrome right there just when you feel
like you're allergic to things or
meaning allergic to certain people are
allergic to certain
emotional situations and this is really
healing for
for dealing with that eva said hello hey
eva hello
going to do moon meditation tonight i
always used your other moon meditation
from your books
eva wait till you try this moon
meditation tonight
it's mind-blowing really the link is in
the description
so the link is in the description now
where do you hear these
episodes i'm going to tell you guys
apple podcast medical medium podcast
is on apple podcast that's the platform
i chose it's uncensored if you
hear these episodes and other platforms
that you could be using you could be
they could be the censored versions and
most likely it is and it's tricky
because
one could be censored one's not or one's
partially censored or
clips are out of it or it's uploaded
wrong and so
make sure apple podcast that's where you
hear it that's
that's the those are the versions that
you you should hear now if you don't
have an apple device
no have no fear okay it's all good all
you need to do is take your android
or any other device you have go to
medicalmedium.com so medicalmedium.com
can go there and at medicalmedium.com
you um you go to the menu you see
podcasts in the menu you can download in
here for free i just want to tell you
guys
share it if you really can michelle l
says i feel
strong energy from the moon incredible
it's really healing this meditation
michelle and can really help
with ptsd because i know you've gone
through some things in your life
and i know that and things haven't been
easy for you along the way with any kind
of struggles with health and all that
and
you're working on your healing process
and moving forward every day and
yes the moon meditation is so helpful
and michelle thank you for all that you
do by the way
because i know that you're out there
spreading the word for medical medium
information helping people heal you have
tremendous compassion and your
information is always
just spot on just uh i'm honored that
you're here
truly honored that you're here um kathy
says what is the lemonade stand meaning
the lemonade stand and the brain
meditation so let's talk about some of
the meanings inside
inside this okay and what happens is
that
there's uh our neurons get tattered
along the way
so when we go through hardships losses
and we
end up getting fear as their soul gets
kicked out of her body so
when we have a hardship when we have a
loss we can get the
depression depersonalization we can
actually have an out-of-body experience
every time we go through something
whether it's a broken relationship
whether it's anything a
hardship and so our soul leaves our our
body for a little bit and then fear
fills in the gap
and when this happens when we get told
bad news or we go through something hard
or something emotionally
trouble troublesome neurons get
overheated in the emotional center of
the brain so neurons get
overheated they just fry you know burn
out
so we get burnout like something too
emotional that wasn't that wasn't fair
or something
we got some we were misunderstood or
betrayal or we got stabbed in the back
and
all of a sudden you get this burnout
occur in the in the emotional center of
the brain well that burnout
um get those neurons get tattered but
they don't have an opportunity to really
heal so easy and our soul gets distant
from our body because of this because of
what we go through in the struggles and
the lemonade stand and the the family
that's fishing
on the bridge and the golden retriever
that's coming to you are all
zoned they're safety zones the neurons
see them as safety zones and when the
neurons see them as safety zones you're
repairing neurons and repairing the
bridge
so that the soul comes back and what
you'll find
i'm not going to for the people who
haven't done the brain meditation yet
not going to you know tell tell you what
happens at the end
but there's a reuniting of your soul
with your physical brain it's just so
powerful
you know share it with someone the link
is in the description please share it
with someone tell them to listen to it
off of apple podcast
um so i love your passion on those
podcasts i love all
i saw a perfect bridge on the brain
meditation from the beginning incredible
julia
you're amazing you're amazing and i'm so
proud of you i really
am truly proud of you and um each other
says having to do these guided
meditations
everything anthony um i look forward
to every morning and evening to doing
them so happy childhood
thank you for all the work you're doing
uh spreading the word
of the medical medium healing
information and saving lives
that you know and that's that's what
you're doing please share you guys
share the meditations share the episodes
did you hear
the egg episode did you hear the air
fresheners episode
air fresheners and scented candles did
you listen to that one
did you listen to the fruit fear episode
some of these episodes are really really
really tough
um so uh marcius marcia says
god help me i lost my son and i'm having
a very difficult time my soul is hurting
so deeply there's no words
for the kind of pain that you're
suffering with uh
you know and my heart pours out to you
pours out to you and
and um and if you if you if you
have a moment and you feel like you can
do one of the meditations
uh please try if you can and um
my heart pours out to you truly truly
truly
really does um dr phan
and everybody's coming on tonight
um sergio uh hi aw i did the moon
meditation last night oh
it was amazing loved it thank you so
much many blessings
so glad you did that so glad um because
it's so helpful it's so helpful
and michelle says haha i'm allergic to
certain people
and you know it can happen it can happen
um exactly we get we get wounded we get
because some people are they're really
toxic with a lot of stuff with emotions
and all kinds of things
um i got to tell you guys this is free
by the way
the the episodes the medical media
podcast is free
it's free on apple podcast to listen to
it's a free
resource and i'm not making any money
off this resource and i'm saying
sponsorships and no infomercials in
these episodes
and on this podcast and so share them if
you can
i don't like to ask for things but if
you guys
feel you can share them that would be
just a blessing and help other people
you would be getting the information
helping others out there because that's
what it's about
it's about making sure we help people
and help them get better katrina i've
always i've already done your moon
meditation
wow fantastic i can't believe you done
that already
because just came out um so proud of you
guys i really
am and so the brain meditation is
another one too
darcy said did it last night i'm so
freaking excited
thank you darcy i'm glad you did the the
meditation share it if you can
surely says hi this sounds so
interesting surely when you get a chance
try the brain meditation okay or the
moon meditation try the brain meditation
first
try that one first okay and it
the link is in the description right
there so you can see it
um go to medicalmedium.com if you don't
have an apple device
go to medicalmedium.com and use an
android or whatever you got
go to the menu see the podcast there and
you can just listen to it
but um but medical media podcast is on
apple podcast it's uncensored
uncensored there so people can heal uh
for sure um did you catch episode four
the air freshener episode air freshener
sent to candles
because air fresheners and scented
candles can irritate our central nervous
system
and it can bring on a little bit of
anxiety bring on a little bit of
some migraines it can bring on a little
bit of depression
it can bring on especially anxiety and
migraines so
you want to pull those air fresheners
out of the wall and boop throw them out
you want to you want to not do that
stuff you sent the candles
don't light them you can keep them there
but don't light them i would i would
remove them and i would get candles that
actually aren't scented by chemicals and
all that
because these chemicals really get into
our lungs they get into our body they
cause
problems they create more anxiety
sensitive nerves they can make us sick
so it's really a great powerful episode
said the candles colognes perfumes
the episode is called killing you smelly
it's air fresheners scented candles
cologne's perfumes
and then eggs eaters lose all that's
another episode too fruit fear's another
episode
um luke how are you luke wish i could
like
wish i could like his videos more than
once thanks anthony have been able to
function for
last year since following your info
you're able to function okay incredible
incredible
um just keep on working on it and so
glad you're able to function so glad
you're able to heal
heidi says your moon meditation is
amazing your voice is soothing love it
thanks heidi and i'm glad you're
listening to it share it with others
please do that
nicole first time doing a full moon um
you guys i'm really proud of you for
doing the meditations they're really
helpful really healing
um and so glad i'm so glad truly what
was your favorite part of the moon
meditation that's what i want to ask you
guys what did you find interesting
share it with others post about it if
you can post about it so others can see
it
what was your favorite part of the brain
meditation what was your favorite part
of the moon meditation
please relieve a review at apple podcast
so others can heal
others can find it please do that if you
can
um because it really really really helps
it really helps
so alondra said can't wait to hear i
love seeing the moon every day
you don't have here's the thing you
don't have to do the moon meditation
during a moon
that you see because the moon is up
there it's up there around the world you
can you know it's it's there we can
still get the gravitational pull
to help us heal but yes it's great
having at the full moon
great having it half moon partial moon a
morning moon
all of that um darcy says i think your
books are my favorite gifts to send my
friends darcy thank you
that's the nicest thing nicest gesture
the nicest gift
um lumila says my five-year-old daughter
always talks to the moon
that's so special that's incredible
it really is debbie says oh my god i
really need this today thank you so much
for helping us heal from ptsd
wait till you try the moon meditation
that's an incredible
ptsd healing meditation
um andrea andrew agent andrea quiety
said
just shared meditation thank you for
just sharing it
bless your heart it really matters and
what you can you can actually have
confidence that they're not going to be
drowned out
by infomercials advertisement
sponsorships and all that i did that
purposely
free resource with none of that michelle
said two full moons this month
and it's unseparate censored at apple
podcast share it at that
that that's the place to share it that's
the place for them to listen so it's
uncensored and all of that so very
important
um really important terry says i use my
crystals when i meditate you can have
your crystals there while doing the moon
meditation
the brain meditation you can have your
crystals there it's fine
fine it definitely is um so
rhonda says the brain meditation was
amazing what's your favorite part of the
brain meditation
and what's your favorite part of the
moon meditation
gene said thank you anthony in spirit
for these meditations i feel my body
healing as well as my
soul tears tingling and over all calm
happens
amazing how this works i'm sharing the
information you are giving us thank you
for sharing sharing is caring god bless
you
kathleen loso says can you do both in
one night the moon and brain meditation
yes
and you can fall asleep to one of them
if you like moon meditation
could really fall asleep too it's really
healing and you still heal even if
you're sleeping during the meditation
because i'm
guiding you in the meditation so that's
the powerful
part of it too the link is in the
description
so you guys know so you guys know and
um and it's uncensored on apple podcast
that's where you want to listen to it if
you can
if you don't have an apple device go to
medicalmedium.com menu
and then podcast and you can download
and listen to it
link is in description though the link
is in the description
you guys so and the uncensored it's
uncensored at apple podcast please know
that
and because any other platforms then hey
it's going to be censored or the little
piece is missing and all that stuff so
very important to know um i you know the
thing is about the brain meditation when
you're ridding
fear from your from soul your soul when
you're reading fear from your body
and your soul comes together in that
connection that bridge
gaps like that all of a sudden it
connects and the gap disappears and your
soul starts to connect with the neurons
in your brain and your physical brain
and body
it's an experience unlike any other so
the brain meditation is that one there
too
um i've always have had meditation so a
medical medium book i put meditations in
there
i've done lectures with meditations i've
done meditations and all kinds of
different
workshops i've done medical media
meditations from above so i want to
tell you guys about this part is that
but this i'm making sure i do guided
ones in a podcast
uncensored for you guys powerful ones
barbara says the fruit fear episode was
great uh hey trisha
trisha marie's here tonight yay um
so yeah it's the thing is i finally not
feeling okay so sandy says i'm finally
not feeling disconnected
like i've had for the last three years
the brain meditation is great i finally
feel like
mixing with people that's incredible
because once you rid the fear
out of the physical body and the soul
healing happens and the moon meditation
pulls the poison out of us too it's so
powerful what happens in that
so powerful chris says i can
seem to focus on one bridge my mind
wanders between different types of
bridges that's okay
your mind could wander between bridges
perfectly fine you're still healing and
going through it and that's
part of the exercise it's part of the
healing part of it where you might
wander through the different bridges in
in your your mind but that means there's
also a lot going on in your neurons that
are healing
susan renee says susan renee perlman
says
i love the the rhyming poetry at the end
of each new podcast
is that the spirit of compassion's
rhyming message yes susan
that those are messages from spirit of
compassion all of those are powerful
messages
from spirit of compassion that are at
the end of the regular episodes
and even even a little bit of a powerful
message at the end of
moon meditation the end of um
the moon meditation the end of brain
meditation but yes powerful messages
are at the end of the egg one the
chemtrail one the fruit fear one
uh the air freshener one powerful
messages
thank you for recognizing that spirit
from spirit of compassion
frederick says love you brother hey man
it means a lot to
it means a lot to me just so you know
tammy says i get chills when i listen to
the brain meditation sometimes
yes and so do i
i listen before bed in the middle of the
night when i wake i
play it and go back to sleep i shared it
thank you for sharing it
listen you guys i don't want to ask
anything of you you know i know i've
been
writing the books for you guys all these
years and i know i've been
putting out information and articles and
blog posts and
and doing lives to help you guys heal
for year after year after year but
but if if there's anything you can do
share it please share
the episode share the podcast it's going
to really help get the information out
there
because there's only so much i can do
and and to get it out there
janice says i lost both my parents six
weeks apart
four years ago and i'm just starting to
process oh my god
a year after more loss in the family
grief
is a crazy way that that hits hard
it does it does it's it's um
it does it's it's really a part of life
that we just
we just it's unimaginable but we don't
really understand it
it's the way life is with when we lose
loved ones and the losses
and i'm just hoping that you get a
chance to maybe do the moon meditation
the brain meditation
if you can sometime and i think you are
i think you were saying that
uh dr sherry green dr sherry green
amazing md the meditations are so
incredible and so
deeply healing sharing with all my
patients yesterday
incredible incredible that's so special
so you're sharing it with your patients
uh thank you doctor thank you doctor
because you're helping people and that's
what you're doing anyway but incredible
you're just working on healing people
um so
you share the info several times
incredible so
you know the thing is with the full moon
meditation you don't have to do on a
full moon you don't have to do a partial
moon you don't have to see the light
from the moon
but if you do it's incredible all of it
but the meditation is just as powerful
you can do it every single
day the link is in the description for
the moon meditation uh for the medical
meeting podcast at apple podcast that's
the uncensored version to listen to
that's the best place to listen to
better than any platform
there's poison that we collect that
resides inside of our soul when
you get betrayed when you have a loss
when you get a broken heart
when someone stabs you in the back when
broken trust happens like i said when
we have a loss when something
a confrontation whatever we go through
um
emotional emotional issues we have
meaning because someone's
you know we get allergic to somebody
because um they might be like
their emotions are really intense and it
might be really hard to
to to to work with it because when
people
are also going through so much they can
then you know then their emotions all of
a sudden
start you know we start taking them in
because we care so much so we need some
healing
and we need some healing and so with the
moon meditation does is the
gravitational pull
you'll see when you do the moon
meditation it
it showcases that color that yellow
color that i talk about in the
meditation
and then draws out the poison you really
have to experience it
um so ma'am says emma's he said a few
days ago that there will be more
meditations
and there will be more meditations
i did said love the brain meditation
keep falling asleep after five minutes
that's incredible because the meditation
is still working
as you fall asleep because i'm in the
meditation
holding your hand through it making sure
that i'm guiding you through it
and it's that powerful and it can heal
you while you're sleeping
and then you you sleep really well after
feel a lot lighter
lately incredible thank you anthony and
um
and spirit of compassion from wales
incredible
valerie says going outside for the moon
meditation tonight you can do the
meditation outside the moon meditation
outside but check this out you guys
you can do the moon meditation inside
you can do it inside
you can do it inside on the bed on the
floor on the couch
relaxing you can do it inside and
put it on and the moon can come through
the window if you don't see the moon
that's okay if a building's in the way
that's okay but yes the moon meditation
catherine elizabeth says i i saw only
yellow colors
whoa whoa whoa whoa that's incredible
um so yeah so really you guys so proud
of you
and the moon meditation the brain
meditation
did you catch the other episodes i know
some of them were really hard
to hear because they're really intense
you got the chemtrail episode you've got
the
fruit fear episode you got um these
episodes are really really and then
you've got the air freshener episode the
egg episode
and we're going to be doing symptoms and
conditions too but always remember that
there's healing information in these
episodes
no matter what and share them if you can
the link is in the description uh please
share
noel shepherd said thanks for holding my
hand and this well
so proud of you noelle who else i've
known noel for years
incredible the work you've done helping
people heal
has it's always mind-blowing please
leave a review at apple podcast
um in the medical meeting podcast at
apple podcast if you can
zavo says love them awesome so glad man
i'm honored i'm honored i'm honored i'm
honored
it all matters um it all matters because
if you love them then
you can then then hey if you love them
then you'll tell someone else someone
else gets a chance to heal then i feel
like
we're doing it we're all doing it
together we're helping others heal too
that's really important and and in your
healing your healing
well zabo says i share it everywhere
you're cool
you're cool love you man love you man
thank you
um i have been playing the brain
meditation for my husband and
grandchildren and we are all
improving uh folklore family
mind-blowing mind-blowing you're all
improving the brain meditation
really really powerful meditation for
healing for getting rid of fear
for removing fear what's powerful about
these meditations is
you know as we go through life and we
feel like we need them they're there for
us
all the time these meditations now i
want to tell you guys these meditations
are from above
so they're not here man