live episode 7 released
this morning i hope you catch it okay
coffee matcha tea
chocolate it's the episode you can't
miss it's really an important one if you
believe
in good health if you're somebody that
maybe thinks about longevity if you're
somebody that thinks about
hey you know i want to feel good
throughout my whole life
this is the episode you don't want to
miss okay because
i talk about the relationship we have
between coffee
matcha tea chocolate and you don't want
to miss this
because it's really powerful and i talk
about like
the longevity factor like because what's
happening here is you'll find you'll
hear out there hey
matcha tea longevity coffee longevity
you know you'll hear about this out
there chocolate's a superfood
but is it is it a superfood and i talk
about
our adrenals and what how caffeine plays
an effect on our adrenals and what that
means
i talk about that and i talk about our
skin
how we age quicker with caffeine so
that's an important factor right there
all in its own
and how we get tricked along the way
thinking hey
this is good for me you know is this
good for me i hear good reports about
this i hear good studies and i talk
about
a little bit about that too so you don't
want to miss this
helena says well i just woke up and saw
it's a new episode you don't want to
miss it it's a powerful episode
and it's packed with information now
when you hear this caffeine episode when
you hear this chocolate episode this
manchester episode this coffee episode
prepare to be mind-blown okay this one
here
is unlike anything i've done and every
single
part of it is jammed packed right across
the board
and so i know you hear you know you're
gonna hear out there people like talk
about hey match t's got good things in
it
it's you know it's good things for your
health for you know longevity and
coffee is good for you and chocolate's
good for you and that's what we're told
and we're told by and i talk about the
caffeine industry involved there and why
we're told these things and how it works
i mean honestly
when you hear this episode you're going
to be enthralled
and from the very beginning to the end
it's that pact it's it's it's that it's
that you know so
anyway you can you can listen to it at
apple podcast the medical medium podcast
at apple podcast make sure you subscribe
so you always get notifications because
you don't want to
miss these you don't want to miss these
and
david david witchin says aw i just
listened to it and it's mind-blowing
so sad but so happy to hear the truth
thanks david for
for listening to this one share it if
you can please share
and if you need to know where this
episode is it's in the description so
the link is in the description right
here
but share the episode if you can david
and thanks so much it's it's
it's mind-blowing right exactly and and
this episode will keep you like we'll
keep you
in it the whole time because the
information
just is something you've never heard
this information before
you just need to know that and when it
comes down to matcha tea when it comes
down to coffee when it comes comes down
to chocolate we're told right now
that it's really great for us that's
what we're told
but there's something inside of us all
that knows a little better than that
we know when we get jacked up we know
you when we get jacked
up on caffeine what that's like right
and i don't blame anyone at all
on any level for being on coffee
for being on chocolate for being on
matcha tea for being on caffeine at all
energy drinks i don't blame anybody at
all and i'm on your side are you kidding
me because
when you got some brain fog and you
don't feel that good
and you know life is hard and we kind of
we
we lean on these things i mean we can
have energy issues we cannot feel good
we can have fatigue
and you know the focus and concentration
so you guys
you have to know like i'm with you i'm
on your side if you have to do chocolate
if you have to do matcha tea if you have
to do coffee to survive
because you've got low energy issues and
fatigue and brain fog
and you can't think because something
else is going on
because that's the whole point where
we're a society today
the human race is bogged down with all
these symptoms now
and so we have to get jacked up on
caffeine
it's and then we get told that it's good
for us
because of a study that may comes that
may come out like antioxidants there
might be some antioxidants in matcha tea
there's some antioxidants in coffee
there's antioxidants and chocolate
and i talk about that too about about
studies
and how they might be kind of biased and
paid for by caffeine industry so it's
really interesting the whole thing is
whole thing is a mind blower i hope you
guys catch it
because it's a mind blower really is
listen and subscribe
so if you can listen to the uh the
episode coffee matcha tea
chocolate and you know other caffeine
too caffeine beverages
and apple podcasts that's the uncensored
version
so i'm hoping you hear it from apple
podcast so it's the uncensored version
so
medical medium podcast at apple podcast
don't miss this one
truly because this one here is just
packed and i thought i i released some
secrets
that i have learned along the way about
coffee so and you don't want to miss
those secrets
it's going to be shocking like you're
going to be definitely shocked
but it's good to know the truth it
really is
and look i talk about withdrawal
so to help you through withdrawal the
best way to
to break the caffeine you know monster
the group the best way to break it is is
you know i talk about tools for that and
i got one on me right now you know
and that's the celery juice right there
and and the cool thing is
already thousands of people have broke
their caffeine addiction
using celery juice as one of the tools
so that's that's really awesome right
there
like marl hi anthony thank you for
everything i healed my acne thanks to
you and will share my results soon oh my
god thank you for sharing results
bless you you're awesome and i'm so
proud of you i really am so proud of you
share the podcast if you can too if you
can there's so many incredible episodes
there's the moon meditation which is
mind-blowing
so check out the moon meditation there's
the brain meditation these are guided
meditations i walk you through
and that i hold your hand and walk you
through for healing fear
for healing emotional deep-seated
emotional wounds so check out those
meditations because
that would be awesome if you do because
those are so
healing they're already healing so many
have you guys tried the meditations yet
um silk says thank you for all your
episodes and especially the last one it
was mind-blowing again
i'm so happy to hear um yeah
yeah the coffee the coffee matcha tea
it's a mind-blowing one the chocolate
one it's a mind-blowing one so yeah i'm
so happy you
you you've heard it you listen share it
if you can
and medical media podcast at apple
podcast the descriptions in the
the you know the links in the
description so make sure you check that
out
and check out the eggs episode eaters
lose all
check out that episode the air freshener
episode the fruit fair episode the
chemtrail episode of course
um yeah david right you can't believe i
shared those secrets
and i you know i wasn't going to because
you
didn't know if a how anybody was going
to handle it and but i had to
i had to i need you guys to know what's
going on about
coffee about matcha tea about chocolate
and a whole bit
and it's important to know like why
we're being told too
like that it's good for us why we're
being fed that so we can stay on our
addictions you know
and look once again i stand behind you
if you have to use those as a crutch if
you have to use those to survive
if you have to use chocolate or matcha
tea or
coffee to get through a day because you
don't feel good
natalie says love the moon meditation
share it with people
tell them where they can hear it please
uh i'm so glad you loved it
and incredible and uh bharari says i
love the meditations incredible
um make sure you share them keep on
sharing them you guys it's gonna be the
only way to get the information out
there it's gonna be the only way for
people to hear it really because
you know i don't run the ads on on those
things there's no commercials there's no
infomercials during those they're in the
podcast episodes and you'll know
it's all free listening for you guys
there's nothing bogging you down
i'm not throwing commercials in there or
anything um
so yes i'm so proud of you guys and
shelley says celery juice has helped me
in several ways so far
uh so you you you don't hurt anymore my
periods are better
my skin looks younger and feel isn't
that incredible because
this is one of those powerful tools the
medical medium celery juice because
yeah it was started the global celery
juice movement
spirit of compassion did and without
this
so many people would have i mean they'd
be struggling it's really turned
people's lives around frederick hey good
to see you there
um so jennifer says uh
wait i missed that goes up you guys
sometimes i can't catch them fast enough
and they go up
so anyway the link is in the description
make sure you check it out
where kimberly says where can i watch
these perfect medical medium podcast
at apple podcast thanks for asking that
truly because
it really reminds me so you guys know
medical medium podcasts at
apple podcast okay and that's the
uncensored platform
in which i i you know made the launch to
be
geared to that because it's important
because any other
platforms you guys all the other
platforms are going to be clipped and
there's no way the caffeine episode is
going to be
completely whole on another platform in
my opinion i would just listen to it at
apple podcast
if you don't have an apple device go to
medicalmedium.com
okay to the menu and see podcast in the
menu
and there you go um or you can subscribe
to the medical medium newsletter i
subscribe to the medical media
newsletter so
because i send the emails out to notify
everybody the link is in the description
and seller anita says celery jesus
helped my daughter
with down syndrome focus so much better
oh my god god bless her that's the best
that's the best news i ever heard
that's so incredible i got the celery
juice right here i haven't even
haven't even uh got into it yet and
and there's margie margie cameron
thank you for all that you're doing out
there you're working on your healing
process
and i know you're listening to the
podcast
incredible um so you guys the coffee
matcha tea okay chocolate episode
it's really jam-packed with information
i talk about how caffeine affects our
adrenals
how it affects our liver how it affects
our skin
how it ages us quicker why we're told
it doesn't age us why we're told that
it's good for us okay
and how and and and how
how we struggle through withdrawal and
how that works on how the caffeine
just just stays in the emotional center
of the brain
and we have this relationship with
caffeine that we can't break
i also talk about surgeons can't go
through withdrawal
so i have a have a friend who's a
surgeon and
and how she filled me in on how surgeons
don't want to go through withdrawal and
there's a whole thing about that i talk
about how
wow i mean the information in this
episode is mind-blowing
catherine says the moon meditation was
so powerful awesome you should do it all
the time even when there's no moon up
there
or no moon in the moment or you can't
see the moon it's that powerful of a
meditation
uh karen says from the bottom of my
heart thank you for all you do for us
with chronic illness the moon meditation
is fantastic i'll keep on doing it
and share it share it on your platforms
you guys share it with anybody you can
facebook youtube all of that please
share it because it's the only way it's
going to
get around because you've got to
remember medical medium information was
always grassroots
it was always people healing only and
that's how it spread around
the world and it's all through that
grassroots
it wasn't through any marketing it
wasn't through any of that
so i never had mark marketing big
marketing pr
never had any of that so the reason why
i got around was because it's healing
people and people
shared it so if you can keep on doing
that share the podcast because the
podcast
is not going to disappoint i promise you
from the chemtrail episode to the fruit
fear episode
to the eggs eaters lose all episode to
the brain meditation the moon meditation
to the air freshener episode to the
caffeine episode that you're
that you're hearing um now that you can
hear now so
margie says i only had one coffee i
think you said
i think what was that it went back up
but it's it's interesting you know it's
like it's hard to
it's hard to get off our coffee much tea
but here's the thing i
support if you have to use it remember
that like i support if
if you're on coffee there's a reason why
you're on coffee you probably don't feel
that great you probably have some focus
concentration things going on
maybe some toxic heavy metals and
other things going on so i get it or
your adrenals they're just they're just
not up to par so then we use caffeine
to try to jack them up but then i talk
about how this can kind of hurt us
hurt us along the way and how we need to
protect ourselves and protect
our adrenals and protect our liver and i
talk about how
it's not as anti-aging as people think
it is so
very important there so yeah
you know what with coffee if you need
coffee to actually
keep yourself level you stay on it if
you need coffee to keep yourself level
you stay on it so
it's that kind of thing if if you have
if you know that it's the only way that
you're gonna push through
and you're doing all these other
incredible things for yourself then you
keep coffee in there
that's that's what you can do and i've
always stood behind that
someone said to me recently they're like
oh you don't like the caffeine thing
you don't like caffeine and the
chocolate and all this stuff and
i go no that's not true that's not true
uh margie says i'm with my lemon water
now
i'm down to one from six a day oh
my god margie incredible
mind-blowing incredible got my celery
juice here i don't have my lemon water
here i already had my lemon water before
i came on
so um natalie hey natalie how you doing
anthony you won't believe this
i used to drink five to six cups of very
strong coffee a day oh my god i
can't imagine that's that's that's
incredible i don't need
coffee anymore after starting the celery
juice and supplements
wow oh my god natalie that's
incredible that is incredible
blown away and margie blown away too
with all that you're doing all you guys
it's
just you guys are mind-blowing me this
morning you guys are blowing my mind
more so than my episode
um anyway uh the link is in the
description
so it's a coffee matcha tea
uh chocolate episode the relationship we
have with caffeine
this is no boring episode just get ready
for a ride
when you hear this thing get ready for a
ride
this is one intense episode and it's
packed right down to the bone too i talk
about
how they grow coffee a little bit what
happens i talk about
how it's not so great for us caffeine i
talk about what it does to our adrenals
our liver our brain
i go into that dehydration i talk about
how it chronically dehydrates us i'm
just giving you a little window into it
but
but it's even more than that more of
that
he said you just signed up to your
podcast to the my podcast
thank you thank you thank you apple
podcast
the medical media podcast at apple
podcast thank you for signing up you're
going to get the uncensored version
there and you'll get mind blown and i
hope you listen to the moon meditation i
hope you listen to brain meditation and
all the other episodes
and you guys keep in mind a lot of
episodes coming
on different symptoms conditions how to
heal
all of that and and the coffee matcha
tea one is like that too i give tips
really powerful tips on how to break
caffeine
how to recover from withdrawal how to
get through withdrawal quick
and and and stay strong and all that so
honestly you guys
i mean it's really really this this
thing is
this episode is not only so mind-blowing
but it's enthralling too so you just
gotta it's you're gonna go for a ride in
this one it's such a great one
um natalie says i save so much money now
so that's incredible
um what's good for the adrenals pat you
got to hear this episode
and you'll see the things that i'm
talking about in there which are so so
powerful
um so
princess says i do not drink hot coffee
anymore
in my 40s i start getting heartburn will
you are you drinking some celery juice
are you doing some of the medical medium
tools do you have cleanse to heal the
book are you
are you doing other things take care of
yourself to get rich so that you
you know i mean i'd love to make sure
that your heartburn is not there anymore
while agreeing i'm glad you're here
today
incredible i hope you heard the episode
comments are flying up here um but yeah
you guys so what i really was
part of me was reluctant it's like do i
release this episode
because this episode is
like this one's a troublemaker because
man i mean i know people love to protect
your eggs totally get it i know they
they love to protect their eggs and when
i release the egg episode i was actually
nervous
and but this episode i'm talking about
the caffeine monster what that is i'm
talking about all of it
and how you know the paid for studies
and
all kinds of different things so this is
really really
a whole nother game here so um
and in the and the bottom line is this i
just want to say this okay
if you had to go on caffeine in your
life if you had to go on some kind of
caffeine
in some kind of way whether it was
coffee matcha tea whether it's green tea
it's another
whether it was an energy drink whether
it was
chocolate and you did it to survive
because of
focus concentration issues fatigue
you know you felt like you weren't alert
you felt like you were dragging in the
morning i completely understand
maybe it was what you used to function
but i want to help you guys
you know make that transition this
episode can help you with that
transition
help you get through the withdrawal fast
help you actually
heal an initial problem that's deep down
inside
it's really about that but at the same
time this episode is a ride
it's it's intriguing it's enthralling
it gets you wrapped up because there's
so much powerful
information in it it is mind-blowing so
karina says almost two years on celery
juice feeling great
proud of you mind blown you guys share
share the the podcast share the medical
medium podcast episodes tell people
about it please it's the only way
i can get that information out there
tell them they can hear the uncensored
version
which is really important to hear it
there at apple podcast and
the link is in the description if they
don't have an apple device just go to my
website medicalmedium.com
menu and you'll see podcasts in the menu
and you can just listen to it there but
just know
that if you share it that's how this has
always happened it's grassroots because
medical medium information has healed so
many and that's how it's always got
around
mark says hi anthony i want to thank you
for your healing books after two years
my cracked
heels are completely healed incredible
now one nail has to heal really amazing
so happy because
need my feet for teaching yoga whoa
you're a yoga teacher whoa
and now they are looking amazing
incredible so proud of you man
so proud of you truly am um
anita says i haven't heard the
meditation podcast and now i can't wait
to listen to them
when you hear the moon meditation uh
just
prepare to do some healing because
that's what's gonna happen
when you hear the brain meditation
prepare to do some healing
because that's gonna happen i'm just
just forewarning you there and
so look out melissa smith hey melissa
how are you doing today
i absolutely love the moon meditation
thank you i just received cleanse to
heal
super excited i'm oh wow so excited you
have that book because
that's the book right there it's it's a
medical textbook
it's mind-blowing it's already healing
hundreds of thousands of people in fact
just just in the us alone and and all
around the world it's healing millions
of people now it's just really taking
people to a
whole nother level of their healing
amanda says love the moon meditation
thank you
so glad you're doing it um i saw a
question what about black tea
well yeah well black tea that's the
caffeine we use caffeine to just jack us
up to jack up our adrenals to try to
get us to move through a day to push
through a day i talk about how we use it
for peristaltic action to try to go to
bathroom if we're dealing with
constipation
and but i talk about so many different
aspects of caffeine that's mind-blowing
you don't want to miss this
this um natalie says the caffeine
monster lives on
every every shelf in every corner the
caffeine monster so you heard the
episode
i talk about the caffeine monster you
don't want to miss this episode
seriously
and i am actually when do i do you know
alive at this time a day and that's how
excited
i am about this episode i mean i
just really am um if you don't want to
get off caffeine
that's okay you still want to hear the
episode
you still want to hear the episode
because there's so much to learn in it
it's enthralling
and it's actually kind of a fun show to
listen to while drinking caffeine if
you're going to be if you're going to be
drinking some kind of caffeine
um yeah so really it's it's so important
and but i got to tell you guys
with with with the information that you
learn
in this episode it's so jam-packed
i'm going to talk about withdrawal how
to do it how to get through it
how to survive it how to get to the
other side of it different tools to use
for it
okay that alone right there is going to
be in there i talk about
studies and if it's anti-aging or not i
talk about how it's what its effects on
the
adrenals the effects on the emotional
center of the brain the effects on our
neurons the effects on our liver
skin aging all of that i talk about
um that whole aspect of it i also tell
you guys
some truths that are hard to bear in
this episode
and i wasn't going to release some of it
but i said you know what you guys have
to hear it you just have to hear it
important cooking with skippy says full
moon great for meditation
yeah can totally do meditation around
that you can do it at other times too
with no problems
um anyway you guys i just wanted to drop
that on you
i want you to check it out um if you've
done the moon meditation remember
that the gravity moon's gravitational
pull has the ability to pull
that hurt out of the soul so hardships
loss betrayals
trust issues all these things remember
the moon meditation
tell other people to listen to that one
too get that one
out there tell them apple podcast tell
them that's where they have to hear it
because it's uncensored it's the best
part for it
um and i talk about hair loss too hair
loss in women
with caffeine or when you're doing
caffeine for a few years or a couple
years or even 10 years and then you get
the hair thinning later for women
and how that's different for men but for
women how you get the hair thinning
because
women's adrenals and i talk about that
with caffeine it's really a powerful
episode talk about different symptoms
too and but when it comes down to the
meditations though
remember that when you do these
meditations they actually work
and because the meditations come from
above okay
they're not man-made and they come from
above so
they have the ability to draw that
poison out of the soul draw that hurt
trust break it
trust breakage betrayal being
backstabbed in life
um you know all kinds of broken promises
losses
hardships struggles emotional
confrontations we've had broken
relationships and friendships the moon
meditation has the ability to help heal
that
it's incredible while the green i'm 4.5
years i'm four and a half years on
celery juice now i've worked up to 48
ounces a day incredible improvement in
anxiety
and ms symptoms while that's incredible
blown away so proud of you
seriously so proud of you
um silk says i am doing one of the
meditations every evening
i love this guided meditations with your
voice thank you so much
my voice is a little raspy this morning
you know and you know here's the thing
you guys
um i guide you through those meditations
so i i hold your hand through those
meditations
and i'm listening the spirit of
compassion when i'm
in that meditation with you guys so you
guys get the most you can get out of
your healing the powerful
level of healing and those meditations
the brain meditation and the moon
meditation
so you want it you want to definitely
check that out and you you want to share
them if you can so
remember medical medium podcast at apple
podcast link is in the description
if you don't have an apple device just
go to medicalmedium.com that's all to
the menu
and look at podcasts and you'll see
um so yeah sandra says okay i'm bracing
myself
sandra brace yourself for the caffeine
episode
okay and yeah it's mind-blowing
judy says good morning good morning so
i'm so proud of you guys for all that
you're doing in your healing process
really proud of you you know and i'm
with you
if you have to use caffeine to get by i
get it i get it if you're involved in
selling caffeine in some way shape form
i got a friend who got a coffee shop i
got a friend who
uh has a coffee business whatever and i
i know what that's like too
i supported all that whatever you got to
do to survive and live but if you're
interested in hearing this episode
learning about what it's doing in our
body learning on how to protect yourself
maybe while we're even drinking it but
it's so important
margie says thank you for telling these
secrets you guys had to
hear this one i'm hoping you listen to
the episode so i'm taking off right now
you guys i love you
stand with you guys stand by your side
100 here
spread the word for me please because
then i know we're healing the world that
we're healing you know
people are able to get this information
so if you can't
share the message so that we can help
heal others and get that information out
there's always been grassroots
medical medium no big pr marketing no
nothing
and and it's spread around the world and
it's healing people around the world
and these these truths are really
powerful too
it's so important to know do a thumbs up
if you can you know like the video
thumbs up the video
leave a review at apple podcast if you
can
all that counts so people know hey
there's great information here taking
off
i'm going to ig if you guys want to come
with me
so i love you god bless you and i'll see
you next time
soon