ugh
we live
you guys I'm kidding around I don't have
a cough but everybody else does
and so I'm gonna tell you right now cold
and flu season is here it's here but you
know what's really cool
cold and flu tool kit right there
download for free medicalmedium.com on
the home page check it out
download this report
it's the cold and flu tool kit I'm going
to make some thyme tea and make some
other things too all that stuff here
I've got to talk about everything you
guys this is incredible the cold and flu
tool kit you can print it out look at
that download this go to medicalme.com
download it it's so easy to use that's
what's incredible about it's easy to
actually use it's easy to work with
that's what's amazing to have this like
this so you go to medicalmedium.com
medicalmedium.com and you download this
and you print it out if you'd like I
like to print things out that's what I
like to do whoa lost it that's okay
I don't have a cough I'm kidding but
everybody else is coughing their asses
off like for real it's no joke be
prepared to keep your immune system
strong through the cold and flu season
so check this out right
yeah lots of coffee Lou Reynolds you
said lots of coughing and sneezing
around
yeah there is there's that much going on
right now so check this out cold and flu
tool kit this thing is incredible easy
to download medicalmedium.com this is
really awesome I got some cool things in
front of me right now I got some great
information so I'm excited to do this
I'm just looking through this I like to
print things out
so I printed out the cold and flu tool
kit right and it has so it's so easy to
use it's awesome check it out whoa time
tea and mortar contain water so there's
some cool things in here too that you
can see so you go to medicalmium.com
when you guys get a chance and print
that out Michael Charles says print it
out that's right cool
I'm excited you guys so I'm here to talk
about cold and flu season a little bit
because it's around now cold and flu is
around 24 7. like it's 24 7.
every month
all year and then year and then year and
then Year all around the planet but
right now okay it's kicking up it's
kicking up big time so this is when it
happens right now and then the holidays
come and everybody's sick everybody's
coughing all of it you know HealthPlus
says it's so great thank you for
creating it you're welcome Liz thank you
for being there in the community doing
all that you do
um yeah so this is it here you can print
it out easy to work with so if you guys
are just coming on here because I'm
talking about cold and flu season and
it's not you know I know I was kidding
around and I was caught I was fake
coughing but it's not a joke I mean I've
seen the flu knock people on their butt
like knock people on their butt I mean
it's not just the phlegm it's not just
the mucus but it's also the cough
involved where they're coughing all
night they're having coughing attacks in
the morning they got the fevers they
don't feel well you got the runny nose
the sniffles your body aches everything
it's all in the above right and
if you're already dealing with something
if you're already compromised in some
way with your health somehow some way
compromised it doesn't make things
easier that's the hard part right there
so what I see out there
as people they're struggling with some
kind of chronic condition or chronic
illness they got all these different
symptoms and then they get whacked with
the flu and then boom you know they're
hit so hard another thing too is a lot
of people have a lot of things inside of
them
they'll have like the Epstein bars
they'll have all these other different
conditions they'll have all these
different bugs and pathogens in them and
I'll have all these other different
things and then the flu comes along and
it just hits you and then you're in it a
lot of people I've seen this and then
you can't come out of it it's too hard
to come out of it's like the flu that
lasts for months long flu and it just
lasts and lasts I talked about this for
years you guys know I've talked about
this for years right so
I don't like cold and flu season I don't
like cold and flu in general because if
it's not the stomach flu then it's
another flu and it's another one so I
don't like it in general because it's
around all the time and it really hits
people but what I wanted to do because I
want to offer as much free information
as possible now check this out you can
go to medicalmium.com there's no pay
wall you don't have to pay for this is
it it isn't a pay scheme that's the
thing like the pay the Ponzi schemes the
pay schemes all that stuff that's out
there that's crazy it's not that it's
free if that's what it is but it wasn't
free to put together that's the whole
point okay it took money to put together
it took medical medium money to put it
together medical medium take money out
of his pockets okay he had to take money
out of his pockets and he had a he has
to have his team working and he has to
pay his team okay a lot of money
and then they helped to put it all
together with me
so I pay to do everything but yeah it's
all free for everybody else that's how
it's done here because I am at your
service is what I am that's your service
of course so anyway
all right you guys let's go let's get
into it we'll talk about can I put my
pockets back in my pants please
I don't think we need to do that
so Kim Miller says Anthony's got the 80s
flare with the popped up collar yes the
pop-up collar is not working good today
one of the colors is over here is not
popped up enough
I've asked just my life anyway so I want
to talk about this because this
information that's really important cold
and flu coming around keep the immune
system strong Diane Eva says ew has a
new hat yes I do indeed I like hats I
like baseball caps it's so easy you
throw it on you don't have to comb your
hair you don't have to do anything and I
have curly hair curly hair does not comb
right so it's a pain in the butt so boom
I throw the hat on and I'm happy and it
takes two seconds
because I'm already busy enough as it is
anyway
I know it's a lazy approach when I do
that but whatever but you guys all right
it's important to keep our immune system
strong during this type of time of year
especially when we're extra stressed
family holidays extra stress everything
involved weather changes all of it so it
is very important so let's talk about
the zinc a little bit I'm gonna take a
little zinc
[Music]
I have a glass to take it but I am going
to try to get a shot glass in a minute
so anyway this is the Imaging products
right you guys know it's I'm going to
tell you right now
hands down there's no company doing what
vimergy does
there's no company out there doing what
the Emoji does
it doesn't exist out there
it's an honor and a privilege to be able
to be in this world right now
while something is created that's
finally really clean it's just it's so
important and um got my shot glass right
there don't throw glasses in the air
whatever you do that was a bad idea so
with a zinc's a great one for the immune
system that's critical I talk about zinc
All Through The Years good zinc
information in the books right all of
that and then you guys know about
um other stuff would sing too of medical
meme information but anyway two proper
folds is what I like right there of the
zinc and I am going to take some now
Sports the immune system which is really
important supports antioxidant
Ellis tasty world says love Emoji so
much amazing so
I'm gonna get some water let me use this
here
we go I got some zinc in here in the
shot glass
so I want to talk to you guys you guys
know I I work with vimrozie now I fully
endorse them and it's because I don't
want this stuff to disappear I get
scared really scared if something's so
good is done so right
and then it disappears or something
happens so like I feel like my job is to
keep things like resources here that
like that are just unbelievable I feel
like that's a big part of my job right
now so if he says is energy going to
have a Black Friday sale yes it's
starting today their Black Friday sale
is starting today so check them out
vimorgy.com these invictor I am is Mary
e r g y
so what I love about the products is
four things I'll give you the four
things really quick they don't have any
hidden things that they're not
disclosing okay
so label requirements allow companies to
hide a certain percentage inside their
supplements a small certain percentage
that you don't know about that's in the
supplements of imagery says no we're not
going to do that it's not going to
happen and that's a big deal all on its
own you can't find that anywhere in my
opinion it does not exist I've asked all
the supplement companies out there that
I could talk to and find I've looked
into so much over the years and it
doesn't happen the other thing is
Bemidji products are third party
independently tested boom I'm telling
you that means so much another thing too
they don't have the natural flavors
they don't have the maltodextrin they
don't have the alcohol they don't have
the vinegar the alcohol is a big one
right now I'm going to tell you right
now
alcohol in supplementation like for
instance the propolis doesn't have the
propylene glycol
the propolis doesn't have the propylene
glycol in it that's critical and even
when there's propolis out there they'll
say oh alcohol free it doesn't work that
way so it's another reason why I love
the Bemidji products because there's no
it's not just about no soy it's not just
about no gluten it's about no vinegar no
caffeine no natural flavors no
artificial flavors no titanium dioxide
no alcohol no citric acid huge one no
maltodextrin huge one it's about all of
that and then it's about not hiding
something in there they're not
disclosing
boom it's incredible when I think about
it and then the quality aspect right so
because you know we're talking about
cold and flu if you guys just got on
here we're talking about cold and flu
support immune system all that's cold
and flu season I'm talking about why I
support memory so Alicia says my family
has dodged the crazy illnesses flying
around my daughter's school I'm so
grateful for zinc shock therapy and
vitamin C shock therapy we're healthier
than we've been in years and I'm gonna
do a little vitamin C shock therapy in a
couple of minutes too that's incredible
and
so the quality aspect see if you take a
bunch of money it's just going to be
straight up and no one talks about this
no one so what you're hearing right now
no one talks about okay if you take a
bunch of money
like a whole ton of money right or
whatever and you want to start your
supplement company
you take a bunch of money
you're gonna go to a manufacturer
somewhere that manufacturer is going to
give you their bottom of the barrel
product
your your ingredients and you're going
to be like well is this quality and
they're like oh yeah it's quality and
you're like okay cool let me just pay
for it and the price point right oh
that's the best one to get sure I'll get
it but it's not the best when no one
talks about is supplement companies by
the lower quality so they can charge
more and then make a bigger profit do
you see how it works
you buy the lower quality ingredient so
you can charge more and make more right
it's all business
and that's what it is the reason why I
endorsed these guys fully wholeheartedly
and I want this stuff to stay around I
want it to be here because it's not
about business it's about people it's
about people
and that's the key and quality really
matters when it's real it makes the
difference
so I'm just I'm gonna say I'm talking
about something people don't talk about
you guys like this is not not allowed to
be talked about out there it's like one
of the secrets so if you start
a supplement company you go to a
manufacturer
and you buy the low quality stuff so you
can make a lot of money right
they don't do that they buy the highest
they can find that's possible the
highest and best quality that they can
find that's possible and they don't care
about the price point the reason why is
because this mom-and-pop company cares
about the person
taking it and that I've never seen
before
I have to talk about it I gotta because
I've never seen it before the energy is
so good for the body and so Milda says
so you guys were talking about cold and
flu I've got the memory supplements in
front of me because that's what I take
to keep my immune system Strong saying
Sue says when I got the Critter last
month on top of bronchitis by the way
I'm sorry that happened to you when I
got the Critter last month on top of
bronchitis and strep throat uh 100
believe the Bemidji supplements saved my
life I know if I would have gotten it
without all the medical medium tools I'd
be dead
it's incredible I'm so glad you're here
truly
and so that's why I'm talking about them
right now because it's what I take to
keep my immune system strong it's what I
recommend my friends and my family if
they have a flu or a cold it's what I
recommend doctors that talk to me all
the time
so incredible Maria says the zinc shock
therapy has worked for me too I love the
zinc shock therapy I just absolutely
love it or Spirit of compassion I mean
who would ever know that that would
exist like who would ever know how what
what a zinc shock therapy like who can
even that just came from above it just
blows my mind
she conscious says zinc shock therapy
works so well
that
my hubby came back from work travel sick
and did not catch it
amazing that's so incredible
see guys I'm talking about the four
reasons why I support the company
and I mean I want to shout it from the
rooftops I want to like scream it from
the rooftops
because it doesn't exist out there and
it's like when you even think about it
it's crazy Allison Sandra says the
pathogen exposure shot vitamin C and
Zinc shock therapy just saved me from
getting sick a few days ago a few
amazing amazing Kim Miller says memories
Angelic that's how I feel
I feel it's Angelic and so what happens
out there so check this out
it's like like if you guys got a second
like this is this is what it this is
what I tell my friends my friends want
to talk to me or something and they want
to hang out with me this is what I tell
them I tell them look if you start a
supplement company
you go to a manufacturer and you get the
ingredients
but everybody who does that they choose
the cheaper a lot of ingredients that
the manufacturer puts all together for
them
so they can make it's about the money
and memory doesn't do that
it's like what the
crazy
so reg lean says my mom used vitamin C
shock and cured her cold sore and sore
throat in a day oh my God that's
incredible
that's just that's so incredible
seriously
see guys so anyway I want to take my
cold and flu and everything but I'm just
running by some cool points that just
blow my mind Alicia says if I spend
dollar dollar on both of them and she
supplements
that last six months and have zero
missed days of work because I'm not
getting sick anymore the investment in
the supplements is a no-brainer I see
people go out and they go into Whole
Foods and they go into all the different
stores
and they spend a lot of money on all
these different like brands of this do
this for your immune system this for
cold flu whatever
and and when you look at what's in there
and you look at it and how it's set
design and everything else
in my opinion it's very gimmicky out
there I want something that's hardcore
real
anyway
you guys all right let's get into it a
little bit oh if you just got here I
just want to run this by you guys for
one more second
this is a free cold and flu tool kit
okay
and it's at medicalmium.com download
this so you have this it's so easy to
use I want things easy for you guys too
you know what I mean and that's a big
deal all on its own and if you look it's
got information in there
so I'm gonna make some stuff
it's got the thyme tea and water
I love that it's so good to have because
you just print it out and put it on your
kitchen table so it's there for you it's
got how to make an Elderberry syrup how
cool is that I can't wait to make that
later
it's got the healing broth in here
Ginger and tea water let's do some
vitamin C right now I want to make
something really cool you guys know this
right
all right so let me get
a little bit of this
warm water
I'm excited
and I wasn't making fun of anybody when
I was coughing my brains out at the
beginning of the show I wasn't at all I
was just saying you don't want to have
to go through that
everybody goes through it it's such a
bummer
out there I'm putting some honey in here
now this product is really
high in antioxidants because it's
vitamin C
all right
I'm going to cut an orange
so what I have right here is the micro C
if you don't know about vimergy V is in
Victor i m e r g y.com
I'm going to put two capsules of micro C
in here
smell
moving the needle that's what I like I
like everything that moves the needle
that's what mm info so I'm making the
medical medium
vitamin C shock therapy is what I'm
making I put two capsules
right there I put a little bit of honey
now let's cut an orange open
now Spirit of compassion created
this vitamin C shock therapy
and there's reasons why
the Orange is in there which is just
amazing now this is the micro C it's
buffered
the problem is with vitamin C's out
there
is they are like straight acid
ascorbic acid
I'm sorry
but I can't tell you how many people
show vitamin C's in my face
and I'm like
no way in hell I don't want to burn a
hole through my stomach I don't want
straight ascorbic acid and I see it all
the time I got friends I got people that
will like contact me and be like
you know I'm on the road this is the
only thing I could find right now and
I'm like yeah and you're gonna burn a
hole right right in your stomach without
a straight ascorbic acid
so what I love about the micro C it's
not it's not that ascorbic acid
right and that's a big deal all on its
own anyway
what I did is just I put a little honey
in here I squeezed some orange in here
got some warm water I put two capsules
of the micro seed in here and I'm mixing
it up
I live by this right here
oh I'm excited
hmm
I just love it
it's so good you guys know about the
continuity test too and I want to talk
more about that
but I've done this with vitamin C's out
there like different vitamin C's and
right you have it in your hand now you
can put it in whatever hand you want to
put it in right I'll put it in my right
hand right now
and put your hand on top of your head
and you make that continuity happen
it goes right from the supplement that's
in your hand
right up to the brain and back down
so and I saw somebody doing it who
posted about it just recently when they
saw me do it right and they did it
and they were describing how they felt
when it's a product that's actually
really pure
and the intentions are pure and that's a
whole other aspect of it so the
continuity test is not just about the
product being pure which with bimbridge
that's that's how incredible they are
right but it's also the intentions that
are in the product it's about the care
it's about the love it's about loving
and caring enough to pick the highest
quality it's about loving and caring
enough not to put garbage in it and it's
about the love and caring enough to make
sure that all that is is there
and so it's the intention too that
continuity test is involved with not
just the quality of the product as well
it's both and that's what you would
really really connect to which is really
exciting
I'm so excited about this if you guys
I'm gonna hang out with you guys right
now a little bit I'm gonna have my micro
C
let's see Missy over here says nope no
cold in over two years thank you aw
you're welcome I have a glass of tea
here what is this huh hmm
that's vitamin C
it tastes divine
why does vitamin C taste that good
is it squeeze of orange is it the Honey
involved here so yummy
um
is it the fact that it's not straight
ascorbic acid yes
hmm
I love knowing that's going inside my
body enter in my body entering now being
delivered
the antioxidants the vitamin C for my
immune system
entering my body entering my cells going
to my immune cells
Hannah says it's so yummy oh my God I am
looking for an immune cell now and I am
looking looking it is right here hold on
you guys
gotta find my immune cell I'm coming
back don't worry I'm back
all right do I have to shout
oh
okay
here's what I do
I told you guys we talked about this one
time right here's what I do
I envision
I'm seeing my white blood cells
I Envision I see them
when you have a product like this
incredible
and that pure and the quality and the
design when you have that type of
product right that type of vitamin C
entering the vitamin C is for the immune
system
okay it's an antioxidant too so
what I do is I envision
seeing my white blood cells and as I'm
relaxing and taking in that vitamin C
and I saw that vitamin C now vitamin C
is entering my body
it's entering my bloodstream I see my
white blood cells going to gobble up and
consume that vitamin C because that's
what I see
and that's a real powerful way to do it
but when you have something so pure and
so incredible in the quality
like democracy which is my favorite
vitamin C in the world before they had a
vitamin C I would have to be like a
prisoner to other vitamin C's I'd have
to do the ascorbic acid I'd have to do
because you you're trying to get a
vitamin C out there how to be a prisoner
and it was like Freedom it was like
freedom
so in beverage you came out through
micro C I was like free I'm free it was
like unbelievable when you think about
it because it's like are you kidding I'm
free from all the garbage vitamin C's
like you guys just freed me like this
mom-and-pop company freed me and that's
what it was and it was unbelievable so
anyway what I do is when I'm sipping the
vitamin C
I'm envisioning the white blood cell
gobbling up that microc
and then getting stronger because it's
feeding off of it
my immune cells are actually eating that
vitamin C up gobbling it up eating that
vitamin C up and that's what I see I see
it I Envision it
I watch it I got my eyes closed and I'm
singing it so that's what I do what I'll
do is I'll have this at night before
going to bed and I'll do that because I
want my immune system be strong while
I'm sleeping and I say go at it white
blood cells get going get moving on it
start eating up all that vitamin C I'll
take another zip
um
and there it goes and I can see it and
that's Envision it that's a powerful
technique a powerful tool all on its own
is actually having that consciousness of
Consciousness your soul your physical
brain all working together
witnessing
that vitamin C going down into your body
then witnessing
it going into your bloodstream
and then validating and witnessing your
white blood cells that are working for
you as your white blood cells gobble up
and feed off of that micro C it's about
validating your white blood cells it's
about validating the work that they're
doing and all that they're doing for you
all that counts
so yes yes the light blast is still
coming up Hey Jude that micro C shock
therapy has worked wonders for us many
times over it's incredible truly is it
really really is
people don't know the history of the
supplements and how bad the quality is
out there for years they just don't know
people don't know the history of the
supplement World they don't know the
history of what's happening out there
like they don't know any of that they
don't know how companies are created
they don't know how it's done they don't
know about the manufacturing facilities
with all their low quality techniques
and low quality products they don't know
about any of that and they're not
supposed to know you're not supposed to
know any of that and so I sit here and
I'm telling you things
you're not supposed to know it's crazy
um health health with Liz
says I do that meditation almost every
night now incredible with your immune
cells with your white blood cells that's
amazing
you guys that's why I'm so excited about
the Vim machine because I use it for
myself my friends my family and I don't
want this stuff to disappear so I fully
endorsed them 100 and yes I want to
support them in any way I can
because when you do things like this
when you create products like this it's
a game changer but it's for real though
real and the quality is unmatched all
right so talk about the propolis first
of all I love all these out here right
I love them all
you know there's something something
about when the micro C goes in you gotta
start laughing I start giggling I start
fooling around more it's really funny
I keep these supplements on hand for my
immune system during cold and flu I
don't want a cold and flu I don't want
to be held back from working I don't
want to be beaten down I run my immune
system drag it so I want to keep feeding
it and keep it strong I want my bone
marrow to produce more really powerful
immune cells I want them to have what
they need and because I burn my like
candle at four ends and I mean it's
amazing what I've done and what I do
and when I think about it and I don't
recommend anybody doing it that way I
don't recommend working seven days a
week year after year after year for
years for decades and then you don't
stop I don't recommend that I think it's
kind of probably not smart but I do it
anyway okay
um okay
I got a news flash for you guys a news
flash I just have to say it I can't help
it I gotta speak my mind it's a news
flash
medical medium information never
ripped down vegans and never ripped down
you know vegans for being vegan meaning
and never ripped down animal protein
eaters
medical medium information is for animal
protein eaters
and vegans
it's for people who don't eat animal
protein and people who eat animal
protein but yet you'll see it every day
someone come out and be like oh I don't
I don't really I only trust some of
medical beams information because you
know he's he says it's all vegan you got
to be vegan when the hell have I ever
said it's all vegan it has to be vegan
and only vegan
the reason why the vegan Community some
of the vegan Community like some of the
big vegan influencers hate medical
medium is because I let people eat
animal protein because I'm not an
ideologue on animal you know against
animal protein
medical medium information actually
gives options for everyone that's the
whole point if you're an animal protein
person I show you how you can use tools
to heal while eating animal protein if
you're a vegan person I show you the
same and vegans don't do it right out
there they don't you can be vegan for 20
years and stay sick
so you can and and still need the tools
you need but I see it every time someone
will do a post and start ripping into
medical medium and his vegan vegan vegan
whatever and meanwhile the vegan doctors
hate medical medium because
I allow people to have protein animal
protein if they like because I support
all and that angers the vegan the vegan
upper echelons it angers them so much
because they're all about you're an evil
person if you even like animal protein
uh you're an evil person about like
that's how they are so they hate medical
meeting because I want people to have
the tools to heal and to know why
they're sick and they can still do
animal protein if they want and vvv and
if they want
John boyntonat says people bring their
own perceptions and Concepts when they
first learn about medical medium
information do they ever do they ever
it is unbelievable
it really is
all right so
back to this back to what we're talking
about that was my news flash
okay and I mean quite honestly you guys
I mean seriously
uh if one more person pops out of the
blue and just says you know I just the
thing is about medical medium
information is
it's it's the one thing out there that
gets just hit all the time like we just
get we get bashed and battered by miss
you know people that don't have it right
they just don't even understand what mm
info is doesn't know about the books
don't never read the books don't know
about the tools it's crazy if you read
brain saver books you'll learn how
people's neurons have trouble
understanding information and I see that
happen too you've got all these people
with all these neuron problems and they
don't really even know what's going on
so they instantly have this emotional
Outburst of
he's just a vegan and that's what he is
he doesn't know any and whatever it's
like okay
um
dude medical medium info I've always
been supportive animal protein people
and vegans are like whatever
it's a bad game out there
um yeah up telephone
is what it is all right so anyway I'm
talking about the propolis
I can't say enough about the propolis
I really can't say enough about it you
see that Liquid Gold
it's unbelievable right
okay
when it's got that active quercetin
inside of it
it's it's from B's screen from like a
certain amount of beekeepers really
incredible on its own
free goes from someone someone's neurons
even if you read brain saver you'll hear
it like you'll hear a story
out there but that story already went
through somebody's kind of like messed
up neurons contaminated neurons and then
went to another person with their
contaminated neurons and went to another
person and The Story Goes Around next
thing you know the story by the end of
it is completely different than what it
was at the beginning
I'm going to put a two dropper folds of
this propolis in here
there's no alcohol in here
the extracted extraction process is like
no other too
like
there's no propolis like this hands down
when you guys try this
this is
like
if someone said look
someone said
I'll give you I'll match the weight of
this with gold with a little bit of gold
say no no keep keep the gold
no way keep the gold I mean that's how
much I love the propolis and what and
and the quality and everything about it
and the thing is here's what's crazy
people don't realize
how good for the immune system propolis
really is they just don't know out there
but it is a must have in my family life
my friend's life my life it is a must
like I shout about it by the way you can
buy all the propolis out there and
compare it to the vimergy and you will
be blown away at the very G propolis
like you can buy all the propolis you
want out there and try to compare it to
the memory propolis and you will be like
oh my God like what is this people are
putting out there like what is this
it's just it's just incredible yeah no
it's Liquid Gold by far so I put two
dropper folds in there
okay
but yeah
it's got the six Active bioactive
polytheanols in there which is amazing
and the vermergy has up to 50 percent
of that which is like what who can say
that and I've been wanting I've been
wanting a propolis to be like the real
thing forever forever I've had to be a
prisoner a slave to crappy propolis for
so many decades like
like the worst kind and coming from the
worst places with the worst extraction
processes and the like the worst hidden
stuff in it and alcohol in it I've had
to been propylene glycol and other
alcohol I've had to be like a slave and
and then it's so hard because you got
Spirit of compassion telling you to be
like you know like a person needs
propolis a person needs this a person
needs that and then but yet I'm telling
Spirit of compassion but I'm a slave
literally to this shittiest propolis to
the crappiest propolis out there to the
whatever and it's been torture for me
you guys hear me crying today because
I'm like crying is that okay okay
because I'm doing a lot of crying right
but it's what my life has been
look a lot of people say oh yeah you
know
that aw
uh I'd love to hang out with him and
talk shop with him you know that would
be amazing you know what you would hear
you would hear me saying this right here
it's like literally I have like gone
through hell and back with the crap out
there you got spiritual compassion
saying they need propolis
the people need that and then me saying
but there's nothing but out there
Spirit of compassion and then he says
can you watch your swears but the point
is
is that that's what it's been like so
when Bemidji decided to change the rules
with propolis because that's what they
did they changed the rules
it's like a Hallelujah moment
it's like an amen moment
when you taste his propolis you'll
instantly know the difference and I'm
going to do the continuity test right
and you know what's incredible you'll
notice with the propolis when you do the
continuity test
remember this isn't Kinesiology
Kinesiology is somebody else's free will
it's somebody else's free will you you
you
submit your own free will your free will
is completely canceled out I'm not
saying anything bad about Kinesiology or
muscle testing I'm not so I don't want
any I got enough people
that hate me for everything for for
telling all the truth for all the truth
bombs I got enough people that freaking
hate me and whatever because of all the
truth bombs
right the apple cider vinegar crowd the
Ayahuasca crowd just everybody hates me
the caffeine crowd whatever just you
know the whole bit right because it's
all about money money money out there
right and so
you know the copper vessel crowd you
know the copper vessel crowd like copper
copper drinking container crap they hate
me because you know you get copper
poisoning from those things but the
point is I got enough I put out all the
truth bombs constantly
and it's just
chill yeah remember she's having a sale
right now
but it's like it's just you know you
constantly put out the information and
you just get bashed for it right that's
what you do you get bashed for it so I'm
not trying to I'm not ripping apart
kinesiologists we have a lot of
Kinesiology people that actually love
medical medium stuff if they're out
there in the community so I'm not
ripping apart Kinesiology or muscle
testing I'm not I'm just saying that
this continuity test Spirit of
compassion taught me is not Kinesiology
because you're using your own free will
you're not submitting your free will
or your soul or anything else for
somebody else's free will to do your
Kinesiology right you're doing your own
there's a big difference right here so
the continuity test is really powerful
your main lining the energy from the
product through your arm to the other
arm into the brain and the brain is
sending it back to your hand
and you're doing with your own free will
and that's the difference when you deal
with the propolis it's like oh my God
anyway
what I really love about the pro now
here's here I just put two dropper full
of propolis in there right if you guys
just came on here I'm talking about a
bunch of stuff cold and flu I'm also
crying the blues
um whatever talking about all kinds of
different stuff anyway
if you just came out here just came out
here right now right
I got the uh vimorgy propolis
which is just an amazing product right
in front of me
and I'm talking about the cold and flu
tool kit right here free
free
broken record anybody everything's for
free with medical media
anyway that's the cold and flu tool kit
go to medicalmium.com download this baby
print it out have it on hand all the
time have it on the coffee table have it
on the kitchen table have it everywhere
have it in your bedroom have it on this
on your nightstand at night grab it and
look through it it's so easy to use and
it's free no pay wall no nothing
just love it but it cost me money to
make and it cost me money to do and it
cost me money to pay my team to help me
with and everything else because I
worked with them on all every bit of it
and it that all costs me money
but yet it's free
so
um Sarah says crazy sale I got 450 worth
of supplements for 300 propolis is on
the way baby if energy.com incredible he
is a Victor i m e r g y.com H2 thank you
aw can't wait to download the cold and
flu flu toolkit now if you hear people
talk about supplements out there
they won't say what I'm I've been saying
they won't it doesn't exist they won't
say it
I'm just telling you
keep that in mind and that's what blows
my like mind
anyway I'm gonna sip a little bit this
we're going to keep on talking about
stuff I'm going to talk about your
immune system again hmm
so that's what I do I've trained myself
or should I say Spirit of compassion has
taught me and then I have
kind of like retrained myself with it
right
every time I sip
the vitamin C shock therapy the medical
medium right
I instantly see my immune cells
you can actually take yourself to the
next level with that
every time I use the propolis every time
I use it
I train myself to connect with my immune
cells and it goes in like that right
as the propolis is going in
I instantly see my immune cells you can
do that
you can wire yourself to connect to your
immune system constantly
and that's what I do so every time I
take a sip
I see my immune cells
and that's what I do
two of my favorite supplements is
support through cold and flu is cat's
claw and Goldenseal
where's my that's my B12 that's my
golden seal right there Goldenseal I
always say speaks for itself
it does not need an intro it does not
need a whole explanation it doesn't need
anything it just needs one word and one
one word only
Goldenseal that's what it needs it
doesn't need any more than that
and that's what I love about Goldenseal
because the plant itself
the plant itself the identity of the
plant if you know herbs
I've been taught about herbs from Spirit
of compassion I spent a lot of time in
the field and just out there in nature
and when I cut you know when you see
Goldenseal
if you ever grown it or anything
it's more of hi Goldenseal my name is
Anthony William
Goldenseal needs nothing else
it just doesn't if anything it's got to
be the opposite
um Goldenseal my name's Anthony
yeah Anthony William the medical medium
yep
and yeah oh you oh oh no I I know all
about you you don't need to explain
anything Goldenseal you don't need to
you know you don't need to explain
yourself one bit no not at all
um me yes uh I've been
um yeah what have I been doing lately
I've been working very hard
anyway
H Jude the 2019 virus protective
protection booklet has saved us
countless times and shared it with many
who needed it
that's incredible
I want to be
a resource I want to be the messenger I
want to be here for you guys I want you
guys to have the information I want you
to have the best products in your life I
want you to have everything
everything I can possibly do so let's
talk about the cat's claw
where is my cat's ball here it is
I'm in the golden sea I'm gonna pop in
here is what I'm gonna do
all right here we are
this is like I'm trying to find
everything here we go I'm gonna put a
little golden seal in here if you guys
don't mind
I am liking this shot
very much I have some zinc in there I
got some golden seal in there I got some
propolis in there now I'm gonna put some
cats call in there
very good cats go up
now I'm not trying to brag or boast or
anything
but cat's claw
is out there
because of the hard work from Spirit of
compassion
uh pushing me to teach about it for over
35 years
so it became something in the
Alternative Health movement
so and I'm not trying to brag or boast
but cat's claw so if you see cat's claw
talked about out there you see cats go
out there you're a welcome you're
welcome you're welcome
he used to be the only
um it used to be the only in dried form
like in dried form and then the cat's
claw that you would find out there in
supplement form I was a slave too if I
wanted it in a supplement form and it
was always low quality always it started
out where it was only in capsules and
then it was in alcohol tinctures with
alcohol like I can't tell you like the
road to get to this point
I I don't even know what to say like in
in cat's Claw is used for Lyme disease
because of medical medium information
but the road with cat's claw has been an
arduous long one okay so it started out
where the only way to get it was just a
bulk dried herb right and it was hard to
get a hold of a long time ago really
hard like I can't even tell you the
process and what it took how to travel
to get it to find inmate connections a
long time ago to actually get it in my
hand right and then to be able to help
people with it okay that's the first and
foremost then that road turned into some
supplement company some low quality
supplement companies out there now
turning it into capsules that was the
next aspect of it right but that was
also a hard Road and that wasn't the
answer and then some bad supplement
companies put it in alcohol tincture so
they put it in an alcohol tincture and
when they did that there was that
arduous Road of trying to get like it's
been torture so to actually have it in
this form right now today in this
quality is just utterly insane when I
think about it so anyway
it's just really special I'm gonna pop
some in there
Brett winter says Goldenseal really
helped me helped me with my acne great
stuff
Goldenseal is very special special
indeed
so I just you know guys I'm going to sip
a little bit of this vitamin C this
micro C right here which I really am
enjoying
mm-hmm and I'm looking through the cold
and flu tool kick too we're going to do
a little bit of that David witchen
is there another medical medium podcast
coming out this year yes there is it's
an interesting one you might want to
listen to it it's going to be cool
there's a lot of good info in there
because it's always original and unique
info in the podcast episodes that no
one's ever heard before and it's just
it's just yeah it's amazing
it's gonna be a great one
medical meme podcast at Apple podcast if
you heard the alien episode
happens
David witchen have you seen the have you
heard or listened to the alien episode
anyway
you guys we're talking about the cold
and flu season so what happens is with
people is when they start getting that
they start getting that scratchy throat
that's one way it hits or they start
feeling they have a golf ball inside
their throat right here or they feel
like they're getting sore throats on the
side or they feel like they got
something like just their chest is heavy
up here and it just starts out and then
you start getting achy but whatever way
they feel it once it starts coming on
it's like no no and that's what people
go through with the cold and flu there's
nothing more annoying than getting that
and it comes in and then it's like I
want to be productive I want to get up
and work in the kitchen but I'm about to
pass out you know I want to go and do
something I want to hop in the car and
you're just you're so sick I just see
people suffer from it it's awful I want
to be helpful in any way I can let's
make some time water
so I got some
water here in front of me
all right it's in this jug
how simple is this
you take your hand
you find some time
nice
you take that time and you pop it in
here
I like simple
simple but powerful
the recipe is in the cold and flu free
toolkit medicalmedium.com download it so
you have it how incredible print it out
is what I recommend
I have time inside this water this water
can go anywhere it can sit here all day
with it in there it can be also in the
refrigerator
when you're using this
you can pour it in
something
right
and then you can add a little bit of
lemon if you really want to you can add
a little bit of lemon or lime a little
bit of honey if you want to you don't
have to have it as plain time water but
I like it plain in here a lot because
that's what I'll do is put in here the
recipes in in the tool kit and then you
have it sitting but that's incredible
all in its own now time is a powerful
tool no question for the immune system
I don't care what anybody says it just
is
you know what's amazing about Spirit of
compassion
right the one piece of Freedom that I've
had throughout this torturous life of
having to do what I have to do right the
curse of hearing Spirit of compassion
since I was age four the one thing
that's really remarkable
is it's information you don't hear
anywhere else but I know here's what the
here's the critics or the not the
critics here's what the haters will do
the haters right so if you say the word
time they'll be like oh that's not
original or unique because he said the
word time he said that well time has
been growing here but when you see
medical meme information on what time
does that's never been said anywhere
else or you see in medical meme
information with celery juices what does
where you can't find anywhere else
that's where it's like the freedom is
everywhere in the mm info the Freedom's
there it's all the original information
that's just freeing people of their
ailments it's amazing I release the info
of these Deca about this decades ago too
and a lot of people steal it so here's
the thing just like the Mercury amalgos
you guys
in the 80s
okay Mercury amalgams were like
being put in everybody without any any
opposition
whatsoever
I would go on like a tour
and go to dental I had a dentist friend
really old guy he was like a 90 year old
dentist he would take me to dentist
conventions
and literally I'd be the only one saying
we can't do the Mercury anymore we can't
do the Mercury anymore
they all just would look at me like are
you insane and these were Advanced
people conventional and alternative it
was like alternative and conventional
people you know it was like the amount
of work to get like the amalgams to stop
going into people's Jaws it took it took
years and years for it to spread and
then teach about it and for it to spread
and teach about it you know I say the
spirit of compassion if I didn't exist
right
and I I wasn't fighting for The Chronic
Leo all these decades going all the way
back what would the landscape look like
it would be unbelievable the difference
would be insane actually
just like what you see happening today I
put something new out brand new
information from the books in the
podcast and the lives and then people
take it and don't cite it back and they
feel like it was out there already
and it wasn't out there already they act
like it was out there already and it
wasn't
anyway
woe is me but at the same time I'm
crying the blues I'm going to sip a
little bit more of this
hurts other people is what it does
because they can't find the information
where it comes from and then they can't
heal that's why the woe is me because
then I my heart hurts for people
time T let's do time T itself
time to use a couple of sprigs of time
you're welcome to do more there's
nothing wrong with that
so I have some time right here I'm gonna
put it in there look at that
okay
I'm going to add the hot water
okay so I have a few sprigs of thyme
there it is the recipe is in the free
toolkit
there you go
and just talking about all this stuff
it's really fun or if you guys just
arrived we're doing the cold and flu
information we're talking about the free
cold and flu tool kit so please download
that off medical medium.com there's no
paywall I feel sorry for the people
taking the info not citing it because
when you leave this short life you do
have to answer somewhere somehow for all
the evil you have done it's like
people think they don't have to answer
it anyway whether it's in their own
conscious mind or subconscious or Soul
when they're leaving here you gotta
answer
if you purposely were doing some nasty
crap to people like purposely like
trying to rob millions of chronically
ill people out of Answers by not citing
back stuff purposely all that stuff it's
just terrible and then ripping down
medical me at the same time you know
what I mean Dr Sherry green Dr Sherry
green is an amazing doctor by the way
I'm honored you're here truly all
threatened by your Advanced information
because rather than embracing it they
just want to be the one exactly instead
of embracing that's Dr Sherry green and
so you're saying instead of embracing
the information of where it comes from
they'd rather be the one steal poach not
cite back other people get hurt by that
and then you got somebody to answer to
or something to answer to you've got to
answer to yourself or whatever when
you're leaving here yeah and I feel bad
all right
so what I do is I have some time T going
here you guys this is fun
just talking about all this we're gonna
add a little Lemon Let's see if we can
throw this lemon in the air
that was a bad throw
I do a little backspin when I throw it
up throw it up in the air it's really
cool I'm gonna add some honey and a
slice of lemon
now I like to squeeze some lemon in
there that's one thing I like to do in
my time tea
okay
I also like to add a slice of lemon too
so if you guys don't mind I'm gonna make
a nice
cool slice here I do like to have a
slice floating around this knife is not
that sharp okay I do like to put a slice
in there you can put it right on the
side but I love that right there I'm
gonna put a little honey in there too
I'm gonna mix it up
so that's my thyme tea
remember
train your mind
right when you sip that time T it
happens for me instantly Spirit of
compassion taught me that the first tip
I take I see my white blood cells
receiving
the power of that time t
this tastes delicious
I love these cold and flu tools
Cindy
I feel so special to have this knowledge
I have a hard time with friends and
family talking about medical medium
that's the burden the community does
hold it's really hard I will tell you
guys like seriously I mean I've talked
about this with Spirit of compassion so
many times I said I just wish the
community didn't have to get so much
pushback when they're talking about
medical medium or anything else
uh
I totally understand Simian read the
rest of your comment I gotta see if I
could find it again
it was really good
anyway so there it is I feel so special
to have this knowledge I have a hard
time with friends and family talking
about medical medium they don't want to
hear it all because of where you get the
information so grateful someone informed
me
and here's the thing
someone informed you right
but in a way that's divine intervention
isn't it is it providential is divine
intervention is it spiritual forces is
it
is it all of the above is it Angelic is
it Angels because Spirit of compassion
always told me that the person who
receives who understands this
information in here whoever receives the
word and and learns from it and and
finds it it's it is spiritual
intervention
from a Divine source
whether an angel had you find it
and it's unbelievable when I think about
that or an angel shows you something and
then you're like what is this
and you know what's crazy yet everyone
out there is so spiritual but yet they
don't want to believe or something that
all this these volumes of of
incredible advanced
a real Advanced information about way
ahead of science and research comes from
a voice I hear
or they'll be like well maybe he's a
genius no I'm not a genius besides
there's Geniuses out there and they
can't even they can't even produce this
it's not possible
so and everybody's so spiritual they're
all going to yoga and they're all
talking spiritual and they're all
sitting around campfires
you know sucking down like
yeah micro dosing mushrooms and sucking
down Ayahuasca and
smoking weed all day and talking about
the universe and everybody's so
spiritual now they're also spiritual
everybody is like everybody now and but
yet what it's hard to believe this or
something
you know you just open up the box and
just see what's in here
really
or are they spiritual
that's the question are they really
spiritual
are they just posers
acting like they're spiritual pretending
they're spiritual or they think they're
spiritual but they're really not
spiritual because they're not even open
open-minded enough to know that this is
like incredible so
are they just posers Spirit of
compassion told me when I was younger
don't don't don't act spiritual I was
like I'm not
sure the company I said don't act
spiritual
don't just go around every second you
know with like a robe on and just be
because you hear it can happen because
you hear you hear me Spirit of
compassion said and because you hear a
voice and you have this information it's
easy to fall into that Spirit of
compassion said don't don't don't act
like a spiritual Guru
don't I mean there's nothing wrong with
praying hands there's nothing wrong with
anything but it's very compassion said
don't like
act like you walk on water or anything
like that I said I don't I just throw my
sloppy clothes on and I'm ready to just
deliver just give me the information so
I can deliver just
I need to get that information out there
and I mean and you know and I pray and
and all of that and I do the medical
media meditations and I pray and
everything but I don't mean by that I
mean by you know what I'm talking about
so anyway olive leaf right there is one
of my favorites but once again it's like
the same old story
being a prisoner to the bad Olive Leafs
out there to the ones in alcohol and the
ones in real bad you know glycerin the
bad bad stuff or be all of that like
just being you know but not just that
hidden ingredients is what I'm saying
like the hidden ingredients out there
like being
a slave to bad Olive leaves that was
something that was really hard so I love
that for the immune system too they all
if I'm gonna put that in here
so
you guys this has been incredible
I don't even know what to say besides
that I'm excited we're in the medical
mediums kitchen we're having fun
we're doing some cold and flu protocols
information
cold and flu toolkit download
medicalme.com it's free
you can get your information in here
it's to take care of yourself during
cold and flu season
I mean that's incredible honestly I'm
hearing it all the time people are just
coming down with colds and flus they're
sick they got the sore throats they got
the fevers they're coughing they got the
mucus so it's like we're in that time of
year even though golden flu like I said
is just worldwide all year but it's
heightened right now at this time of
year people are stressed out their
immune systems are already being
battered and then boom they end up with
the cold or a flu or anything like that
so yeah you guys incredible I will see
you guys again thank you for your time
and energy check out medical meme
podcasts at Apple podcast
and look out for imposter's tubes that's
something I want you guys to keep a
lookout at Medical medium.com you can
report an imposter so keep that in mind
so if you go to medicalme.com I'm
enhancing the website it's all free of
course there's no pay walls there's
information on there but you can go to
medicalbeam.com and you can find that
little spot where you can report an
imposter someone that says through
medical medium or they're Anthony
William the medical medium and they
offer consultations or whatever it is
that they do so make sure you have that
opportunity to actually report them
which is incredible if you can leave
reviews on amazon.com that would be
amazing remember the books are 40 off
amazon.com right now these two
incredible books get them free at the
library if you can't afford the 26
dollars
but these books are absolutely
incredible so check these out when you
get a chance leave reviews if you'd like
to and there's a light blast
announcement coming soon
but the only thing is you got to get on
my newsletter so you can find out when
the light blast is gonna happen so you
have to be on my newsletter so you can
find out when that light blast happens
and the light blast needs to be live
replays don't work
their replays are meditative to listen
to
and they're healing in other ways but
the replay is not the live light blast
in the moment where Spirit of compassion
is sending down the light in that moment
in real time live
anyway you guys
I love you greatly and I'll see you soon