it's a seven day Journey
that is going to be so profound and so
powerful it's going to blow your mind
it's going to move you forward
you're not going to experience anything
like this
it's a seven day Journey I'm going to
guide you personally through
this is the summer of healing
this is a summer of healing emotionally
mentally spiritually
I'm very happy to announce
that today's registration and you can
sign up to the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
so make sure you do that if you get a
chance and I want to run a few things by
you in a minute
so this is oh you're excited everybody's
excited incredible so you're signed up
amazing
so Stones admit frequencies
and so do we
Stones can receive frequencies so can we
we are made up of minerals but every
single
living
creature
living vegetation
on this planet living body of water is
made up of minerals
stones are made up of minerals
every single living life form in this
solar system
and Beyond in the galaxy and other
galaxies and other solar systems in
other galaxies and
anywhere else in the universe
is made up of minerals
mineral precious mineral compositions
so all life
everywhere
if you're someone that doesn't believe
there's life beyond our planet then just
all life here on this planet
if you're somebody that doesn't believe
there's life in another solar system
in another galaxy somewhere else in the
universe that's fine then all life here
in this solar system
so I want to invite you guys to sign up
to the collecting Stones meditation
Journey because it is going to be
profoundly
healing
and I can't wait for you to experience
it so let's talk about it a little bit
each day you're gonna get
some videos
and
what we're going to do is it starts on
the 19th so first of all let's just get
organized on that level today's
registration today's the 12th
the 19th
is when it starts
now if you're familiar with the
collecting Stone's meditation out here
in in medical medium New Edition if
you're familiar with this or you've done
this before through the book okay we've
never done this before though we've
never done one where I'm guiding you
through a seven day
Journey with this but if you're somebody
that's done this before
collect your stones on the day it starts
if you can if you can't collect your
stones on the day it starts
so I got three stones right here
I'm using these Stones as examples right
so if you haven't collected your Stones
yet
wait until the 19th the first day of the
seven day collecting Stone's meditation
Journey now for some reason if you're
not going to be able to do it that day
if you're not going to be somewhere
where there's Stones if you're not going
to be able to find any stones for some
reason maybe you're traveling maybe
you're doing something then collect your
Stones before
the 19th
so collect them at an earlier time frame
if it's the only chance you have and the
only way you can actually do this
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
so it's going to be really exciting so
you might probably but here's the thing
here's what I recommend go and scope out
a spot
maybe have an idea of where you're going
to collect your stones
maybe it's going to be some grassy
Knolls somewhere maybe it's going to be
some field maybe it's going to be some
trail maybe it's going to be a park
maybe it's going to be a beach wherever
it is
kind of get that in a place mentally
emotionally where am I going to get my
Stones where am I going to go and you
can make that plan is it going to be in
your yard is it going to be around your
apartment building is it going to be
around your house is it going to be
around a friend's house someone said
Trails I saw that
so if you had trouble signing up through
the link earlier we sent out a new link
via email and you can sign up to that
link in the description of this live or
the profile
so if you had a harder time signing up
earlier and it was difficult because I
saw some people had a difficult time
signing up
then try to sign up now we have a
different link we're using
a different
way of doing it so
let's go into it a little bit
so what is the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
I was saying before stones have an
ability
to absorb
but that ability is not tapped into
totally
walking by stones
having a stone in your hand for a minute
throwing a stone into a lake or into a
river stream and you're just kind of
skipping Stones right
skipping rocks
there's only a moment in time
where there's a connection happening
so if you go to a beach and you want to
skip some stones
on a body of water
there's only that second where you pick
the stone up
and you're like I'm gonna just skip the
stone here right and you do that
the connection is small
it's quick
there's a big difference though when
you're doing the collecting Stones
meditation because
when you're doing it that way
something incredible happens
and a deeper connection starts to occur
and when that deeper connection starts
to occur something else starts to happen
too
so there's a
phrase where you say well you become one
with something
you become connected with something
well when you're doing the collecting
Stones meditation Journey starting on
the 19th you got to sign up for it to
get the videos by the way it's free
but you guys already know that because
that's all I do is free stuff
but what happens is when you start that
Journey on the 19th
something's going to happen
a deep deep rooted connection is going
to occur with you and your stones that
you choose
put my Stones right there
and that deep connection is gonna allow
a transference process to happen
sounds incredible
yeah because it is incredible
incredibly incredible
if I dare say
because what's going to happen is this
transference is going to occur where
something inside of you is going to
frequency out of you
it's going to travel on a frequency
holding information
that's going to absorb into your stones
now if you're somebody that loves
crystals I don't recommend taking your
favorite crystals and using it it's not
going to work I'm not saying your
favorite crystals don't have powers or
frequencies that's not it at all
this is different
entirely different
because your favorite crystals have
already been in your home they've been
in your apartment
they were also
crafted
by man
Crystal collectors
that machine them make them look
beautiful
turn them into certain shapes cut them
in certain shapes
the stones you're going to find are
stones that are naturally in the
environment wherever they lay wherever
they lie
however they are
and these Stones don't know you
so if you have like crystals you really
like you're like well I'll just use my
crystals I'll go to my crystal
collection
do not do that it won't do the same
thing when you do the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
you're going to be getting
stones that are out in the wild
that could even mean a grassy edge of a
parking lot
but in the wild
not stones that have been sitting in
your dresser
in your house
up against your windows
for years
those are special those need to stay in
your home they're in your home they need
to stay in your life the way you like
them to but this is different
because the stones you're going to seek
out
come the 19th after you signed up
hopefully you signed up now and today to
the collecting Stone's meditation
Journey
those stones
are going to be meant
for you
for this reason
for this profound way to transmit
something out of you
to frequency something out of you
to absorb and draw something out of you
that shouldn't be there anymore
that's how profound and that's how
incredible
this journey is going to be
because what we do is we Harbor toxic
baggage from wounds that have been
sitting inside of us for a very long
time inside of our soul
side of our heart inside of our spirit
however you want to see it
sign up to the collecting Stones
meditation Journey so you can get your
instructions
Iona says I live in the city and there
are barely any Stones kicking about
if you are in a place where you're not
going to be able to get Stones you can't
find them in a park
in the city you live in
you can't find them on the edge of a
sidewalk
in a park
we can't find them on the edge of a
sidewalk
in a grassy little section in the city
if you can't find
stones
and you don't know somebody else that
may have stones in their area or you
don't have a friend or anything
of sorts
then that's when I would probably resort
to purchasing
some Stones if you can't before it
starts
maybe there's a website where you can
purchase a few stones and you can choose
the stones you want to use for this
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
so that that would be if you have no
other way to do this
why does this work because those stones
don't know you
they don't know you
and your connection to those stones are
going to be brand new
but it's only if for some reason you
can't get anywhere to find some Stones
anywhere anyhow wherever you can't find
them Parks Trails beaches Lakes grassy
Knolls sidewalks near grass Parks again
wherever
Hannity says Stones here are all
clusters of shells and sand will that
work
if it if it isn't just a clump of sand
that falls apart once you squeeze it
then it'll work
so if it's a stone that like it's made
out of shells and sand but really
really hardened
Chrissy says how many do we need
probably need a bucket you do not need a
bucket what you see right there is three
stones
on the medical medium New Edition
if you don't have the medical mean new
edition you should get it
so make sure you get the medical meme
New Edition the collecting Stones
meditation is inside this book
but the collecting Stones meditation
Journey
is going to be a series of videos
that you're going to receive it's a
seven day
Journey I'm guiding you through but you
should have the medical medium New
Edition where the collecting Stones
meditation originates from
and you can see in there it's three
stones
and I have three zones in my hand right
now
we walk around with old hurt inside of
us
from many many years ago in our lives
from betrayal broken trust
not being validated not being heard
being misunderstood being hurt by people
that we love people we don't love
relationships relationship breakups
work relationships
and that's just one Avenue of how we get
hurt on this planet
if anyone ever says I will never get
hurt I've never been hurt I've never had
a single upset from birth to whenever
then they're not being truthful every
single person
feels hurt
and gets a wound one way or another
do we need to collect new Stones if we
already have them yes you do
you have to collect new stones for this
journey
if you already have stones and you got
them sitting in your house they've been
there for years or they've been there
for months they're on the windowsill
they're on your desk
they're on
your nightstand or wherever you keep
stones or crystals or so forth
you need
three new stones for this collecting
Stone meditation Journey
if you can't collect them on the 19th on
the first day of the collecting Stone
meditation Journey
then collect them before that
and then get ready for that Journey
that's coming
link is in the description link is in
the profile
sign up hit the link
it's working better now it was a little
sticky this morning I heard a lot of
people could not get on
Trixie says zoom out after clicking the
link and you will see the pop-up
registration box thank you Trixie over
there on YouTube
really appreciate it
so I'm going to tell you something you
guys
this is going to be a ride
something you've never experienced in
your life
I'm giving you kind of like a
forewarning
disclaimer whatever you call it
but it may seem like oh it can't be
anything that great
but when you're doing this journey
you're gonna feel it
a deep connection is going to grow
an unbelievably deep connection
is going to grow
is something miraculous is going to
occur
with this collecting Stone's meditation
Journey
I'm preparing you now which is
a little talk
saying hi to let you guys know
that this is going to be a profound
experience
I have a smile on my face for a reason
because when you do this journey
it's going to be extremely emotional but
extremely emotional
in an incredible way
life-changing way
extremely emotional
in a good way
in a way that clears
the Slate
I can't tell you how excited I am for
anyone
and all of you that are partaking in
this
and by the way it's not three thousand
dollars it's not two thousand dollars
it's not anything
it's free
and it starts on the 19th
so I'm happy to announce that today's
registration day if you guys are coming
on right now
don't miss out
on the medical medium
collecting Stone's meditation Journey
the link is in the description link is
in the profile
sign up
and start to think about where you're
going to get your stones
where are they
where are these Stones going to be
where can they be
are they in the park are they on a trail
are they at the beach are they just in
the yard are they on a grassy sidewalk
where are these Stones now here's
another thing too the size of the Stone
doesn't matter in the sense that there
has to be a rule where the stone has to
be a certain length or a certain size
your stone can be any size you choose
there's going to be three stones
that are chosen
now as you're choosing Stones you'll see
on the 19th
some tips as far as choosing them
but size of the stones
determines on how comfortable you are
obviously you probably don't want to
choose a stone that's like this big
super heavy
super cumbersome
but if for some reason that's the stones
you choose because that's what you want
then I understand
as you see here there's an example
there's three stones in my hand right
now
and wait until Monday
July 19th to choose your Stones unless
you have no ability to choose your
stones on July 19th
and you need to choose them a little bit
earlier it's Wednesday not Monday
some so Wednesday July 19th
choose your Stones then unless you have
no ability to choose your stones
that day on any level and you want to
choose them earlier
so Stones can be of any size they can be
this big they can be that big they can
be this big they can be smaller than
this
if for some reason all you can find what
looks like is little Pebbles and that's
what you can find out there
in nature or wherever you are then
that's what you choose
and stones are going to resonate to you
when you see them
and you're going to have a knowing but
I'm really excited about this link is in
the description the link is in the
profile
and get ready for this this is going to
be an experience you will never forget
when you go through the seven day
collecting Stones meditation Journey
and we all finish as a community
together
you will never
ever forget
what happened
with this journey how you felt what
occurred and you will never forget this
journey
that's how powerful it is
anyway
all right
just wanted to let you guys know it
might pop up again at some point just to
remind everybody just to let people know
they should sign up as soon as they can
registration was today sign up link is
in the profile link is in the
description
if you signed up and you didn't get the
confirmation email check your spam check
other promotions folders also make sure
you entered your email address correctly
because you can lose an opportunity I
don't want you to lose the opportunity
so make sure you check your spam your
promotions folders
very important because it could go
through right into spam also check on
your desktop because sometimes the
mobile apps don't work good with the
emails and you want to check your
desktop
I can't wait
I've been excited about this for weeks
and weeks
you will know and you will see and you
will feel it when you do the seven day
Journey
foreign
match your service I'll be guiding you
through the process anyway all right I
love you guys make sure you sign up when
you can manarnica says could someone
else bring us the stones that bedridden
yes
if you're bedridden if you're in a
difficult situation if you're struggling
in some way can't get your stone someone
can go and get stones and bring them to
you definitely
I love you guys
God bless you
I'll see you soon