do you struggle with mental health
issues do you battle difficult emotions
and thoughts
have you been let down betrayed suffer
from loss
or you just have a hard time getting
through each day and not sure really why
if this is you then you're not going to
want to miss the collecting Stones
meditation Journey
everyone is soul-searching even if we
don't know it even if we don't call it
that it's what we're doing
we Soul search because part of us feels
lost or we don't feel whole or because
we feel like we're not living up to our
souls potential
we Soul search after a heartbreak after
a loss or disappointment we Soul search
when we fall ill with symptoms that
won't go away we Soul search because of
life's hardships we turn to soul
searching when we can't find answers it
is a way to heal and Elevate our souls
and to strengthen our purpose in life
soul wounds can act as triggers opening
up a crack and allowing for
susceptibilities to seep into our bodies
I'm Anthony William author of the
medical medium book series and over 35
years of experience of helping people
overcome chronic illness and mental
health struggles
I'm going to invite you on a special
Journey with me a journey that will help
you heal a hurting Soul a journey that
will cleanse you of challenging emotions
and emotional wounds it's called the
collecting Stones meditation Journey it
doesn't require a great deal of physical
strength it doesn't require any money it
doesn't even require a great deal of
time all it requires is three simple
Stones just like these
this experience is unlike anything you
have felt before it's going to blow your
mind
going to help your soul heart and spirit
heal which supports your physical
well-being too so get ready you're about
to learn secrets to revive your soul
heart and spirit and find peace and feel
whole again join me on the collecting
Stones meditation Journey now