and then never been right since you know
dizziness balance issues even like
ringing in the ears ttis have you ever
bumped your head really hard getting
into your car boom or getting out of
your car boom or cleaning your car and
you're get the back of your head even if
it's a small hit right or say in the
kitchen somewhere or you slip boom bang
the back of your head or something just
happens where something whaps you in the
head who knows what it is that just
something waps you in the head right how
many people have had concussions mild
concussions super uber Uber Uber mild
concussions where they're so mild they
don't even know it and then it lingers
and lingers and lingers and lingers and
lingers we're talking about headbanging
that's right we're doing that today why
because there's a crap ton of people
walking into walls bumping their heads
everywhere and for years I've always
gotten calls like I just bang my head
really hard do I need to go to the
hospital I just bang my head really hard
I'm scared I can't fall asleep at night
if I fall asleep I'll never wake up I'll
die I bang my head so hard I got an egg
on there it's like a pounding egg on
there what do I do oh my child banged
their head my my daughter slipped on the
floor banged her head my son banged his
head on the table like I've heard it all
forever for years and years and years so
what are we talking about headbanging
we're talking about concussions too like
what about the concussion you get into a
car accident and then you are struggling
and suffering with like chronic illness
for the rest of your life when you were
fine like you were fine now you're
diagnosed with fibromyalgia you're
diagnosed with this and then you're
diagnosed with lime and then you're
diagnosed with that and then you're
diagn it's just crazy how it works and
then there's so much more to it than
just this as well there's a lot more but
so many people
struggle and they struggle what H they
struggle when they go through some kind
of Crisis what about sports injuries
that's another thing well I was playing
High School football and gotten to a
concussion issue boom and it was just
lingering and lingering there's a lot of
people who have struggled so many times
and then we're going to talk about like
good things for it good things for it
you Bang Your Head okay you're somebody
like I'm not going to get a concussion
don't say that don't say that might be
somebody that's like I don't remember
the last time I banged my head but
people do and they do it all the time
another thing we're talking about is
white lung white lung again a little bit
right
pneumonia I'm trying to l everybody know
that is coming to town and it's a
it's a wave where everybody in the
family is going to be coughing their
guts out I've been trying to tell you
the media is keeping it quiet under WPS
right cuz right now what's happening
there's the flu that's going around SE
is going around too right so that's
going around right now already so people
already caught their so-called colds
they already caught their so-called flu
depending on what was happening maybe it
was C maybe it was flu maybe it was C
maybe it was flu maybe they got tested
and it didn't come up a c but then it
did later like whatever's going on the
point I'm trying to say is on top of all
the so-called colds flu RSV right and
all of that right now white lungs coming
into the town on top of it and it's
going to be
like right over all that stuff that's
what it's going to do so that means you
know people I I got over my flu I got
over the cold I had two weeks ago that
wasn't the white lung pneumonia going
around that is coming to
town it is anyway I'm letting people
know so just a a friendly
reminder do you have your zinc friendly
reminder do you have your golden seal
friendly reminder do you have your stuff
do you have your vitamin C do you have
that it's a reminder too what do you
have do you have your stuff I'm just
saying there's a golden seal right there
are you ready are you ready so that's
important to know that's the vimergy
stuff right you guys know I work with
them so anyway so much to talk about
it's crazy what do you think
about ketam ketamine and mushrooms for a
concussion so let's talk about
concussions a little bit what happens
while I got this pan on oh by the way
wait wait what we get
there making this one right here you
guys right it's not really a holiday
it's not really a holiday it's just what
I wanted to eat today so I selfish am I
possibly really selfish cuz I wanted to
eat this here today and didn't make a
holiday meal for
everybody well is it the holidays quite
yet yeah it is but yes I'm actually
making this what is this curried potato
pee and cilantro hash and it's delicious
I've made it before but I was in the
mood for it I got the pan on so I got
everything okay let let me introduce you
here potatoes steamed potatoes look at
these incredible potatoes right onion
garlic Cayenne from the garden I grow so
many Cayenne I got some steamed peas
right here if you can see that right
there you guys you see that steam Peas I
also have some frozen peas that are not
steamed yet I might throw those in the
pan and get this kind of toasty and use
those
instead Tomatoes red bell peppers I got
these some red bell peppers and I got
some lemons right there and I got
different spices I got maple syrup I got
some tomato paste we're going to use for
this recipe
cilantro arugula making a green salad
with French
dressing we wee all right I think I
pretty much covered it let's talk about
headbanging stuff right let's get the
old board out for a second I don't know
maybe we can have fun with this yes we
might yes we we can let me draw
somebody's head right there okay let's
do that someone's not going to be happy
though if they bang their head really
hard I can tell you
that and I'm
also
going to get Samantha's head model out
that's Samantha's head model and she
will be coming someday just things have
been crazy she said she's been so busy
talking about protein and helping people
about with their protein needs that she
said that she could not come yet um but
anyway the point is is we're going into
little bit of the head stuff why not
where have you banged your head right
was it the front really bad so we're
going to go into sharp objects so you
bang into something really sharp right
like something sharp like the corner of
a table versus something that's not
sharp and your head hits it really hard
and your whole head shakes so we're
going to go into those details too okay
so that'll be good
so
anyway let's get that up there
ready so I want to talk about this topic
because I think it's
under understood it's under understood
it's misunderstood it's not talked about
nobody really cares about it there a lot
of tortured people though chronically
suffering because they banged her head
lots of them out there life was never
the same anymore and then no one knew
why how come it happened and what's
going on and they went and got a bunch
of MRIs and a whole bunch of different
CAT scans and they're taking you know
getting scans of their brain and they're
looking for that hollowed out section in
the middle of the brain is what they're
looking for maybe you have that disease
where you're missing the middle of your
brain and it's starting to hollow out
and people are looking for that they're
looking for a gap in their brain because
so when people have headaches and
problems and injuries the doctor might
say well you know you had those old
sports injuries you had all those
problems you had that car accident so
maybe you've got that missing piece of
brain that develops right where it
atrophies is in the center of the brain
and so forth right above the brain stem
so um but let's go into it some Basics
first besides like heavy concussions
injuries and so forth let's go into
Basics right you bend your head on
something sharp something that has a
point to it right so something that's
Jagged hits your head okay and it hurts
maybe a piece of metal sticking out of
some porch on your house and you're not
you you're in the area and you just
banged your head on it maybe you banged
your head on something else but either
way the injury happens and it's the
frontal lobe area right you bang your
head here it's a sharp
object
okay first thing that happens here is
you don't have to bend your head that
hard to get this type of injury but when
you get this type of injury it's a
pinpoint injury it's where it's a direct
pinpoint now I don't like those you can
get a you can get a hematoma from those
you can get problems with those but what
happens here is if you don't ice this
fast if you don't get the ice out quick
right this can be become a problem this
can turn into a storm for so many
different people so you have to know
what to do when you do when you actually
bang your head and it's a sharp object
so with this kind of bump on your head
you'll get an egg that egg will start to
occur that's the body's defense
mechanism right there where the body's
like the body's actually reacting that's
the reaction that's reaction you get to
actually protect your brain so the egg
the bump on the SK skull that starts to
occur is a mechanism to protect your
brain that's what that's for it's like a
sealant it's trying to seal the
potential fracture or hole in your skull
but that doesn't happen with 99% or 98%
or whatever 90% of people just banging
their head they're not going to get a
fracture in that moment they're not
going to get a hole in their skull but
there's this defense mechanism our body
has
where it it this inflammation occurs
instantly around the bone around the
skull and right right inside so then you
get this egg that egg is to
seal it's to
seal any kind of imped Ms anything
that's been opened any kind of access or
open ways right but yeah even though you
get an egg when nothing happened
terribly and you get that sharp egg on
your head when nothing went terribly
wrong your body still gets that egg it
still gets that crazy
inflammatory development where boom it
rises really quick and it starts to
pound and then you feel it it's sharp as
heck and you feel that pain radiating
around it right but it's sharp and it
was a small hit so something like you
know something sticking out of a wall or
something and you walk by and you Peg
yourself and you're like wow that really
hurt and then you're kind of like oh my
God and you're feeling that little spot
it's critical to get ice on that spot
quick so you don't want to be like well
you know what I'll deal with this later
I'll just rub it for a second and I'll
deal with this later you want to deal
with it in the moment you want to get
cold compress you want to get some ice
in a bag you want something like that
and you want to press it on the spot but
keep in mind there this is really
important to know I mean maybe you don't
care about this information but I think
it's really important you don't want to
ice your whole head around the spot when
it's like a pinpoint hit where you hook
it into something sharp something
meaning something pointy the corner of a
counter okay maybe the hood of your car
like some pointy thing sticking out of
the hood of your car whatever it is you
don't want to just ice the entire area
you want to pinpoint that ice on the
spot that's what you want to do and
that's very important so here's the next
part too if you hit your head here on
this side say your right side on that
spot there you want to ice the front
right here okay and you want to pinpoint
the ice right on top of it and you want
to do that for whatever 5 10 minutes you
can back off the ice you can put it back
on you can back off the ice you can put
it back back on by the way call your
doctor go to the hospital whatever
anybody needs of course but I'm just
saying that this is stuff I would do if
I happen to me or my family and so forth
but you you put the ice on the spot you
back the ice off you put it back on it's
going to hurt you back it off you do
this put it on for another minute or two
3 four minutes right directly on here it
could be a cloth wrapped around the ice
could be just a cloth and then you back
it off okay what you're doing here is
you're applying cold super cold for
moments and then backing off the cold
for for a moment when you back off the
cold you give your body a chance to
recalibrate and heal so you give this
area a chance to actually heal faster
then you put the ice back on and you
give it a few minutes and if you can't
stand it anymore and it hurts you back
the ice off right and you do this where
you you on and off you take the ice off
you put the ice on that little
pinpointed egg that egg spot what
happens is it's this intermittent icing
that allows the body to respond
different differently it takes the body
out of crisis mode and puts it more into
healing mode so that's important to know
so say you get a bigger bump you bump
the front of your head and it's a bigger
bump okay so I'm going to do a little
bit of a bigger bump if you guys don't
mind I hope this is interesting I find
it quite
interesting um
okay so what you have right there sure I
got that ink on my cutting board so I
can eat it later so what you have right
here is a larger bump it's not so much
as a pinpoint it's a little bigger of a
bump it's a little bigger of a hit the
egg is bigger the egg is
bigger this kind of bump you want to do
similar you want to get ice onto it
immediately you don't want to let this
sit you don't want the inflammation
to get out of control you don't want it
just taking over you want to get that
cold compress on here quick very
important to know get the cold compress
on there quick and when it's a bigger
bump and it's a bigger egg okay you do
the same thing you hold the compress on
there you back off after a few minutes
or even five minutes if it if it feels
good enough right you can do this thing
where you're intermittent you're on
you're off you're on you're off but the
difference is with this bump here being
that it's a larger egg and you feel it's
a larger egg and it feels like you're
feeling pain in other areas you want to
put an ice pack you want to take your
ice pack off of that bump and then you
want to put the ice pack on the back of
your head you want to put it on the back
of your head where that side of the bump
is so here's the bump right here okay
that's your bigger bump right there all
right now you want to put the ice pad
back on the back of the head just like
this you see this there's the bump right
here it's a good size egg it's larger
than this little pinpoint
bump and then but you want to get the
cold pack on the back of the head you
want to do that for a couple of minutes
that's not where the bump is no it's not
what this does is this actually slows
down the body's mechanism of Crisis
State because you got a bigger egg
bigger bump it's a bigger problem and so
you want to get cold compress on the
back of your
head instead for a moment and then when
you do that for a couple of minutes you
switch back up and you get the bump
right here what this does is it calms
the body
down so that you don't have a storm
going on because when we bang our head
heads weird stuff happens blood vessels
start to pop and break we get
bleeders we get
hematomas we get blood clots we get
blood pooling so blood pulling where it
pulls in
Eddies okay different things happen when
we bang our head and so what you're
doing is this bigger hit right here
means most likely your head moved your
brain moved apologize your brain moved
this one here this pinpoint one sharp
object I mean not razor sharp where
you'd be bleeding everywhere and you
need stitches you got to go to the
hospital and get stitched up right but
this sharp one right here this pinpoint
one where oh it's an egg and it hurts
and you feel it chances are that your
brain didn't
SLO you didn't have any slashing effects
with your brain I'm going to go into
that in a little bit too okay this one
here is a bigger egg you bend your head
you might have even seen a star R2 or
some type of maybe like some weird
squiggly things going across when you
hit maybe you you saw something when you
hit maybe you just saw black when you
hit but either way this bigger bump
right here you want to ice the front
with the C pack you know comfortably
comfortably I mean if it's killing you
or it's too cold you know back off and
you can go back and forth but with this
one you want to get the cold compress on
the other side after a few minutes so
here you are you're applying your ice
pack right here you're putting it on the
spot and then after a few minutes or 3
to five minutes you flip
it and you put it in the same
hemisphere
same hemisphere but on the
back that's what you do you don't put it
on the other
Hemisphere and then the back of it you
put the same hemisphere as the big bump
went there's the big bump okay see the
midline canal right right hemisphere
left hemisphere you see the midline
midline
canal well what you want to do is you
want to make
sure you get the right hemisphere so on
this bump you got to get the cold p on
the other side what this can do is
literally halt
hematomas blood vessel
breakage weird blood
clots
contusions it can halt those bring those
down okay because your head your brain
moved a little bit probably on the
bigger bump your brain moved a little
bit and if your brain moves a little
bit you want to get the cold pack on the
back right there now let's do another
hit now you just freaking hit your head
now you boom you hit it you're walking
on a sidewalk you trip you got your
sandals on you stub your toe you get
caught on something and you go down and
you bang your forehead really hard on a
metal bicycle on a park bench on a
whatever some front door on the cement
on the
curb on a car you bang the crap out of
the front of your head where you just
boom in this
situation you may not get an egg you may
not get a bump you may not get this huge
bump or egg on your head you might get a
little one but the hit was much harder
than what the bump shows keep that in
mind you're a hit really hard but you
don't have an egg you don't have really
a bump but you're hit hard frontal lobe
you hit it boom really
hard so in this
situation obviously you know you call
your doctor and so forth see what your
doctor wants to do but in this situation
what I would do okay is I would get ice
pack right on the frontal lobe right on
the front and I would do a couple of
different things I would ice the front
of my head where it hit okay but when
you hit your brain slashed
forward so your brain went forward is
what it did it went that way so you went
like this boom
and your brain then went boom it's kind
of like an elevator the elevator's going
down you're on an elevator and the cord
was cut or the elevator broke and you're
going down in that elevator the elevator
hits and then you
go right same thing you're walking along
you trip
boom your head hits something and your
brain slashes
forward and when that happens you will
have to first and foremost you have to
ice the front for a little bit but now
you got to do the back of the head you
have to ice the back of the head so
that's the next thing so you got to
definitely ice behind Okay the back of
the head not just the front of the head
the reason why is because your brain
shook from its cage connective tissue
the spider web of nerves and connected
tissue between the skull and the Brain
okay your brain moved away from the back
of your
skull and was
shooken it was
shaken and because of that inflammation
is going to start occurring in the back
of the brain if you don't do the quick
icing on the back of the brain and you
only ice the front of the brain the
frontal lobe in that situation it's not
going to be enough to protect you to
give you a fighting chance so your
concussion is
less so your concussion is less so you
don't have all the after effects you're
not
suffering so you have to do a front cold
pack then you got to go around the back
leave the front alone and you got to do
the back yeah you didn't hit the back of
your head you didn't hit the back there
no you didn't do that see but you still
got to get the cold pack on the back of
the head because that brain of yours
left that
area and It Slam into the front of your
skull and the back now is going to get
in inflamed and
swollen kind of similar to a car
accident car accident you ban your head
on the steering wheel some people an
airbag can literally give them a
concussion not some people half the
people out there that get into car
accidents the airbag itself gives them a
concussion so it's like oh I got my
airbags I'll be fine I get into a car
accident I got my airbags and all be
what oh you boom
and that airbag just knocks you silly
gives most people or not most but I'd
say 50% of the people that get into car
accidents and that airbag goes off boom
right in their face 50% get a mild
concussion some get severe
concussions so in this situation you
bang your head in the front really hard
you got to get some ice on there quick
because you're stopping a
storm you're stopping a reaction a
crisis State reaction you have to slow
that crisis State reaction
down reminds me of a story a long time
ago where this guy was driving a
motorcycle and he had his helmet on okay
he got into a crash on the
highway his bike went down he was going
80 90 M an hour something happened
another car and so forth and he went
down and then he got up from the ground
and was walking
around cops got there Medics got there
fire department got there everybody got
there the ambulances got there the other
people were being addressed and taking
care of they were taking care of him
too and the guy was told by someone not
to remove his helmet not to remove his
helmet he had his helmet on and what was
happening was there was a crisis The
Happening inside his head inside his
brain he was walking around
fine the police department was there the
Medics were there right paramedics were
there the EMTs were there everybody was
there the state police were there and he
took off his helmet and he
died his helmet was on but he wasn't
getting care for a long time because
there was confusion because even though
he wiped out he was walking around fine
and talking perfectly fine he was like
yeah know I'm all right yeah that's my
motorcycle it's 100 yards down that way
I got a bad scratch on my leg but I
don't need a stretcher I don't need
anything I don't have to worry about
nothing I don't need to go into the
ambulance and they sat him down and
they're like okay he's talking fine they
did a little check on his eyes his
helmet was still on he did a little
check on his eyes right little
flashlight in there dilation pupils and
all that and it was going on too long it
was like 45 minutes because the accident
report was being filled out people were
being taken care of tow trucks were
coming and grabbing grabbing things but
it went so long without something to
slow down the crisis that the minute the
guy took off his helmet and one
paramedic was like hey wait a minute you
were in that accident don't take off sir
don't take off your helmet sir don't
take off your helmet stop stop right now
the guy took off his helmet
and he died right there hit the ground
and died everything came
apart because in that 45 minutes of that
head injury they didn't have they didn't
cold pack him they didn't ice him they
didn't ice his head and at least slow
that progression down of that storm
before they can get him to the hospital
get him into Imaging and see where the
bleeders are and see where the
inflammation was really compounding see
if the skull was
fractured but it never got to that point
and never got to that point so we're
talking about mild stuff right here
though in the whole bit head injuries
can be huge triggers let's go into head
injuries can be a huge trigger but
before I go into that I just want to say
so you bump your head in the front and
it's a pretty good bump and you know it
because you felt it you saw
Stars you want to not just put a cold
compress on the front you want to switch
and put on the back you want to slow
down the inflammation that occurs from
the brain
leaving the cockpit and moving forward
okay so now what happens when it's the
back of your head let's do that really
quick how many people have bang their
head the back of their head
right how many people have done
that you bumped your head you slipped
you fell down now it's the back of
that
okay all right that's the front again
what am I
doing there's nothing like
alive so that's the back of the head
here we go so now you fall and you bang
the back of your head head really hard
you see stars you almost black out most
guaranteed to have a mild concussion
coming right first thing you got to do
is compress cold compress again but
starting on the back of the head you
want to pinpoint not pinpoint but you
want to generalize it to the back of the
head because you won't know really where
you hit it when you slipped and fell and
the back of your head hit the ground you
won't really know
where you might have pain you might feel
it you might kind of know where but you
kind of won't know where so you put that
cold pack on the back of the head right
here you do that for what few minutes at
a time too cold you can back it off a
little bit then put it back on you can
back it off a little bit then put it
back on right can do that but you also
then want to switch it to the front now
yeah you didn't hit the front of your
face and you didn't hit the front of
your head but you want to get the front
you want to make sure you hit the ice on
the front give it some time few minutes
and so forth then flip it on the back
what you're doing is slowing down the
storm you're going to have a milder
concussion because of this this is
important information you're going to
have a milder
concussion because of this move right
here right here so you bend your head
really bad on the back oh you slipped
boom slipped on some ice boom right you
got the ice back here you're cold
compressing and then after a few minutes
or sometime you flip it you put it on
the
front put it on the front the only
difference here when it comes down to
hitting the back of your
head is you want to put ice on the back
and then you want to
then you want to put it on the top you
want to go front back top front back top
whatever Back front top do that few
minutes on the top few minutes on the
back but you don't want to put your
whole head in ice you don't want to go
into an ice bath you want you don't want
to submerge your body into an ice bath
if you banged your head that's not what
you do you don't want ice everywhere on
your head this is critical to know
because if you put it everywhere you're
slowing down the healing
process it has to be localized boom
right in the back where you hit it you
wait a few minutes or or you know four
five minutes or three minutes and then
it's on top 3 four minutes and then it's
in the front that's how you prevent
concussions that are going to spiral out
of control and become someone's bane of
their existence I heard it so many times
over and over and over again I heard
people you know what a w the reason why
I came to see you is because I had a car
accident 20 years ago and I'm still not
right something's still terribly wrong
I'm sick with all these problems my head
my eyes I got this I got that the whole
bit I know you're not lying so caramel
says I know you're not lying I've been
several car in several car accidents and
they sent me into a very deep depression
I was diagnosed with TMJ all kind of
weird symptoms developed you can get
diagnosed with TMJ from that you can get
diagnosed with a lot of different things
um so many different things fibro TMJ ra
you can just get literally diagnosed
with
everything and so that's what can happen
right so
um so I just want to tell you something
about you know C right
that's going around and stuff like that
and all that you know how there's After
Effects there's Long Haul C you know how
long haul SE what's a medical medium
thing to start with I published it first
talked about it first Long Haul flu
right so um I've done lives on it years
ago I've done lectures on it what
happens when you catch the flu and then
you're not the same after you catch a
bad flu and you're beaten down and it's
and you're just you're you're tired got
fatigued got symptoms well the same
thing can happen with concussion so like
Long Haul
concussion same thing happens with those
concussions where they last for a long
time they can last forever for people
they can last for 10 years 5 years this
is a serious problem when it comes down
to the chronically ill and so many
people with chronic illnesses don't
realize they've been triggered because
they banged their head and they don't
realize that they've been set back
because they Bang hang their head
they've had a car accident they've had
an injury with their head sosed
around and so they've got into these
situations but what's really more
annoying is that someone who's stuck
with some type of situation where
they're head was injured whether a car
accident or something else and then
they're sick for years they got the
symptoms like TMJ like all these other
different symptoms you can have like
neck pain migraines head pain dizziness
vertigo ringing in the ear tontis all
that's happening and then you bang your
head again and then you bang your head
again
darn you get into a little fender bender
and your head gets jostled you get a
little Whiplash and your head slams the
back of your seat and then you bang it
again that's what happens to everybody
they bang their head again they slip
they fall boom they bang their head
again it happens all over again so
that's why this is important right here
so anybody who's chronically ill
chronically sick so let's go into that a
little bit so in the brainsaver
protocols there is concussion in here in
the brain saver protocols let's go find
it here it
is
so um aha concussion recovery side
effects so what you'll see right here I
know it's hard to see I'm just showing
you this is in brain saver protocols
okay it says concussion recover recy
side effects all
right there's a a list of things you can
do so I want to read off some of these
some of these things if you're
going
somewhere and you're out and about and
you bang your head you injure your head
you get into an accident or you just
simply bang it in the car door somewhere
how many people get out of their car
bang it on the top of their door jam or
whatever I mean so many things happen
there's a list of things to do right
away first first thing you might want to
do is you might want to get some
cucumber juice in
you right away celery juice in you right
away these are options freshly squeezed
orange juice in you right away okay even
if it's just that even if you just
choose one of these things so here you
go you bend your head not even
concussion level I'm just talking about
like an egg just like I was showing you
before you Bang Your Head freshly
squeezed orange juice right away if
that's what you have a bunch of oranges
then that's what you do okay all right
cucumber juice if you got a bunch of
cucumbers cucumber juice right away okay
another thing you can do is a heavy
metal detox smoothie if you already do
it here's one right here the spinach
soup that's in the medical medium books
get on the spinach soup that day doesn't
have to be in that moment but the same
day you injure your head it's important
right there okay okay so let's talk
about
supplementation if this if it's just one
thing you do like I tell family friends
after a like a head injury a headbang or
something happened an accident get on
curcumin right away just and whatever
curcumin you have just get on it right
away that's the vimergy one but I'm just
saying make sure you get human and get
on it so it's one thing right there
important vitamin C B12 B12 you get a
head injury B12 right away and I'll tell
you
why
nerves very important to know nerves
nerve
inflammation your brain slashes around
the demand for B12 is going to be off
the
chart the you will eat up your B12 like
nobody's business you bang your
head you eat up the B12 your head shakes
around a little you burn through your
B12 reserves every cell in your brain
every single cell in your skull is going
to be requiring B12 in that moment in
that crisis so B12 is critical for any
kind of stuff with head injuries any
kind of problems where you actually hurt
your head neck too included because
we're talking about the brain stem as
well even
neck because it can ring right up there
and get up there curcumin so what I like
about curcumin for any kind of head
injury any kind of bump on the Noggin is
it helps to get inflammation down it
helps to push it down so not only are
doing the ice and the ice packs and any
kind of bumps and bruises on your head
but you're doing the curcumin to help
bring that down and that's one of the
things that's in the protocol right
there cumin B12 is in there zinc's
another one so what I love about zinc is
it dumbs down the cyto storm right zinc
dumbs down the reaction that happens
when your body's in crisis you bang your
head I tell family and friends get on a
little bit of
zinc you Bang Your Head get on a little
bit of Z so that's right there something
that's really important to know vitamin
C is another one if it's only one thing
you have you only have beads 12 that's
when you use it right there one thing
you have vitamin C is another one too so
that's a great one because vitamin C
that high antioxidant level helps to
bring down that pre radical crap that
happens when your body goes into a
crisis State and all this junk is
produced from it that's another one too
all on its own and
then um check the book out when you can
there's other also other information in
there about that so that's brain saer
protocols I didn't kill myself on that
book so I can't you know so that people
you know don't have options I want to
make sure they have options they have a
chance to
heal and so there we go all right so
let's just make some food you guys I'm
into it um I got some mango right
here so I'm just draining a little bit
of the
water out of this mango Bowl so I'm
going to put this
here all right I got the pan hot I'm
going to chop up some potatoes but first
I'm going to do some onion I think as
we'll do let's get some onion going
let's make some food you guys there's so
much more to talk about with that I'm
just giving you as much as I can in the
a lot of time I
have so I'm going to cut an
onion get it in the
pan that pan should be
hot but I want to also talk about
pneumonia a lot of people are getting
pneumonia right now their lungs are
getting filled with
mucus there's some places in the United
States right now where hospitals are
overrun from this whole white lung thing
basically it's just a crappy
crappy bronchitis that instantly turns
into pneumonia for a lot of people it's
really gnarly gives you a fever in the
whole bit but I'd like to let people
know that you know you should be
prepared do you have the cold and flu
kit you
know the flu tool kit the medical medium
one you have that that has information
in there for this kind of thing all
right so I'm chopping up these onions
really
quick going to make some
food okay there we
go
let's get that in
there it's already
sizzling now it says about a half a cup
of onion but I'm telling you I'm partial
to onion so I put a little bit more in
there because I really really like it I
don't know about you guys but I love
onion
okay all right next thing on the list
let's get some garlic cloves in there
three garlic cloves of course you can
put more you're welcome to do that I'm
going to pop in three garlic cloves get
it on this pan really
quick all
right there we
go and this comes better comes together
really easy these potatoes are steamed
makes it go faster makes it better I
like it that
way there we go
all right that one I'm going to just
chop up some garlic really quick
probably do another
one so when it comes down to it's
interesting I noticed something when it
comes down to the bugs that come into
town and people get
sick if it's pretty
bad and I'm noticing they're being quiet
about it a little bit more quiet about
it it's like I don't know you can use
your imagination why but this bug that's
coming around is I got a friend who
works in an ER it's a
doctor he says they're all
like they're like underwater there
because of it all
right let's get this cooking
up nice we're going to
get we're going to get some spices in
here really quick going to put a little
bit of curry powder in
here all right got some fun stuff here
curry powder that in
here all right some more stuff coming in
there we'll do some
cumin
caramon here we
go
just going a little quicker
today yeah c a little tumeric in here
too guys I'm dropping some spices in
this pan I'll show you real quick there
you go right in the onion right in the
garlic I smell an
aroma that's really good woo
woohoo it's all I can
say it's
intense chili powder let's get some
cayenne in there I'd like to put a fresh
cayenne in
there chopping this up how many of you
guys have been through a head injury
before it's a it's a trigger that tends
to lower the immune system
allowing Epstein bar to rise up in a lot
of people so they end up with so many
different diagnoses because they're
dealing with
problems okay CH
powder this is a spicy Brew right
here okay and I'm going to add some
potato in here so I got some potato here
I'm going to cut it up in pieces these
potatoes are kind of
crumbly there's a there's one person can
bang their head one person can bang
their head really
hard another person can bang their head
just as hard and have less issues
another person can literally get
triggered into chronic sickness for
years happens all the time to
people so I cubed this up and I'm going
to put a bunch more in here I want to
make a little bit of a bigger one grab
another potato right here that's a
steamed
potato that's a really good one too by
the way it's a
beauty the steamed
russet this is like a a a pleaser for a
lot of people Crow pleaser believe it or
not it feels really hearty it feels
really
good take a look nice here we
go I'm kind of like putting these big
like cubes and rectangles and stuff in
here I don't want it to
um there we
go all right I'm going to put one more
that was two potatoes but I got these
really nice big ones so what I'm going
to do is take this potato here let's go
with one more if you guys don't
mind someone might say why is he talking
about like you know head injuries and
stuff I'll tell you
why so many people with chronic illness
their lives have changed because they
banged their head they had a head injury
of some kind and and it wasn't addressed
properly and their nerves became frayed
in in different areas and their brain
stem and their cranial nerve became
inflamed because of because of say
Epstein bar and the shingles rising up
because their immune system was knocked
down so when we go through something
like some kind of trauma our immune
system drops we have an adrenaline surge
when we go through some kind of trauma
or adrenaline is just pouring pouring
into our bloodstream from our adrenals
pumping and pouring in and then our
immune system starts to drop through the
crisis right and then if someone's just
on the edge of that that um Epstein bar
breakout they're just on the edge of
that simplex one breakout or that
shingles breakout they get in trouble
because some of those viruses like the
obscene bar can cling to the nerves the
root hairs from these nerves and then
they're at the doctor's office like I
got fibromyalgia now I got problems I
never had before and they're just
dealing with all all this
stuff
okay so I got some frozen peas over here
I'm going to pop in a little bit I also
have um some steam peas too I just
thought I would have both some people
steam them where they're soft like this
I do love them like this I like them
when they got this like really soft kind
of kind of you know they're they lose
some of that green color but they're so
good though right and then you can have
them differently too where kind of
popping you can make them toasty but
they're not as
soft these are frozen
peas
okay want to show you guys over here on
IG can you take a look that's the
skillet right there that I'm showing you
that's the curried potato and pea and
cilantro I'm not going to put the
cilantro in yet I don't want to cook the
cilantro down I don't I want the
cilantro to
[Music]
be right I want the cilantro to be um
fresh right on
top I don't know if you guys like that
too all right let's get some diced
tomato in
there and a little bit of water if you
want let's do that
going to put a little bit of water on
this
pan
okay you don't want it like you don't
want to drown it you don't want to put
cups and cups of water in you just want
to just put just
enough okay let me get some tomato
out okay nice I'm going to pop a little
bit of these in here you guys don't mind
chopping up there you go
awesome see H over there I'm recovering
concussion you're Rec recovering from a
concussion I'm so going through flare up
yeah I feel so bad for you the
concussions are just so annoying and
they can really linger and it's
important to kind
of know what you can do for it like for
instance the concussion protocol has a
lot of different things in here to work
with but there's a reason for it because
we get these viral flares on top of
concussion issues
right I'm going to put some tomato in
here not a lot I'm just going to put
some it's kind of like this the
concussion can be a problem all on its
own because your head was shook your
brain was shook but it also can trigger
off other things that are inside of our
body immune system drops
lot of people suffer from concussion
issues a year if you're young sometimes
it takes a year to power through it I
mean it just
can depending on how bad look
everybody's concussion is different but
still cold white spring I saw they just
recognized Long Haul flu
oh they didn't recognize it they stole
it ha published in a New York Times
best-selling book also I live streamed
all about it and lectured about it in
2019 September 15 2019 talking about flu
Long Haul flu meaning what happens you
get the flu it knocks you down in your
immune system and then all these other
things start
happening medical medium
information right there and I did it
before the pandemic so I published
multiple
Avenues of that but I was talking to
somebody who um is scientist guy who's
interested in medical medium books and
he says like why don't we do a whole
bunch of studies on this I'm like hey
why not he said you know they're taking
your info right I go yeah no I know I
know they took
that all right I thought they're the all
knowing they're all powerful out there
in the medical world why do they need my
books why do they need my
information like what's up with that I
thought they knew everything and then
they call me names at the same time and
try to keep the medical medium down
medical medium information down but they
steal and they take and they poach it
it's actually
sick all
right I'm going to put some P's in here
too and I might even throw a quick
little lid on this when these peas go
in I'm going to drop some frozen peas in
here you
guys you don't need a lot of them cup
cup or
so let's get these mixed up in
here over there in IG you see this IG
Land There you
go let's just get some heat in there I
want those frozen peas to cook I'm going
to pop a little lid on
there
boom I'm going to start the
salad I
am and I got to get a dressing going
first let me make the dressing
first we got to get some raw honey in
here which one do you you guys like the
maple syrup or do you like the raw honey
maple syrup or raw honey I can't you
know what I like both I'm going to go
with some raw honey in this
one couple
teaspoons let that
cook I just like a little extra honey in
mine you could use way less if you want
all
right and is there anything else I'm
going to do some salad now and I got the
mango ready that's going to be part of
the salad
here
okay all right I'm going to make a
dressing ter appan to try and make
themselves look good and cover their
mistakes indeed I believe that's true I
do Katherine Elizabeth they should be
sued because the world needs to know the
truth love that passion I do I
do I agree
wholeheartedly okay making some dressing
now so in the dressing I'm going to put
mango in here one cup of
mango where's my
cup here it
is one cup of mango you guys in this
dressing how do you like
that
okay what's next garlic
clove
what garlic clove if you guys don't like
garlic keep it out if you don't like
garlic keep it out that's
okay multitasking just bear with me
that's looking amazing just about done
put that clove of garlic in there that's
right let's
go okay
okay we be faster red bell pepper
next show you how I like to chop these
up right like to do that see that that's
it that nice piece right
there put that in
there get the center out love
that okay chop this up in pieces it's
going in so I'm not going to I'm going
to
um trying to think if there's something
else that's that I'm going to do here
before I put that
in now here's how I take the seeds
out see take a look I'll cut one more
for
you take a look you
guys see that piece right there nice
okay this is how I remove the seeds take
the whole thing look at that pop them
out gone right what is there one seed
left there you are gone gone
gone how cool is that that's what we're
talking
about let's get this pepper in here
let's stop foing around
here
yep here you
go you want the dressing the color
beautiful color red I got a clove in
there now I'm going to put some lemon
juice in there it's next lemon
juice okay going to get a little
strainer
okay can you see guys see
this all
right
don't want to burn it don't want it
burnt peas are coming out really good in
here IG you see
this take a
look get some lemon going in this
dressing three tablespoons of fresh
lemon juice doing it
now okay we're going to get maple syrup
in this
one mustard powder which I have one more
lemon I mean
seriously this is really
good I'm turning this griddle off cuz
that is some hot stuff right
there okay
all right maybe I'll put a little bit
more lemon in
here just to really follow the
instructions
okay mustard
powder boom little touch of
that okay onion
powder
Touch of that it's going to taste so
good little bit of maple
syrup what's going on
here I'm going to do a decent amount of
maple
syrup I'm going to do two
tablespoons that's actually pretty funny
right there and some do slakes little
half teaspoon of do FL we go that's czy
let's blend it
up guys I'll bring the blender over
let's
roll
okay is there a
song or is it just Christmas songs right
now everybody
singing all
right want to get that red color a
little better I'm just going
to pop a little bit more red pepper in
here
yep multitasking you guys I'm making
sure this this is nice and good here I'm
blending here we
go that is a
dressing
I Ed the nicest red bell peppers
too it's got a little bit of an orange
color instead of dark red but it's
beautiful
still all
right good thing I put that extra bell
pepper in
there okay guys
it's a little dressing we have it's
gorgeous it's here all right let's get
the salad
together all right so this is a rugala
salad I'm just going to put some
beautiful aruga in this
bowl you don't
mind you know I you know it's just
concerns me greatly like what with
people with chronic illness what they
suffer with and struggle with no one
that's it they just don't get it unless
they've gone through it you know I so
many times people try to tell other
people like you don't understand them
it's so hard everything's so hard what I
go through and everything and just
people just don't get it they
don't and then you know when they get
sick it's different you know when they
catch the flu it's
different okay all
right I have cold and flu protocols in
brain saver right here that's the
concussion but we got cold and flu
protocols all through
here all right let me get the salad
together I'm going to chop up some
tomato for the salad right
here see if you guys can see
this I'm doing these tomato slices right
here there you go some tomato
slices which you're going to go in
sprinkled the about let's get some more
here
nice Trading Places says if still
chronically ill um with postconcussion
so you're still if still chronically ill
with postconcussion symptoms what is
recommended that is exactly what in here
seriously I mean exactly I know I fool
around a lot you guys and I kid around
on some stuff and I try to keep things
really lighthearted but
seriously critical information is in
here just for that just for
that I
mean seriously people need that
information
um I don't want anybody left out you
know someone's like well hey you know I
don't really have this chronic illness
but what I have is I got into a car
accident years ago and Anthony you're
not talking about it too much even
though I have talked about car accidents
and what happens why people get
triggered why it triggers people but
I've had this concussion and I've been
sick for years and um and I just want
everybody to have a chance to heal I
just do let's pop these beautiful
tomatoes in here there we go all right
so the cucumber is what I'm missing
right now so bow says why do you always
complain about Doc's benefit from your
information didn't you write books for
everyone and why do you care if they
attribute you or not amazing amazing
I'll tell you why because they can tell
somebody they got long haul
flu but that's all they can do doesn't
that suck
that sucks so if I had long haul flu and
I'm suffering and I can't get help and
my life sucks and I can't work and I I'm
struggling and I'm sick with who knows
what after I had the flu for six months
now and I'm not getting out of it and I
go and find some article somewhere or
somebody you know they they took a grab
they grabbed the medical M information
and they grabbed it and they said you
have long haul flu here's what you know
here's how it works you catch the flu
and you don't get better they don't give
you the answer answers they don't give
you the answers they don't say hey
look we know now that this exists we
took it from medical medium books it was
published in his New York Times
best-selling books we took
it but we really can't help you but then
in the medical medium books the answers
to because that's where it originates it
originates from there you know about
they know about the long ha flu because
it origin Ates from the medical medium
books so that's where the answers to how
to heal it also the answers to why you
even have it the best they can do is
they steal the concept and they say you
got long haul flu but they don't tell
you how it really happens like the real
details of how you got long haul flu
they don't tell you that and they don't
tell you how to fix it either they don't
tell you where it originated it
originated
here and then on top of it they tell you
medical medium don't listen to listen to
that guy oh medical medium don't listen
to that guy he's not a doctor oh he's a
grifter don't listen to him we'll steal
his New York Times best-selling
information and we'll poach it and we'll
and we won't site him but don't go to
that don't go to that book don't talk to
that guy and it it's actually a sickness
man poaching and not
sighting and your question is a good
question why do you care aw like why do
you care I care
because if it's you you're not going to
be able to get the answers you're going
to read an article you're going to look
for it you're going to hear somebody
talking about it but they're not going
to have an answer to getting you
recovered getting you better you're just
going to be okay I got long haul flu now
what oh I'm just going to be sick now
and you're stuck in it and they didn't
tell you they didn't say hey um by the
way you can get better and get back to
work get your life better but nobody
gives a that's why and on top of it
all they bully the medical M community
so the medical mem Community they bully
them they bully the people who are
chronically sick that are healing with
this information they bully them and
then they poach and steal the
information and then someone sees it out
there oh that's interesting that's long
haul flu hey honey honey you've been
bedridden now for eight months after you
had that really bad flu I just read an
article from blah blah blah science SL
blah and they just said there's Long
Haul flu honey how do you like that we
have an answer this is why you're in bed
for 8 months it's like okay well what do
we do about it husband what do we do
about it honey oh I don't know they
really didn't say um they said it's like
some people 5% of the people get the flu
they're sick so they and you know it's
Insanity they're not saying like whoa
the original source of the longa flu has
also the answers to recovery and why
you're sick like why you're still sick
sick they don't say anything about that
and that's what's crazy about it all
really you know all right so I got a
salad here I'm going to throw a couple
more tomatoes in here you can put
anything in this salad you can put
anything in here if you really want
right I got some cilantro which is going
to go in the other dish
okay let's see
onig Vina says yes they yes they
do Bully us yeah they do they bully the
medical medum community bad
bad
yep because you guys got the answers you
guys are seasoned you know what's up
they bully the medical mam Community
bad I mean it's really crazy so if
you're wondering like I get it I get it
don't you just want to get your book
information out no matter what aw don't
you just want it out there why do you
care if you get cited or not why should
you care is it an ego thing aw because
didn't you just want to get the
information out there yeah that would be
great if it worked like that but they
don't do that either they don't take and
steal the information and then give
people the real
answers they don't even give them that
they steal the information look good for
a hot
second and talk trash about medical
medium yeah all right all right I got a
salad going I got a dressing going let
me plate up some
food let's plate up some food really
quick you
guys all right kaard over there on
Facebook so true aw 14 Medical
Specialists dismissed me over a 2-year
period because they couldn't tell me
what what was wrong with me much less
how to address it grateful to you and S
so for sharing the lifes saving info
with
Humanity you know what's crazy it's like
you guys I mean medical Med books are
virtually in every country around the
world they're helping people people are
drinking celery juice all around the
world they're drinking it in their
closets every supermodel shrinking just
almost every single supermodel is
drinking celery juice and every now and
then you kind of see it you know show up
like someone will tell me this model was
drinking celery juice everybody's doing
celery juice they can't keep it in the
storees still they can't keep celery in
the stores still I mean it has grown
like no one's business like when the
celery juice was hitting like was
starting to really catch on more and
more and more with the medical medium
books it got to a point now where it's
like they have trucks that are separate
trucks that go to the stores with just
celery now largest produce crop in the
world the largest produce crop in the
world I'm not talking about corn I'm not
talking about a grain I'm talking about
like a herb the largest herb crop is
celery it's insane right and they're
still talking about celery juice
and medical medium what so uh let see
medical medum healing says it takes away
respect and credibility from aw and then
disrespects us for following him that's
what they're doing and you guys by the
way listen okay I just want to say this
right we're going to kind of like we're
just going to say it right there's a
campaign going on right
now okay a campaign that it's
multifaceted right it's to shame anybody
who's following medical
medium to shame everybody who's
following medical medium
right and then at the same time steal
the medical medium information at the
same time try to convince people who
follow medical medium that the
information isn't original and it's not
from my books or from the medical medium
at the same time trying to say medical
meds of
fraud like a campaign at the same
time the medical establishment in the
medical world and the medical system is
stealing all the medical medium
information and they're putting it
online they have nothing to back it up
we know we we've done the research and
we've actually caught them in like
hundreds of different places where they
actually take it right out of the book
right out of the books at the same time
all of this is happening mm's being
censored at the same time all that's
happening
like you know they must really fear me
must really really fear me and then
there's different levels of it like
these campaigns and then there's the and
then this the crazy thing is we have all
the factual data to prove it's happening
we have all of it because it's happening
it's crazy how it works just nuts
man just
nuts and keep your
eyes and ears
open all
right I got to get some cilantro on here
too
okay cool I'm going to make a little bit
of room here too which is great cuz I
got some salad I want to get in here
there you go I want to get some gorgeous
Greens in it I want to chop up a little
bit of cilantro and put it on
top I don't know if you guys can see
this all right Dr Fawn an amazing
medical doctor there is a campaign you
really have to be made of something
strong to withstand some of
it years ago you know what they said
about medical Med you're monopolizing
the entire Health movement that's what
they
said they said you're
monopolizing the entire Health movement
and what I said was no it's just that
millions are healing worldwide that no
one has ever seen before no one has ever
seen this kind of healing with people
with real chronic illness bedridden and
getting out of their wheelchairs no
one's ever seen that before no matter
how many eat better books came out no
matter how much stuff came out nobody
ever seen that before and so what they
did was they took
they took that as all these people are
healing celery juice is out of control
heavy metal detox out of control
everything he's dominating he's
monopolizing the entire Health Movement
we got to stop him we got to stop him so
let's talk trash about
them right so there's a couple of things
you can do it cilantro you can make it
look really nice by just giving it a
gentle gentle chop you you can also chop
it up differently I'm going to put a
little bit of cilantro right on here
okay like that I mean I love cilantro
I'll eat all the
cilantro in one
shot I got my salad here and I'm going
to put the dressing on the side so let
me
just we moving
around doing a dance
that's right then they try to silence me
and tell me I'm not allowed to speak and
set the record
straight that's how it rolls but you
can't silence
me
um and you guys might want to be paying
attention you might want to be want
might want to be paying attention coming
up
when the time is
right it's all coming
out some salad right there I'm going to
put the dressing in this nice
little take a look at this you guys this
is insane Juliet luell when I read the
medical medium books I feel the truth of
the words I feel better from reading it
they are healing words and I'm going to
tell you something right now you guys
the gossip and the rumors have nothing
behind it
the gossip the
rumors the
BS has nothing substantial behind it
like there's no evidence behind it
there's no anything behind it's just
made up
stuff
but get
ready get
ready all
right so what I want to do is just put a
little dress in bowl over
here just bear with
me okay so I want to get some dressing
in
here there we
go now you can just pour it right on the
salad I'm just going to set it up like
this if you don't mind this is the way I
like it
right there we go take a
look now I'm going to show
you that is the curried potato and pea
and cilantro hash with an incredible
green salad with French dressing right
there take a look on IG what do you guys
think does that look good I see the
steam arising look at that amazing this
is going to taste so so so good you guys
see over there on YouTube how you guys
doing give me a thumbs up if you guys
like this show don't like it give me a
middle finger it's fine with me yeah I
know it's ready I'm
excited yeah Stacy says I'm telling you
that you are right I am being attacked
by people in some of the Facebook groups
I'm in they argue and tell me that
there's no scientific evidence and I
tell them how I was almost dead and the
medical medium saved my life makes me so
mad how they are attacking us they are
but they're not attacking anybody else
out there this is what they're doing but
they're told to do that you guys there's
a campaign that's paid for too and
there's other campaigns that aren't even
paid for but there's some paid for
campaigns and there's some non-paid for
campaigns but there's campaigns running
to actually confuse you tell you you're
you know this is tell you the
information is not good no matter how
many millions have healed no matter how
it saved your life that must be crap
that must be and then they
throw all these stories out
that are actually not even
real and also just influencers are out
there want to sell all their stuff now
so what they do is they say about
medical medium then it brings in a crowd
because anything medical medium just
brings people in right and they say
about medical medium then people come in
and then they do that so they can sell
their they can sell other people's
stuff and sell this and that and sell
their stuff it's like it's crazy what's
happening but it's just a storm we just
have to ride through it that's all we
have to just ride through it and we'll
get to the other side of it meanwhile
science research is taking medical M
information and not citing it everywhere
they're doing it on all the clinic Pages
we we see it we we actually capture it
they do it in all kinds of other
places it's actually amazing it's
amazing just check this out I me can I
get get a fork
out I shall get a fork
out right here that is the ultimate sign
that Med medical medium is legit because
it's challenged so heavily that's the
sign that's the ultimate sign that it is
legit where did that medical information
come from when no one had it before
where did it come from came from above
you know science when science research
takes your information constantly like
multiple sceris is caused by obscene bar
I published it years before and then
they took it how I've bars behind like
all of a sudden all these symptoms and
neurological stuff they didn't know that
that's medical medium information in
depth though like when they steal all
that then you know it's legit you know
it's Untouchable stuff and I was told
over and over again that you're
monopolizing the entire Health movement
because number one I was one of the
people that were here first 35 plus
years into this into the the the you
know to where we are and another thing
too let me just give you guys a little
heads up medical medium has made
Industries billions and billions of
dollars
now billions of dollars the entire
Health movement has changed because of
mm info the amount of product selling in
the world is unbelievable because of
medical medum information billions and
billions of dollars of celery Farms
built billions of dollars of like like
you name it the whole heavy metal thing
out there has prompted everybody Under
the Sun to come up with some
crazy concoction and literally say this
is what's going on here's here's this
metal thing there's like it's it's
turning into a trillion doll industry
Medical medium has shifted the healing
world to turn it into like a trillion
doll industry right now it's crazy
because I put out the information about
neurological problems and what fixes it
and how it works there's so many
Industries now coaching services around
the world think about that there are
thousands and thousands of coaching
Services built off of like just because
they were inspired by medical medium
information and we're talking it's
billions of dollars now you guys has
been generated from mm info including
the haters selling all of their stuff by
dragging people in with my name and then
selling all their stuff we're talking
billions at this point you guys it's no
joke billions and billions of
dollars is being made every day off of
medical medium information that's not
lining my pockets it's not lining your
pockets you need to know this so you can
see through the BS you need to know this
so you can see through it all by the way
the swear words are catchy the person
that really kind person that left a
comment and and said the
FW I thought I would join in because I
want to let you know that I could say it
too with you brain saver protocols
recipe by the way is brain
Savers I just didn't want you feeling
like by yourself on that on that swear
word you you that I
read I want you to know that I'm with
you too I'll gladly swear okay look you
guys I'm going to have some can't help
it
boom Journey sg1
where were you talking about sugar 35
years ago was talking about wheat
talking about sugar was talking about
all of it I was talking about lemon
water flushing the body of toxins and
the liver of toxins flushing the
liver flushing the body this is so
good this
insane all right you
guys I'm going to drop a little bit of
this dressing in
here love you guys it was fun
today God bless you
you guys make sure you sign up make sure
you subscribe to my telegram I leave
messages personal messages about healing
about moving forward so get on to my
telegram please please please get on to
my telegram get on to my newsletter so
you can get the updates and also what
you've missed each week get on my
newsletter and you guys I got some
really great stuff and I'm going to say
this right now I'm going to give you a
hint I'm going to give you a
hint coming up pretty soon I'm trying to
make it happen so you guys can see me in
person not oneon-one
but I'm just giving you hint I'm not
sure how Which Way but I'm working on it
or I might even do something where if
you bring me your book I will sign it
I'm just I'm just saying I'm I'm I'm
working on that I'm hoping it happens it
takes a lot takes a lot a lot a lot but
I'm letting you know I'm just giving you
the 411 that I'm working on
something coming up in
where I'll be somewhere in person you
bring me the
book right
there I'll sign
it I'm working on
something we'll see if we can make it
happen all right you guys