right now facebook and youtube got a
estonian stew going on here some pretty
psych carrots
got the parsley you guys got potatoes as
well
and some green cabbage right got some
green cabbage
got some onion you know talking about
death
by a thousand cuts too as well we're
going to cover that a little bit
it's important you know what we're doing
to ourselves when we don't know we're
doing it
maybe it doesn't matter if we feel great
but if we're sick
or got to our struggling it matters
hello hey wendy thanks for coming on
uma thanks for coming on you know that's
great deanna
hmm
well huh
well i'm killing myself without knowing
it
what do you mean what
death by a thousand cuts what are you
talking about
apple cider vinegar come on like that's
a big deal
you mean it all adds up what
this is crazy really what else
nutritional yeast yeah i do that i did
it last week
i only did it once last week it was on
some kale chips
huh that that's that bad
well yeah i had a glass of wine so what
one glass of wine on the weekends what
so you're saying what it's just they all
add up together
yeah i ate a chocolate bar yesterday it
was 90
dark chocolate yeah i felt it i got a
rush
i did so that that's ruining my adrenals
what do you mean yeah but what's wrong
with a little bit of chocolate
it's not just the chocolate yeah i
i had a cheeseburger that was last month
though i told you it was just a
cheeseburger
yeah i was with friends and i had a
cheeseburger it was a double
but it was one cheeseburger so how can
it be death by a thousand cuts what do
you mean i'm killing myself
it's adding up so you're saying
nutritional yeast and the apple cider
vinegar and then the burger and then the
chocolate
and then you forgot the wine you up the
wine
what there's even more
i got i'm gonna hang up on you i'm
getting so stressed out this is terrible
guys we're live right now um glad you
guys are coming on
nirashini good to see you
um you guys are amazing i'm glad yeah
death by a thousand cheeseburgers look
you guys i'm gonna be making a stew
right here i'm talking about
stuff and here's the thing
i'm in the new edition right revise and
expand expand it the new edition
okay and i'm in here and i'm looking
and i'm talking about troublemaker foods
list right
so here it is you got the eggs
okay they're trouble i talk about why
okay so you guys know i talk about why
these eggs are trouble
okay you got the eggs you got the dairy
products milk cheese butter yogurt cream
kefir you got the gluten you do gluten
once in a while
you do gluten once in a while do acv
once in a while you do acv
why acv cassie it's the teeth
destroyer teeth destroyer i think i hear
the phone ringing
it's the teeth destroyer that's what it
is
and it's important to know how you're
being duped
like ridiculously duped over and that's
important to know
i mean especially when it comes
especially when it comes to
people not understanding how it works
the
apple cider vinegar can really really
damage teeth and people don't realize
this they just don't realize it you know
hello yeah i'm doing apple cider vinegar
two tablespoons
every single morning yep
i i got it on i well no i'm raw
yeah apple cider vinegar the raw stuff
the really good stuff
that's right you know the stuff
everybody talks about
what do you mean it dissolves my teeth i
i use a straw i do two tablespoons
and i put the straw down my throat a
little bit
and i suck it up past my teeth
so you don't got me there you're not
gonna get me there i i can do my apples
what it draws calcium
out of my teeth out of my bones because
of the acetic acid
so when my teeth start falling apart i
know why
huh and my teeth are actually already
falling apart yeah i was at the dentist
yeah they're doing all kinds of work now
yeah you know what the dentist told me
to not do any lemon water but to make
sure i do lots of apple cider vinegar
all right i'm going to start the stew
now
yeah people are getting fooled on that
when it's sad it's a sad sad day i'm
going to start the stew here
my doctor told me to drink acv for my
acid reflux and it only made it a
hundred times worse and wrecked my teeth
austin it's a teeth destroyer
first of all i feel bad for you on that
it's it's
that's just oh my god i need these eggs
off of here
um chop up some carrots here this is the
estonian stew doing some carrot chopping
real quick you guys i got to get the
stew going
is what i got to do yeah
that's what's really sad
i'm serious reading comments as i'm
going along
you guys i got to get this stew going uh
just bear with me okay
please bear with me right
let's get the carrots in here do you
guys see what's going on do you get a
good enough pitcher over here
are you getting some carrots in here
okay i got the healing broth in here
i made it earlier but i just i today
went crazy and i was like whoa i don't
know if i could do it all
in one shot but let's see what we can do
you should hear the the uh apple cider
vinegar
podcast that medical medium podcast at
apple podcast
you guys listen i try not to ask for
much
because you guys you know got your your
own everyday stuff going on you guys are
busy
you guys got life you know some many of
you don't feel good you're working on
your healing process but
can you share the medical mean podcast
at apple podcast so people can actually
do some great healing um
the episodes are just incredible
this is the estonian stew just so you
know
don't cut my fingers i'm gonna try not
to kobe
i'm gonna try not to cut my fingers
just cut my finger no i didn't
i'm gonna try not to right all right
uh catherine you're planning on cooking
the estonian stew
good to know good to know i love that i
love that let's get some potato chopped
up real quick in this stew
okay let's get that going
we're gonna be quick on this quicker on
this
[Music]
let's get the potatoes in here so i want
to talk about death by a thousand cuts
for a couple of minutes
it's serious it's not not really a joke
laura are you going to come out with
any more meditation podcasts i most
certainly will
absolutely i have it planned
and yeah
i got it planned let's get some potato
in here
diana hi anthony i have three of your
books you are helping me
so much survive epstein barr after 40
years of damage
[Music]
i want you to survive i want you to
thrive
i want you to get your life back that's
what i want
i love how people and health are
pretending they care about
people who are chronically sick that's
the new thing now
you know they're like why is the medical
medium so successful
doesn't make any sense he's got to be
doing something oh
he cares about people he cares
that's what it is and uh and so now you
just see it now there's you know
you see it now people are actually
acting like they care in the health
movement they
never cared all the gurus in the health
field
never gave a crap i can't tell you how
many i've talked to all of them
throughout the years
and i'd be trying to tell them what
people go through and be like you don't
know what it's like in their shoes
and they'd be like what i'd be like you
don't know what it's like in their shoes
and be like you don't get it
you don't know what it's like to be in
their shoes and they'd be like
huh you know little phone thing that's
not really happening because i got to
get you guys moving on this
let's cut some onion
i want the stew to cook while we're
talking
it was like this i was thinking do i
just prep it all and
throw it in the pot no let's cut it
let's cut it during it
i gotta talk to you guys about something
austin said my wife is seeing me healing
and is only getting sicker and she asked
me yesterday to make her celery juice
austin that's incredible
that is incred i don't like the fact
that she's getting sicker
but if she starts to do the work right
you get her started on stuff and some
celery juice that's that's incredible
that's amazing get some onion in here
all right here we go
austin you're on there again everyone
hated me on
everybody hated on me for doing mm and
that was only until they see me healing
now they are asking to do it too phone's
ringing
heck's going on
austin hey hey austin
i just want to tell you something i'm
really
really proud of you man you don't even
know you don't even know
i mean i know it's not easy with
everybody giving you
i know i know i know brother
and you've been through a lot you've
been through a lot
yeah yeah i get it i do
i do i i know people don't get it out
there i know
but you're doing the work man and i'm
blown away i'm actually blown away
yeah i love you too i love you too
all right we got some stew cooking i
think we
oh yeah i think we're getting there
i'm gonna put the cabbage in a little
later like the recipe calls
okay all right
i'm gonna put the um dill and the
parsley a little bit later
okay lorraine can celery force replace
celery juice when needed it can't
replace
it celery force is i mean i use it every
day
okay it it wakes up my mind
and that's kind of scary because my
friends and family tell me my mind's
already away
you know awake in the sense where i'm
going going going going and
you know like all day and i don't stop
and i'm on the phone and everything
and that's without celery force but i
take celery force myself personally
when i get three hours of sleep at night
not because i can't sleep but because i
push myself
to the limit to a dangerous limit
and with all the information i got to
put out with the books i'm trying to
write everything right
and so what i'll do is i'll like uh
spirit is it is it okay is it okay if i
take some celery force right now
it's rid of compassion soc is like go
ahead take it i know you're only on
three hours two and a half hours of
sleep
but take it you can push yourself a
little harder if that's what you want to
do but take the celery force
next thing you know two and a half hours
of sleep in me and i'm actually going
like as if i didn't even feel like the
sleep even hit me and that's how i use
it i don't know
a lot of people use it because it gives
them this focus and concentration
and it clears their mind and
just if you don't know what i'm talking
about you guys let me show you
you know if you don't know you might not
even know what i'm talking about
so i'm talking about the celery force
there's no celery in it
this is it's that's what's so amazing
and just in general it's so cool
there's no celery in it that's the
celery force right there
that's the vimergy bees and victor i am
as mary e
r g y vimergi.com and i'm not sponsored
just lo i just love i love the people
that that
own the company are just unbelievable
people
um i've known him for years amazing
people and i try to get
relationships with all these supplement
company owners to see if i can
you know at all just know what they're
doing so i can
trust in what i can recommend people
because health is
everything can i have cultured
vegetables
yeah you can just look out for just
here's the thing
a cultured vegetable fermented foods
if it's if it's a vinegar-based one i
wouldn't
i wouldn't have it vinegar is bad it
just is
okay now if you're eating a fermented
food because you're looking for the
microorganisms those microorganisms are
not the microorganisms that give us life
those are the ones
that end up on things that died right
because because a fermented vegetable
means it died
right it's not like you picked parsley
out of in
this book right here the new edition
okay revised and expanded the new
edition
talks about elevated biotics when you
grow your own parsley
you guys this is critical information
this is a goodie
when you grow your own parsley okay even
if it's just
one little tiny sprig
that you grew yourself on your
windowsill okay
just just remember this lorraine l's
here tonight amazing
just remember this okay when you grow
that parsley microorganisms
end up on the parsley they're called
elevated biotics
they end up on the parsley it's like a
miracle they appear
on the parcel you stick it outside on
your porch microorganisms
the kind that sit inside your helium you
should read about it in medical medium
new edition what you can learn instead
everybody's chasing fermented foods
after the death the death
micro microorganisms they appear on
things that
die when something dies right
when a body dies all that stuff starts
happening when an
animal dies all this stuff starts
happening it's all microorganisms that
we
that don't do anything for us except for
devour
things that have died and that's the
mess up with fermented foods and i talk
about
why people do why fermented foods is so
old in culture right
it's ancient it was to survive crops so
because
at the end of the year you died if you
didn't have any food throughout the
winter
so you had to throw everything you had
in the garden in a giant
vat in hopes to god that it preserves
through a process of the micro
microorganisms just eating away at it
right just keeping that
slop that stinky slop alive that
fermented slop alive right
and then you think the the
microorganisms are giving you all this
stuff but that's not how it works
it's just a preserved technique for for
villages 2 000 years ago that knew there
would be no food for the winter i took
all about it in here
suzanna asked for a half file of blood
being drawn tech asked if i was
following mm
that's insane yes
she was the first follower i found
locally
we were both so excited to find each
other through him
uh susannah can you tell the tech i said
hi
hello yeah susannah said i can call you
i just want to tell you personally thank
you for actually
following mm stuff info life saving info
thank you for actually being on board
with the half files thank you for
helping susanna
thank you i love you for it alexandra
why would someone without a thyroid have
hashimoto's antibodies
exactly why would they
the reason why they would is because
hashimoto's thyroiditis is nothing like
anybody knows
hashimoto's thyroiditis is a mystery to
medical research and science
they don't know what it is okay but
it's epstein-barr virus thyroid or no
thyroid you're still going to have the
epstein-barr virus
see the epstein-barr virus caused the
thyroid to begin with
we end up having your thyroids removed
because of epstein-barr
that's how how it works epstein-barr
gets into the thyroid causes thyroid
problems thyroid diseases thyroid
conditions we end up losing thyroids
many times we don't have a thyroid
anymore afterwards and then
we end up still keeping the epstein bar
it's in her system and that's why it's
critical
to work on healing it take this to your
doctor if you want the medical medium
revised and expanded if you guys don't
have this book you should get it
get it free of the library if you don't
want to buy it it's um
suzanna half filed blood amazing
you know that's a whole big gigantic
vial but not that big i've seen them do
tubes this big just one tube like i've
seen them do 12
tubes this big but but
but they'll take 70 milliliters they'll
take easily they'll take five vials six
vial seven vials boom boom boom boom
raw reiki i tried celery juice years ago
but it gave me
all my bad food intolerance symptoms huh
i tried celery juice years ago but it
gave me
all my bad food intolerance symptoms
now i'm trying it again along with some
apple and pineapple i hope it will help
hello yeah
yeah i'm putting pineapple and apple in
my celery juice
yeah i thought it'd be a great idea
even though what even though aw in his
book says just don't mix it with
anything
but it might help it's gonna make the
celery juice not work really so the
celery just won't work
okay all right
what do i do all right i gotta hang up
so what i would do is i if um
be your own detective what else was
happening in your life
what else was going on what else were
you eating
did you pick up some type of
bug everybody's picking bugs up left and
right
streptococcus here extra staff here
extra e coli here
what what was happening in your life
very important to know
and who said it was giving you
intolerances
uh uh that's
interesting all in its own okay like
who said it was giving anybody
intolerances in general right
when it's amazing the all cat all the
food intolerance um
all the food intolerant tolerance tests
all the food sensitivity tests
all of that are never accurate they've
never been accurate
they're still not going to be accurate
right so what was happening in your life
whether what other foods were you doing
were you under some kind of enormous
stress what happened before it was where
you do nutritional yeast where you do an
acv where you're doing
all these different things what were you
doing and um
all these things have to be accounted
for all these things
michelle l michelle i just want to thank
you for all the work you're doing like
helping others yeah
yeah michelle i mean i know you're
dealing with trolls and stuff i saw that
i know did you do you see how whacked
out that troll was
see all the crap they were causing yeah
they were saying terrible things
yeah they don't know what it's like to
be sick they don't know anything now i
know
just try not to listen to them keep up
all the good work helping people
because you care like you care like
nobody i've seen out there
care i mean you actually care about
everybody
yeah you care about their symptoms and
everything just know you're awesome
phone call just keeps on phone calls
just keep on coming through
it's it's actually
[Music]
all right um lorraine said michelle
so food intolerances it's important to
know how it works okay it's like
it's okay so your food intolerance
specialist
doesn't know why you're sick okay
doesn't know why people have lupus lyme
disease
ms tingles and numbness aches and pains
vertigo dizziness tinnitus
burning skin jaw pain neck pain back
pain
all mysterious eczema psoriasis
surprises already
vitiligo rosacea uh the list goes on and
on
and on and on all right just keep the
list going on to another 100 autoimmune
conditions right
but what they'll do is like well that
problem you're having must be that
celery juice it's it's
we got to keep this in mind too on how
it works too
celery juice also destroys pathogens if
you're high on the bar of pathogens
celery juice is knocking those pathogens
back you want to know more about celery
juice and stuff
you guys check out the revised new
edition if you guys don't have the book
really narashini
we love you too michelle
see cindy lou's here tonight
cindy lose like from what i can tell in
comments when i read them she's working
on some foods too she's
tight with her foods um
where's meditate for love that's what
i'm wondering too
i don't see you meditate for love
so i got some stew going on
i wonder what utensil i should use for
it
emma mono eating cleanse now dot dot dot
three weeks dot dot feel i'm healing
amazing emma amazing blown away
blown away hey courtney made it here
linda miner hello aw love the book
hey that makes me happy because
you love the book it you know
i put all this everything i got with
spirit of compassion of me into the
books and
we we want you to heal so
you have the book and love it too
natasha amazing so i'm going to cut up a
cabbage in a minute you guys
i'm going to chop up some parsley yeah
i'm going to chop up some parsley soon i
think let me just take a look at this
stew
the stew is cooking down oh yeah the
stew stew's cooking down
yep this is a stew
it's cooking if you guys just got here i
got a stew going watch it from the
beginning if you can
all right nicole said you have to be
exhausted dealing with all the
misinformation that people are believing
and have having to constantly clear up
the misinformation
and on top of it dealing with trolls
okay very interesting you know when you
take a look at medical medium book one
right
that word misinformation is is is in
here okay
all my articles all my blog posts
everything had the word misinformation
because
for years all my lectures were
misinformation
misinformation right all my lectures the
nightshade fear misinformation
um the lectin thing misinformation like
everything's misinformation right i used
it usually used it
i used it with the conventional system
really
like chickenpox is shingles
says the medical system
wrong well
yeah head the medical system yeah that's
us
yeah yeah we believe chickenpox is the
shingles
that's what we tell everybody yeah
it's not what do you mean it's not
they're two different viruses
huh i didn't know that shingles and
chickenpox are not the same
they're two different viruses if the
medical system can make a mistake that
easy and brainwash
generations of people so that your
grandparents go
go uh shingles
that's the chickenpox right yeah eleanor
that's the chickenpox
you know and what happens is for that
this is misinformation it's everywhere
right now
here's what's happening there's this new
health movement coming up
they're spawned out of misinformation
never before
and now they're throwing back my word
when no one used that word
i obviously don't own that word
misinformation but it's the one i used
in the health scene
no one used the word i used it for years
in health misinformation right
and now they're like medical medium stop
with your misinformation i'm like
dude what and that's what's happening
it's actually deranged
it can tire you out but what are you
gonna do there's a
there's a lot of just you know this is
great denise says love your books also
how long does it take to heal on your
protocols
some people heal like this it
everybody's different
i'll tell you why everybody's different
because you may have something else
happening you may have
a streptococcus a different variety you
may have an epstein-barr a different
variety
you may have a shingles and epson bar
and some mercury you may have
copper no mercury and some aluminum
meaning low in the mercury
you may be high in aluminum high in
copper
low in mercury right and then have a
little bit of lead
okay someone might have a bug that's a
little bit more annoying
a little bit more aggressive one of the
60 varieties of epsilon bar
someone might have three varieties of
epstein-barr someone might have a
simplex
a cytomegalovirus three varieties of
epstein-barr two shingles varieties
three streptococcus and and a
whole bunch of mercury and just mercury
right
low on some other stuff and someone
might have emotional hardships
someone else might have financial
hardships someone else might have
different pathogens different toxins
somebody might have more pesticides
herbicides fungicides somebody might be
living in a place with air fresheners
and scented candles
somebody might be working in a gas
station and they breathe in gas and get
it on their hands every day
it's it's it's an endless combination
right someone might be eating lots of
eggs every single day and someone might
not be eating many at
all it matters someone might be doing a
lot of caffeine throughout their life
and someone else might not be doing any
caffeine throughout their life okay
do you see what i'm saying this is what
matters so why
why does all this matter it all matters
because the medical medium books are
geared with a thousand protocols
to take somebody to the end for one you
can get rid of your eggs your dairy
products your gluten
right you can go to another level get
rid of your pork
your tuna and your corn you can go to
another level
get rid of soy lamb seafood
canola oil palm oil corn oil sapphire or
sapphire
safflower oil soybean oil vegetable oil
right you can go to another level
get rid of your acv your fermented foods
your caffeine your chocolate you can go
to another level get rid of all grains
except for some millet and some oats
get rid of all oils right because you
can you can
customize your protocol then you can do
the 28 day cleanse right
you can do the 369 advanced you can do
the 369 original
you can do a mono eating cleanse for
digestive problems
you can then work with supplementation
right open the book
okay you're in here now i just landed on
pcos
right so now i'm in pcos here we are
you know reproductive cysts or not the
cysts
and in the high androgen right so here
we are we're on pcos and i'm looking
here and i'm seeing well you got the 32
ounces of celery juice which is critical
and you'll see the right supplementation
you'll see cat's claw
that's what you'll see hmm very
interesting
you'll see some curcumin which i don't
have right here in front of me
you'll see um some glutathione you'll
see
lemon balm right all this is vimergy
what i use
that's just what i use someone said the
other day oh you like to show the energy
products
what do you want me to do is what i use
do you want me to get
a junkie supplement somewhere
and show that every day and hide what i
use i mean doesn't make any sense and
i'm not sponsored i'm just saying
um anyway there's no preservatives no
alcohol in these the quality is
incredible and that's the whole point
and um no natural flavors but anyway so
this is the vimergy so that's the
vimergy lemon balm it's in here so for
pcos
you got the lemon balm right you've got
the ly
scene for pcos there it is
it shows dosages you got um
the micro c right well it's vitamin c
but i
i like the micro c right you got the
micro c so i got that
i'm just saying you go through here
there's there's you can start with one
thing in the supplements list you can
start with just celery
but that's the whole point you can go as
far as you need to go but if you're
going to use
supplements that aren't good or high
quality then that's going to slow you
down too you see the differences
somebody could be like i tried that
meanwhile you look it's like they tried
that
hello yeah i'm a fly
uh-huh i'm annoying
yeah yeah i buzz around
what does it sound like uh
[Music]
is that annoying yeah i know what do i
do
yeah i sit on the wall yeah did you see
the supplements she was using
did you see those uh-huh they had
alcohol in them i know
i know i'm a fly yeah i'm on the wall
uh-huh i'm annoying did you see the
supplement that had acacia gum in it
and natural flavors uh-huh i saw that
because i'm a fly i'm in the wall i'm on
the wall
uh-huh i got close to the stove and
almost got burnt
yeah yeah my wings got singed uh-huh
that's right i was trying to get a
better look at everything i saw all
these bad supplements in the cupboard
yeah but here's what's funny right the
person's not healing
uh huh and then i heard the person on
the phone telling their friend
that they were gonna say on social media
how medical medium
doesn't work uh-huh but meanwhile they
had all this stuff in the cupboard
including apple cider vinegar and then i
saw them down
a whole bunch of nutritional yeast they
put it on their salad
and there were a couple of hard-boiled
eggs on their salad too i know
and then yeah and they're gonna say that
medical medium doesn't work because
they're just doing celery
uh-huh and they're doing like a couple
of things
yeah i know i'm a fly okay
um
and then what about the high fat too
it's another thing you know
be open-hearted glad you're here tonight
um
anyway i gotta i gotta put some cabbage
in here you guys
i got some stew going that's stew
that stew man that stew cooked down
quick whoa
that stew cooked down real quick let me
get some cabbage in this dude
[Music]
that that stew just
that stew just really cooked down quick
the smell of cabbage is something else
isn't it you guys
the smell of cabbage
that stew's pumping i'm gonna pop some
dill in here real quick
[Music]
guys i'm gonna pop some parsley in here
too spear with me
now what you want to do is wait to the
see the cabbage softens up a little bit
you guys see that sorry about this
yeah i ate up a lot of that broth i had
that thing on real high just letting you
guys know i'm gonna put a little parsley
in here
amazing
that stew is good it's really done it's
just not as liquidy like
a bowl of liquid but there's liquid on
the bottom um
so it's a thick stew you know which
actually is what i like
uh kimberly said kimberly miller says
she's coming over my house for dinner
amazing um because i i got to share this
dish with somebody so
if you're interested in stoning and
estonian stew
you might not like it um
and then what about other things too you
know a lot of people are doing a lot of
steps it all depends like
all these factors matter what about
medications what about benzos
you'll find somebody that they've been
on like a lot of benzos and it's like
they want to heal fast but it takes a
little more time
see there's there's there's but that's
the thing and i talk about all these
things like
in the cleanse of heal book i talk about
the medications you know i talk about
that too
the medications and cleanse the heal
right
this stew looks so good i'm actually
going to put it in a bowl
incredible pumped about it
and a lot of people do a lot of radical
fat lorraine l says i like thicker stews
too
awesome awesome lorraine and that coming
from you
is is is a big deal to me
it is coming from you is a big deal to
me
yep
um i got some stew right here
i'm putting it in a bowl
estonian stew i'm gonna put some fresh a
little bit of fresh more
fresh parsley right on top i'm gonna
move this cabbage
right you guys you guys um
i'm gonna put a little fresh parsley
right on top over it
which is something i like to do you
don't have to do that though
that's the stew right here estonians do
it's really hearty
really good now here's here's what i
recommend if you're an animal protein
person
you don't even need to have animal
protein that night this thing's gonna
hold you
over and then some you know
even more than animal protein really if
you're a plant-based
person you don't have to put a whole
bunch of fat in this this is fat-free
now if um
that's the whole point we're keeping the
radical fats out so i'm keeping the
nut butters the oils i'm keeping all
that out i'm keeping the avocado out i'm
keeping
nuts and seeds out i'm keeping you know
meat and
and chicken out i'm keeping dairy
products out keeping butter out
just keeping the fat out right you don't
need to have the fat this is a healing
healing
um so i talk about the pandemic
and i just saw a pandemic someone's
asking about it talk about
um the plague in here
talk about the plague in here okay it's
got
just the the really most solid
solid based information you could ever
find on the play
the amount of crap i've heard out there
since it started has been just utterly
ridiculous
so this is really this is really a spot
where you can you can
hear about this and this is about
healing after the plague
this is about healing if you've you had
the plague or you you
know somebody that had it or you know
and you're beaten down from it and then
you get the reactivated epstein-barr
and that's that information comes
originally from medical medium so you'll
hear it talked about out there
you guys i'm heading over to
deb mac i heal tendinitis vertigo high
blood pressure acid reflux of an mm
protocol incredible
i did not use any supplements am
committed to doing celery juice daily
that's the thing
heavy metal detox smoothie and no eggs
gluten or dairy and reduced all fats you
see how that's the route you took
with the medical medium information and
someone else they might have to add a
few more
they might have to add a few supplements
they might have to do a little bit more
here or a little bit more here but the
information's in the books
to actually make it so you can you can
customize and what you did deb
is you customized your protocol that's
what you did
incredible incredible you guys
i'm going to ig and i'm going to tick
tock
just know i love you guys made the stew
talked about some good stuff
clay says that's in the original medical
medium book the corona
no i'm talking about the new edition
revised and expanded so this isn't the
original book
this is part of the original book with a
whole big book
put into it this is
this is a new book this is what this is
okay instagram and tick tock right now
love you guys
go in there now okay are you coming with
me gonna be ig on ig and tick tock