right now
live on rumble
youtube facebook tick tock telegram i'm
excited you guys day one medical medium
anti-bug
challenge do you have the book
critical piece of the puzzle right here
is having the book and if you don't you
don't that's fine it's fine
get the book free at the library you can
walk into a library somewhere ask for it
get it for free that way
amazon incredible sale on this book
particularly on this book and that's
16.99 51
off right now which is it's incredible
because it costs more to print it not
just more a lot more to print it it's a
heavy medical textbook it's packed with
information just giving a rundown on
this a little bit it's got the anti-bug
cleanse in it which we're doing now
we're day one of that it's also got the
mono cleanses wow the healing people do
with the mono cleanses in here is
amazing right
i mean it's incredible it's got the
heavy metal detox cleanse getting metals
out saving lives that way it's got the
369 advanced original it's got all that
in here too 200 symptoms in condition 75
recipes i'm making a recipe today i'm
doing the potato salad i am pumped you
see i got my stuff out here i got some
radishes that's a healing food right
there i got radishes i got garlic i got
cucumbers i got parsley i got chives
we're day one we got the medical medium
cleanse heel book in our hand okay this
is a life-saving book the street cred is
there
okay
facts are in so many people healing
around the world with this book saving
lives you wouldn't believe how many
people are getting that fresh start you
know fresh start oh i didn't know i had
10 lives you know i thought i only had
nine lives like a cat now i got 10 lives
i got my life back i was able to get my
life back
that's how important this book is you
guys i'm excited
we're in the cleanse
what level did you choose did you choose
level one level two level three level
four or did you choose level five did
you choose level five plus bonus
that's one thing i had to mention right
there are you making the meal with me
are you guys making the meal with me is
this cool or what are we doing the
potato salad i got some potatoes right
here okay these are these are still hot
i cut them in half but these are hot
rusted potatoes we're making the potato
salad
if anyone has potato fear
fear no more
because
they're so healing they're anti-viral
they're anti-bug
it's important to know there's no
guessing games here like oh wait is this
bad for you is this good for you
is this bad for you by the way
uh later on 6 15 so making an
announcement 6 15 eastern
3 15
pacific i'm doing a rumble so it's just
a rumble exclusive okay
and i'm gonna throw some zingers in
there it's gonna be an exclusive rumble
i'm talking about
possibly oxalates and some other stuff
you don't wanna miss it it's gonna be
really fun okay so rumble.com forward
slash medical medium and i just want to
let you know okay if you have a hard
time catching me live
right at that time that exclusive time
refresh is what you do
okay or shut it down and start it back
up because i could be a minute late or
it's because it's a brand new
it's a brand new uh stream situation
they have at rumble okay they just
started streaming lives all right
look for the top video
at the top for the video and then you
could refresh and so forth but check it
out when you get a chance if you have
any difficulties with that so
are you guys making the
um recipe with me i'm gonna do that in a
little bit so
let's talk about
why we're even doing this
why even bother why are we doing this
why are we doing the anti-blood cleanse
what's the point
and what are we cleansing
what are we even doing
here's the first thing we're doing is
we're getting rid
of bug
fuel
you know how your car takes fuel your
car needs fuel so you can drive maybe
you got an electric car
and your car still needs fuel because
that battery's going to go dead so you
got to charge the battery
whether you have to charge the battery
you've got to put gasoline or you've got
to put diesel in a truck whatever it is
it needs fuel
and that's important to know right it
needs fuel well bugs need fuel
the bugs that make you sick
need fuel
everybody's loaded with bad
bugs and if you think it's a parasite
for some reason you've been brainwashed
in in a sense of the parasite world
right from the old parasite cleanse
thing and parasite knowledge thing then
fine think it's a parasite
then let's starve the parasite okay but
what's really happening is people have
bacteria they have lots of viruses
lots of viruses inside of them
and if you're somebody just came on here
and you're like what do you mean viruses
like what viruses what are you talking
about right fever blisters cold sores
viruses simplex herpes too right simply
right
boom viruses okay h pylori bacteria
and then you know of shingles virus
and e coli bacteria staph bacteria right
and we have all these bugs inside of us
we just do and they sit inside of a
strep throat maybe had strep throat at
one time maybe had mono at one time
here's the thing
and medical medium information brought
this to the world right if you had mono
so if you had mono at some time in your
life
you may not even know you had it and you
had it
that bug is the epstein bar and it comes
back later
it comes back later with fibromyalgia it
comes back later with chronic fatigue
syndrome hashimoto's thyroiditis
hyperthyroidism
nodule cysts tumors on the thyroid
that's epstein-barr rheumatoid arthritis
lyme disease all these things
neurological lyme are viral caused right
so it's important to know so why are we
doing this
we're doing this because your eczema is
viral cause your psoriasis is viral
caused okay your your skin conditions
viral caused vitiligo is viral caused
your fibrosis your lupus your multiple
sclerosis your als there's a lot of
stuff and metals play a role too i've
talked all about that for years you guys
know that but viruses play this huge
role including anxiety upping the game
with crippling anxiety
so it's metals and viruses but viruses
need to eat
and bugs need to eat if you had chronic
sinusitis
if you got sinus sensitivities if you
had sinus surgeries that's streptococcus
that strep needs to eat so it'll sit
inside of you and percolate if you get
bronchitis if you get chronic coughs if
you've got mucus in your lungs that's
that chronic strep you have the strep
throat chronic strep bacterial vaginosis
utis bladder infections kidney
infections right sty's conjunctivitis
that's streptococcus
acne
any of you guys deal with acne on and
off throughout your life
that's streptococcus that's strep that's
the original strap from childhood that's
the original strap that you you you had
when you were younger okay and you got
the acne from that strap and maybe you
have more than one variety of strap so
we're doing the anti-bunk cleanse right
there i got the book we'll talk about
the different levels
so
it's important
to know
that these bugs sit inside of us
diverticulosis
diverticulitis we got some bugs it's e
coli and strep eating away at pockets
inside your intestinal tract you see
acid reflux boom lots of bugs causing
that the acid reflux so we have to
realize that all your problems
all your problems
unless you were somebody that got
drenched in some kind of toxic chaotic
pesticide or something and and that hits
your nervous system and did some
physical damage
all your problems
really stem from
those bugs so it's the bugs this is the
anti-bug
cleanse
you see how it makes so much sense you
see how important it really is
when you really add it up right there
guys we're live right now telegram we're
live on rumble we're live on
youtube facebook tick tock so we got it
all going on we're day one of the
medical medium anti-bug cleanse i'm
making the potato salad in a couple of
minutes i'm hoping you guys make it with
me i got my cucumbers do you guys have
those ready i got this the radishes do
you guys have those ready
i got garlic
um i got my lemon right here
i got the parsley i got the chives i got
the potatoes and you know what i even
have some nice steamed asparagus you can
use raw asparagus if you want i steam
these so i got the steamed asparagus
okay it's better like that you know for
this makes it nice and comforting okay
and if you're doing this cleanse you
know about the celery juice i made this
earlier right here so you got your 16
ounces of celery juice i'm doing 32 you
can do 32.
that's in the mix right lemon water
you're drinking your lemon water you're
doing that okay you can sip coconut
water but drink at least 32 ounces lemon
water to a liter
making sure you're doing that daily make
sure you're drinking some water so you
flush out those dead
bugs
you want to flush out the dead bugs okay
so that's important
whatever level you pick you're gonna
kill more bugs
so whatever level you pick you're gonna
kill more bugs are you picking level one
okay
are you picking level two
which one are you doing right
are you just here for the show are you
just here to hang out and chill to
perfectly fine you'll learn some
information maybe you'll do the anti
bugs book lens someday maybe you'll get
the book so you can take care of
yourself right
but the goal
is to starve
the bugs
they go hungry
once they go hungry
they start
to implode
that's how bugs work they need fuel all
the time what are you feeding your bugs
are you feeding your bugs some eggs
you feed because that's the number one
bug fuel right there you feed you guys
on telegram you feeding your bugs i'm
like did you have some eggs the other
day anybody anybody eating some eggs you
feeding though you feeding those buggies
the eggs huh here you go little buggies
here you go and have some fried eggs
right here okay
wait a minute did you just do a
hard-boiled egg what was it a heart you
thought you were outsmarting everybody
so you just did hard-boiled eggs how
many people i see
out there they got their salad going
their little salad they take their
hard-boiled eggs they crack the shells
off and they think they're eating really
healthy keto or something they're
cutting up their egg slices they're
putting it in their salad and they're
feeding their bugs and they're
guaranteeing guaranteeing
a ticket
in badlands down the road
look
everybody gets sick we're in a different
world now
nobody goes the whole way through
without getting sick
and sicker and sicker
we're in a different place in a
different time frame in history we're in
a different world
you don't want to keep on feeding your
bugs you want to learn how to stop
feeding your bugs
that's what you want to do
okay
lactose free dairy still feeds the bugs
keep that in mind you guys a little note
right there lactose free dairy still
feeds the bugs the protein
in lactose free dairy
feeds the bugs
keep that in mind right there really
important to know so dairy protein will
feed the bugs
so
the goal is
to starve out and kill off the bugs
what level are you doing to do that if
you do level one that's okay you get rid
of eggs you get rid of dairy products
you get rid of gluten
get rid of soft drinks too you know why
a lot of soft drinks will have that corn
syrup that gmo corn syrup which is a bug
fuel
all right that's a grain that feeds the
bugs okay
and
you can do level one you can do that
right
and that's fine
level two is another level now keep in
mind
you take food away from the bugs
they go hungry
and they're gonna make
you
very
emotionally hungry for that food so bugs
control
our
habits
our habits once you start destroying
those bugs keep this in mind you guys
once you start
it gets hard it gets hard it's all of a
sudden once you start killing off those
bugs it gets hard it's like
i'm gonna make a dozen egg omelet now
because once i start killing off those
bugs and they start dying in me okay and
once those bugs start dying
right you see that in telegram you guys
tick tock
to rumble once those bugs start dying
you're going to want to make a dozen egg
omelet
and put some cheese on top too
and you're going to want to cook that
those babies in butter on a nice skillet
because
the bugs are going to talk for you
they're going to talk for you is what
they're going to do they're going to say
i'm hungry
i'm hungry wait oh my god you're
starving me
you're starving me
you're starving me hey um susan
susan
jennifer
um
stephen hey
uh
jack
i'm hungry
you're hurting me
you're hurting me and that's what's
gonna happen they're gonna do that you
don't know that's what they're doing
you don't know they're talking to you
but you're gonna make you crazy like i'm
hungry order a pizza
so the key is
we're not on a deprivation
cleanse
keep that in mind
we're not on a deprivation
cleanse
this isn't deprivation this is eating so
if you guys aren't eating
then i don't know where you are
i don't know where you are
i think you arrived at the wrong place
or you wouldn't i think
i think you're in the wrong cleanse
if you guys are not eating
and decided not to eat all day
we're in the wrong i think you're in the
wrong room
thank you you entered the wrong room
because we're eating and we're making a
meal and we're making i'm hoping you
guys had some fruit i'm hoping you guys
had your fruit smoothies i'm hoping you
guys had your maybe you had your heavy
metal detox movies maybe some of you
guys are already on your monoclines
maybe you're on a 369 but i hope you
guys are eating
because this isn't about deprivation
it's not about starving you
it's about starving the pathogens the
bugs that's why it's the anti-blood
cleanse
that's why
how are the bugs coming out of the body
poop and pee
that's how they're coming out
poop
pee
that's how they come out they also come
out of here
when you're sleeping
they come out of the eyes
they're not crawling out of the eyes
that's not how they do it
the dead bug aparts can come out in just
tears
not when you're crying or anything but
you know the sandman you know the
sandman right you got all that gunk in
your eyes and stuff it can come out in
there
it can come right out in there it can
come out of your nose got to blow my
nose a few times it can come out of
there
and of course poop and pee right
so
that's how the bugs come out so it's
interesting
and one of the ways the bugs come out i
want to give you a better you know what
you guys let me give you a better
description of how it comes out okay
your liver is filled with bugs i'm going
to bring the bring it over here a little
bit all right can i move these cucumbers
over and
you guys don't mind right move things
over
and
all right
so
our livers is where a lot of the bugs
are happening so that's the party town
that's where it's happening that's party
zone right here party central four bugs
it's in the liver
different varieties of epstein-barr
streptococcus inside the liver hhv-6
hhv7 you guys you wouldn't believe how
many bugs people have they'll have hhv-6
hhv-7 they'll have two varieties of
epsom bar they'll have a shingles
they'll have a cytomegalovirus all
sitting inside their liver waiting to
give you health throughout your whole
life
and so it's in here a lot of these bugs
so here's what's happening all that food
you eat so if you eat an egg just let's
use an egg as an example right
if you're eating an egg
the egg goes down into your intestinal
tract
particles from that egg
micro particles from that egg get sucked
up through the hepatic portal vein into
your liver the hepatic portal vein is
attached to the intestinal tract
you guys there's a vein that goes from
the intestinal tract to the liver a vein
okay and what happens is those egg
particles get sucked up the vein and go
right up into the liver
and then the bugs feed off of the eggs
inside your liver so when you're having
your eggs
you're just filling your liver up with
egg particles and feeding the bugs
happy happy are they
right
here's what happens you start to starve
them you don't feed them with their used
to be what they're used to eating
the weak ones
die first
so the weak epstein bar
the weak streptococcus the weak sediment
virus
the weak hpv
the weak
hiv
these bugs start to die first and then
they shoot up
the bile duct out of the liver into
the gallbladder
and back into the intestinal tract and
then you poop them out
you don't hear that at the doctor's
office do you
you don't hear that at the alternative
people's offices you don't hear that in
anybody's books you don't hear that
anywhere it's all mm info it's why
people heal
so
the bugs aren't coming out through your
sweat
keep that in mind
they come out through other passageways
they have to be direct like your
nostrils
they come out through your eyes
they can come out sometimes
through the ears
but they mostly come out
through the intestinal tract and your
kidneys letting you know
we're inside bug cleanse we're day one
if you guys just came on here i
recommend watching this from the
beginning everything is vital pertinent
and important the information is
critical
i'm get just let me give you a small
announcement right here i'm going to be
on rumble exclusively at 6 15 eastern
time 3 15 pacific time it's going to be
a private talk on rumble exclusive there
make sure you're there okay another
thing to
make sure you have the book through
these cleanses or if you don't have it
now get one critical okay
16.99 amazon.com us it's on sale i call
it divine intervention angelic
intervention because they priced the
book for some reason
and you know what it's possibly priced
at this low to actually try to hurt me
or something right because there's so
much discrimination against medical
meaning for a lot of reasons because
being the number one health author in
the world for almost seven years running
has gotten so many people mad it's
ridiculous right because because people
heal that's why
and and that's why the books have been
out there because so many people healed
but they lowered the price
on this book i call it like divine
intervention
um
probably thinking they'll just hurt my
pocket or something like hey he won't
get his 10 cents we're gonna make sure
that we under price it so he doesn't
live
and can't pay the light bill but the
point is
is what's incredible about it because it
costs way more to print what's
incredible about them doing that right
on amazon.com us is you can get this
medical textbook for nothing practically
so it's 16.99 get it now if you can or
get it free at the library this is an
incredible opportunity when you see this
book you'll be mind blown i know you
guys that do have it it's helped you so
much saved a lot of lives already around
the world but i just want to let people
know that that's where the anti-bug
cleanse is
this isn't the only time i'm going to do
the anti-bug cleanse with you guys i'm
probably going to do it again
so
i have the book so it's there for that
too glad to see you guys it's uh health
with liz says it's definitely a steal um
yeah i mean it's incredible right so
we're talking about getting rid of the
bugs i gave you guys a run down on the
liver where the bugs sit and how it can
spew up back into your bile out your
intestinal tract and you poop out the
bugs
the weak bugs die first the stronger
they're going to be talking to you
that's what they're going to be doing
the stronger bugs are going to be
talking to you and they're going to be
telling you break your cleanse break
your cleanse fast
start eating a whole bunch of chocolate
bars so you can get your adrenaline
running and which because adrenaline's
not good either too much adrenaline that
whole adrenaline thing can can lower the
immune system and the bugs love that too
so they'll be like eat lots of chocolate
drink lots of coffee do you know do do
eat eat a lot of dairy eat some cheese
you know make sure you're doing
nutritional yeast your bugs are going to
be talking and trying to get you to eat
things so let's talk about the different
levels
and
and if you guys just came on here i'm
glad you're coming on because we're
going to be making a recipe i hope some
of you guys make it with me too
all right
level one
level one is remove eggs
milk cheese butter which is dairy remove
gluten remove soft drinks that's number
one
boom that's it level one
who's doing that
level one right there
if you want to take it to the next level
remove pork right so remove pork okay
remove some pork there's piggy right
here
right there's piggy
remove pork remove tuna
right there tuna
definitely tik tok you guys tuna keep
the tuna fish out i know so many people
love their tuna salads they love their
tuna sandwiches completely understand
completely understand
sushi
you're not eating something healthy when
you have sushi news newsflash newsflash
newsflash you're not eating healthy when
you have sushi you're not eating healthy
when you have sushi
you know the spicy apple drink spicy
apple
juice is that you guys i heated this up
and i actually made a nice spicy hot
apple juice right
and i think it's starting to kick in
all right
you're not eating healthy with sushi
it's loaded with vinegar
okay
you can get some you can get some bugs
it's loaded with mercury
so that's okay corn
corn keep the corn out
keep it out no cork corn tortillas no
corn taco shells no corn no popcorn
where did my popcorn go again
bring it out later no popcorn keep it
out
right
it's gmo all of it even the organic
stuff keep it out
so that's level two level two is what we
talked about eggs dairy gluten soft
drinks and now tuna pork corn that's
level two you guys doing level three
who's doing no nachos question mark
yeah if you want to do level two no not
you nachos but if you do level one you
can do nachos
yeah if you do level one if you do level
one where you just take out the eggs the
dairy and everything then you probably
could
it's still gonna feed some bugs oh wait
wait
your nachos might have cheese on it no
you can't do nachos
not even on level one
there goes that no nachos out the window
level three who's doing level three this
is when now you get rid of industrial
food oils
vegetable oil palm oil canola oil corn
oil safflower oil soybean oil you get
rid of soy and you get rid of lamb right
and then you get rid of lamb
does a lamb do that or is this a sheep
are they the same are they different
we get rid of lamb
okay
that's the next thing it's important get
rid of the lamb
so that's the next thing there
the next thing
fish
get rid of fish
and all seafood but you can have salmon
trout or sardines
salmon trout or sardines so on level
three you can actually eat some salmon
you can have some trout you can have
some sardines you can't have the egg on
this plate you guys i got a lot of
different egg props over here you can't
have the egg but you can have the salmon
you can't have industrial oils on the
salmon
but you can have the salmon on level
three i mean how cool is that
right
and you need to read the troublemaker
foods chapter always read that in this
book that's critical so if you guys just
came on here i want you to watch us from
the beginning we're talking about a lot
of incredible pertinent information
critical information this is about
taking control over your health
i'm not doing this for a song and dance
to have some fun like okay we're having
fun we're having fun let's go do this
i'm a superstar i love being on camera
that's why i'm doing this i'm doing this
to try to save lives
i'm doing this because it's critical to
take control over your health i don't
want you guys sick i don't want you guys
suffering i don't want you guys
struggling anymore i know many of you
come here it's your first time and
you're like you guys you're many of you
are brainwashed and when you come here
you're going to come here so brainwashed
i saw a comment earlier today on youtube
and it was something like
you don't know anything about fats
aw you know nothing about fats it's
omega-6s that are the bad ones and you
know omega-3s are critical
fats high-fat diets are amazing for us
you don't know anything about healthy
fats
you just don't get it
and you know when i read that i was like
okay first of all you don't get it
because that's vegan doctor information
that's outdated and antiquated
okay because yeah sure okay omega-6s
aren't the best fat but when it comes
down to
making
like
the break of health in a sense of making
that break in your life like getting to
that finish line crossing that finish
line like getting better from severe
chronic illness any fat will take you
down
and what people don't realize
is that the fats
stop your nerves your nerve cells from
receiving nutrients
that they need
including glucose so you can recover
from multiple sclerosis als chronic
fatigue syndrome fibromyalgia lupus and
so much more neurological lyme so if
you're not so sick and you you hear some
antiquated outdated information about
how good fats are for you and how it's
just the omega-6s like sunflower oil you
need to look out for you're totally
behind
this is
advanced information yeah if you're
coming from a standard american diet or
standard european diet you come from
just a junk food diet and you go and you
eat a healthy keto diet plant-based or
animal protein you're going to see
benefits
but if you're somebody who's really sick
and you're going down and out for the
count and you can't function and you
can't feed your kids or you can't work
or you can't drive your car and you're
on mattress island
any fat will stop you from healing
so
i love when someone tries to school me
like i don't know something they give me
outdated antiquated information some
from some vegan doctor that just doesn't
even know why anybody's sick but you
know what that's just the way it goes
the point is
and where i'm going here right
is that
this is about no knowledge and it's
about taking control of your health and
anybody new here and coming here
i'm not trying to lecture you guys on
this anybody new here are coming here
you're going to be like what
what bugs i don't have any bugs huh
um
remove what he's removing
what uh healthy food
uh you know and this is good for flu
this is good for flu this is good for
plague this is good for the play going
around this is good for all of that but
again because a lot of new people come
on board and they don't know they're
just like okay what's he even talking
about you guys just came here just now
we're day one of the anti-bug cleanse
we're in cleanse the heel right now
okay and
you know look you know what's amazing
for years i watched people in an
alternative health movement not even no
viruses existed
didn't even know they just like
didn't even know
so many patients coming in now their
offices they write books they just
didn't know they think it's maybe you're
creating it or something you're creating
your sickness
and then the and then the supernatural
believing people they're just like you
chopped you had your head chopped off
you drowned in a river back in 1804 and
you came back again and the reason why
you're sick and having all those
problems at night and restless legs is
because you drowned in your past life
or you were you know you were during you
know king charles and you had your you
know you were tortured in a torture
chamber in a dungeon and you know in
in in 1547
and you know what happens is that like
no one knew why anyone was sick
it's the bugs you guys
even when i did that documentary years
ago i was was was invited to do that
documentary so only one talking about
how viruses were everybody was else is
sick
everybody else is talking about oh it's
your thoughts you just you have lupus
because you thought
you know let me tell you something your
lupus your ms your ms is not because you
created it with your thoughts okay
long-haul covet is not because you
created it with your thoughts
you know
that's epstein-barr long-haul covert
it's epstein-barr being reactivated this
medical medium information so why are we
doing this why are we even here
why are we even here
we're here to take control true
empowerment
we're here to get our health back
we're here to knock out the bugs
hpv is a bug
it's a bug
i know no one wanted to believe it but
people need to know this simplex one
cold sore is a bug it guarantees
someone having trigeminal neurology down
the road and clenching
jaws
acne
is a bug
it's streptococcus and people have loads
of strep in their system eczema is a
bug
important to know
utis are bugs
so we have all these bugs
it's in our system they exist and they
keep you down anytime i've run any time
i've run to anybody that's younger that
has the the cold sore
any time i've ever with anybody to come
to my office over the last 35 years
doctors that talk to me that you know
that know about the cold source right i
always say
that cold sore is going to be trigeminal
neuralgia when you're 55 years old
it always does unless you clean it up
now and kill it off
unless you knock it back and know how to
get rid of it
because you're going to have that teeth
clenching you're gonna need retainers to
stop grinding your teeth
you're gonna get dental work and your
teeth drilled down the road you're gonna
need botox for your nerve pain in your
neck from that simplex one
everybody who has simplex one ends up
getting botox whether they're 60 years
old or they get it when they're 30 they
get botox in their jaw and in their neck
from the pain
because they don't know what it is and
their teeth is clenching and they need
you know they need guards teeth guards
in their mouth look i don't want people
to suffer and struggle
and then the acne thing man it can creep
up and slam you again because that strip
comes back out you clean up your diet
doing some keto cute thing and then boom
you're back to your acne and you don't
know why the bugs are there i want to
stop them in people this is the anti-bug
lens i want people to learn i want them
to grow let's make some potato salad
so i got some potatoes here
i'm going to dump them out and chop them
up a little bit you can take the skins
off if you want i mean you can do that
in the recipe they're peeled back a
little so i'm just removing some of the
skins here
okay i'm just moving stuff around a
little bit you guys
we're day one of the anti-bug cleanse
and i just want to do
a little bit announcement gonna be
exclusive on rumble later
and it's a different talk it's not gonna
be about the cleanse it's a different
talk not quite sure still what i'm gonna
talk about but i'm going to talk about
something
and
i'm just peeling back some of the skins
i cut these steamed potatoes these are
steamed potatoes i cut them in half and
i'm just taking some of the skins skins
are really healthy for you they're so
good for you potato skin so you can keep
them on they're incredible
a lot of a lot of different compounds
antiviral compounds are in the skin too
and in and in the potato itself the
flesh of the potato
this is a cleanse to heal recipe i'm
working on right now this is the potato
salad
you can make a big one if you want if
you're really hungry this isn't about
deprivation you can make this dish and
eat this dish all day you can cook a
whole bunch of potatoes you guys make a
very large portion and eat this you know
for lunch later on for dinner if you
want snack on it a little more if you
wanted to and guess what you're killing
off bugs because you're not feeding the
bugs anything else how incredible is
that when you think about it so i'm just
peeling back a little bit of the skin
right here you guys thank you for being
here at this free cleanse
no one's being charged anything
um i don't want that at all i just want
you guys to have
the freedom to be here
by your choice
wanting answers wanting to do some
healing right
so
i just peeled some of the skin off so it
has a look to it not because the skins
aren't delicious because they really are
i love potatoes love potato skins right
so i'm just going to cut up a few pieces
of these in these like little hunks
these little squares i'm going to pop
these in the bowl
that's what i'm going to do
and
are you guys making it with me some of
you guys or did you already make it you
were probably already really hungry
you're like he's taking too long i'm
gonna make mine now
right
so i'm cutting him like wedges see this
kind of you know cutting them in wedges
right now
it gets all sticky is what it does
they get all sticky
so
so i'm getting them in here
right
cutting them up as quick as i can for
you guys
yes i'm making you're making it with me
lori malone amazing
so
what happens is if you this is a dairy
free dish this is cheese free this is a
cheese free dish this is a dairy free
dish keep that in mind okay
and i'm cutting these up
there's no butter in here now one thing
about potatoes you know why potatoes
become bad
potatoes become bad
when you're adding butter to them that's
when they become a problem somebody
might say oh i have problems with
potatoes
i have you know a lot of issues with
potatoes and that's what i have somebody
might think that
okay
and you can cut in smaller pieces too
somebody might think that because
they're like okay well
you know i'm having problems with
potatoes they don't make me feel good
well this is a steamed potato this is
without
this is without the
butter this is without
the cheese there we go
i might cut them a little bit smaller in
here some of them are still a little bit
bigger right
but i like them hunky
but you can make them smaller if you
want right
i'm gonna thinly slice some radishes
you guys okay with that
i'm cutting off the root of the radish
i'm cutting off the back of the radish
just just for aesthetics of course you
could eat those if you really wanted to
right and i'm just going to basically
thinly slice
some radishes right here the board's
really slick because of the potato
it slicks up the board right
i'm gonna thinly slice some radishes
right here you guys what i love about
this dish it's so good for you these
radishes are really a powerful food
i'm gonna slice them a little thinner
so
nice and thin
look you can be you right you can do it
the way you want to do it i'm just
showing you the recipe the way i like to
do it i like the thin radishes
there we go
but of course you guys
can make it the way you want to
i'm gonna put a little bit more radish
in mine if you guys don't mind
now what i love about the radish
is i talk about it life-changing foods
removing toxic heavy metals it does help
with removing metals
i also love about the radish it's
anti-bug it's anti-viral
the radish is anti-bug anti-viral
so
anti-bacteria
so ulcers people with ulcers
radishes
okay
help to knock out that bacteria you know
people have bacteria all in their mouth
with what about that they have the
bacteria all in their mouth
they're losing their teeth
you know i mean the gums are getting
eaten away they get the cavities but you
know what happens though it's all the
caffeine and the vinegar that weakens
the enamel so bacteria in somebody's
mouth can eat away so easily
everybody gets the reckoning in the
dentist chair doing the caffeine
doing the caffeine for too many years
they get the reckoning in the dentist
chair
the caffeine and the unless you're a
child and you didn't do all the caffeine
you just came in with severe mineral
deficiencies
high levels of mercury too and then that
could happen but you know everybody gets
the reckoning down the road too if their
teeth are pretty good to start with next
thing you know it down the road
i'm doing some thin slices of cucumber
the vinegar and the caffeine really
weaken the enamel so that bacteria can
start eating away what i love about the
radishes i was talking about before with
the radish is the radish does
knock down bacteria in the mouth and
your celery juice does too your celery
just does so i'm putting some pieces of
cucumber in here i'm going to mix this
up too
we're going to get this looking good
be open-hearted says nice slice job
can't believe you think so
amazing
i'm honored okay so i'm gonna chop up a
little bit of parsley here now look you
guys i'm gonna use a little bit more
parsley
so i'm gonna do a little parsley and
then i'm gonna do a little chive right
so i'm gonna do a little bit more
parsley
okay
i'm gonna do a little bit more not a ton
i want the recipe to look all nice but
i'm gonna finely chop
a bunch of parsley here okay
so
i'm gonna do a little
you can do it thicker if you want you
can keep it thicker that's fine
you guys follow me along on telegram
right i'm gonna do a little fine chop
here
pop a little bit of parsley in there i'm
going to chop up some chives now i love
this recipe i don't know about you guys
but i love this recipe
i really do now i'm finely chopping them
but you can do bigger pieces of chives
if you love that but i'm doing a fine
chive chop right
we're making the potato salad
out of the cleanse the heel book
parsley
is such a sell
like
a cell restoring herb i like using it as
a leafy green the nutrients and parsley
are off the charts they haven't even
tapped into it you know food science the
funny thing about food science
right
anything about food science
it hasn't even looked at really any food
there's so many undiscovered
phytochemical compounds in parsley that
bring health back
they haven't even looked or discovered
if you don't know what you're looking
for how do you discover it it takes
years and years and years 100 years from
now they'll still be finding things in
parsley
let's get some parsley on here
boom
right
so we got the parsley on top of this you
guys let me move my apple drink
isn't that better than alcohol
you know no i won't drink apple juice
too much sugar
but let me have a glass of wine
what yummy people
stay away no i'm staying away from sugar
all week oh but i'm going to be having a
glass of wine on saturday night i'll
have a glass of champagne no i hate
sugar i can't eat sugar no i won't drink
any apple juice isn't that bad for you
but i'll have a glass of champagne
hey let me take a look at that cookie
can i have a cookie
my doctor says stay away from apple
juice
i said my doctor says stay away from
apple juice
but i better make sure i have a nice
chocolate bar right here i you know stay
away from my doctor says stay away from
apple juice it's really bad for me but
i'm in whole foods i picked up this 90
percent
riddled in sugar chocolate bar though
i'll pick up this my doctor says i can
have a psychoactive drug i can treat
myself with a psychoactive drug but i
can't have a glass of orange juice can't
have a glass of apple juice god forbid
but i can have a psychoactive drug
and i'm gonna need medication because i
can't sleep at night but don't know it's
chocolate
don't know it's a psychoactive drug and
i'm not sleeping good at night so i
better get a sleeping pill for my doctor
all right you guys let's stop fooling
around
put a little mustard powder on here
it's raining mustard
okay we got a little bit of what about a
garlic clove
a little bit of garlic
let's say you guys garlic
and i still got something else to add so
i'm gonna put a little bit of garlic in
there look you put a little bit if you
don't like garlic or don't put any at
all i'm gonna put put a
little bit more maybe maybe a little
couple little pieces here
boom
all right i'm gonna add some lemon juice
if you guys are okay
before i add the lemon juice i'm going
to take some
of these babies right here
these are
beautiful asparagus i got some asparagus
right here you guys i don't know if you
can see
right i'm going to chop up some of these
asparagus
this is a healing meal
keep that in mind asparagus is an
incredible food for the liver
detoxifying for the liver
keep that in mind there that's important
to know okay
so asparagus is a really incredible food
all right so i'm going to mix this up
let me grab a spoon
i'm going to put a little bit of lemon
on here too the healing foods in here
you know what kind of healing foods we
have in here cucumbers credible for the
kidneys people with kidney disease
should be eating cucumbers every day
incredible think about that right there
asparagus cleans the liver asparagus is
anti-viral anti-bug it's a bug killer
i'm putting lemon juice on here right
lemon juice you got that calcium and
that vitamin c so important really is
you got the radishes radishes enter into
the thyroid and start knocking out
epstein-barr that's what radishes do
think about that parsley feeds every
cell in the body strengthens the immune
system right you know parsley is an
incredible herb so i'm mixing this up
this is just this is an amazing dish
right here you can eat this all day long
if you want i'm gonna make a quick
announcement too
there we go
this is the potato salad you know what's
missing in here
huh
there's no oil in here that's missing
there's no eggs in here no there's no
cheese in here right that's missing what
else is missing in here right no dairy
no butter
right
and what happens is when you do this fat
free healing meal
that's how you allow bugs to leave your
system you if you're tanking too much
fat
you can't even get all the bugs you want
out that's why i like level three level
four level five level five because when
you go further down the levels
you're actually allowing more bugs to
get out of the system but level one
starts killing off bugs too but hey how
far do you want to go
see you guys that meal right there
isn't bug fuel it also doesn't thicken
the blood it doesn't dehydrate the body
and it doesn't contribute to toxins
inside the body those are the four
groups that doesn't happen with this
recipe keep that in mind okay
it's an incredible recipe i want to make
a quick announcement 6 15. later
eastern time
3 15 pacific time i'm gonna be on rumble
exclusively first for a little talk
might throw some zingers out
some stingers some zingers whatever
and who knows what i'm gonna say i hope
you guys subscribe and join me there
because he's spending a lot of time on
there and telegram too so hope you guys
are also joining telegram
because i'm doing private messages
meaning like you know yeah private
messages on telegram because i'm not
leaving these private audio messages
anywhere else so
there are audio messages on telegram
right i'm going to be doing that a lot
so make sure you join telegram subscribe
there subscribe to rumble because i'm
going to be on there a lot
and you guys just letting you guys know
on tick tock letting you guys know on
facebook and youtube okay
and you guys of course i'm on youtube
too you know you know that
so it's you know t dot
m e forward slash medical medium that's
um telegram how to get me there
right
we're day one of the anti-bug cleanse i
just made the recipe i'm pumped up about
it i got a fork right here
okay
so good
it really is
you guys this is a great recipe for
this cleanse incredible now
look don't be shy
if you want to crack into any recipes
and cleanse the heel crack into any
recipes
don't worry it's okay
perfectly fine
all right so you can crack into it just
one more reminder
try to pick up the book when you can
okay 16.99 amazon.com us
incredible price unbelievable and it's a
medical textbook over 200 symptoms
conditions the causes and what to do
get it free at the library if you want
go to a library and try to get a copy
but take advantage of the sale you won't
be sorry this is the best book out there
in health by far just make sure you have
it in your own personal
own personal library in your house okay
the anti-bug cleanses in there and um
i will be going live again at 4 30
eastern
1 30 pacific i'll be live on ig
tik tok and telegram
and then later on at 3 15 pacific 6 15
eastern i'll be rumble exclusive i love
you guys
thanks for being here thanks for joining
the cleanse with me and i'll see you
soon i hope you hang out and we go all
day