[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
of the medical community brings you out
therapy challenge
so here we are betrayal and broken trust
stabilizer
the stabilizer a lot of people have been
betrayed
their trust broken they've had hard
times in life all kinds of different
emotional wounds we're gonna go into
detail about it we're gonna find out
from the brain saver books
what happens inside the brain when we're
betrayed when someone
gives us bad news
what goes on inside here what's the
mystery how come our brains get so
screwed up when we have something bad
happen or some kind of challenge or some
kind of problem in our lives
and our brain gets all twisted up what
happens inside of there day two of the
medical medium brain shot therapy
challenge okay let's get the books out
you guys I'm excited look what I got in
front of me some incredible ingredients
ingredients that go together
and they do a lot of incredible stuff
for us so I'm excited we're here day two
you guys excited about day two or what
because I am I am okay
here we are we're in like we're in the
book The Brain saver book as we speak
right here and this is what we're doing
we're doing
check this out you guys the Betrayal
and broken trust stabilizer right there
right there that's it check it out I'll
show you one more time
that's the one right there get ready too
did you guys do it already this morning
Spirit of compassion is telling me a
bunch of you guys have already done it
maybe a half we're gonna do it I'm gonna
do I'm excited about this so what's
going on with this betrayal and broken
trust stabilizer like why
is this in here I asked Spirit of
compassion
why do you want a betrayal and broken
trust stabilizer and it's very
compassion told me what I was sitting at
my desk and I was writing the
information down
which SOC said was people have these
wounds they get injured in the brain
from all kinds of different things
breakups relationship breaks up breakups
confrontations divorces all kinds of
other issues bad news all kinds of
stress all kinds of broken trust all
kinds of let downs and it compiles
inside the brain little injuries in the
blood vessels and we need to heal and
fix it and then the emotional wound
stays in there and it percolates and it
festers and it rots inside of us and
then we carry it on and we bring it on
that's what happens we bring it on to
other people too when we're injured and
we got those emotional injuries inside
our brain and it's not cleared it's not
lifted it's not healed
then we're actually holding on to those
wounds
and that's why so it's like okay
incredible this is going to be an
amazing brain shot therapy right here
powerful brain shot therapy and one of
the most important so let's move on a
little bit here too let's go on to the
next little thing brain shot
therapy
so I'm in the book right now
medical medium brain shot therapy offers
instant relief
instant relief while it's actually
healing everything from deep within
within that issue like betrayal and
broken trust
they're designed to be highly absorbable
in the mouth this is incredible
so the brain shot therapies were created
to absorb quicker than anything else in
the mouth
so when they enter into your mouth
they absorb faster
now if you had just spinach or a mango
by itself it would not do that what's
incredible about this it has to be the
mango the spinach
the celery the okay turmeric
the lime
in the ingredients and the levels that
they are in the order that they are
for that incredible power to kick in so
they absorb so quick when they enter the
mouth and what does that mean when it
absorbs so quickly when it enters the
mouth it goes to the brain fast it
drives to the brain so
I've tried this betrayal shot a few
times last week since I did it all my
symptoms started feeling better like
healing betrayals let me heal other
things too now that's incredible because
that's how it works
when you're clearing the house of injury
that we don't know that's sitting in
here I mean it'll just sit in there for
years we live our life we've been hurt
and that resolve never really happened
inside here the result never really
happened inside the tissue it never
really happened inside the brain tissue
the soul all of it combined so it sits
with us and sits with us
and it just kind of percolates through
us and doesn't go away and we try a lot
of things to get it to go away
we do we try a lot of different stuff we
do the yoga and we do all kinds of other
things and we we exercise we do all
these things to try to get that to go
away we go on spiritual retreats
we do all these meditations right but
but we need also a real kicker a real
kicker something the boom really hit it
so that everything else you're doing
also helps so all the things that you're
doing your meditations
out there so many people doing different
meditations in the world all the things
you're trying your yoga whatever it is
your exercises everything that you're
doing your nature walks
everything that's helping with emotional
injuries of the past
are there to help but we want something
to slam that betrayal out of you kick it
so hard out of you activate that push to
get it out so that when you do all those
other things
healing happens
the adrenal fight or flight shot was so
calming things got very still I felt
that too when I took one it took one
recently I could see my thoughts going
by but was not attached to them that's
incredible the adrenal fight or flight
shot here's the thing about these brain
shots they're going to do a lot of
different things and you're going to
experience that
I was promised that from above when I
was put putting the information in here
and and I was like well this is going to
be incredible so that means that someone
who's doing this adrenal fight or flight
they're doing this brain shot this is
gonna happen as an SOC was just like yes
but you have to prepare them I'm like
what do you mean prepare them how can I
prepare them I don't I don't understand
well I remember sitting on my desk and
SOC said you have to prepare them you
have to foreword them
so they're not caught off guard because
they're that potent because people don't
get instant relief out there
and so when you get instant relief it's
like boom and so it's about being
prepared because when you do that expect
it to happen
it's important so you're not caught off
guard they're that powerful is what I
mean they're not powerful
and that's a big deal
here's a comment so excited for this one
try the negative energy exposure and
this effect was amazing I felt so calm
and happy first time in months when I
did the negative energy exposure I felt
tingles
that was the the it was a negative
energy that was releasing and leaving
tingles
here's a comment right here what happens
in the body with the shots is real
oh it's real oh it's real you can't
avoid it you can be somebody that's like
somebody that's just like no nothing's
gonna happen whatever you do the brain
shot therapy you sit down with it for a
second it's gonna happen
here's a comment I noticed an instant
feeling in my head after the day one
negative energy exposure shot that one
was so potent this is day two betrayal
and broken trust stabilizer
and I am
absolutely thrilled and excited about
this one because I know all of us
carry a little bit of hurt
some of us carry a lot of hurt some of
us carry
you know a moderate amount of hurt some
of us carry a little bit of hurt
some of us get exposed to problems that
come our way some of us had it years ago
here's a comment I cannot believe how
this works my husband and I both feel so
calm
well that's the thing you don't even
have to believe there's people that
aren't believing that these can work and
they're trying them and they're like I
can't believe it I didn't think that was
going to happen or what's going on
here's a comment right here my brain
works so much better on these oh yeah
you don't have to be a believer and I've
said that about medical medium
information in the past you don't have
to believe it
do your celery juice and get rid of
those problems and start healing up all
those symptoms right you don't have to
believe in celery juice for it to work
because it works when it comes down to
these brain shot therapies you don't
have to believe
in the brain shot therapy just get ready
because it works
and you can be the judge of it you can
be the judge of it they're really potent
they're really powerful but
get ready for the trolls
because that's what happens
get ready for the people that want to
stop the healing from happening in the
communities get ready for them because
they're going to be paid to pretend
they're doing the shot and pretend it
didn't work for them
let's get ready for that because that
will be on its way because this is
exploding out there
books are getting around the world
people are having life-changing results
from these brain shot therapies and what
that does is that creates a problem with
Darkness
companies
and what happens is then all of a sudden
the paid four stuff comes in like oh
those those didn't work those brain
shots for me and they never even try it
the 5G shot is amazing it's really
helping my whole family
incredible it's amazing comment right
there that's so good I love the 5G shot
for sure love it so what happens is if
whether you believe it or not if you do
administer these into your life you're
gonna feel them and they're gonna be
life-changing I was told that's how it
would work and it does it does it for
anybody I know who's using this and
everything else
all right so I mean
I talk a little bit about this the
medical medium brain shot therapy is
Uncharted Territory
never been done before
it doesn't matter what kind of alchemy
somebody thought they were mixing a
bunch of fruits and vegetables in some
shots or glasses or drinks this is an
entirely different situation it's
specifically for
these targeted areas
specifically for what someone's dealing
with with the right combinations but we
would never know what the right
combinations are I would never know in a
million years even if I was a guy that
was an avid juicer I was a juicing fan I
would never know what to put together it
would be impossible there's no food
science that would know there's no
science research that would know there's
no nutritionist that would know I would
never know no one would know what
exactly you need to put together just
right to make that happen so something
changes inside the brain it comes from
above it's the only place it could be
known for known from it's the only place
we can get that information
these are special
configurations synergistically combined
just right to crack the code
of how a fruit
an herb
have a fruit herb how a leafy green
how a wild food and vegetables can work
as medicine
while creative juices juice concoctions
are out there can make all the Creative
Juice concoctions we want we can put
together all these things it's not going
to do this
these brain shots
come from above the healing shots of
medical medium brain shot therapy are
tools that come from above these brain
shots are composed of specific
combinations of ingredients working
together systematically you guys for
specific reasons that only a source
above could know
the relationships among these
ingredients are intricate and unknown to
anyone
so the relationship that these have
together in all these brain shot
therapies there's 30 brain shot
therapies if you don't know the medical
medium books I'm reading right out of
brain saver if you don't have one go to
amazon.com us or wherever so there's 40
off right now at amazon.com us right now
get both the books they're both critical
they're both needed
can't just have one you have to have
both and the reason why they were all
one big book originally too big to
publish weighed 10 pounds they had to
cut it into two huge books
and that's the whole point so we got the
brain saver book and we got the brain
saver protocols right you have to have
both of them right there
and that's the whole point there were
one huge book like I just said the
relationships among these ingredients
are intricate and unknown to anyone
until now this knowledge from above
was untapped
this is one of the huge surprises out of
the brain saver books I wanted to
everybody to experience
but here's the thing
brain shot therapies build on
themselves
and man when you do the brain shot
therapy cleanses
there's seven different brain shot
therapy cleanses and that leads us to
the next part we're doing
the entry level
and we're doing a 10-day entry level
here's a comment I can feel it change
within myself that I just can't explain
I find myself looking at the trees
outside my window and feeling completely
connected
that's what happens when the brain shots
get to the brain when those the right
combinations
another comment I did the burnout
stabilizer one of my favorites because I
am trying to purposely burn myself to
the ground working 20 hours a day and
burning the candles before end I like
the burnout stabilizer too so I did the
burnout stabilizer this morning and I
felt tingling running through my brain
well that's the thing A lot of people
are going to feel that tingling I felt
the tingles going down my neck and my
spine on the negative energy exposure
shot
incredible it's incredible it feels like
electricity can't wait to try the next
one and that's another thing we're going
to talk about electricity a little bit
what happens with betrayal and broken
trust
so if we get betrayed or if we have
broken trust happen in our life we've
been let down something happens in the
brain it heats up the electricity goes
crazy
so we got to talk about that
so yeah so anyway
we're in the medical medium brand shot
therapy we're going to talk about the
levels so we're going to talk about the
entry level next in a little bit but
first first
we're gonna go to page 76.
I'm going to read a little bit about
what happens in our brain
as we go through life we come across
difficult situations betrayal loss
heartbreak loneliness confrontation
all of us experience these one way or
another somehow or some way in
boy is that true
we get emotionally hurt
if we don't recognize we've been
emotionally hurt it doesn't do Us
justice
we have to have that validation that
we've been emotionally hurt
and the physical aspect of this goes
wholly ignored and here's the most one
of the most incredible parts of what
we're talking about today and it's in
the brain saver books when we get
emotionally hurt
something happens physically to our
brain
that's completely ignored medical
research and science doesn't know
other health books whatever don't know
we need to address the physical core
strength of the brain
so that no matter what we're
experiencing emotionally or what we're
thinking that inner core strength of our
brain can survive emotional injuries so
the point is you guys we're gonna always
have some kind of inconsistency in our
life and we're going to have some kind
of emotional blow whether it's mild
small small to somebody else bigger to
another whatever it is
baby just somebody else smaller to
another whatever it is we're gonna
always have something come our way
that's just life on planet Earth
and so but we can actually do some real
healing inside the brain strengthening
the core of the brain you strengthen the
core of the brain
then we have an entirely different story
going on then we can handle emotional
blows now we're talking about the
Betrayal and broken trust stabilizer
shot which is incredible that's one way
to really get down into it strengthen
the brain to help it heal from emotional
blows so we're less triggered as well
when we have loss or betrayal our
physical brain can become injured how do
you like that
what science research
what are best psychiatrists
would our best anybody in health and
wellness in the world
doesn't know
is that when we have any kind of
emotional blow something happens
physically inside our brain
so when something goes wrong and we're
betrayed our physical brain can become
injured especially if our brain doesn't
have what it needs and that's the
problem too we need to have what our
brain needs like we need the information
right we need the things we need for our
brain you guys this is exciting because
we're doing this betrayal shot I can't
wait I'm actually
I want to jump to it right away actually
part of what injures the brain is not
the broken trust itself so our trust
gets broken but that's not all that is
what it's about
it's the fire that occurs when an event
like this happens it's the fire
you get upset because we've been let
down and betrayed or some kind of broken
trust fire occurs in the brain our brain
ignites it lights up it gets hot
so if there was an old breakup
relationship if there was a
misunderstanding if we were upset about
something if somebody broke our trust or
let us down or whatever it is
there's a fire that just explodes inside
our brain and that fire is where we get
in trouble that fire is the heating up
of the brain an intense electrical heat
someone had something right two years
ago when they called somebody hot-headed
or blow off steam
300 years ago when they called somebody
hot-headed they had that right
that was one thing that actually had
right
was we can get hot-headed or need to
blow off steam
not that someone needs to be angry for
this to happen so that's another Point
too you don't have to be angry
for the brain to just burn up in heat
the electricity of the brain you don't
have to be mad
you don't have to be angry you could be
quiet you can be peaceful looking you
can be laying in your bed but upset
internally you can be lying there upset
someone's looking at you and you're not
reacting you're just standing there or
lying there in bed but inside you're
hurting and you're hurting deep inside
why did that person break up with me how
come it didn't work out what went wrong
with this other thing
and whatever it is that's happening in
your life any kind of letdown how come I
didn't how come they didn't accept me
into the school I wanted to go into
whatever it is how come I didn't get
that job how come I was fired whatever
it is when you're sitting down lying
down standing there whatever and you're
thinking about it you're burning hot and
that's just how it goes
sometimes we're not even showing emotion
and the fire within our brain Burns
hotter than ever you could be lying in
bed hurt by betrayal not expressing a
word hurt by a friend a friend could
have hurt you and someone who saw you
wouldn't even know you were burning up
inside
more
coming here because publicly known
medical research in science only knows a
tiny fraction about the brain
so that means research and science
really doesn't know a lot about how the
brain works
if by some miraculous chance the Earth
is still alive a thousand years from now
and not blown up and not
tor
and broken
if the Earth actually exists and life is
on the earth a thousand years from now
we're still not going to know if the if
the Earth is just a rock that's dead
floating in space
no matter what we're still not gonna Not
Gonna Know science and research does not
have advanced enough information and
they never will about this what happens
when we get emotionally hurt and the
injuries that happen inside the brain
even though the overheating of our
physical brains can't be weighed or
measured it is just as real as the burn
you feel from touching a hot stove
it's as real as spilling hot coffee on
your lap it says real is walking
barefoot across scalding parking lot at
the beach this heating of the brain
occurs instantly when we experience an
emotional challenge of any kind what I'm
trying to tell you right here I'm
reading some information in here but
what I'm trying to say is the Betrayal
broken trust stabilizer
takes down the heat
but it also helps to heal that betrayal
that happened to us
it helps to heal from any of those
emotional injuries that happen to us it
helps to heal the physical injury inside
the brain so when you take that brain
shot therapy all kinds of stuff can
happen and everybody can experience a
little bit of a different situation
because they may have been hurt
emotionally different than someone else
was hurt emotionally many years ago or
recently
so when we do this brain shot
this stabilizer
something can change
and it will first of all anything
percolating like old betrayal that's
been stuck inside the brain circulating
within the neurons can get blasted out
knocked out pushed out by the brain shot
therapy second any injuries that were
sustained along the way from any kind of
emotional hardship
creating blood vessel damage
overheating of the neurons and nerves
inside the brain and the nerve cells and
the glial cells
can start to heal because there's
something within this combination nobody
ever knew existed
and in this combination
is the secret
to unlocking the Betrayal and broken
trust injuries
yeah
amazing
so medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanses we're doing the entry level
cleanse that's the one we're doing it's
10 days this is day two so I want
everybody to know where we are now if
you just got here and this is brand new
to you and you just happen to hop on
here this is a free
shot therapy challenge cleanse
and you can go to medicalmedium.com
you can sign up you can get your PDF
which is the grocery shopping list and
all the information you need for free
it's all free
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanses I'm on page 516 of brain saver
these cleanses are imperative for what's
to come in this world have you noticed
it hasn't been easy out there people
getting sick
people struggling
there's a lot of toxicity
the onslaught of domestic chemical
warfare in our homes like the air
fresheners and the scented candles
and the cleaning agents and the
pesticides herbicides and the
insecticides all of that
it's all in our face every day
when you embark on these cleanse options
and we're doing level one and it's a
10-day cleanse
you're using your free will and your
intention to clean and project this
stuff out of your body that means that
if it's not if we're not just up against
actual physical chemicals we're also up
against betrayal and broken trust
we're up against that as well
that can Harbor inside of us just like a
toxic chemical can just like a heavy
metal can just like anything can inside
our brain
so we're going to be using the Betrayal
and broken trust stabilizer to propel
and rocket that out here's a comment yes
felt the tingle with the burnout shot
and a boost of extra energy
and with the negative energy exposure
shot I felt so happy that I called a
friend and we had a hilarious
conversation and you know when you have
that hilarious conversation that joy and
you're actually laughing and you feel
light-hearted the healing that happens
from that alone
so the negative energy exposure shot
was activating that joyous healing
inside
it's really incredible
the brain shot therapy cleanses and
we're doing the entry level you guys
are Beyond just the physical
these are also metaphysical that's the
whole point
it's all about the soul it's all all
about
our emotional state mental state
here's a comment I got my life back
because of those shots they're truly a
miracle
Hal Bernadette
I am so happy that you got your life
back because of these shots
they're so potent they're that powerful
and they're miraculous I mean that's
what I'm telling my friends it's what
I'm telling people that are just opening
people that I know that they contact me
and they're like hey I just opened the
book I'm doing the brain shot and my
life just changed
it's about the subconsciousness the
consciousness
our soul and our physical brain all of
that needs house cleaning and the brain
shot therapies help to house clinging
all of that
the brain shot therapies also help to
connect our subconsciousness
Consciousness to our physical brain
to our soul
so many people get disconnected
their subconsciousness and their
Consciousness completely disconnected
their soul and their subconsciousness
completely disconnected
their Consciousness and their physical
brain completely disconnected so people
walk around disconnecting what you're
going to find when you're doing these
brain shot therapy cleanses is you're
going to find a connection happening
and you're gonna be like wait a minute
just like that comment I read earlier
when someone was saying they were
looking out their window I think right
and they're looking at the trees
and feeling so connected
what happens is with the brain shot
therapy cleanses
and the brain shot therapy cleanses is
that in the shots they're connecting
pieces that are disconnected in US
when our subconscious Consciousness is
too far from our consciousness
when our physical brain itself is
disconnected from our soul
when our soul is disconnected from her
consciousness
all this that's happening inside here
and so what the brain shots are doing is
starting to actually bring it all
together
and when that comes together
these experiences happen
and you're you're actually witnessing
yourself what these experiences are like
here's the part that I was reading about
yesterday
these cleanses purify your brain Temple
so this is your temple right here
I know that a lot of people say well my
body is my temple
my physical body is my temple that's the
temple
that's the temple
the temple is the place where the soul
resides
the true Temple is here
it's the brain because the true Temple
has the ghost in the machine the true
Temple has
the soul
inside the physical brain
so you're purifying your temple your
brain Temple
here's the incredible part that I was
reading yesterday
you're intuitive
psychic telepathic Clairvoyant skills
will start to surface
think about that for a minute
so when you're doing these brain shot
therapy cleanses like the entry level
right now or 10 day cleanse or on day
two if you just got here
we're working on
surfacing your intuitive psychic
telepathic skills
your Clairvoyance skills that everybody
has inside of them everybody has the
ability inside of them
but we're actually clearing the air
we're reading things that shouldn't be
in the brain we're also jump starting
the brain
and that's what these brain shot
therapies do they shock the brain
out of triggers
pushing away things that shouldn't be
there reigniting and rewiring and here's
one of my favorite parts
these spiritual and physical cleanses
like the brain shot therapy
is rewiring
our brain
and that's another reason why people
have profound experiences
because of rewiring is happening
so there's multitude a multitude of
things in the process when you do these
brain shot therapies it's healing the
physical brain
it's healing the soul
metaphysical brain it's connecting the
subconscious Consciousness and the
consciousness
it's rewiring and reconnecting
everything
and when you think about all that and
you put that all together
it's no wonder why they work
instant relief is happening and of
course you're doing the other medical
medium tools because you want to work on
other problems and you want to work
deeper into other areas
because the books have lots of
information in them but the brain shot
Therapies
are profound and Powerful all on their
own
so let's head to the brain shot therapy
well actually we're the entry level
let's just talk about that for a little
bit
so we're in the entry level of the brain
shot therapy cleanse we're doing the
10-day version now you can do a 20-day
you can do a 30 day you can pick
any shot you'd like now we chose
the shots
that we're using
we chose the 10 shots for this brain
shot therapy entry level
[Music]
you guys want to do the robot with me
let's go let's crank up the music
what kind of robot can you do
[Music]
what's your love when the Music Stops
and you're in the middle of a good move
all right
so we're in the entry level drink one
brain shot per day
your choice
10 day 20 day or 30 day we're doing the
10 day you can carry this on for 20 days
you can carry this on for 30 days
it's day two of the medical medium brain
shot therapy cleanse challenge
your choice of which brain shot option
from day to day if you want to do a
different one do a different one if you
don't want to do the Betrayal and broken
trust one today but you wanted to do the
negative energy exposure or another one
or the EMF exposure or something else
you're welcome to do it
incredible
I love it when you do the robot Anthony
so funny
thank you
try to drink a minimum of 50 50 ounces
of water every day when you're doing
this so make sure you're drinking some
water
because remember you're cleansing now
here's the thing don't put the water
right next to the brain shot
so when you do your brain shot
don't just guzzle some water it's like
here's my brain shot going down oh I'm
gonna drink a whole bunch of water now
don't do that
got to keep a light heart it's important
life is hard enough a little fun and
humor is always the way to go you guys
know it's important but here's the thing
don't do water with your shot don't
juice your shot and dump water in there
don't dilute this shot don't dilute the
medicine but you do need 50 ounces a
minimum of 50 ounces of water every day
when you're doing the brain shot therapy
cleanse now we're in the entry level
so back to this again we're drinking one
shot per day but here's the thing
you can do two or three shots a day I'm
doing three shots a day yesterday I did
three negative energy exposure shots you
could do One A Day and that's fine
they're really powerful I did three and
I did them periodically through the day
today I'm doing three betrayal and
broken truss stabilizer shots
and I'm gonna space them out I'm not
gonna do them like every 10 minutes and
send them down I'm gonna do one wait a
little while till later do another then
maybe at the end of the day do one more
try to wait 15 to 30 minutes before you
do something else like eat
so before you eat something so when you
do your brain shot stabilizer your brain
shot exposure your brain shot shifter
whichever one you choose out of 30 brain
shots
when you do it
don't just eat something like five
minutes later two minutes later don't
down a whole bunch of foods yet give it
some time try to give it 15 minutes
minimal there's more details in the book
and that's what's incredible about even
with children doing the brain shot
therapy too so you can get all the
details about children doing the brain
shot therapy
and in adults
and all the details around it
so we're doing
our shot so let's get ready for it here
I'm actually really excited you guys so
we're in the stabilizer shots these
brain shots are designed to stabilize
you
that's the whole point
it's about stabilizing it's about also
uprooting
and propelling out of you it's also
about rewiring so all these things
matter
we're in the Betrayal and broken trust
stabilizer right there we're entry level
it's 10 days we're on the second day
and we're getting ready to do it
so let's roll
so
I'm gonna get the juicer out right here
I'm excited about this you guys got your
juicer
now you can use any juicer this is the
mm1500 right here it's on sale it's 20
off right now
and we're going to be doing the Betrayal
and broken trust stabilizer shot
I have the juicer ready now what's
incredible about this juicer and it's
why I like it it's not just that I work
with them I work with them because it
squeezes it has a compression it
squeezes as much juice that can possibly
be squeezed and I can't find that with
other juicers so with the rising costs
of food this juicer actually saves me
money so every time I use it it's paying
for itself over and over again and
that's what I love about it and that
that right there that's one thing out of
a bunch of things I love about it so
it's about the dryer pulp in the basket
where it's so dry
and this is the mm1500 it's 20 off
at Omega right you'll see the link in
the description so this is the one it's
the mm-1500
it's also really quiet if you don't want
a screaming loud juicer so I love it all
on its own for that
and there's also no the metal gear it
doesn't have metal gears rubbing against
each other like other juicers do where
they're grinding the metals rubbing
against each other
and so I thought I'd show you guys this
because it's the one I use everybody
asked me about a juicer or whatever
what's the best kind this is the one and
it's on sale right now so let's start
right up half inch
of turmeric going in here so I'm gonna
put a piece of turmeric in here
excited
all right next one is going to be frozen
mango
[Music]
about a half a cup
half a cup of Frozen mango now you can
use fresh mango you're allowed to do
that of course if I had a fresh mango I
would be doing
a fresh mango but the Frozen mango works
really incredible it's
a great a great way of doing it I love
Frozen mango personally
put a little bit more I'm going to get
about a half a cup in here just grabbing
some pieces
that aren't so Frozen
okay
now I'm going to do a half a peeled lime
you guys have your lime
so I'm going to cut the slime in half I
peeled it already
there you go
now it's going to go in
now I'm gonna go with a quarter cup
of tightly packed spinach
now the way of doing it in my hand where
I can kind of measure it I've actually
done this where I've done this in my
hand then I put into measuring cup so I
know exactly what I'm doing so I'm going
with a quarter cup
of tightly packed spinach
if you had anything happening in your
life any kind of Betrayal on any level
even on the most mildest form
like you sat on the phone
with the phone company waiting to get
help and they disconnected you
and you waited for two hours
get the Betrayal broken trust shot out
right away
so we're doing a quarter cup of spinach
in there and then a half a stock of
celery
[Music]
okay here we go
let that do its thing
and then we're gonna do a 16th of a
teaspoon of cinnamon but the cinnamon is
going to go into the juice when you mix
it up at the egg so you don't want to
put your cinnamon in here I mean you
probably could put it in your juicer
right there but it's probably not the
best way to go
you could you really need to just put it
in the container wherever your juice
ended up and you put that 16th of
of a teaspoon of cinnamon in there
all right
I'm excited
so you got your little strainer and then
we can do is kind of massage any
leftover juice
through the
strainer
whatever strainer that you have
[Music]
I'm like a little nervous because I've
been betrayed
[Music]
I know there's people that don't want to
think they've been betrayed once in a
while or in their life at some point
[Music]
and that's okay but it can still sit
inside of them
and wreak havoc and if we don't get it
out of us
it can stay in there and then be like a
silent
Darkness it resides inside of us inside
of our brain
[Music]
put a little cinnamon here there we go
16th of a teaspoon
and then what happens is we walk around
with that broken trust those wounds we
walk around with that betrayal the
wounds inside of us
we walk around with it for years
and then we get the trade again
somewhere somehow
and then
when that happens
[Music]
it adds on to the Old Wounds and we get
triggered
sits inside of us
we have the shot you guys have yours
ready
here it is
the thing is as I sit with it for a
second
before I send it down
I connect with it because I know what
it's going to do and I already feel it I
feel something kind of a sensation
because I'm smelling the ingredients
and getting ready
[Music]
I'm gonna let it sit
it's getting to my brain
it's hitting my brain
it absorbs right through my mouth you
can feel that absorption go right
through your mouth
and right into your throat getting right
to the brain
I feel it going to my forehead
and I'm thinking about
so many things that have happened in my
life
and I know it's leaving
because there's an ignition happening
there's a rewiring happening I'm gonna
do a little bit more
[Music]
whoo
I could feel it
bartender give me another
[Music]
to know that those ingredients were put
together just right for this reason
incredible you're taking yours amazing
Michelle says I'm crying it's working
I'm actually I could feel like a little
bit of a welling up
in my eyes
you know like as if I don't know as if I
I cried or something but I didn't cry
right now but yet I feel like I did
and that's incredible because I'm really
thinking
because I have this experience as if I
just cried I have this experience like I
was crying for an hour and I'm I'm not
crying anymore but I haven't experienced
this if I did or something I'm feeling
that
this one has a really unique flavor does
it ever but you can you can just read
the flavors as it's happening
have you guys tried this brain shot what
did you feel what did you experience
right now what are you experiencing
right now can you please share a story
post a post or a story tag at Medical
medium medical medium so I can see them
and then repost them too
because oh my God I'm I actually feel
like emotional but I don't feel the
emotion I feel like it was already there
and it's leaving me it's so strange
it's almost like
angels have gifted me the the ability to
get rid of whatever that was the hurt
without me having to go through
like the experience again how can I
explain that are you guys having that at
all because that's what I'm I'm feeling
right now I'm feeling like
I'm clearing it out
and I feel like I cried but I didn't
but I feel like I'm clearing it out but
I don't I'm not I'm not hurting
you know as it's leaving this is like
being really like a cloud lifting it's
incredible and you guys when you post
your stories or share your stories
videos are best because they're easy to
share so tag at Medical medium hashtag
medical medium this is day two betrayal
and broken trust stabilizer
there's something that happens when a
little bit of that cinnamon is mixed
with exactly these other five
ingredients
that nobody would ever know about that
came from above
truly a miracle
I can't say enough
I just saw somebody said I gotta get
this book
if you're gonna get the book amazon.com
us is 40 off
get it for family members gifts
holidays whatever and this isn't just
the book it's two books
there were one huge book but
my publisher said we can't print it it's
too big it would be 10 pounds they had
to be broken into two massive books
they're packed with information
right there
it's a brain saver books
you guys
be the judge yourself read the content
be prepared to be mind blown I don't
even I like I feel are you feeling that
from the Betrayal of broken trust shot
I don't know I mean
I I believe that even if like the worst
troll on the planet came on right now
and said something really terrible I
don't even think I would get upset on
any level
I I just there's I feel so good Allison
says I totally just burst out crying
with a huge healing release I that's I
feel the healing release and I feel like
I already cried does that make any sense
Michelle says such a release
Rachel Clark says I just want to hug
myself
Suzanne says
I am with chills in my entire body ready
for another shot
I'm doing three of these shots today is
what I'm doing I'm doing three of them
I'm gonna do one leader and then one
later on
[Music]
Sharon says I've been doing the advanced
cleanse with three shots a day and
experience profound Clarity do you guys
have the mm1500 it's 20 off right now
which is unbelievable it's the mm-1500
it squeezes all the juice out of the
ingredients so that you save money and
you're not buying double the celery
double the spinach double the turmeric
double the kit whatever it is that's
going to be in these double the mango
you're not buying double and having to
run double through to get that much
juice like all the other juicers
this is the juicer that actually saves
the community money if you guys are
juicing and doing this it saves me money
because it pays for itself over and over
again because of that very squeezing
method that's in there
anyway just thought I'd tell you so you
know Mildred said what's in this shot
that makes me want to dance
that's the thing you're unique and
everybody might have a unique experience
with these brain shot therapies keep
that in mind because you're unique and
what has happened to you in your life or
what you're going through is unique so
experience different things like I'm
experiencing this thing where I thought
I just cried for an hour but I didn't
but yet it feels like that and my eyes
are kind of like welled up as if I did
cry
and I feel this light-heartedness but at
the same time like something left that
shouldn't have been there
Karen says wow that shot is crazy good I
wasn't expecting anything to happen my
eyes started to almost water that's the
whole point like I cried I felt tingling
in my mouth of all places I feel great
now and what you're going to notice with
the brain shot therapies many of them
are going to create this this tingling
this mysterious tingling of healing
because you're rewiring the rewiring is
happening inside your brain
so keep that in mind
and and one thing like Karen said I
wasn't expecting anything to happen well
that's why I was trying to forewarn
everybody because people are not going
to expect an instant result but you're
going to get an instant result from the
brain shot therapies I have to forewarn
you I don't want you caught off guard
Genie says I feel like I don't have to
take hurts personally anymore that's why
I said if the worst troll on the planet
came on and said some horrible grotesque
thing or some terrifying thing I
actually wouldn't get upset right now I
would just feel sorry for the troll
it's it's it's unbelievable what has
happened right here
so
it really is
seven brain shot therapy cleanses in
these books
can you imagine seven brain shot therapy
cleanses we're doing the entry level
30 brain shots to choose from We're
choosing the 10 we're choosing for this
brain shot therapy cleanse if you've got
on here and you don't even know what's
going on here and you're like who's hot
what what where go to medicalmedium.com
sign up to the to the brain shot therapy
cleanse get download your free pdf it's
free
it's free if you don't want to get the
book on sale on amazon.com
then just go to your library
beat down their door and say I want the
medical medium brain saver books tell
the library you want both the brain
saver books get it for free I don't care
everything can be free
the brain shot therapy cleanses have an
ability to rid people of a hundred
symptoms over time
by the way there's over 300 symptoms
conditions and protocols incredible
protocols for advanced conditions
when people are really suffering and
struggling inside the braid saver
um books there's seven brain shot
therapy cleanses and seven heavy metal
detox cleanses including Advanced and
the extractor the protocols for 300
symptoms conditions and a hundred plus
recipes
there's 12 books in both these books six
books minimum in each book
that's why they're so big that's why
they're so packed
and everything told you guys about the
heavy metal detox lenses in here too so
yeah
that was day two we're getting ready
you guys are gonna be there for day
three right I hope you don't miss it
I'm hoping you don't miss you guys want
to do the robot with me right now let's
do it
let's do the robot
[Music]
I'll see you tomorrow
see you guys tomorrow what
these brain shots are doing something to
me I don't know what it is I can't
describe it I don't even know what's
happening right now
like what is this
tomorrow's day three of the medical
medium brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge guess what we're doing
tomorrow OMG
OMG we're doing the obsessive thoughts
shifter brain shot
you want to experience something
get ready for the obsessive thought
shifter brain shot get ready for that
that's a whole another level you guys
will do the robot on the way out here
come on
[Music]
I'll see you guys tomorrow