hello I'm Danielle delate and welcome
back it is night three of the Cafe
Gratitude medical medium popup dinner
collaboration and tonight we're
switching things up we have a new
location in Venice and we're going to
start tonight with the meet and greet
with aw so let's go and check that
out I'm good how are you back for you
yes please hi Anthony how are you than
nice to see you again nice to see you
how are you good I'm wonderful thank you
for having this beautiful dinner for us
and course of course I um I didn't I
didn't have anybody to take a photo can
I ask somebody to well we have a photo
come right here we're going to get one
so I don't need to do my own no you
don't then um see that yeah right here
right here there's two
cameras
more thank you can I give you up of
course of course amazing to see you
medicine and healer for me I still am in
a cancer Journey but it's going to get
better and easier and fun working hard
I'm proud of you just yep keep on
forging I'm going to keep sharing with
you so incredible well I'll see you
okay hey how are you good how are you
good good so happy to be here
celebrating the collaboration uh I'm
very happy I'm is this your family yes
this is my mom it's an honor nice to
meet you husband hey great to meet you
fantastic all you guys came a little bit
closer up here there you go thank you
wonderful so how are you guys doing
tonight okay Good Feeling Good Feeling
wonderful excited for some good
food you you call
forers good good cuz I love that because
I'm an eater too and the food's amazing
so I'm excited you guys are here want to
get a picture together together let do
that want come I'll I'll be here do you
want to be on this side here
how would you like to do this okay yes
over here you're asking a bunch of
indecisive people okay
ready amazing thank you thank you for
coming thank you so it's a great honor
to have you here seriously okay thank
you thank you how you doing sir hey how
are you it's a pleasure let me introduce
my wife this is Carla hey hi car from
from eler as well wa Cal America and you
made the trip you made the trip here yes
sir we did well it's a great honor to
have you here yeah no well you just saw
her cousin coming right up really yeah
okay that's cool that's cool so the
whole family is here the whole family's
here just to meet too how do you like it
here in La well my sister actually lives
in Corona so she does yeah are you
staying with her while you're you know
here or you guys oh we're we're we're
juggling families and everything else so
we stay at her sister's place we stay at
my sister that's great you got family
lots of family I love that do you guys
want a picture with me sure all right
let's go let's do this all right I'll
have you guys come up a little further
okay amazing thank you seriously for
coming okay I love the ink right there
that's a really really cool too thank
you enjoy the food thank you hey hi
Anthony from happiness from within how
are you oh my God I saw you in calabases
oh incredible I just wanted to say
really quick yeah because of your
protocols I've been able to reverse
a um an incurable condition that I've
had in my knee for 20 years my God and I
didn't have to have a fourth knee
surgery because of your information so
and you had previous knee surgeries and
everything and they wanted to do another
one and you oh sorry go ahead and you
did all you did the you did certain
things you did the certain protocols did
you customize it for yourself a little
bit yeah I just came to realize it's EBV
a certain form you know cuz of so thank
you so much waa that's that that is just
amazing love to have and you're standing
you're standing it's a gift you're
walking you're here yeah you're the most
incredible human being on the planet
thank you for what you do well thank you
for doing everything you're doing too
okay let's get a picture together
straight ahead it's Michael
well I hope you enjoy the food okay hope
to have you on happiness from within
hopefully one day that will be fun that
will be fun please do please do hey you
got a book for me I do if you don't mind
saying it of course to the Clover City
Event but I wasn't able to get a a
signature that day and I went to the
calabas event well I'm sorry you didn't
get a signature that day we got one now
though okay yeah yeah but I just I just
want to say thank you for everything
that you've done um
yeah I've been dealing with a lot of
chronic illness
eczema it was really bad in Calabasas
but it's a lot it's getting a lot better
CU I don't even see it I don't even see
the see it right here I mean it's hard
though it's hard to see yeah yeah but
you know that's how good that's how good
things are getting yeah yeah and I'm
trying to do like the mono cleanse and
the protocol Brave I'm doing the spinach
you're brave okay to do that you're
brave thank you thank you so much keep
on doing that the monoc cleanse which is
your favorite monoc cleans oh I love um
well I I love eating bananas like I just
love eting a bunch of bananas and
potatoes okay that's that's good that's
good potato are my favorite yeah well
let's get a picture together yeah that's
actually my favorite too oh awesome
that's great here we go and then two
more right here great thank you those
are my favorite twoo thank you for
coming am I an old soul or a New Soul or
am I an ancient you're an old soul
definitely for being here yes sure and
all that you've gone through
hi's nice to you oh my gosh I'm shaking
I can't believe I'm meeting you right
now come on are you kidding I know I
know but this is like you know this the
best best that you guys are here you got
your mom your dad I don't cry
W no you don't you don't I'm sure s
probably knows that but oh my gosh I'm
turning into my mom well Julia thanks
for coming seriously for do this is from
our friends you be here and there's a
letter from me in there your friend
couldn't come with um a letter for me I
had to use notebook paper cuz I was
doing school work um I hope you don't
mind getting me choked up well thank you
so letters in here all right I'll make
sure I see this tonight okay and and
afterwards all right when I get home I I
I will read it all right take your time
no rush do you want to get a picture yes
please
okay camera yeah
two
more that is so cool that is you guys
want to get a family pick too though do
you want to do that we'll get let's get
let's get a family
pck do you want to get on this side side
do you want to be on this side
I you
ready it's amazing thank you so much
it's an honor okay thank you for also
serving the public like you've had all
these years appreciate that seriously
good to see you kiddo thank you thank
you so much I'll see you okay you guys
going to get some good food tonight
excited about it all right amazing thank
you you guys are the best thank
[Music]
you he you hi hey how are you good can I
give you a hike yes yes yes good to see
you good to see you I'm getting my words
out just want to thank you for
everything that you do for the community
and for me from the bottom of my heart
you're welcome and and so grateful well
I'll I'll do my best and keep on doing
my best and you know and I appreciate
what you do you're the reason why I get
out of bed okay you're the reason all
right and you understand you I do you
know so I do thank you of my do you want
to get a picture I do okay Straight
Ahead there's
like wonderful have you tried the foods
yet not yet for it's going to be awesome
it's going to be
awesome hey Wy and sunflowers oh my God
it's crazy you know known you forever I
know that's how it works you know well
good to see you I cannot thank you
enough and I also wanted to tell you
that if there's ever anything that you
need I'm your person I got you I mean
I'm just so appreciative that means the
world okay any support I can get that
that means the world all right really do
appreciate I know you already do already
support and just I I mean I feel like
I've known you forever and I'm just so
grateful to you I can't it's an honor
it's an honor to have you
here amazing you so much hope you enjoy
the food oh I know I will thank you hey
is it okay to hug you yeah hi oh my gosh
it's so amazing to meet you thank you so
much I mean I can't express enough
gratitude for what you did in my life I
was so sick and you just I mean you had
a really hard struggle going all the way
back yeah and it was just amazing I mean
everything you said and did in spirit of
compassion just you found out what you
needed to do you found out yes it was
amazing yes so all that matters you know
getting the answers is everything and
and you're seasoned you've been there
you tried this you tried that exactly
well I'm so proud of you okay I am I
know you worked hard though thank you
here come up a little further that'd be
great I know you worked really hard
though so keep on keep on doing all that
you're doing
wonderful hey what's this did I get a
signature for friend she's really
struggling and she's just she's been
doing medical for so
long oh you didn't it come out okay S I
didn't open it up
thanks so
much send my blessings okay and thank
you so much I will tell your friend I
care about her and what she's going
through thank you do you want to get a
picture yes I have here come step step
up a little closer yeah could I ask
Spirit of compassion one
question
okay
more y my husband did a w drop blood
test um and it just has never been
working out so I wanted to ask um if the
if just the technology would be like the
right one to whenever it would be
possible to continue with that to
continue with it or um does he look at
the books does he look at the
information he does he read no he does
not we there's information in there you
have to look at your symptoms the
symptoms are important yeah and then you
take the sympoms he's doing he um
invented a blood test a Wonder blood
test like a long time ago and um oh he
invented a he invented it yeah so my
question was like if the technology that
he is using um like it was for Spirit of
compassion if the technology that he's
using is I'd have to look at it and
really see and ask a lot of questions to
so like because it's complicated so I
would have to ask continual questions so
maybe we can someday figure out and take
a look at that technology or get you in
touch with someone okay okay thank you
hey what's going
on I saw you on Monday
but to see you again yeah it's really
great to see you and um I just want to
yeah my name is Alex I came all the way
from South Africa yes um you remember I
remember um and yeah um I want to tell
you that um I have heal from emotional
wounds more than anything else and also
Mandy Morris and Oliver n have really
really helped me and my life is so much
better than it's ever been before and
I'm so so
grateful and can I ask one question from
s
so um I want to know if there's anything
more I can do to help my husband to heal
and to help my
marriage you know you know him more than
anybody that's what s so says you
understand him more than anybody nobody
else does so keep that in mind okay so
you have to find a way to make it to see
and make it work cu no one knows him
more than you do okay right thank you
thank
you how are you hey how are you so good
to see you good to see you I can't
believe it cool leather
jacket listen one of the things I never
got to tell you is just like you've just
totally enabled one of the things I've
always wanted to do is make a difference
in the medical field and you but you
have though but you're a medical doctor
and you're out there say saving lives
and you're changing the the way things
are out there you you're doing all that
but it's it's amazing and just an honor
to be able to just do what you brought
here I feel like you've saved my life
from so many ways that you have no idea
just You' worked really hard okay you've
worked really hard right so much you
want to get a picture together I sure do
okay of course I do you going step up
here
oh two more
than well try to get some good food I
will
excited hey how are you what's going on
how are you do you know who I
am where'd you come from Mexico really
and you made the trip here yes wa three
hours you know because one of my biggest
dreams is meeting you my second dream is
to heal you know and you're working on
it you're doing all the different things
yeah I've been doing follow I follow me
for years you know and it changed my
life and you were the reason I wake up
every day it's been really thought
really really hard but I know I will get
there I just want to know if there's
something I should focus on what's the
best food well look you know you you
have the information it's in your hands
okay and do you pray a lot yep you pray
every night not every night not every
night I was okay well you you got to get
you got to get that deep connection
going like you you you are and then
what's going to happen you're going to
open up the books okay or you're going
to see something that I'm talking about
but you're going to see wait a minute
the I can do this I can try this and
you're going to you're going to keep on
moving forward and the tip to regrow
hair faster the tip to regrow hair
faster the tip to regrow hair faster
which is oh it's you know how it's all
the adrenals remember I talk about that
in all the books it's all the adrenals
and it's very important to connect with
that the adrenal information so that's
it for me I'm going to be
okay thank you thank you for coming
thank you for making the
trip hi hey I'm satar I'm I know you are
it's nice to see you how are you doing
good to see you too good she's here
she's here yeah I know I know how are
you doing good good um I just wanted to
tell you how much medical medium
information has completely changed Thea
trajectory of my life and I'm just so
grateful and that's insane that's
unbelievable changed my career and my
life and now I'm I'm pregnant I know I
know you are it's just so exciting and
I'm just so grateful for you and thank
you for just fighting for us and working
so hard for us oh I would do it any day
okay and thank you for all the energy
time that you put into it all seriously
and the support I know you're doing
amazing things okay and I really
appreciate it I was hoping to run into
you here I was hoping you came so this
is really great oh I'm so glad and I
also wanted to say the the recent light
blast at the Calabasas event really move
the needle in my PTSD and I'm just I'm
Blown Away by it so I'm so grateful well
there's one coming tonight God willing
there's one coming tonight do you want
to get a picture
yeah thank you for being an amazing
doctor too so much that matters to me
yeah it does thank you so much nice to
see you I'll see you later I'll see you
later hello what's going on nice to meet
you how are you Jenny Jenny my husband
check look at
you and when I uh first came across your
first book in July 2016 I'd already been
searching for answers for 30 years and
so I I thought it was just another leg
in my search I read the book oh yeah
you've been doing it for so long and
you've been you know yeah of course good
you looked at this you said let me give
this to try right and I did and it was
the best medical book I'd ever read in
my life and I the line disease chapter
remember that and you ended my search
and now I'm learning and healing and
thank you I appreciate it and it makes
sense right oh and every time every time
you try to you you you go and you look
at this it doesn't make sense you look
at it and you come back to this
information it's like it's it's like
test it try it and you know it's tested
constantly you try it and try it and and
you know it works yeah so it's awesome
and you tried everything else so oh gosh
yes
amazing so thank you so much trial and
error
mostly well I'm really proud of you yeah
well thank you so much for all you do
let's get a picture you guys okay get
got enough room for all of
us fantastic I'll see you guys
later hold on one second
like I need something to drink my
throat's really dry can I get coconut
water not water though
yeah or
Mike
e
e e
mom on the phone really yeah let me say
hi yes cuz she uh saw met you or not met
you she found you 10 years ago when you
just in consultations and she did she
introduce uh me to
you everything and I came here kind of
to represent her cuz she lives in the
east coast of New Jersey and she yeah
and she's homebound so you know she is
unable to come here but she really
wanted me to come and meet you so hey
how are
you you good to see
you thank you so much amazing amazing I
love you well thank you for thank you
for sending her okay
here step up here step up here awesome
yes so we'll get all a picture together
all three of us we're getting a picture
the same
yes amazing perect thank you for coming
yeah of course thank what I'm proud of
her oh yeah Dr Dr Green is her doctors
oh amazing amazing well thank you okay
thank you for telling your daughter
thank you hey hi it's such an honor to
meet you it's honor to meet you are you
kidding you have have literally saved my
life and it is just such a pleasure to
be standing here in your presence and I
just wanted to say thank you so much for
everything you have done everything that
you do and everything that you continue
to do because you saved my life and my
family's life and it means the world
well that means the world to me okay it
does it means the world to me truly okay
do you want to get a picture absolutely
can you got a book my book got a book
for me to sign the only one that's not
falling apart from overuse yep that's
what happens the medical medium books
are used more than any health book any
book in my house
y thank you so much well let's get a
picture oh that's mine I'll take that is
this your pen yeah come on step up here
here pick up the
book amazing amazing enjoy the food
tonight hey how are you do you recognize
me yes I do I talk about negative
entities yeah
Z my God I remembered my name of course
I do seven years seven years now that
that I didn't that I didn't remember I
knew it was a long time but seven years
this whole yeah I know I know you like
the you like talking about the negative
energies and all that what are you going
to talk about more Dark Forces they
literally almost killed me I believe I
believe that I know fighting through
that I know I know listen I'm trying to
people because a lot of people are
struggling oh no you are and you're
helping others you're helping others
please talk about it so people believe
it I'm going to I promise thank
you and Aliens cuz I have aliens in my
room I have a surprise I'm working on
and I'm going to be talking about that
than you so much God bless you God bless
you hey hi how are you I'm good how are
you nice to see you I just want to thank
you I just want to let you know that I'm
originally from Italy so I'm bringing
Itali bra so bringing you to Italy all
my friends and I have to go to Italy
someday I hope I see you out there okay
so I have to get out there every summer
for three month what part of Italy um
North close to B North yeah my favorite
okay so if you there but a lot of people
knows you because I'm bringing you there
oh
sorry you want to come forward
sure I'm sorry the medical medium food
doesn't hold the standard of Italian
food in Italy but here this is different
though I promise I need your opinion
because this is the best I swear wait
till wait till you see
[Laughter]
okay hi how are you I'm good thank you
so much I just I can't believe what you
do for us and I'm so grateful to you
well I'm grateful you're here okay you
sacrif I know you've been through a lot
I know you've been through a lot you've
sacrificed so much for us but you you
have too you've sacrificed for other
people in your lives that's what so says
you've done sacrificing for others
that's what you do and and we know that
okay so I I have to least to do my part
all right do you want to come up here
come up
here amazing well please enjoy the food
okay and I'm
honored okay you got a book for me huh
what's going on what are you doing what
is that what it what does it say good
morning medical medium I like my
smoothie the green one I love your mm
pizza the potato crust oh yeah yeah we
like to potato too and little tapioca
flour and you're four and a half she'll
be five in December amazing is this for
me or this is for me J you want to take
this yeah oh my God you got a book for
me this is for um a friend of mine is
having a kidney transplant to her
daughter her name's Mira I wrote her
name for um you could write a message
for her she would love
that you
excited thank you so much I really
appreciate that want thank you for
everything and the Calabasas event
I'll never forget you want to step up
here we'll come up here oh sorry the
book
yeah awesome amazing enjoy the food
tonight
okay thank you for the
[Laughter]
gift oh my God what's that you got notes
for me
uh-oh whoa hello medical medium I love
the green smoothie
I like Maple in my lemon water I have
healed so much thank you love LS6 wao
what is this here this gu this is very
special too high medical medium what is
your favorite food
mine I like potatoes so do I with
avocado oh that's a treat that's a treat
mashed up with lettuce scooped up I like
your red glasses I'll wear the red ones
again thank you love Noah you guys are
inred incredible these are amazing Jay
can you take these I don't want to lose
those you want to get a picture just
wanted to get a hug oh yes I know I know
you I know you thank you so much for all
of that stuff you do you really Chang
family I'm hon stand you want to want to
come up here we got to come up close we
got to your way back here come on up
come
here piure there we go we got to be up
here all
right amazing so
thank you so much I know I know you
worked hard too thank you thank you for
coming hey you hi can I give you a hi
yes yes thank you so I've improved like
over a 100 symptoms myself but that is
not what I even care about that's all no
well that's amazing no but wait because
I've been working with kids for 30 years
over 30 years and the stuff I'm able to
do for them because of
you yeah that that's definitely some
God's work there it is and they've
changed as different the kids are up
against things that they didn't used to
be up against and people think it's
normal and it's not and I can bring your
tools that's amazing I can give them
hmds and their Tantrums come oh my God
yeah and you see it you see what's
happening when you do that and there's
no there's no placebo effect cuz they
they don't care they're they be no no
they a picture amazing that's
great awes amazing thank you thank you
forut it means the world I can't even
tell you it does it does what's going on
what's this whoa my God that's amazing
there's something on the back here dear
medical Medium you're four years
old you're the
best I love
you almost six years and I have been oh
almost 6 years old and I have been
drinking celery juice in hmds since I
was a baby since you were a baby you
have yeah
what that's
incredible thank you and you got a
little wild blueberry here and all of
that and what's the four
Hearts what is that I like
that whose is this is this mine now okay
okay that's very special you want to get
a picture good good good to meet you
seriously it's an honor it's an honor
okay it's
okay it's an honor
truly you want to get
here no do you want to step up closer
here we'll get up a little closer how's
that Mikey we're going to look right
here everybody okay that's great good
job amazing enjoy the food okay so much
have a message for us tonight you guys
honestly so is extremely proud of what
you've done seriously you have to know
that cuz what happens is people don't
you're hard on yourselves and I know
that he says that you guys get hard on
yourselves sometimes I see it okay but
you come so far you have to understand
that you're doing things no one would do
and and that's a big that's a big deal
okay thank you so much Anthony I
appreciate it you so much love you
too what's going on how are you what's
happening
I have so much I want to say I know
there's a lot of things to say I know I
know I just want to thank you so much
you've like helped me heal my daughter
from cancer and like me from so many
things oh my god oh thank you said my
love thank you okay okay amazing want to
sit want to stand here yeah
sure come on Mike you're
asleep thank you so much than for thank
you you have a good night pleasure to
meet you Mr willing meet pleasure
pleasure indeed sir I love that I love
that I use the word indeed too a lot
it's a great word and I really
appreciate you coming here oh it's been
a pleasure pleasure you're a strong guy
you're a strong guy let me tell you
thank you thank you yeah it's been a
pleasure travel far oh just from Orange
County yeah really close yeah really
close and um yeah yeah so D thank you so
much for everything I feel the same way
okay okay I do it it takes two remember
that okay do it I'm only as good as you
are all right okay
more all right thank you I'm proud of
you thank you so hi Anthony hey how are
you I'm fine thanks how are you step up
here thank you um I had a question I'm
hoping that at some point you and S so
can address um the blood condition that
I have and help me understand it a
little bit more I'll do more stuff about
blood that's what I'll do I really
appreciate that help that in mind so
then I can do more stuff it's a rare
thing okay I understand appreciate it I
I understand completely thank
you
great sorry thank you for coming enjoy
hello hey you know what uh before I F in
today I I drank celery juice and M MD
hmds um after 30 minutes yeah yeah so is
um morning routine every single day
every day yeah how long
um um like year and a half that's a good
long time yeah yeah keep it up yeah yeah
I mean you don't want to stop right you
want to keep on doing it it is it makes
you feel better um in Long Run I believe
in it not you know yeah yeah that's good
that's good if you stop you'll feel it
yes you'll feel it I do after a month of
not doing it you'll be like what was I
doing I got to go back on it yes I feel
confident every single time I drinking C
is yours good good makes me happy yeah
here let's get a picture
yep thank you thank you um get some food
it's amazing thank you hey hey how are
you what's going on I only have one
question okay shoot uh what would Spirit
say about what are some of the most
beneficial gemstones to wear like rose
quartz or Jade or lapis you know I I've
asked uh spirit of compassion this
question
thousands of times throughout the years
the last you know 50 years and more um
and um it it's about it's about
something that really resonates with you
okay that's that's the key okay it's
about how it feels in your hand okay and
how it resonates there there's no
strongest
one um it's it's more of which one is
the most like dear to your heart and how
it feels keep that in mind I love that
let's come up here okay thank
thank you for coming I hope you like the
food I thank you such an honor to meet
you it's honor to meet you amazing is
this your guy this is my little guy and
you you got
D oh my God yeah you got a baby nice to
meet you hey nice to meet you too
pleasure little Errol had open heart
surgery a couple months ago so I just
wanted to come and hopefully get some
light PL
energy for him and we're definitely
doing a light blast okay we're going to
do one all right we are we are all right
and I'll ask S so to make sure a little
baby gets a lot of light thank you all
right proud of you guys thank you I know
you've been through a lot look at you
though huh oh my God yeah he's uh doing
great doing great I hope you guys enjoy
tonight I really do and hang in there
and uh we'll get some food
hopefully yeah let's get a picture thank
you you ready
that's thank you for coming too
seriously oh than
thanks Christian again how's it going
good I wouldn't have it any of the way
yeah this be here you know are you ready
for another good meal oh it's incredible
clean ingredients yeah I it's fresh I
felt so good afterwards I know and the
fact that he's you know grown for us I
know is isn't that awesome is it is
awesome you look great you look great
man thanks I'm trying getting my liver
good and cleaning it up Tak care try the
best I can best I can you know taking it
easy on myself a lot it is a lot you're
always you're always hard on yourself I
am I am really hard on myself my whole
life and uh you know it's it's work in
progress it'll take time and uh look
you're doing it you're doing what you
need to do that's what counts okay all
right you can be proud of that for sure
okay yeah all right so be easy on
yourself you're doing all yeah you're
doing all the right things and you're
going to move forward okay yeah do you
want to get another pick yeah sure let's
do
it I got
you you know I love you brother yeah I I
know that I love you too all right get a
good seat all right too love you
too working on it hey hi good to see you
you got a book for me who's this guy
Mark good to you my daughter this is
your daughter I was going try and carry
or like the other kid I couldn't quite
get there good to see you guys where'd
you guys come from from Orange County
really yeah that's a great place to far
we're so grateful no that's amazing I
I'm so glad that you guys came are you
kidding I am so grateful for you well I
am so grateful than you for bringing a
book for me to sign well this is the
book that started it all and um a friend
of mine shared it with me over the phone
she was reading excerpts from it and she
was um reading about the wild
blueberries to me and I started to cry
on the phone with her I said that is so
beautiful how someone could write about
a blueberry and sounds like poetry to me
you're gonna get me all all choked up
right now because you know it it's it's
uh when you're when you're getting the
information about that wild blueberry
and you're trying to put it down in here
you wonder if anybody's going to
understand or see it I understand it I
understand it I understand you I
understand Spirit of compassion I've
always been very spiritual I'm
empathic well I can't believe you're
here it's elevated my I can't believe
here my life so much and I talk to the
angels all the time I'm so grateful for
you and I meet you in Calabasas and I
told you that I pray for you and I will
always pray for you and always be
grateful for you in the spirit I'm
honored love you so
much
great thank you thank you thank you guys
I'm proud of you okay are you going to
go and get some good food absolutely at
this guy huh nice to meet you nice to
meet
you hey hey what's up nice to meet you
again in person um so I'm pregnant with
twins and um I'm really hoping that you
can do some segment on like pregnancy
and babies and I will it's overdue it's
overdue I have to do that it's
definitely overdue I'm so I'm I'm so
grateful for you it's like you've
literally changed my life and you
changed everybody's lives and it's just
so amazing so thank you so much for
actually like being here in person and
allowing us to talk to you thank you for
com CU in the other events like it was
like a little bit too fast so didn't
really get to talk to you so I'm really
like grateful to actually like be here
right now I can't believe you came and
you're here this is this is amazing you
want to get another pict yeah
sure thank you I'm excited to see what
you think about the food much thank you
so much thank you for coming
what's going on nice to meet you I just
want to say thank you for everything
I've been following you for almost four
years now and it changed my life thank
you it's a long time you're dedicated
very much so committed too that's that's
that's amazing it truly is you know it
you know it works for you you know you
know that yes thank you so much how long
you been sick before um with different
things right during Co you got more than
one thing going on yes I know I know I
know thank you but I'm feeling better
now thank you so much it's you know uh s
so says it's just about
getting um as many symptoms better and
then the rest of it starts to come
together okay it all comes together it
just knock out a few symptoms and the
rest comes okay thank you thank you so
much thank you that's great we go two
more right
here thank you thank thank you thank you
Spirit
compassion hi I'm first time I'm here
with my girlfriend really that oh great
thank you for for a long time so yeah so
you know all her process you know what
she's been doing you know what she's
been working on did she get you on
anything are you doing any celery juice
sometimes yeah I do some stuff good good
good well you know just here to yeah
well thank you for coming let's get a
picture sure I'm glad you're supporting
her and you're here for
her that's amazing you're such a good
friend yes and that that
matters hey hi what's going on hi thank
you just thank you for being a prophet
and giving your life for us and all of
this and you've saved my life and my
kids too my daughter's right there God I
wouldn't be I wouldn't be here I'm from
Jacksonville Florida and wow she's from
Michigan and um and you came from
Michigan to here and came from Florida
to here please yeah please tell us more
about the secrets of this world and do
you like when I talk about all that
stuff love I love it we know that we've
been lying and things like that yes
about everything right yeah yeah it's
great thank you I'm going to do a lot of
that I am cuz I I have fun doing that we
love it we need more and um I need to
know what to do with my teeth if I
should get dental implants or
not well no matter what you have to take
care of yourself okay so things don't
get worse I'm still that's that's still
healing that has to happen no matter
what okay so always do that but things
don't get worse when it comes down to
dental you're taking care of yourself
okay thank you Anthony for
everything than you thank you for
coming here's your daughter good to meet
you you came from Michigan amazing it's
so great to meet you your's amazing be
here with you yeah mom is amazing mom
was doing it before I even was doing it
and uh she and she got you on to she got
you on to the medical medium oh yes and
I've done so much healing and I'm still
on my healing Journey but um it's
wonderful because it's it's so much more
than food like I'm my faith has really
been restored from I listened to your
telegram that was about how so many
people people are faithless and even
people who believe in God I believed I
always believed in God but I I didn't
have the faith and that hit me so hard
and it changed it changed everything for
me listening to that one telegram thank
you for listening to that and I haven't
done a telegram in the last couple days
and I I feel bad and but things have
been so crazy I haven't had a chance to
and I want to do more about that so and
um I know this is kind of a maybe a
little left field but I feel like it's
the only chance I have to to really talk
to you about it but I I work as a
realtor for a living and I really want
to see some medical medium communities
grow and I I want to be part of that
that's amazing and uh I'm not sure I'm
just asking for guidance but um if if I
uh if I brought you a oh my business
card I need to give you my business card
well well look um maybe we can get it to
somebody like security or something your
card okay okay okay
[Music]
amazing thank you for supporting your
mom what's going on raw man yeah and the
raw God yeah yeah that's right yeah
amazing good to see you here okay yeah
you too yeah glad you're here you go by
Nate or Nathan uh Nathan's good yeah
Nate's good it all works you know
familiarity feels
great thanks for coming bro yeah thanks
for you know I'm proud of you right yes
you working hard yeah well I'd like to
be working harder but yeah not too hard
on myself you know all right good good
keep up all the good stuff you're doing
thank you you know I'm proud of you
yeah love you I love you
bro hi hey a hug what's going on huh I'm
good how are you where you from I'm from
the UK UK and you made the trip no I
you're here you're here you live here I
just want to say do you live in LA
California yeah K City over City oh
amazing yeah I'm I'm new to the you know
medical medium really how how new like
two months two months yeah but it's
already changed my life already and I'm
so excited two months is great I know it
could be two days and I'm happy okay
yeah yeah cuz I want you to be able to
do the things you need to do to heal and
that's all that matters and if you
started yesterday that's incredible and
two months is good that's a good good
amount of time yeah okay yeah I'm just
so inspired by you and I think you're
amazing and I'm just so happy to found
you oh I'm honored you're here thank you
for making the drive and getting here
yeah um have you tried the food yet I
have yeah I've been coming here a lot
amazing yeah and I've been trying your
recipes too okay good good let's get a
picture thank you for coming seriously
thank you thank
you hey what's going on how are you oh
my God I'm so excited to meet you
excited to meet you too yeah thank you
did you travel far yes I came from New
York whoa yeah I just came yesterday I'm
honored thank you for coming super
excited yeah you like I'm going to be
there and I actually make my food
inspired by you okay that's a great
honor thank you so soldier in the fight
I guess thank you thank you I need all
the soldiers in the fight I can get okay
yeah thank
you a
little more
wow thank you enjoy enjoy tonight enjoy
the food thank
you thank you oh you're welcome hi hey
thank you so much saved my life I can't
even begin to thank you
enough look you've been through a lot
okay and I know so but you know you
worked hard to get to this point yeah
you know and still working you still are
but you're doing it your intentions are
there you're doing it and you know it's
working yeah okay and you're here you're
here now look how far you've come you're
here you're actually standing right here
on the red carpet with me how crazy that
it's made me want to be here too like
what it's given me is Hope again and
close to God and I've come so far and I
just hope the depersonalization goes
away and I'm that I recognize it
personalization always goes away when
you do the right things it always goes
away okay can I hug you thank you so
much just up everything you're doing I
really appreciate it all but it always
does it always goes
away amazing God bless you thank you so
much what is going on 2015 buddy
nice that is great 2015
yeah okay all right that is a long time
that's a long time that's 10 years in a
in a month okay that's 10 years can I
ask you a
question
stach you do the you do the mono stuff
do you do the mono cleanse sometimes
sometimes you do look into that and see
what hits you okay look into it all
right let's get a picture okay buddy I
love you so much that's
great more thank you thank you for
coming though okay God bless you thank
you so much God bless you thank you for
coming Jess what's happening my man so
awesome to see you again hey good to see
you thank you so much for all the how
well you speak of me your videos it gets
me every time man so thank you very much
man I I mean it yeah I mean it you know
well I feel like the honor is all
mine I know that name just
Lane by the way remember the first com
you read of mine you actually said Jan
Jan
cess but Jan was my dad whoa who passed
when I was very young now I know why
Spirit did that okay so anyway that that
was uh very special with me so well you
get getting me choked up cuz that's a
big deal to me yeah yeah so I got you a
little something too so oh awesome man I
will look at this McDonald's gift card
this means a lot that's cool I'll take
it I'll be I'll be there tomorrow great
great thank you you know I love you man
let's get
I bet you my face like you're like 65 or
66 man
66 awesome thank I love you I love you
brother love you too what's going on
what's going on how you doing good how
are you good good I'm Liam mam me 787
son oh my god really yeah okay that's
cool do I have a old soul do I have an
old soul I I know what you
asked yeah it actually is it's really
old though it's older than mine is it
older than my dad's come here I'll find
out me too 78 no I know who you are me
I'm how are you me tube that's right I
know I
know you're older than your dad that's
good yeah yeah hope that's okay that is
that's good that's okay that's good you
know I love you guys right thank you
thank you for the support seriously
scking around
thanks for the support man I've read
your comments from like since you
started commenting on my feed you know
means the world um how can I make a
loved one make better decisions let's do
a light blast tonight okay send some
light divide it have some go to you send
it to the loved one okay okay all right
thank you any advice let's get a picture
going ins all right right
here can you back up just a little okay
that's perect right
there one
more
that's know I love you guys okay thank
you get some good food thanks me too
thank you love you brother what's going
on no way no way hi no way no you're
going to make me cry thank you for I'm
so
[Laughter]
happy thanks for making the trip and
getting here yeah oh my gosh do you
remember the first time we met yeah I do
I do my gosh you said two words to me
nearly did yeah you said thank you you
looked at me you're about to cry you
said Thank you and I remember running
away cuz I was so
brokenhearted and I'm so happy now no
reason to be brokenhearted no reason I
know not anymore not anymore yeah well
thank you for coming and making the trip
okay yeah it's a big deal yeah do you
want to get a picture yeah my mom is
here this is my mom do you want to do a
pick all together and who's this fyon
look at you look at that
ink oh thank you you know there's no
stopping point you look that you're
that's amazing but you got to slow him
down yeah you got to slow him down he's
going to be covered from here to here
soon let's get a pick thank you thank
you here you guys are going to have to
come up I'm I'm all in this here we go
there we go I'm getting pushed
out oh we're coming for forward well you
guys would have to come forward too
oh that's nice here
go amazing thank you seriously thank you
the best thank you so much good to see
you brother I love you
man what's up I'm how are you oh that's
a handshake oh my God I'm sorry no it's
good it's good I'm always get I'm always
getting uh uh people always say I shake
too hard I grab I grab their hand you
know yeah but you got hands like I've
never seen my hands are a little big
yeah yeah I got big hands your hands are
twice the size of mine yeah so come here
for say thank you for you know help my
family you know there a lot of heals in
my family you know my wife is here right
now in uh my kids you're here who's here
no who's here they out there she's
interview oh she's interviewing right
now okay okay okay no you're going thank
you very much thank you for everything
too thank you for support okay no
abolutely it's 100% you know it's uh
it's really amazing how we had a lot of
Hees my family you know my kids world
yeah it means world let's get a photo
here amazing it thank you Italian I'm
Italian my family is from tus yeah my
last name is Virginia tus tus that's
unbelievable thank
you hey Anthony what's going on to meet
you thank you for all you do I've healed
so much because of mm information so I'm
So You Keep On Healing okay and that's
that's a big deal all right healing so
much is a big deal all the different
symptoms you've knocked a lot of
symptoms away okay I S so he knows that
believe me I mean I wish I had an hour I
would love to talk to you cuz I know how
much you've been through and so just
know that you got my respect okay thank
so let's get a
picture right here
thank thank you for coming hey hi how
are you great how are you good ni neckl
I love that thank you thank you very
much thanks for coming oh thank you you
just amazing person amazing thank you so
much for everything everything you do
for me and everyone else I'm honored I'm
honored thank you thank you you want to
get a picture together
thank hope you enjoy the food today
thank you I will thank you so
much what's going on what's going
on good to see you it's a great honor I
love the I love the crystal right there
thank you very nice first time wearing
it actually first time yes it it looks
great it's very powerful I can tell oh
thank you a definitely a a different
shape how are you guys
doing good tired doing right you're
tired yeah tired I am too don't worry
don't
worry no no but that's good that's good
that you're here though yeah it's good
to see when when's the last time you had
a
snack three apples in the hotel three
apples in the hotel before 3 hours ago
well it's time to eat it's time it's
time to eat you want to get a picture
yeah okay let's do that picture we're
going to have to come up here though
we're going to have to come up this way
closer the look right here at the
white amazing can I just get the kids
with you
too can I just oh oh just the kids oh
yes yes
yes one
more okay that's too cool that's too
cool that's amazing thank you for coming
truly hello what's going on I know you
oh my God are you good to see you oh
thank you for coming what's this Angel
yeah
angel angel a piece that's very nice
that's very nice I'm going to hold on to
that thank you and I have a question yes
um from the last uh podcast episode you
said about God's song what is it God's
song can you tell me I'm actually going
to I'm actually going to write something
that that explains that because I
because uh it's so powerful I want
people to know what that was oh okay so
you're going to know you're going to
know don't worry yeah I promise thank
you so
much thank you for coming okay hope you
enjoy the food thank you so much thank
you you're the best what's going on me I
I saw you at every one I met you for the
first time I'm from Mexico I'm from
enada amazing and I'm so happy to be
here I'm like we live like near here so
every time you going to be here and
we're going to be here thank you thank
you okay I'm going to try to be here a
lot is this your man where did you find
him where did you find them uh 35 years
ago and you're still around I'm still
around you want to get a picture
yes thank
you here
thank you guys enjoy the food enjoy the
food I hope you like
it hey how are you I'm fine I hope I
won't lose my voice again um it's a
blessing to be here you have a strong
voice you do okay I do that's good I'm
uh full of love and I know I'm on
purpose plus but I'm full of um doubt
and and fears and I would just love to
get a message from
so the things you fear about you don't
you you don't have to fear about those
things I don't know what it means I'm
just getting okay there certain things
we have to fear about it's important to
fear about them and then there's certain
things we don't have to there's some
things that that you don't have to fear
about that's that's what Spirit say okay
thank you okay and then you you know you
can you you know okay I'll know it thank
you so
much I love
you thank you for so much I'm so
grateful get some good food you yes
what's going on hi hi Anthony Esmeralda
pleasure to meet you likewise thank you
for coming I just
um you know my question I wanted to ask
you if I was going to be okay but I
think being here is a testament of that
we're going to do a light blast later
and direct the light where you want to
direct it yes okay and I want to thank
you Anthony for Having the courage to
Prevail for not only yourself but for
others because you truly are answering
prayers people that are broken lost
hopeless people that are not sure if
they're going to wait to see another day
I know that was me and that's why I you
understand you understand what that is
that's a big deal to me and and
uh I know that people don't understand
that and it and it feels like uh it
feels like you're alone it is feels very
lonely it is but there but there's some
people here that understand it thank you
for coming yes thank you Anthony and I
understand and on on just behalf of not
only myself I want to thank you to those
that that are praying and you know just
remind them that they're heard they're
enough and they can and will be okay
thank you that means the world thank
youthy do it does
amazing give some good food thank you
for
coming what's going on it's so nice to
meet you nice to meet you is this your
guy yes what's happening how are you he
nice to meet you nice to meet you nice
to meet you too hey uh we've been
helping out kby he's watching right now
Island okay I was wonder if we have a
message for S so for him tell him tell
him we love him okay tell him we love
him okay okay wonderful we understand
thank you thank you all right and keep
fighting absolutely appreciate it thank
you for all the sacrifices you do for us
thank you for thank you for looking out
for him absolutely absolutely I mean it
I mean it yeah of course and you guys
are doing just beautiful things and
you're always supporting me and I love
you for it absolutely I always wanted to
tell you that thank you just didn't have
a chance yet absolutely well thank you
for this chance and opportunity well
let's get a pick we ask oh can we do the
robot with you rob robot pose yeah robot
pose robot pose let's
go okay okay Step Up step up a little
bit
you thank you be good all right
hi Anthony hey what's going on trying to
be calm this time I'm trying to be calm
too don't worry I'm staying
calm good to see you so I have a request
um I don't know I know you don't have a
prompt for your speech every night but
maybe you can talk about when our souls
all came before together maybe I can
maybe I can ask Spirit of compassion to
give me a little bit more Soul stuff
tonight yeah okay I'll do that I'll do
that thanks so much who knows what
spirit will say
try to get some good food
thanks what's going on I was just
thanking Joel for the music of calabas
was great that was great Heart of Gold
blue skies yeah I kept going and going
um so I thought a lot about what I
wanted to say and there's two things one
I'm one of those medical medium husbands
that gets dragged into this yep and you
know guys out there if you're listening
to me let yourself get dragged into this
you would not believe how much healing
I've accomplished by doing this for 9
years and the other thing is what I
wanted to thank you for is not just the
information but for bringing people
together to let people know they're not
alone that there's a community doing
events like this connecting people
online your Instagram stories you repost
give all those people a really strong
voice in the community it's just super
powerful and I just means world I really
appreciate it and and I know you
understand I do and I know that like
really understand I understand I
understand now more than ever yes it's
super important it means the world to me
Community I'm not kidding and that's why
I'm here it means the world to me let's
get a pick yeah do it but it really does
hey big guy Straight Ahead
yeah yeah right on I'm honored you're
here thanks man I love you
man what's going on Judy Gro hey Judy
nice to see you this is the thir time I
S uhhuh I'm honored can I sign this or
no yes I'm the brave one who gave you
the fession fruit and the lemon wait a
minute huh I'm the brave one who gave
you a passion fruit and the lemon oh my
God I ate those well you know what I
still have some more left the passion
fruits talking about the basket yes yeah
I I have that seriously yeah I've been
eating them I I wasn't hoping I took
them home with me and then they they
keep for a long time I had to get them
out of the basket so they stay preserved
that's amazing thanks you want to get a
picture thanks um and this is um hungar
that's really cool that's my first
one you're from Hungary
mhm 20 that's an amazing country by the
way oh been there yeah it's an amazing I
haven't been there but it's an amazing
country I uh spirit always tells
me hey how are you good how are you good
nice to see you again I know thank you
for coming third time now that's
incredible yeah yeah it's wonderful
thanks
for e
but I haven't been in front of a kitten
bet I know I know even crazy busy but I
love we should we should I'd love to jam
sometime you play drums uh guitar
play gu then I'll have to do the drums
on that g yeah you got let's get a pick
all
right give me the
point you know I'm proud of you you know
that thank you for coming again you're
got it thanks thank
you what is going on I'm Aton that's how
you say my name Aton at yeah okay like
it sounds like an I I'm not going to
forget okay and I wanted to say that I
felt like last night I was like just
asking me me me me me but I just want
you to know like you're freaking amazing
and the bomb.com and I just really
really like I want to speak for my heart
sometimes it's hard because I have
Metals in my brain but you'll get them
out yeah I know but I just seriously
appreciate you appreciate you too okay I
would love to hear anything you have to
say to me well we'll get a picture okay
here
okay
more thank you
Spirit knows that you like to be
organized and you like to have
everything in like you know good working
order in life and you don't like when
things are messy and all kinds of stuff
and you're very hard on yourself you
just have to be easy on yourself you're
doing the right things you're moving
forward okay okay thank
you thank you hey hey what's going on
how are you how are you doing good yes
yes do you need anything no no but I got
your support that's all that counts okay
yeah I got your support thank you you're
welcome you're doing awesome thank you
and amazing and you are amazing well
thank you for coming seriously do you
want to get a
picture you
ready
here oh you're the best thank you see
you welcome what's going on I know I
know that's great though that's great
let's get a pick yeah sure how you doing
you're doing okay tonight hey you know
I'm I'm enjoying myself I'm here with
wonderful people and getting to meet you
again going to have some fun tonight oh
man dude you have no idea love that I
love that yeah so
Cera perfect cool cool yeah well hang in
there for the night we're going to have
some fun okay any speci love brother any
good work for me this night just keep on
moving forward like you do okay you got
good intentions every day you're a good
man yeah thanks man what's going on how
are you you're back today this is great
we are back I know I know you gave me
cookies when did you make them today no
I made them on when did we fly out
Monday Monday I made them on Sunday and
froze them okay good good good I can't
wait to have them I'm going to eat them
I'm going to eat them at 1:00 in the
morning oh good enjoy them all right
let's all right looking right here you
guys are pros at this
point amazing love you guys see you guys
see you a little bit hello hey good to
see you always proud of all the things
you're doing okay thank you it's good to
see you guys how you going you know you
know the information I know that all
your posts are always so great I mean
you're you're a great support you know I
care and that it means the world to me
so I just wanted you to know that cuz I
never got a chance to tell you okay
thank
you come come up a little bit further
okay thank you so much I'll cat you
later have a good
night hey I missed you hey what's going
on thank you for coming okay oh yes I
got an opportunity so I wanted to see
you again yes well this that's good
that's good you should be here okay
let's get a pick yeah we'll get another
one
let Fe that bag here
we incredible Joy the night thank you so
much hey what's going on got a guitar
pick I do cuz somebody gave it to
me anything you can tell me anything you
can tell me about me well you have to
always remember that you're a good
person okay you didn't do anything wrong
you're a good person keep that in your
mind cuz somewhere in back of your
Consciousness s so tells me that you you
have a hard time with that okay let's
get a picture I have one
question can you heal from chronic pain
two more right here one two three look
right
there the answers are there for that for
sure you've got to just look into and
dig in
okay hey you have the most beautiful
skin I do you it's a miracle and you
have beautiful hands I notice it on the
videos all the time I know they've been
getting kind of choppy and beat up I've
been you know I've been you know
scraping them up by accident and
whatever but I can't I do the best I can
well you're doing the best you can for
all of us so you get it's an honor it's
an honor hi my name is tomara nice to
meet you tomorrow today it's a great
name thank you it's a great name and I'm
Alexander Sophia from Alexander Sophia
Facebook yes of course oh my God so cute
what yeah may give you hug oh my God hi
oh my God and Nicholas Russell told me
to give you a high five really I'll take
it I'll take it um do we have like a
quick second for me to show you a
picture of a dog I'm trying to help
stenosis of the
Year oh my God I know I just spent
$1,000 today oh this way I'm not sure
it's all these cameras right here right
here
it thank
you thank you well thank you for showing
me if something comes I'll I'll get a
hold of you guys okay thank you thank
you for everything an you I appreciate
you hey hello what's going
on let's get a picture of you guys yes
good good good here step up here
probably go up a little further you
ready
2 camera okay okay I got you now
amazing thank you guys for coming again
okay than you I love your hat again I
know I wor so
you what's going on what do you got
there little Journal
you're I was just wanted to say thank
you again and tell spirit thank you you
guys worked so hard for us and I
appreciate it I appreciate you guys okay
all of you but all the work you do I
appreciate that you know that I care
okay means the world to me oh you want a
photo you better get one better get
one that's great right there more thank
you thank you amazing love you thank you
what's going on I'm doing good thank you
for coming oh thank you thank you for
all you do
okay thank you thank you amazing thank
you so much enjoy the food don't worry
thank you for
coming my hi hey how are you nice to
meet you nice to meet you too um thank
you for coming yes I very nervous so I
wrote down a couple things you wrote
down some things just a couple
things the adrenals
yep so you got all that
pain and other things going on yeah
swelling all the
time but most important I I I I sent all
this up here okay and and so keep keep
an eye out when you go to sleep at night
listen out for Angels listen out for any
kind of responses that could come okay
okay all right thank you thank you let's
get a picture
okay whoa there you are I can't see
thank you for coming thank
you hey good to see you yeah good to see
you again yes I know I know it's great
to see you thank you for coming do you
want to get a picture sure here step
right up here if you
can thank you for coming I always wanted
to say to you um thank you for
I'm so nervous now actually and I can't
get it out for having found me and for
thank you for for actually saving my
life this is something I wanted to means
the world that that that happened okay
cuz you're here right now it's all that
matters keep up all the good stuff
you're doing okay thank you I'm really
proud of you thanks so much that it's
the best news I've ever heard Maran hey
sorry what's going on oh
no it's all good no that was good I that
was that was
cool thank you for coming yeah again
again I was your last night and before
and I can't stop thinking you um I'm
honored you're here yeah well let's get
a picture yeah step right up here I just
a prayer because I have a cancer scare
and I don't know what's going on and I
just just well we're going to do a light
blast so let's just okay let's do that
thank you
thank you for coming thank you I'll see
you okay yes we love
you nice to meet you sir hey nice to
meet you good to see you you as well
thank you for coming yeah thanks I'm a
virgin to this so hey that's all right
it's brand new yeah brand new never
heard of it till an hour ago are you
serious dead ass oh pardon my language
that's incredible man yeah let's uh
let's get it picked together all right
sounds good step up
right here that's
great two
more thank you I'm honored you're here
all right thank you sir okay I am I
am hey what's happening I'm so glad to
see you again thanks for coming yeah
thank you for being here I have two
questions so you can you got a
question it's on this this note paper
yeah
well you're getting strong okay you're
strong strong person this is going to
come that's going to come s right yeah
that's going to come and you and you got
to you know know that you have
everything it takes get get your
confidence up to match all the good
things you have okay yeah you got to get
your all these beautiful things that you
have you can do so much but confidence
you got to at least match that okay so
my confidence needs to go we got to get
that up a little bit to match how many
good things you have yeah okay okay all
right well thank you wait do we get a
picture where
[Music]
that
for good to see you thank you for
everything you do I healed my thyroid
now I help women I'm I'm an intuitive
wealth co uh health coach
I just became a Hay House author so no
way really this is my card if you ever
want to do a YouTube about women's
health us or somewhere else here here
amazing I lived in um London I'm from
Australia amazing well thank you I'll
I'll uh take this thank you all right
all right I've giv you two others at the
other two events but we're friends now
okay okay good let's let's get a
picture
more when did you become coming hey aome
I won the Riders competition no coming
out in July my God I'm proud you coming
out I'm proud of you thank you so much
I'll see
you hey hi Anthony how are you how are
you good to see you are thank you for
coming thanks for doing this um I wasn't
really prepared to actually have a
moment to speak with you but it's so
nice that we get the chance to do that
so just thank you thank you for that I
appreciate that I appreciate you coming
making the trip just getting here
waiting in line and being here I I I'm
honored okay let's get a picture sure
all right I'll have you come up further
how's
that amazing are you going to get some
good food in there I'm so excited to get
some can I ask is there anything Spirit
wants to tell me just quickly before I
get out of here anything Spirit wants to
say before I get out of here you got to
think about some of the things like in
the past that were really good okay
because you lose track of some of the
good things that have happened in your
life you kind of don't connect with it
as much make sure you
do oh my God got the red
hair I know what to say I'm overwhelmed
I just love you so much and thank you
for everything you do I'm just um
thankful and grateful forever that I
found your book which book did you find
did you find the first one oh my God
found I saw you the first time when you
came like 14 years ago in Los Angeles
when you had the big event that was the
first time that book just came to me I
remember that thank you thank you can I
give you a yes oh my
God so much let's get a picture and also
I want to tell you um my mom oh yeah
thank
you send send Mom my blessings thank you
and she's from Germany so she follows
you too and she's 84 years old and
changed completely her diet send my love
please and that's amazing tell her
that's incredible thank
you hey hello how are you how you been
good how are you how are you're doing
good I'm doing great thank you I was in
your the practitioners group when that
was and I'm colon therapist and I tell
everybody every day C juice every single
client that comes in oh my God you're
such a so you in the prti
back 8 years ago yeah that's
unbelievable I was you made a comment
when we had we had to submit questions
yes and I was asking about Cambo because
I tried everything in the time you're
like oh somebody's crazy on that frog
juice or whatever frog frog poison that
was me terrible stuff terrible stuff I
was like what did I do to my life I
don't know yeah I know people are
misguided out there but that's that's
how what happens when people are
searching for answers they don't know
let's get a
come on up here I'm going to have to
walk up
here amazing I hope you get some good
food okay much oh my gosh I live a mile
down the road oh my God okay
perfect
music oo I like that is that silver no
it doesn't look it's not it looks like
shiny like silver let's get a picture
okay one quick question okay if there's
144,000 Angels does that mean the Raptor
is kind of a
joke
amazing and I can't wait are you going
to go and get some good food is there
going to be a Rapture is there going to
be I'm going to do a whole thing about
all of that pry thank
you hi hey pleasure to meet you Anthony
pleasure to meet you Cassandra Cassandra
nice to meet you thank you for coming
thank you for having us I just want to
say thank you for all the work you've
done um been following a few years and
it's just been a lovely experience and
I'm local so even better that you've
posted everything oh my God that's
amazing okay that's perfect it works out
thanks for doing like medical medium
stuff and supporting me for a few years
now thank you I I really appreciate it
likewise what's kind of picture I did
have one question um hot yoga what's oh
I I don't I don't like hot yoga
okay it's too hard on anybody with
chronic illness I think it's way too
hard and I think people who aren't
chronically sick and do it we themselves
and don't know it okay yeah that's kind
of what I was gathering so thank you for
your time appreciate it of course let's
get a picture I don't want you to to not
get a
picture thank you thanks thank you so
much have a wonderful
night hey how are you how are you doing
Lucy good oh my God you're my name made
my day it's funny first time I saw you I
froze I barely said thank you that the
book sign in second time I wanted to
make sure I'd let you know how grateful
my family is because with your
information I was able to save my mom's
life this time I'm like I don't tell her
tell her I send my love okay she's oh
she's so excited I'm here then the third
time I was like I got to make sure I say
my name and you already know it I
already know it let's get a I do have a
question um here come without having a
med
okay thank you okay great you got about
heavy medals no no um without a medical
degree you know to help other people
other than family and friends you just
got to do what's what's good in your
heart okay I am trying but I don't feel
like I'm reaching enough well there's
things you can do I mean there's there's
you might you might want to get
something then like of course a
potential those are amazing you can do
that if you need to but but keep on
forging ahead with the work okay all
right thank
you hey how are you very good nice to
see you you
too thanks for com thank you thank you
just wondering if you had any
messages you're in you live in
California right I do yes I know I know
you I do and you have you don't it's
okay I do okay I think I do let's get a
picture I never watch you before I mean
I had seen me
before she look so
familiar thank you for coming have you
tried the food here um yes how would I
know you're from
California thank you so much thank you
thank
you hello Anthony I'm Sophia hey thank
you from the bottom of my heart for your
sacrifices really well I appreciate you
being here and now let's take a photo
before I st crying do you want to get a
picture yeah we better get one then
thanks
thank you thank you for coming I hope
you get some good food it's so
amazing Stella sorry for waiting so long
no it was totally worth it I would do it
again five times over here come over
here okay thank you so much you've
really changed my life and I was
hospitalized for severe eczema and Mera
and um you totally changed my life so
thank you thank you for hanging in there
okay yeah it was really that's brutal
yeah it was like a lifelong thing so
yeah
I'm so very special person thank you to
get through that and be on the other
side of that yeah proud thank
you thank you for coming I hope you
enjoy the food tonight I will really
good yeah I'm
excited what's going on how are you how
are you thanks to meet you nice to meet
you too uh my name's Claire hi Claire I
just wanted to say um thank you for
giving people like something really good
to believe in and like giving people
hope oh I'm honored you're here and that
means the world to me okay and I receive
that thank you I do let's get a picture
okay thank you thank you so much
[Music]
hey there you amazing our family has
been working with medical medium
protocols we would love to ask you a
question of the spirit of compassion is
is there anything that might help my
brother who has
Parkinson's um if you're able just if
you're able nothing expected otherwise
and and and we're doing the metal we're
doing heavy metal detox and we're doing
all the protocols to do with the brain
saver protocols and cleans the 28 day
cleanse and maybe just a signature or
anything that comes to mind yeah we just
have to we have to continue to get the
metal out for sure right okay yes that's
critical
yes lot of copper a lot of copper
wonderful okay and um
um there's a way to heal beautiful
beautiful God bless you thank you love
you too want to get a picture you guys
sure yes
please yes take a step turn take a step
take a step good beautiful God bless you
you're amazing thank you so much for
everything you
do
okay good okay very good you we love you
too so
much we love you so
much hi Anthony what's going on talk to
me I like those glasses
I'm holding a vision since watching your
videos I'm holding a vision of the
spiritual war ending without a war I
know I know I'm cross fingers crossed
I'm working on I'm working on the
spiritual book a little bit at a time
and working on some other stuff and and
I'm going to be bringing some of that
information in oh the good stuff let's
let's hope it's well in this letter in
this letter for you our information that
I'm hoping will change your life okay
thank you let's get a picture let's step
up here though
perfect thank you you can I keep this
yes that's yours
okay what's going on guys hi
everything's going on how are you who's
this strapping guy John Kelly John Kelly
good name good Kelly yes yes I've been
waiting eight years to meet you oh my
God are you kidding I'm not Kidd where
you guys from houon Texas Houston Texas
I'm a Texas Fan yeah that's great great
place to be look I want to thank you for
giving my giving me my my wife back so
my God she was sick and sick and you
gave me my wife back you gave me my life
back you saved our marriage yes thank
God and now you guys you guys are are
meant to be together you know that's the
whole point well we want to help other
people um other couples that are going
through all this thank you thank you
that's a big deal it's tremendous
purpose right there just can't take you
enough well I appreciate you guys so
much yeah yeah oh thank you seriously
for getting here okay did you guys fly
from there to here yeah sure we came
just for for you guys are
amazing seriously here oh oh thank you
amazing do you want to get a picture
together of course you remember this
forever you guys ready right here this
camera got it here we go
M this way
got it I'm excited about that have a
picture with you guys it's an honor
listen it is okay a Texas guy thank you
love you guys you too hope you enjoy the
food thank
you hey you how you again what's going
on S oh my God so honored to meet you
again thanks for coming I Met You in
Calabasas I know I know remember me from
Scotland we talked about Scot know I
know I know I'm a big fan of Scotland
for a lot of reasons history
the Earth there is different yeah when
you put a shovel in it it's it's
entirely different it's it's a little
it's a little rocky but it's
beautiful yeah here step got some
ancient history and very sacred know I
know and people who come from there they
go back a long ways thank you for
putting this on for us so inspired by
your ability to channel this wisdom come
onor thank you hope you enjoy everything
enjoy the food thank you thank you for
being
here what's going on how are you oh
pleasure I painted something for what do
you got you got something this is for
you waa that's that's
incredable it symbolizes the fact that
your information just absolutely changed
my life and allowed me to pursue my
passions which is arts and so I can do
that now because of you and so you're
going to get me definitely teared up
here because I you know know the fact
that that was kind of being held back
from not being well is heartbreaking for
me to hear so to know that you're you're
here though and you're you're doing it
okay it means the world there's
something in the back for you too you
don't have to read it now but you're
tired you're tired read it another time
but please we step right up here that's
I will read it I will read
it that's so cool thank you okay I
treasure this all right
you hi Anthony thank you so much my name
is na and I love I'm so grateful for so
many things and I just want to say the
what you say about the emotions and the
energy the food I will I'll sit and when
I'm having the food sometimes I'll
reread cuz it's like a whole Alchemy a
whole universe there's so many but I
wanted to share that cuz I haven't heard
anybody share about that so oh thank you
thank you for coming here let's get a
picture together step right up here all
right oh sorry right here thank you it's
bright right here
smile amazing thank you enjoy the food
thank you so
much what's going on hey how you doing
doing thank you so much for everything
that's you for everything you're amazing
oh thanks for coming okay thank you I'm
from South Africa wa um did you fly from
there to here or you here you're in area
I here but I walked from a few blocks
away so that's
I sometimes it's harder to go a few
blocks to here than fly here for some
people so okay so that's very good I
just wanted to thank you and also to
quickly ask is there am I allowed to ask
if there's anything that so says I
should do or my mom in South Africa
who's dealing with a brain
problem she's eating all the good stuff
she is she's got your books brain sa
good good she has the that's actually
the best book to have for that tell just
keep on digging being deep in there that
there's information in there to help
with everything that she's doing so just
keep up the good work she's very smart
that's it that's what she says she's
very smart okay so um she is connected
too spiritually and smart so she can
find the information she needs in there
okay want to get a picture and anything
I need to do you're you're her greatest
suppor here we go two two more thank you
always stay hydrated okay thank you so
much
thanks hi hey again good to see you
thank you for coming thank you so much I
thank you for saving my life I'm I'm
actually finally starting to enjoy life
again and
sorry so I appreciate you being here
okay I do all right thank you sorry I I
just can't put into what what I feeling
I know I know it's hard to it's hard
hard to to get it out it's hard to get
it out but you got you got to do what I
do right I try to laugh I try to laugh
when it's starting to starting to come
out and pour and that's so I try to
laugh and I and that's coming now y here
thank you so
much more thank you thank you for coming
okay you're the best you're the best
love you hello what's going on good to
see you good to see you too
thank you for coming yeah of course
thank you for everything do you want to
get a picture yes
okay you ready
yes are you going to have some good food
yes all right cool we're going to have
fun yes we
are hello what's going on what's
happening I'm so grateful I'm grateful
for you to be here okay my life back I
was on my knees to
God and so you so so you're you're one
of the people that hear when I say that
and I say there's a big difference when
you're on your hands and knees praying
to God because you don't know where to
go with this and then you find the
answer I find the answer my heart pours
out okay gave me my life back my my
heart pours out my doctor is this for me
yes who's it from from my doctor this is
from your doctor yes really she Drew
this for you
you Sarah here step right up
here this is celery ju this is from your
daughter yes you want to show it or not
yes I do okay it's very special awesome
look it right here two more beautiful
thank you this celery juice in your
clothes she's an artist yes okay this is
very important to me thank you
okay what's going on you guys hey hey
I'm
Shana Shana Shana Shana my husband your
husband fedo fed Rico amazing how are
you I'm Kira Kira it's good to meet you
Sophie Sophia Sophia thank you guys for
coming it's very nice I really
appreciate it okay here thank you for
everything I appreciate you okay
and really yes every day no matter where
we are okay yeah okay my mind is blown
okay all right it is I left you a CD
with your you did okay good I'll make
sure I see that okay let's get a picture
you guys all right we'll come on
this how's this we we'll do this Mikey
can you get us all
in we're going to look straight ahead
yep that's
awesome than you guys than you guys
thank you so much some good food okay I
hope you enjoy
it hey you
hi good to see you yeah you want to get
a picture I want to yeah do you want to
step up
here looking right here yes can can you
write something what is important for
me down for the next
step can you write something what is
important for me down for the next step
I should go should do um focus on
I
I scared I misunderstood you last time
or that you misunder me last
time she want to
that's your guy that's my husband that's
your husband he's taking off he's
running away from us I know good to see
you he's shy uh thank you for everything
that you do for everybody and your
message welcome thank you for coming
where did you come from I live in Tango
oh my God you took the trip later you
took the drive down the hill were you
way up there minutes it's 20 minutes
down the the windy road down TOA to here
okay here come step over here oh okay
that's right here great
more thank you thank you for coming yeah
thank you so much you going to have some
good food yeah very excited
thanks hey good to see you that's for
you man really yeah I wonder what could
be in here little trinket used to be my
mom's wa it used to be your mom's yeah
that's a big deal that's a big deal
let's get a pick all
right right
here that's awesome two more you can put
the thumb down for this one mix it up
thank you thank you my brother means the
world okay thank you thank you you saved
my
life hey what's going on thanks for
coming you want to get another Pig yeah
can I Let's do let's go one here step
right up here
[Music]
okay thank you for coming tonight
okay got a little
dog do you remember me yes of course no
you don't I
do Spirit tells me I remember what's
this this your purse you want me to take
it let's get a picture
okay look at this camera right
here here we
go few more got it
thank you thank you for bringing your
little pup oh yeah thank you H yeah
you thank you hey what's going
on nice to meet you nice to see you you
it's great to see you love you be on the
Stars man we've been doing your stuff
means the world to me listen to me we've
been doing it since
20166 16 it tell you what talk to me
it's been a journey since I was 9 okay
and then then and and then but you're
working on it with the medical medium
information definitely are you kidding
we do all the prots he's studied like
over a thousand hours over th hours
since 16 and he help me did you watch
all the videos listen to all the podcast
bless you no dude the podcast everyone
really I got all my
notes oh yeah yeah we we spread the
words people I love you guys we're
grateful for you okay and I believe that
let's get a picture together come on
it's a great honor by the way thanks
brother this camera here that's awesome
right here
way thank you for spreading the word too
oh you are okay I love you you ever
going to do anything you ever going to
do anything with AI I am I am it's
something a little different but I am in
the future I can help um I can volunteer
if you like all right good to know
that's good to know for
me hi you got the mask yeah good good do
you remember me yeah come here come step
up here how are you good how about you I
like this this is good yeah
how how you been um good yeah doesc have
anything to say to me doesc have
anything to say to me
just you know you're
you you need to every now and then just
go a little bit
further that's what that's what he says
just go a little bit further here let's
get a picture I don't know what it means
but all right right here this camera
okay thank you and two more
thank you thank you for coming thank
you that's it that's it oh everybody the
meet and greet with aw just wrapped and
now we're going to go inside Cafe
Gratitude to enjoy the medical medium
for course dinner let's
go thank you
my parents did this with me
[Applause]
know
I knew we ADR
[Applause]
I wanted to talk to you so I struggle
with a lot of dark thoughts like about
ending my life and stuff about ending my
life and stuff just you got to you got
to if you're if you're if you're
suffering from that you have to be you
have to be easy on yourself okay sorry
was a no it's okay it's okay world this
is great here we go little smile for
this one aesome and it's because of just
all the suffering I've been through and
the but what happens is that the dark
thoughts you got to not you got to not
fear them and you have to you have to
be you have to know that it's okay to
have them because attacks me how can I
[Music]
wish
[Applause]
AR
you
[Applause]
your
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
[Applause]
that
left
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
a
[Music]
[Applause]
you're always
after I get the hey guys look
here everyone look this way can you guys
Le in at the back
we go
[Applause]
every
[Music]
[Applause]
to
CL
[Applause]
[Music]
real
[Applause]
[Music]
I could say that
[Applause]
friend
[Music]
need
[Applause]
GRE
[Music]
say
[Applause]
[Music]
I went
to for
[Applause]
[Music]
some
I
[Applause]
[Music]
also
[Applause]
great
every
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
[Applause]
I just want to say
hi I just wanted to say hi
r
[Music]
[Applause]
got
[Music]
[Applause]
what are you doing
[Music]
[Applause]
us e
[Music]
[Applause]
to
[Music]
k
[Applause]
for this amazing opportunity to be here
thank youc thank you C gratitude we
appreciate you so much thank you thank
you thank you you're the most incredible
human being on the planet thank you for
all you do to fight for the chronically
ill
thank so much so thank you Chef Drew and
Cafe Gratitude and all the wonderful
people here that are making this happen
it's truly is a dream come true and we
need more places like this and we just
we appreciate it so much more than than
you'll ever know it means so much thank
you from the bottom of our heart
the other one
[Applause]
to
spe
[Applause]
[Music]
for all
[Applause]
spe
[Music]
[Applause]
e for
all right so this is a big crowd
tonight how's the food going all
right what do you guys think is it going
good that looks good too right
there what's going on guys how you guys
doing good to see you all
right yeah yeah it's a big crowd it is
can you hear me
okay okay all right good good good good
where are we we're on the third course
yet what do you guys think is it good
it's amazing right I know incredible
legendary restaurant legendary truly is
you got people outside too and
everything so I have to say hi over
there yeah yeah M good to see you again
good to see you guys incredible so
everybody's happy then everybody's happy
I don't have to
[Applause]
worry I'm over there you know getting
nervous I want people happy here I'm
glad I'm glad that's that's amazing this
rest has a lot of deep meaning for me
okay like I I first came here many years
ago Scott first came here many years ago
all right sat down in this restaurant
right here and honestly honestly just an
amazing experience I had personally hey
chars and you know it it still has that
incredible
incredible feeling to it when I step
into it years later eer and I don't have
that with other restaurants it's not
like you know things change as time goes
on but they really really kept the
energy here there's a soul in this
restaurant and I can't find that in
other places so this has great meaning
to me and I wanted to tell you guys
that and with restaurants over time you
know things happen and then when they
happen you know it's not the same end
energy cuz it's years go by but they
kept it strong and that soul is strong
and that's the kind of place that I love
to have medical medium recipes in and
this is it you guys have it you're
eating it it's mind-blowing it really
is truly
truly honestly and listen I'll go around
here for a minute here too is there
anybody outside is that what's happening
some people out there as
well um amazing I'm just going to peek
my head over here you guys just hang
on so we got people out
here all
right all
right all right the Rowdy bunch is out
here okay I get it this is hey Christian
good to see you again amazing man
amazing you guys food's okay out here
right all right good good great to see
you guys seriously beautiful I I
oh
yeah I was saying and I know you guys
probably heard it it's a legendary
restaurant deep meaning in my heart in
my life you know and I've even had
dreams many years ago about this
restaurant which is the strangest thing
I wasn't standing in the restaurant with
my shirt off or anything in the dream
okay and wondering oh no what happened
but I was in here eating in a dream one
time yeah I was and you know I I've
thought about it on and off over the
years and I wonder if that dream was
because yeah we're having the medical
medium party in here okay think about
that what a beautiful night and a
beautiful chance to be outside too you
guys have great seats incredible I love
you too you guys you guys are
amazing so yeah um I want to introduce
you guys to two people if I could find
them here's one right here Patrick hosis
right
here all right this is the COO of Cafe
Gratitude all right Chef Drew Ellis
right
here yeah he's got to get the Applause
all right we
got I remember being on a zoom call okay
a zoom call with these two all right I'm
sure they were probably looking at me
like all right what do we got here what
do we got here and we were talking and
Chef Drew was like no we're going to do
we're going to do something with these
recipes we're going to fix these up I'm
like fix these
[Laughter]
up and he did he did he took it to a
level where I can't stop eating it all
right
so um I don't know about your favorite
dish out of these dishes right I love
all of them but those Nores those sushi
rolls those are
insane Cafe Gratitude has a question of
the day the question is what are you
grateful for right I don't know if you
want to take the
mic well to to give a little bit of a
context we founded Cafe Gratitude
Matthew and tury Englehart found a cafe
gratitude in 2004 so this is our 20th
anniversary this is one of
the this is one of the initiatives that
we are undertaking this collaboration
with medical medium to celebrate the 20
years and there was the original Cafe
was founded uh around a board game that
Matthew and trusy created maybe some of
you know this story um a a a board game
in abundance and gratitude so they would
come into the cafe they open the cafe so
that people could come in and play this
board game in abundance and gratitude
and part of what that you know the
affirmations on the menu the question of
the day this was all part of the
practice of putting our attention in
gratitude which I know you as a
community this is probably why you're
finding your home here and there's a
resonance here right so as I said
earlier we do ask a question of the day
to every customer that comes in the door
we ask it internally to each other at
the beginning of our days at the
beginning of our shifts um for many
years it was what are you grateful for
um and that's what it's going to be
tonight so you might I invite you to
share with the person next to you what
you might be grateful for today but we
do change it every day so and it it's
really just the question of the day is
really there to put your attention on
gratitude and abundance so that's what
we do that's what we do here that's what
you guys are doing out in the world so
it's a great a great
combination Chef Drew um he's been
working really hard right and he makes
it just look like it's effortless he
just does if I was uh sweating back
there making these Foods I'd be like
passed out on the ground so
where well I'm honored I'm honored but I
just want to say that these two amazing
human beings right here made this happen
okay all
right they made this happen okay I am
grateful for that that's what I'm
grateful for all right so I want to tell
everybody that too um Chef Drew Ellis
is's a really really experienced Chef
longtime Chef I got tremendous respect
for that you know I've been called a
chef but I'm
not I've been called the chef by friends
and family but believe me there's a
difference okay you guys are
experiencing that difference and um and
I just can't thank you guys enough
seriously Patrick okay and you can tell
these guys care about the community they
care about you know everybody who needs
good food and they just keep that strong
and it's in their hearts it's in their
souls it's in my heart and soul thank
you guys for enjoying this food and and
being here with all of us
[Music]
seriously well we'll let you guys eat
for a little bit okay then I'll come
back in a little while maybe we'll have
a talk and who knows what we'll say all
right amazing all right you guys I'll
head back over here love
you love you man love you all right you
guys out side you guys are okay you got
enough good good all right there you
are good good you got enough food so far
still
coming all right amazing
while
[Applause]
GRE
[Music]
this my HB
[Applause]
de
for a couple Mons
[Applause]
like
e
e e
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
[Applause]
meander
you
[Applause]
CH chill CH am
that's so awesome
[Applause]
spe for
[Music]
to
[Applause]
e
e for
[Applause]
think
they were like
[Music]
[Applause]
light
really
[Applause]
know
pry amaz
[Applause]
[Music]
for e
[Applause]
okay
that was really good
[Applause]
they
[Music]
e e
[Applause]
B
you
[Music]
[Applause]
C
[Music]
[Applause]
for for
[Music]
[Applause]
ni
everybody
[Applause]
think
[Music]
[Applause]
amaz
you e
[Applause]
[Music]
like e
[Applause]
[Music]
it
[Applause]
for e
[Music]
the
hey everyone so we're inside Cafe
Gratitude in Venus and we're going to
talk to some of our diners here about
their uh dining experience with the
medical medium menu what are you eating
at the moment um we're eating the potato
and bean and cow dish oh beautiful
beautiful you can have a look here here
it is here that's the I am Noble right
correct yeah beautiful I just finished
it myself it was great tonight I've had
it the last two nights and I feel like
tonight it was upped again the level was
amazing yeah what did you think of it I
had so much flavor lot of flavor really
good the whole meal the whole night has
been great what was your favorite
dish probably the
fajitas they were really really
good those heers with the Millet
tortilla oh my gosh what about your
favorite dish uh
Sushi I haven't had uh rice for 3 and
1/2 years so that was a treat oh
beautiful beautiful and if you don't
mind I'm going to kind of put my arm
across here but I'm going to ask you
what your favorite meal was that's
really hard to pick actually
[Applause]
what did you think of the guacamole oh
so good very good probably the best
guacamole I've ever had really good wow
do you think that F gratitude offering
this medical medium menu on their menu
uh will help people with their healing
Journey make it a bit easier for them
more enjoyable definitely yeah I think
having this option of something easy to
come get and will definitely help people
Inspire their healing and just work hard
at it yeah now did you all know each
other before this
evening um well Mary and I met uh in the
June in June and I've just met Teresa
and Masa today I just met these two
today oh yeah we just met a little bit
ago like a month ago and we decided to
drive down from the Bay Area to this
event so it's been really amazing such a
great are you enjoying hanging out with
the community this evening yes
yeah well thank you so much for talking
to us really appreciate your time thank
you thank you okay we're going to go
find some more people to talk to see
what they think of the food but everyone
is having such a great time here as you
can hear everyone's talking away having
a great time yes hi a so nice to meet
you can I sit down next to you this is
awesome oh well now look this is perfect
so nice to meet you what's your name I'm
Janette so nice to meet you so nice to
meet you too what are your what's your
name Lanna Lanna and Karen so nice to
meet you now were you all friends before
this event tonight no actually we we met
here we're friends now we're friends now
yes that's beautiful so what made you
want to come to this dinner tonight well
Anthony Williams uh really changed my
life I had this um rare condition in my
knee called pbns and um basically a
doctor said oh you have to keep getting
surgeries and that's the only way to
heal it I was like there's got to be
something more than that right and so
just to condense a story in like 202s
basically um I started reading his books
right in 2020 and um
I was like oh it's viral I said that's
what it is you know and so I was
supposed to have like my fourth knee
surgery like a year and a half ago but
because of his information the condition
in my knee you know like it even after
three knee surgeries like they're like
it's not spreading anymore right like
and um so it's he's completely changed
my life to be able to continue to walk
you know that's incredible yeah thank
you oh thank you so much for sharing
that what are you eating at the moment
here as well we got to have a look at
this oh yeah so we're having the spicy
portabello fajitas which is this and
then we're having the bean and spicy
potato bitable it's really cool you kind
of see how it looks like cheese but
that's actually potato oh yeah that's so
cool right what was your favorite out of
this menu I really like the potato the
the kelp noodles were really good too
the second one here y it was really
really good yeah yeah oh beautiful what
about you what what are you eating at
the moment um I'm I'm still working on
my tacos and my potatoes over here it's
very very delicious um I really enjoyed
everything everything was amazing like
even the presentation of everything was
so thoughtful and beautiful um my
favorite thing was the sushi actually
and I'm looking at this and I'm like oh
I'm going to take this home and I'm
going to recreate this and I'm realizing
that this is going to take me days like
days to make one sushi roll like to
marinate the pumpkin seeds and soak them
overnight and then make the tofu and
then let the tofu set up overnight like
I mean this is like days of prep you
know so you used to be a chef I worked
as a chef for N9 years in South Florida
yeah so I I really connected with with
Chef Drew on that and I I have a lot of
respect for anyone who does this for a
living it's really a lot of work it's a
labor of love and to even do like
healing food like this
is just it's on another level it's
incredible and I have to say like when
you get into medical medium and you
start cooking without oil and without
like Butters and all these things it
completely changes everything it's like
you have to learn how to cook all over
again because nothing comes out the same
when you're not cooking with tons of
salt and tons of oils and Butters and
things like that so for this to be this
good it really is an Testament to
their skill level really truly talented
very talented Cooks back there very
blessed by them and we we ask the angels
to bless them as well I love that we're
getting your feedback as a former Chef
because there is a lot of work that goes
into this and that Sushi the way that
it's made and presented like you're
saying is just I mean it's incredible
it's really it is a lot of work oh my
gosh yeah it it really is so much work
and you know that these guys are on
their feet for you know 9 hours a day
back there doing all of this work and
it's a treat for us because we're the
ones that are always doing all this work
you know it's we don't get to go to a
place where we have food like this like
it's such a gift for us I do all the
cooking at home I do all the prep work I
do all the the shopping and all the um
washing and cutting and peeling and so
for me to have a meal like this served
to me is like is truly truly a gift that
I'm so thankful for so thank you Anthony
thank you and what is your favorite of
the dishes can you pick a favorite oh
yeah hands down I loved the sushi like
that was my favorite I'm hoping there's
some extra to take
home and do you have a favorite what are
you eating there um these Millet
tortillas are delicious and uh this
fajita with it's like a pello mushroom
it's really really delicious and I I
love the sushi too that was that was a
treat that was amazing and I'm looking
forward to that dessert sounds really
good too smoothie smoothie Is Amazing by
the way yes yes oh my I yes I am
precious the Smoothie guys oh it is it's
such a like it's a beautiful it does
feel kind of like a guilty pleasure
dessert but you know everything that is
good in it you
know it's very healthy this is such a
blessing because everything is healthy
the food don't have to worry about the
ingredients and look at us going out
being like regular people eating out at
our restaurant and we have our healing
food you know it's just really amazing
so
amazing sitting at this table I feel
like I should have been in here dining
with you did you have another guest here
or did I take this seat this seat the
seat is for you a thank you thank you I
just want to say you're a really good
host you just got to keep doing that
thank you so much you're have so sweet
kind picture with you we'll do a quick
selfie but we have to be quick cuz we're
still on the live stream but we can do a
quick selfie on the live
stream thank you so much I've had so
much fun I might come back and have the
smoothie with you we'll see if I can
sneak away and join your table I might
do that such an honor thank you so much
oh such an honor talking to you you're
beautiful oh thank you so much thank you
I'm going to go talk to some other
guests quickly but I'll be back I'll be
back thank you all for talking to us
okay we have another table here that is
look I think that they're liking the
food so much they're packing up some
to-go boxes but we're going to go in
here can I squeeze in
here I'm sorry you're eating I'll let
you finish eating before we talk to you
the food so good you've only got a
little bit left we were coming to check
out your food but it's all gone
last so how was the dining experience
this evening oh pretty wonderful I've
been thinking that it's been a long time
since I've been in a restaurant where we
could both eat the same thing and I
could have a full meal is pretty fun and
so you came together then yes my husband
oh so I toate you thank you yeah so we
don't get to sit down in a restaurant
together almost ever yeah used to do it
a lot yeah so this is a great treat that
and that's why when she first heard
about this she was immediately excited
because it it's it becomes a restaurant
where she can quit wearing anything on
the menu is absolutely fair game you
know so what a treat that is you know so
what a treat I feel like it looks like
you've enjoyed the food cuz there's
nothing left huh yep yep very much what
was your favorite meal I liked the Nori
rolls and the burrito bowl those are my
favorites so good what was your favorite
over here uh yeah the uh I am
Noble you're very
Noble so I must be yeah yeah very Noble
so was this a bit of a date night for
you
twoo well yeah kind of a date overnight
we're staying in a hotel so yeah yeah we
just drove down from San Elizabeth bow
and yeah yeah yeah we've been married a
couple years so it's nice to have a trip
out yeah yeah and if you're staying
overnight you can always come back
tomorrow as well well we'll be staying
overnight in Calabasas so oh calabas
drive back yet it is a bit of a drive
back but you can always come back for
another weekend away absolutely yeah
that'd be fun well thank you so much for
talking to us I'm going to around to the
other guests at your table too yeah
thank you thank you I'm going to I'm
going to I'm going to be over here but
just one moment would you like to talk
to us yes can I squeeze in I'm crashing
everyone's
table what did you think of the meal
this evening it was very good delicious
absolutely delicious from the
sushi to the all the rest of the meals
just like wow tastes so good and we were
starving yes yes I know it was a little
bit of a weight tonight but you got in
and it made it worth it yes definitely
worth it we we Devour the sushi in like
seconds she's feeding the babies there
there wait tell me more tell me
more what was that oh yeah I'm I'm
having
twins yes how many months along are you
I'm starting my 9 months so yeah 35 and
A2 weeks 36 weeks what a special night
out am I allowed to ask is are you
Partners or friends or just okay you're
here on your own or just met I have to
get permission from
tell wait who are you here with tonight
are you just on your own or you with
okay so the three of you and then you
just met these lovely Lov group I met
you too on the on the last event too so
yeah
so yeah uhhuh close oh my God we I show
you how to eat um sushi tonight with the
Wasabi mix into the um soy sauce yeah
yeah and he liked it and you liked it no
no she's great she she knows what to
do dishes for tour oh well isn't he
lucky to sit at the table with you and
you can you know very
lucky what is it like for you guys
coming to these events and connecting
with the community do you enjoy that
love it I mean it's such a wonderful
Community every one is just so nice like
it's so special I'm pretending
now oh you're having so much fun here
you've got one more course the dessert
the I am precious forward to that the
dessert so excited dessert yes who
doesn't
right of course and the great thing is
you have it and you still feel light and
happy and healthy it's beautiful yes
absolutely we want to thank Anthony
William and so for everything that you
guys have done for us we're so forever
grateful I mean this is like I think I'm
just we're so blessed to be born the
same Century as Anthony we really are I
mean this is a lifetime and to
experience such a wonderful meeting with
Anthony tonight I mean the at the Culver
City one we weren't able to really have
that oneon-one
and even at the last one in calabas and
not that to be able to see him talk to
us and spend a little time with us wow
it's it's a miracle because you know
what if I've known that I would buy all
the tickets for the last 4 days and come
and just talk to him no seriously it's a
it's a blessing in the sky and we want
to thank Anthony for that yeah nice of
you to mention that they work very hard
behind the scenes to bring to put these
events on and to bring that together he
works very hard so that's very nice of
you to mention that doing it keep doing
it yeah we will always come yeah and
every event that I all these three
events that IED they've just been
running amazingly it's un I've never
seen anything like it the old production
everything and you all the people behind
it everything is
just got
unbelievable for that well I'm so glad
that you're all enjoying the evening
having a great time uh I think I'm just
going to hang out here for a little
moment because I I think we might just
be going back to showing some more of
the diners and that but that's it from
me here inside here at the dining
experience the Cafe Gratitude medical
medium collaboration this is so so much
fun thank you for letting me crash your
[Laughter]
table yeah thank you oh there's the
dessert there's the dessert
yeah oh look you get a little bottle
too
[Applause]
e e
w
[Applause]
why
spe
[Applause]
[Music]
real
[Applause]
is for
w
[Applause]
for for
[Music]
[Applause]
so e
[Music]
[Applause]
what's your favorite color
[Music]
[Applause]
you for
I for
[Applause]
good
for
[Applause]
[Music]
e for
[Applause]
know
e e
[Applause]
spe
for for
in
[Applause]
[Music]
I
[Applause]
last e
really
you guys ready for a little
talk about time
[Applause]
right good to see you guys you guys okay
out there okay thank
youy
so you guys one thing that Spirit of
compassion always tells me is that time
is one of the things that so much of us
on planet Earth are stuck worrying about
it's
time and seems to have a law over our
heads every day time for this time for
that chasing our
taals time just rules
everything and the one thing though
about time that's interesting and I just
want to start with this is when you
first get sick do you guys remember the
first time you got sick the first time
you got a symptom you remember remember
what year it
was maybe what month it
was some people what day it was it was
October this you know was this
day that's how much time means so much
to
us that's how much it governs us as well
we remember things just like when we
were SI
and
then there's something really
interesting about the medical meme
information and it really doesn't have
that law over its head Spirit of
compassion has always told me that the
medical medium information because it
comes from above it doesn't come from me
it's
Timeless there's something to say about
that because there's so many things out
there like biohacks and Trends and
everything else it's not timeless
it screws people up it hurts them it
throws them in different
directions but it's not
Timeless it's not
Timeless and so the medical medium
information from above is timeless and
that brings me to the next thing I
wanted to tell you
guys is about our soul are you guys
ready to talk a little bit about our
soul
[Applause]
so because we're under the law of time
here on planet Earth and it brings about
so much stress because it does got to
get to work on time you got to call
somebody on time everything has to be on
time so we're governed by that and it's
very stressful and difficult but our
souls it's a different story our souls
don't really see time the same
they just don't in fact when we leave
here someday whether it's 100 years 50
years whatever it is and we leave here
our soul is free from time itself and it
floats through space and time it
travels from this Earth through the
solar system it's not governed by any
time at all and it's free and it lives
forever I think that a lot of people
people what holds them back is feeling
like they're trapped under the law of
time they don't they don't think that
they're ever going to have another
chance but that's not true that's not
true and I think one part of how we heal
is to
know these very laws to understand this
a little bit it's a big part of healing
it's critical the angels don't actually
get governed by time
either they're not under that rule or
that law but we can access them anytime
we want we can they're at our fingertips
if we need them they're there for us how
many of you guys are accessing angels
are any of you guys trying to do
that are you guys talking angels do you
talk to angels at night before
bed it's a powerful connection that
everybody has the god-given right to do
is to access the Angels talk to the
angels use them to help you battle
time because the angels
can when we're going through life and
we're chasing our tails and we're lost
and confused we have tools that we can
have access to and we do have access to
every single day and one is the
connection to the angels the other is
understanding that our soul lives
forever no matter what I think a lot of
people think that this is the only shot
you got down here and it's not your only
shot you live forever all the
information you gather and Learn and
Grow from stays in our soul it travels
far and wide in the future 100 years
from now it's these very things that can
give you some peace while you're healing
your physical body body here now and
that's critical having peace while
you're healing how many of you struggled
with not having the peace while
healing did you ever have that battle
you're trying to heal but this is in
your way you're trying to heal but
that's in your way you're trying to heal
but you don't really know how you're up
against so
much right so it's critical to get
moments of peace in our life while we're
healing
and we have that it's in our hands we
can gather that piece and part of it is
the information that comes above have
you gotten any piece from the
information from s
so I know it feels like this you know
we're on a
ship and we're out at
Sea and we're floating out there and
floating out
there and we're on the sea of confusion
any of you remember the Sea of confusion
right and that sea of confusion can be a
long time for a lot of you guys with
chronic illness how many of you guys
have been out in that sea before you
found this information from above you've
been out there you know what it's like
to be lost at
sea it's it's
real that's real and you find this
information from above and then you're
freed from that sea of
confusion and that's
powerful keep in mind that your body's
healing every day I know some of you get
kind of lost with that and you don't
think you're healing anymore I know that
can creep up that's how it works here
fears creep up concerns creep up and
then we think we're not healing but your
body is healing it's healing every
single day and all you have to do is
just apply one thing one thing that's
the information of the medical medium
information you apply one thing and it's
life- changing for your body life
changing for your body just one thing
just the wild blueberry every single day
it's one thing right just a celery juice
it's one thing but just one thing and
things are changing inside the
body they are you can find peace in that
if you do one thing you find peace in
that if you need to access an angel you
can find peace in that so I wanted to
talk a little bit about this because so
many people struggle with this how many
people do you know in your life that are
struggling do you know anybody in your
life that's struggling and you care
about them you love them you're worried
about them and they're struggling
somebody in your life you know
somebody right and they're struggling
with what trying to have peace is that
what it is peace in their hearts peace
in their mind peace in their
head okay and so I want you to know that
if you need to get this information to
them and say look you can find peace
it's there you just need to know your
body's healing no matter what it will
heal just give it something and it will
heal sure it might might take a little
while for some somebody might take some
time for some people but it can heal and
it will heal over time and letting them
know and the other thing is having the
faith how many people you know struggle
with faith do you know anybody that
struggles with faith you guys you do
it's a difficult one right there it's a
difficult one because this world kind of
sucks it out of you sucks it away from
you it beats you down and it takes away
our faith that's what this world is like
right that's what it
does but that's okay because we can
build that back up we can build it up
and build it up a little bit each day
and a little bit each day I tell
people that look for therapies all the
time they're looking for therapies of
the mind they're looking for help
through the mind and they're visiting
their old old baggage of yester year and
they're clinging on to it and clinging
on to it and it's holding them down
every day how many people have a little
bit of that you you think something's
holding you back from the past
that's something that takes our peace
away as well and we can cut that line
that's holding back all that baggage
that's keeping it attached to us we can
cut that fishing line we can let it go
and that's another form of Peace we can
get and what you'll find out there when
you really break it break it down and
you talk to somebody they're missing
that peace they're missing that Faith
they're missing something they don't
have that strength or that belief that
they can talk to an angel they're not
sure about any information working it's
hard to get them to understand say
medical medium
information but all this can change but
you guys have already come this far
you've already gone through all this you
beat out the Sea of confusion you got
away from there you got off that
ocean you know medical medium
information is classic and timeless
it's timeless it is it's here for you
today it's here for you tomorrow it's
here for somebody a year from now 10
years from now a 100 years from now it's
here for them and it's always going to
beat out the other stuff out there that
keeps on recycling all over again and
all over again because this will always
be here because it came from
above and the other thing is being hard
on yourself too I notice
that today right here everybody coming
in a lot of people are hard on
themselves Spirit of compassion was
telling me this person's hard on
themselves this person is hard on
themselves they think they're a bad
person they have a lot of fears have a
lot of worries all these
things and we don't have to have that
because you're a good person you didn't
do anything wrong you're a good person
you didn't do anything wrong you didn't
create your illness you're not the
reason why you got sick you're not the
reason why you're sick now and still
struggling you're not it's not your
fault but we tend to kind of believe
that somehow and carry that and then
punish
ourselves and we have to learn to let
that go too now I've heard that saying
let it go and it's really insulting it's
like just let it go how many times have
you heard that out there just let it go
just let it go
right yeah you can't let something go if
you don't understand it you can't let
something go if you just don't have
another way to do it and one way to do
it is you didn't create your illness you
didn't you didn't create your problem
you're not the reason for it you didn't
start it you're not a bad person it's
not your fault you're not faulty you're
not
broken that has to be embedded in your
Consciousness forever in your soul and
you guys know this and you're doing
it when I was just sitting over here a
little bit a couple minutes ago Spirit
of compassion was saying let them know
that they are good you are good doesn't
matter what happened in the past a lot
of times we beat ourselves up when we
get sick we beat ourselves up when we
get chronic illness it just happens
that's the way the world kind of
like does its
thing but you guys don't have to believe
or think that anymore you're good people
you've been through hell and back how
many of you guys have been through so
much I somebody told me they were on
their hands and knees praying to God
they
were and you're here now you're standing
you're
healing and it's a
miracle the thing about me is I can only
do so much I need you guys to do the
other part and I talked about that the
other night a little bit and you guys
are doing the other part I've never seen
anything anything like it I've never
seen anything like it seriously all the
years over for three
decades you guys have me so blown away
it's it's
unbelievable
[Applause]
yeah how many of you are having dreams
where you have a struggle in a
dream how many of you have a dream where
it's
difficult how many of you have a dream
where it's a bad
dream I know there's a a few of you and
I just want to tell you right now and I
said something about this recently is
that's you healing the
emotional body that's you healing the
soul and the emotional parts of the
brain how many of you have PTSD
throughout the years you got PTSD
really you got
PTSD right okay after this light blast
tonight we're knocking that stuff back
I'm telling you now
[Music]
[Applause]
out tonight's the night we really clean
up some things okay because you guys
know you know what you're doing you do
you do but we're really going to help it
along tonight we
are s so wanted me to talk about these
various things for a moment kind of
opening things up Consciousness wise
soulwise kind of airing some things
things out it's going to be a little
emotional and then we're going to send
some serious light
down this is going to be an incredible
night I know that when you get sick it's
hard to be heard it's hard to be
validated it is when you're somebody
with chronic sickness or you have a
symtom it's hard for that to hear that
validation to get that validation have
you struggled with that at all we're
getting that
validation right right that alone is
hard to deal with all on its own and
then being heard that's another thing
too the light that's coming down
tonight's a little
different it's a little different than
the light that came down yesterday it's
a little different than the light that
came down the other day and that's what
I've been
told when I was over there on the red
carpet and I was greeting you
guys Spirit of compassion was is telling
me some different things okay there's
something to do with the way the stars
are set up tonight something to do with
where we are in history in the
moment few things that were coming down
the information it's pretty
intense and S so said tonight's a
different night it's a different
night and this light blast that's right
is going to be different
many of you are going to see it I know
that many of you saw it for the first
time yesterday where you saw the
light you're going to see it again it's
going to be a little different a little
intense and your dreams are going to be
more different than normal which is why
I brought those up so tonight kind of
get an idea or keep track of what you're
dreaming about when you wake up in the
morning and so forth because your dreams
are going to be different tonight they
are
[Applause]
let's do a little light blast if you
guys are ready you guys ready out there
okay all
right so where do you want the light to
hit keep that in
mind tonight Spirit of compassion was
telling me that you can split the light
if you really need to if you want to
send some of it to somebody else and
keep some yourself that's how different
of a night it
is you can direct all the light to
somebody if you want but you can also
like I said split it now I've never
heard that before from Spirit of
compassion so it's not like I knew this
for years and years and years oh you can
just split the light that's all you can
split the light this is new for
me but I'm always surp I still get
surprises I'm always surprised this is
how it
works because it's not coming from me I
get thrown these
Louis but splitting the light is what's
happening tonight if you want to send it
to somebody else and also keep
it A lot's coming down and we're able to
do
it so where do you want the light to hit
who do you want it to hit is it somebody
you love is it somebody that you know is
it somebody that you care about is it
somebody that you just want to see
recover and they need some kind of
ignition like a starting point some kind
of moment where it's ignite it it's
going to ignite inside of us and you can
send a little to somebody else if you
choose and you don't have to do that
either just keep it all for yourself
it's perfectly fine you'll be glowing
for quite a while and anybody you touch
after this point for quite a while is
going to feel
it this light's going to come out of the
pal your hand when you do Touch Somebody
by the way it's a piece of information
that's important to know so anybody you
know and you touch them on top of the
head it's going to come right out of the
palm of your hand when you touch the top
of their
head think about the Stars everybody
close your eyes for a moment Close Your
Eyes For a Moment Close Your Eyes For a
Moment think about the
Stars you see the stars doesn't have to
be perfect but do you see them and then
think about what's behind those stars
because that's where the light's coming
from it's coming from
there on the count of three take a deep
breath then release we're not going to
do a light blast yet one 2 three deep
breath
in and then
release like I said before it's not a
contest you don't have to hold your
breath or take the biggest deepest
breath
count a three again one two three deep
in and then
release fantastic we're going to do the
first one I'm just waiting right now
for I'm being patient I'm
waiting right about now okay the first
one count of three we're going to take a
deep breath and we're going to hold it
and then I'll say release okay when we
release count of three one two three
deep breath in hold it light light light
release it's a much more
powerful blast of light than normal so
we're we we had to kind of back that
down for a second and now we're going to
just gradually acclimate we're going to
do one more right now on the count of
three deep breath in one two three deep
breath in hold it light light Light
Light
release you guys hanging in there you're
hanging in
there all right get ready for this
then on the count of three deep breath
in one 2 3 deep breath
in hold it light light light light light
release okay okay we only have a few
people in here that are blocked we have
about 25 or or
30 do you feel a block anybody still you
feel a block there's one over here
there's one over here
okay on the count of three this is a
much more potent one one 2 3 deep breath
in hold it light light light light
release
there's only about two more people in
here everybody just relax for a second
take a deep breath in and out count of
three one 2 3 deep breath in and then
release okay where do you want that
light to hit this is going to be one of
the last
ones think about where you want the
light to hit get ready count of three 1
2 3 deep breath
in hold it
light light light light
release we have one person in here we
have one person in
here I think they're out
there this is the last one right
here okay yep get ready last one
one two 3 deep breath in hold it light
light light light
release success you guys
success don't don't don't operate heavy
machinery
like in the next 10
minutes okay everybody just relax and
have a good time this one's going to
stick a little longer and it's going to
be interesting because things are going
to happen like
realizations lots of
realizations are going to kick in in the
next coming just two days keep that in
mind so don't be surprised don't be
shocked just say oh you know what I knew
it was
coming I knew it was
coming as I said before the other night
you guys are old souls and I have to say
it again I just can't ignore it it it's
rare I get a chance to be physically in
person with you guys is it
rare is
it it is it's very rare so I have to say
cuz not only is it true has great
meaning in my heart you guys are old
souls even the little
baby very old soul little babies older
Soul than the parents of course
[Laughter]
some of you guys have been around for
10,000
years some even a little longer I'm
jealous I mean I'd be lucky if I can get
years but some of you guys are really
old
souls and I think from what I can hear
from s so constantly that there's an
appreciation for having you here for
having you you do what you're doing for
believing in the information in the work
for believing in me that's a big
deal it takes something to really trust
a lot of you guys lot of trust has been
broken in your
life it hasn't been
easy and I know how that
works and you guys trust in so so and
you trust in me and I can't thank you
enough and I'm truly grateful for
that from here on out I want you guys to
know something has
changed if you feel like you've been
stuck something has changed
tonight I'm telling you this because I'm
hearing that right now
[Applause]
Spirit of compassion tries to slip in a
few
words wants me to stop talking
sometimes tells me okay enough of
that this is
important I'm like well no I think this
is important that's so he says this is
important and so it's critical critical
to
know something has changed tonight and I
have to say that again I have no
choice but I need you guys to know
that anybody in here and everybody in
here and even a few people walking by
the street who got hit by
light because a bunch
did and they weren't even part of the
party
yeah there's a change that has happened
keep that in mind when you realize a
pattern has been
broken because patterns have been broken
as of
tonight you guys you know I love you and
this has been an incredible
day and thank you for being being
patient thank you for hanging out thank
you for eating this incredible
food and um hope to see you guys again
[Applause]
okay restaurant everybody knows about
Cafe Gratitude and what we're looking at
right here I'm with Chef Drew right here
okay and I am honored to actually be
standing here for a lot of reasons the
food's incredible here but what's
happening is medical medium dishes are
going to be on the menu here they are
right here Drew just dressed them up
this is an incredible thing happening I
don't even know what to say cuz I'm that
excited Drew thank you for doing all
that you've done to help this happen to
make this happen and I think people are
really going to love this because
because this is incredible healing food
no oils we don't even have nuts in these
dishes this is incredible no soy in
these dishes these are clean as clean
and pure can ever get here at Cafe
Gratitude where only that could happen
here that's incredible that's how
incredible this restaurant is so I'm
excited true thank you thank you for the
opportunity to work together I think
this is an incredibly inspiring
collaboration I'm really really excited
about it well I'm honored can you tell
us a little bit about your work right
here what Chef Drew did he elevated the
medical medium recipes and he was like
look we can do this and we can do a
little bit of this your people will love
it and I'm like oh my God bring it on
and now they are unbelievable so medical
medium food is like now was here now
it's here and in here so it doesn't get
any better than that so that's how
excited I am thank you I mean it's it's
an alignment of working with Whole Foods
working with with herbs rather than and
spices no oils which you know really
allows you to explore other palletes
which I think is really an exciting
opportunity as a chef I love that I'm
excited I can't wait to see people come
in order these dishes taste them and
taste that healing effects that clean
incredible Pure Food going into their
body here at Cafe Gratitude I mean that
I'm so excited about this to see people
their reactions how they feel with the
food they're going to love it already
people love the medical medium you know
recipes the medical medium Entre and all
that but when they come here and they
actually have your work collaborated
with these medical medium recipes and
you I mean Drew you were amazing Cafe
Gratitude they're just like what do you
like we'll do this we'll do that what
what do your people look out for what
are they worried about right all of that
Organics for sure that's something that
we're really focused on Whole Foods for
sure we don't use any of the processed
you know sort of plant-based Foods and I
just really feel like people will come
and have experience this menu in a way
that doesn't feel like it was an
afterthought you know to be able to come
in and have the dietary guidelines that
you're promoting out in the world coming
into a restaurant setting and still
having a really flavorful Rich
experience I mean it's it's incredible
and you worked hard on these that's the
thing you weren't like hey aw give me a
couple of dishes you're like let's work
on this let's work together on this and
you worked hard we did it this is
incredible and it's right here and and
when people come in they're going to be
like oh my God I'm actually able to get
medical medium dishes in Cafe Gratitude
yeah that is a big deal that is huge for
the medical medium community so many
people they they have a hard time
getting dishes out there getting foods
that they want out there and restaurants
and they're always in restaurants saying
can you give me this can you give me
that they don't know what they're
getting they're always worried and so
they don't have to worry when they come
in and Cafe Gratitude that's what's
incredible it's like all that worry goes
away you just come in and you get the
best of the best right here don't even
have to think about it the highest
quality and that's mind-blowing right
there and I'm excited that the cafe
gratitud customer is going to be able to
experience this other way of eating
which they may have not have had the
experience before so that's another
exciting yeah yeah totally it's like
people going to be like what is this
medical medium you know like what is
what is the protocol what what does it
heal you know how can I learn more about
it so that's what they're going to get
from from this menu incredible and then
you elevated you actually brought even
more flavor to it and that is you took
it to the next level of more flavor so I
really appreciate it and the medical
medium people are going to appreciate
that too they're going to be like this
is better than making it themselves or
this is better than any any place they
can get it's not even possible actually
this is where you get it it's right here
at Cafe Gratitude so I'm grateful and
thank you for all your hard work this is
amazing
[Music]
what an incredible talk by aw and light
blast wow uh we just finished the dinner
inside at Cafe Gratitude and I'm
standing here with Jen Jen what was that
life blast like for you it was
incredibly powerful I'm so grateful yes
how would you describe what were your
feeling you
know the way he was describing the
difference in the light tonight really
touched me um and I was directing the
light to my soul specifically
so it felt like the right right time to
do that so it was profound wow beautiful
and what was your experience like
earlier in the evening meeting aw you
know I was really just trying to be calm
the last couple times I met him I was a
little bit frenetic so I was just so
glad that I was able to be grounded and
stay
calm yeah and I did request that he
speak about the soul tonight if he could
so I was just so grateful that he was
able to honor that yeah what was it
about this event that made you want to
come here to Cafe Gratitude this
evening so I've been using the medical
medium information for 9 and a half
years now um and I found that
information in June of
2015 um when we were living in LA
and my mother-in-law was starting a
decline in her health toward the end of
her life and
um she ended up in a care facility just
about a mile east of here and it was
very difficult watching her will give up
as the months went
on and she lost that will to live um and
so we were coming to visit her at that
care facility every few days um toward
the end of her life and it was so hard
to watch that and witness it as her life
force was sort of eing away
um and so we were trying to implement
Anthony's information um and we would
come out of that care facility feeling
just
exhausted and hungry and tired and just
needing a place of comfort and I
remember finding Cafe Gratitude on the
phone and it was a plant-based organic
restaurant and so we would come here and
this was our refuge during that time um
and it really became a safe haven for us
during that difficult um time period and
she did end up passing um and she wanted
to be buried in Southern Illinois where
she was from um so we ended up arranging
her burial and we did a road trip across
the country from La um and it turned out
it's very interesting timing um my
youngest brother had just moved to
Kansas
City and he had moved because he was
trying to escape a heroin
addiction and he wanted a fresh start in
a new
city and so he had only been there a
week or two and he was desperate to find
a job so he could stabilize in Kansas
City um and keep himself sober so we
ended up meeting up with him on our road
trip to go to her
funeral and I was desperate to find a
place to eat and Kansas
City and so I remember we were driving
into Kansas City I've never been there
in my life I don't know where to eat
it's famous for barbecue right and um
I'm looking at the phone and and I'm
like you know vegan organic restaurant
and the first result is Cafe
Gratitude there's a Cafe Gratitude in
Kansas City really yeah wow
so I thought oh my God am I still
looking at the LA search results right I
was so confused but it turned out no
there is indeed a Cafe Gratitude in
Kansas city
so we met my brother and we said hey we
know you don't care about vegan food but
that's what we want to eat and you know
we're taking you out to eat so you have
to eat at this restaurant with us and so
we took him there um and he loved it it
absolutely changed something for him the
approach of Cafe Gratitude and the
attitude and the treatment of their
employees and their customer customers
um so impressed him he had worked in the
food industry previously and he was so
impressed that night with Cafe Gratitude
that he decided to apply for a job and
he um he he got the job and he ended up
working at that Cafe Gratitude in Kansas
City for several years and they helped
him with his drug
rehabilitation and um he was able to
establish himself in Kansas City and
have that fresh start and go to college
and um you know start a career and get
married and
buy a house and it's just such a mayy
hug yeah
oh I know it's been difficult for you to
tell this story like you felt now was
the right time yeah it's just um it's
such a
beautiful you know the way it's woven
together medical medium which led me to
Cafe Gratitude which helped me to make
this difference in my brother's life
yeah and so I'm just so grateful to you
know to Cafe Gratitude for being that
place of Refuge for us and that place of
Refuge for my brother and um and for
Anthony cuz he was the start of it all
does your brother know that you're here
this evening uh I don't think
so but hi John if you're if you're
[Music]
watching cuz this is such a special
moment for you yeah you know I've really
avoided the camera at the other
events so yeah oh well thank you for
being so vulnerable and courageous for
sharing your story with us did you enjoy
the night did you have fun yeah it was
so special we got to um meet up with our
friends that we met in line in June and
we just had a lovely evening with them
and just been fantastic yeah isn't that
great about the community as well with
the with medical medium Community it's
just it's so awesome and I love that
people make friends in line here waiting
for event yeah there I mean it was like
we found our family waiting in the line
yeah in June and it's just it's amazing
and what was your favorite meal to see
evening I think I have to say the
fajitas
mhm those are good you should come get
them yeah they are so good do do you
think Cafe Gratitude will help people on
their healing journey by having these
items available on their menu help their
healing journey and make it easier and
more enjoyable for them absolutely I
hope that everybody in the Southern
California area comes and takes
advantage of this amazing opportunity to
have this beautiful healing menu a Cafe
Gratitude yeah yeah thank you so much
again for opening up I that you're
amazing yeah you're
amazing uh enjoy the rest of the evening
I think you're heading off this way to
see Shelly over there and then we'll
we've got some other people to interview
yeah it wasn't too bad was it it wasn't
too bad thanks Danielle thank you so
much okay bye okay we've got a couple of
other people hi I'm Daniel meet you I'm
Kira hi Daniel to meet you Danielle how
was your evening this evening oh my God
so magical we feel so blessed to be here
and so grateful yeah
yeah I forgot to say my name I'm Soph
it's okay it's okay it's all good uh
with the evening what was your favorite
part of it oh I aside from the food
definitely the light blast I think this
is definitely like the closest we've
ever been like in proximity to Anthony
and it felt so strong like I felt like
my hands get warm did you feel it I it
felt like I feel like warm but also
light you know cuz light yeah wow and
what was your experience like meeting aw
I was like I was I didn't know how I was
going to feel I was like am I going to
be nervous like am I going to be like
really awkward but then like the second
like we stepped into like so chill and
to meet him I was like I felt a calming
presence I was like very Serene right
yeah very chill yeah very chill very
welcoming yeah what was your favorite
part of the meal Do you have a favorite
okay yeah you go to favorite the beans
in the the beans in the uh potato dish
yes I am Noble I am Noble the beans and
I Noble for sure the beans are very
Noble they are with each like um course
that came out I was like oh this is the
one like this is this is the Highlight
like every time I was like they can't
top this and then every time I I would
say next time we come back I think I'm
getting the
fajitas I'm getting no I'll steal some
potatoes from your Bo for make it Family
Style again we'll get it family style
every time I'm like and then we also
have to get the salad again and then we
also have to get the sushi again it's
it's all so good we already asy would
say it's incredible it's incredible it's
incredible yeah so you're saying that
like your locals are you locals yeah we
are we actually we live a little closer
to the largemont location but we live in
Monrovia um it was like it was like it
was kind of long today it was like a
2hour drive I think but like yeah
definitely local was I the whole time
aren't you lucky you the
driver I love I love that for you do you
love connecting with the community at
these events yeah oh my gosh we met so
many amazing people and it's just oh
it's such a great Community seriously
everyone's so awesome everyone's so cool
everyone's so nice yeah and amazing and
it's great to hear people's stories
seriously I'm like it's
amazing talking about stories do you
have a story you would like to share
with us in regards to how you discovered
the medical medium information and how
it helped you hail yeah so do you want
do you want to go first like like these
stories yeah like how how his um medical
medium information helped you helped us
or how do we find him how did you well
you could say how you found him okay so
our mom found him we were we were at
Disneyland one day and then she like
came across medical medium and like when
we came home and she was like guys guys
like um because she she has been
struggling with like chronic illnesses
for a really long time um and now you
know with medical medium information
like I know for you like do you want to
do you want to talk a little bit about
um yeah I mean when when I was younger I
had like auditory
processing um disorder and it it was
like definitely hard to like
process what I was hearing at times it
like it just like
sounded very echoey and sometimes I
actually remember like like not really
hearing like anything for like half a
second but like it like it it's gone now
sometimes I still like you know have
issues listening well like not listening
but like sometimes like processing
things and uh yeah it's like it's
helping with you know just like my
stress and um yeah like I feel so much
better after having all that stuff than
I was when when we first came here so
yeah that you're saying that your mom
put you on to it is that correct yeah
yeah she found it through like a
newsletter I think like there was like
I'm not sure if like Anthony was like
interviewed and then um yeah and then
she our whole family is now it's great
to have like that support system like
within your family like we're all you
know following the protocol and we're
like making like the dishes is like at
home and it it's great it's like it's a
family it's a family affair that's so
cool that's fun to get on in the kitchen
and juice of celery together yeah I know
it's so funny because our mom it's like
we're like in the beginning a lot we
were like we're like can we like can we
help you she she's very like meditative
about it she likes to do it she has her
process but it's like when we go like
when we go on when we go out of town
it's like we're doing this stuff like
we're making the smooth and we're just
like it's so funny to be the ones doing
it because usually it's like it's like
her thing she she really likes to do it
for everyone like her special it's her
special thing that's beautiful where's
mom tonight she she and our dad are
inside I think
wait well that's great you all came as a
family yeah we all came as a I know it
was we're so lucky that we were all able
all able to come together tonight yeah
all able to get tickets that's awesome
birthday was yesterday so like this is
like birthday dinner it's so cute so
does it feel great to be out to eat out
and not worry about any of the
ingredients know it's all good for you
and yeah I yeah this is like this is
like the dream collab like it's our it's
our favorite restaurant and like our
favorite person like when we found out
about this we're like no way this is the
craziest thing ever and now it's like it
it's accessible to like so many people
who might just like you know be be
coming to Cafe Gratitude and then
they're like wait what is this and then
they get to they get to try the dishes
and maybe it's like opening up a whole
new world for people exactly yes we were
talking about that the other night like
people will find medical medium on the
menu and go what's this let's try a dish
and then you know have a look at the
books and you know learn like discover
him that way yeah it's amazing oh yeah I
really hope people do I'm like I'm like
guys come on this is It's amazing oh and
the dishes are just so good I'm like or
the opposite like they find Cafe
Gratitude people like wait wait medical
medium and Cafe
Gratitude this goated restaurant it's
goated what you have your story yeah oh
my story yeah yeah okay M yeah you want
to sure thank you for helping me out I
love that it was Prett um
yeah I I had a lot of issues with like
brain fog and like Focus um and you know
like I also had problems with my skin
like I had like eczema on my hands and
like since following the protocol like
it's all disappeared like there's a
Clarity that like you when you're
struggling with that stuff like you
don't even know it's attainable I'm like
I'm seeing the world in 4k
now yeah oh that's so beautiful yeah
it's amazing yes well thank you so much
for talking to us so to meet you so nice
to meet you I think you're heading out
this way who do we have
next okay oh come over one second I
think we're going to we're going to
we're good to go okay yes come over it's
all good yeah I'm
Danielle so nice to meet you you have a
lovely glow thank you did you have a
beautiful evening it was the best I've
this is my third event that I've come to
and I just feel like the community here
and the energy is just so overwhelming
and you it's just like hard not to feel
Joy so yeah what were the other events
that you went to um I did the the Culver
City and the Calabasas ones yeah yes
must have missed you at the calabas why
I didn't get to meet you yet so I'm glad
that we got to meet you tonight yeah
same yes what what was your favorite
dish cuz we're got to talk about the
food and what you thought about it I um
I love the sushi but I also really like
the flavor that was in the potato dish
um like the black beans I thought that
was really really good oh yes and what
was your experience like meeting aw this
evening um um really overwhelming very
exciting it's he's when you see him he's
just as kind and warm in person um yeah
it's just it's a really exhilarating
experience he's just his kindness just
really
radiates yeah and the light blast what
was that experience like for you if you
could describe that for everyone
watching you know it's it's I feel like
this was like the first time anyone has
ever experienced like the ability to
split the light blast
and like to be able to share it with
others and I thought that was really
really amazing um so yeah and this one
he said is different from the other one
so I'm actually really looking forward
to seeing like any noticeable benefits
cuz I have benefited from the previous
light blasts oh wow so in what ways do
you feel you benefited from those other
light Bloss um so I've been doing
medical medium protocol since 2018 and
I've I've done really really I've had
really wonderful progress but my most
lingering symptoms were like PTSD
related and there is a PTSD protocol
that I was working on before I got
pregnant and um I really felt like this
last event the Calabasas event um that
one really held my PTSD with driving
I've had like um previous episodes where
when I was really sick I almost fainted
at the wheel and that was really
traumatic for me and I since then I've
been like afraid to drive um on highways
and I still do but it's like really
stressful for me and um ever since that
event I don't have that anymore and it's
the only thing that I can attribute to
that change and it's been really amazing
wow that's incredible so let's take it
back a little bit to when you first
discovered the medical medium
information how that came about and what
symptoms you were going through and
you're talking about the PTSD but a
little bit about the other things you
were dealing with as well yeah so my
story is pretty long but um that's okay
so I'm I'm 34 now and I got sick when I
was like 22 23 I ended up getting food
poisoning and I was working as an ICU
nurse at the time I ended up getting
food poisoning from the hospital
cafeteria
and that ended up triggering my chronic
illness and I started developing
neurological symptoms chronic fatigue um
fainting digestive issues
eccema um like vertigo a lot of
neurological symptoms and eventually got
to the point where I became bed bound
and then I I was sick for about six
years before I found medical medium
information I was going through all
these different I was trying
conventional medicine functional
medicine all these alternative remedies
and then in 2018 I found medical medium
information and then 6 months later I
was medication free and um yeah wow yeah
it's been incredible obviously my my
journey I will say has not been linear
I've had lots of ups and downs and
setbacks and things like that but um my
health has been very good the last
several years thanks to Medical medium
information and I'm just eternally
grateful wow that's incredible so you
say the food poisoning kind of started
this that was my trigger okay yes your
trigger um what were some of those
symptoms and conditions you were dealing
with after that that the medical medium
helped you improve if you wouldn't mind
talking bit more in detail about those
yeah so you know I I had a lot of like
hormone imbalances and adrenal issues I
I struggled with a lot of chronic
fatigue there were months u i was
bedbound for months at a time um I
couldn't stand up without feeling light
headed or weak I couldn't really shower
I you know I just I had difficulty
swallowing I had food sensitivities and
I mean I I I've had like over 50
symptoms so oh go I think those symptoms
now that you've been on the protocol for
sometime are you symptom free are you
still working towards it have a lot of
them lifted um most of them are gone
thank god um I think the most lingering
was the
PTSD um but yeah I thankfully my health
has been very good the last few years so
I'm very grateful amazing and
congratulations you mentioned you were
pregnant
congratulations uh wow that's so
beautiful that you're now healthy and
you're pregnant having a baby I'm just
so happy for you special thank you yeah
it's it's been like like amazing it's
been very validating and um it's yeah
it's been really wonderful and I've had
a really wonderful pregnancy and I I
really do attribute that to Medical
medium information keeping me really
healthy and strong and yeah I just feel
really really lucky I'm super lucky to
be having a life Blaster this time too I
know three times this baby better come
out an angel because there's so much
light in this
baby glowing yes I am so do you like
connecting with all the community out
here it's it's the greatest experience
because I feel like unfortunately as
people members of the community like
we're like the weird ones right like
we're different where um you know people
question us and um question our choices
so it's just really nice to be around
like-minded people who've struggled who
are compassionate who are kind um who
just get it yeah yeah if you have uh a
few words that you might like to share
with the community watching online just
an encouraging message to help them with
their healing Journey yeah I think um I
don't know if anyone follows um Anthony
on telegram but he leaves these really
um beautiful messages and the most one
that really stuck with me is he talked
about how when we're really really sick
it can feel like we're like completely
missing out on life and um like we're
just like have this like fear of missing
out like everyone's else's lives are
like moving forward and you're just
stuck at home and you're really sick and
you're really miserable but he said that
um when you come out of chronic illness
you will be so much more
productive um than you ever could have
been before you ever got sick and I just
remember feeling that way when I was
really sick I just remember like think I
was sick through all my 20s I just
remember like thinking like all my
friends are like getting married and
having kids and like doing all these
different things and I really felt
really limited and um you know since
I've come out of chronic illness I've
like started my own practice and I got
married and now I'm having my first
child and it's just um I just if you're
feeling that way and you're feeling like
really held back by your illness just
know that when you come out of this it's
your life is just going to be so amazing
and you're going to be doing all the
things you've ever wanted to do oh wow
yeah I feel like on that note we're
about to wrap things up I couldn't think
of a better way to end this evening what
a beautiful message for everyone guys
that's it for night three we'll be back
tomorrow night for one final night we're
so excited here at Cafe Gratitude for
the medical medium Cafe Gratitude
collaboration thank you so much for
tuning in