Sure Shot how powerful and amazing and
empowering that is right there I'm
excited there it is let's see what it
looks like whoa that's really that's
awesome that's what we're doing right
there today I am pumped up big time
but more so than that I am excited to be
talking about the pesticide herbicide
fungicide exposure it's one of my
favorite topics to be honest
It's a combination of being sad
huh
and happy
yeah it's a combination of both because
when you think about pesticides
herbicides and fungicides and how they
actually really do affect our lives and
how we do get exposed to them and then
that's the sad part like what I'm
exposed to this this is what we're going
to talk about which is kind of shocking
look out your mind might go boom right
and then the happy part can we do
anything about it is there anything to
do about it what can we do and that's
the other part I'm Anthony William the
medical medium this is the brain saver
book I'm reading this is the brain saver
medical medium range shot therapy
cleanse challenge I'm excited you guys
so let's get down to it why not
why not because this is look I got a
thing for pesticides and herbicides and
fungicides I really do because it's one
of those antagonists that neuro
antagonists that are in everybody's face
but people don't know it and they don't
realize it
and so I like this topic because when
people don't know what's going on
and you can actually educate you can
provide information that's incredible so
they can then protect themselves it
feels good like this is a feel-good
topic for me
because it's about awareness and when
people become aware it changes the world
and that's amazing so let's go into it a
little bit so I'm on page 224 by the way
it's day 18. I'm actually blown away
like how are we getting through this
we're going 20 days are we really gonna
do this
I'm on page 224 brain saver right there
let's cut into it
Rogue spraying practices whoa that's
interesting on a Zone let's just I'm
going through this now this is
incredible common chemical neuro
antagonists just going to give you a
little bit of a rundown
chemical fertilizers
okay but you're not exposed to any of
those
yes you are
lawn treatments lawn treatments huh but
you're not exposed to any of those
yes you are
insecticides including ant killer
Roach Killer
spider killer
wasp killer silverfish killer
tick killer
flea killer might kill her you're not
exposed to any of this uh yes you are
mosquito killer you're definitely
exposed to Mosquito Killers sorry to say
that this is this is an interesting
episode today
we're live right now by the way termite
killer uh-huh termite killer yeah and
gypsy moth killer oh I'm not exposed to
gypsy moth killer yes you are
all right
here's a bullet point right here
nighttime aerial insecticide spray
uh-huh planet Earth
has something very evil
within it
and they do the nighttime aerial spray
on every village
on every town
in every County
in every state
in every country across the world
that's what they do
it's so certain helicopters with vials
on them releasing a mist
and it's aerosol
aerial insecticide spray
all right see why this is like one of my
favorite favorite subjects
so we're on page 24
not page 24 sorry chapter 24 page 223 a
brain saver
and we're reading about chemical neuro
antagonists and we don't think we're
exposed to
now I personally would rather know what
I'm exposed to so that I can do things
to look out I can be careful I could
make sure I don't walk into a lawn
treatment that's being sprayed I make
sure that a family member or family
members aren't walking into a lawn
treatment that's being sprayed or
whatever so it's like I like this
information because you can do something
it's empowering
larvicides yeah heck yeah rodenticides a
hot rat killer
there's rat killer everywhere on crops
conventional crops there's rat killer
and buildings there's rat killer and
condos there's Rock rat killer
everywhere around buildings
other pesticides of course
sea trails
yep
chemical neuro antagonists sea trails
that's right
herbicides you know sea trails
right
herbicides DDT and fungicides but ddt's
not around here anymore all right we
don't have to worry about DDT anymore
no we don't have to right it's only
dropped out of planes
up in the sky that leave the streak in
the sky with old abandoned
excess DDT
that has been filled into it right DDT
is everywhere too by the way it floats
around continents it floats around the
earth we still breathe it in and
everybody still has a portion of DDT
inside their livers and bodies that's
passed down from generation to
generation to generation PBT didn't go
away
like I said sea Trails right
the old plane
and fungicides that's another one
fungicides I don't get exposed to
fungicides are you kidding oh yeah you
do you do get exposed to fungicides
every single new article of clothing you
buy including organic clothing can be
laced with the fungicide you can smell
it
if you learn the smell of fungicide
smoke exposure of any kind
including cigarettes
yum yum marijuana
yum yum vaping yum yum
yummy smoke smells
smells good anyway people get exposed to
that too and how about this one
fluoride
fluoride interesting right yeah fluoride
treatments fluoride in general and
chlorine how many people are exposed to
chlorine so I love that chemical neuro
antagonist section
inside brain saver I'm going to read a
little bit about it let's do the fun
part that wasn't even the fun part
okay
chemical neuro antagonists sounds like
such a serious category that it must be
difficult to come in contact with any of
these chemical agents right
I'm not exposed to any chemical neuro
antagonists what kind of world are you
living in that's not me I'm not exposed
to that
quite the contrary
we're up against these brain betrayers
more than we know
walk through a park
if you walk through a park
they hose those Parks down they've been
doing it for a hundred years
parks are hosed down
with all kinds of chemical neuro
antagonists hosed down
I know
it's just a fact
s are hosed down with chemical
antagonists
golf anybody want to play some golf
right
well golf it's the same way golf courses
really hose down chemical fertilizers
that's a huge one chemical fertilizers
pesticides herbicides especially
herbicides all sprayed on golf courses
they're at least sometimes twice a week
what else campus green
campus greens
what is that college universities campus
greens laced with fungicides herbicides
pesticides rodenticides
so we got that one there that's a fun
one or Town Commons you're sitting in
the town common the Town Square the town
green definitely
laced
eating conventional grown produce duh
we get a little bit of that in us anyway
food made from a conventional grown crop
or even organic food grown on former
conventional fields and that's another
thing we can't ex we can't escape the
neuro antagonists we can avoid a lot of
them
but organic food is grown out of land
that's been saturated from DDT saturated
from conventional sprays
saturated from pesticide herbicides
they wait like seven years and then an
organic farm moves in and organic crops
are grown right seven years doesn't rip
DDT out of soil I'm sorry but it doesn't
and it doesn't rip DDT out of soil from
50 years ago it doesn't read pesticides
out of soil
organic crops have pesticides we can't
get away from it
organic food grown on former
conventional fields which is virtually
almost every single organic feel this is
critical to know they're not chopping
down forest here in the United States to
grow a organic field
organic fields are organic fields that
have taken over conventional fields we
need to understand this it's yes eat
organic food absolutely
but understand
that that organic food is growing
unconventional fields
because they were all conventional
fields
all of them were conventional fields to
start with going back decades ago they
were all conventional produce Fields you
guys
and slowly organic moved in on these
fields
they bought the conventional farms and
they grew organic produce that's how
it's done
incredible information right
okay eat
conventionally raised chicken or pork or
beef or fish people do that all the time
yes they get exposure
handle conventionally grown
flowers
someone sent me flowers the other day
they're released
it was a really good
nice gift it was incredible gesture
it was pleasing
there's beautiful flowers
but they're laced
conventional grown flowers
and then
there's neighbors chemically treated
yards
so that's a big one there so neighbors
if you have a neighbor they chemically
treat the yards does everybody know but
most everybody does if the neighbor
doesn't the other neighbor does
if the other neighbor doesn't this
neighbor does
so there's a treatment coming somewhere
someone's getting a spray around their
house someone's getting into remote
spray someone's getting some kind of
mosquito spray or tick spray someone's
getting a ant spray
it's just over and over again someone's
getting fertilizer on their little lawn
patch someone's getting some fungicide
sprayed on their weeds someone's getting
some weed killer sprayed on their weeds
it's just you can't get away from it if
it isn't this neighbor then it's this
neighbor here and then the wind blows
that to you then it's if it's not that
neighbor it's this neighbor here and the
wind blows that to you if you're in an
apartment building same thing
same thing people bomb their Apartments
Apartment next door to you inside an
apartment building they're bombing it
that bombing is a pesticide herbicide
fungicide bomb
it happens all the time people get
people get pesticide bombs inside their
Apartments to get rid of bed bugs to get
rid of silverfish to get rid of fleas
so in apartment buildings it's all the
same everybody's bombing for fleas in
one apartment at Roaches for another one
silverfish in another one bed bugs in
another one
foreign
can't you see why this is one of my
favorite topics
in chemical lawn fertilizers and
treatments people often spray the
interiors and exteriors of schools oh
that's a big one right there the
institutions the institutions
have to purchase spray
they have to have contracts with
chemical
spray companies
so schools
have to have contracts with all of the
extermination services and everything
else
they spray the interiors and exteriors
of schools offices apartment complexes
dorm rooms dorm rooms are big
the bed bug spray they use in those
unbelievable dorm rooms hotels houses
warehouses storage facilities and other
buildings with roach killer ant killer
termite killer wasp killer mosquito
killer tick killer and more
so it's all too easy to breathe in or
even touch chemical neuro antagonist
contamination you guys
it's how easy it is
fear-mongering anyone no
it's important to know what's around you
because it stops a person from walking
into it I've watched it for years I see
it outside if I'm in a car somewhere
driving or being driven around or
something I see like literally people
with those canisters and people walking
by just not even realizing and breathing
it in it happens everywhere on the side
of Highways every place
it's really incredible
Jenny Jen on YouTube my next door
neighbor at my apartment doused the bush
next to my bedroom window
with diesel gasoline to kill it I was
waking up with massive headaches and my
apartment was filled with the smell
so many horror stories like that Jenny
Jen I've seen out there too and I've
heard from friends and so forth and from
people in general throughout the years
it's real it's real this is real
this is real
okay I'm gonna read the next part right
here
all right take Holloman on YouTube and
take great info love all these lives so
grateful so grateful you're here
incredible thank you for being here
amazing
and
um
Tate says
I've healed and got rid of over a dozen
symptoms using conventional produce with
the medical media books and info and t I
talk about that that people can use
conventional produce and heal absolutely
I talk about how conventional celery you
can't get organic conventional produce
if you can't get organic
foreign practices
Rogue
keep in mind on that word rogue
organic crops
whoa
while organic crops aren't sprayed with
conventional pesticides
and herbicides
still come with exposures
for one
organic farming relies upon
the same solvents
degreasers
and cleaning agents for their equipment
tractors and trucks
as conventional farming
if you know anything like that
I've driven a tractor
I've greased a tractor
I've maintenance
equipment
I know what this means
it's not like Organic Farms
are free from solvents chemicals
degreasers
all kinds of different
agents
exhaust coming out of tractors gets
blown on all the crops your Organic Crop
is still going to get diesel fumes
blown
on all the crops
every single day as the tractors go up
and down
foreign
it's just interesting right I mean isn't
that interesting it's just it's
incredible to have this window of
information
this exposure Finds Its way into produce
plus dangerous mosquito sprays and other
insecticides are dumped out of
helicopters and planes all around the
U.S and other places around the world I
talked about that
these high concentrations of mosquito
spray
from low-flying planes and low-flying
helicopters Dallas organic crops
including Fields where grass-fed cattle
are grazing
just as they do any other Farm or yard
why do they spray mosquito spray in
every single part of the world
because they grow the mosquitoes
genetically mutate and alter them
GMO the mosquitoes and let trillions and
trillions of mosquitoes out daily
so that the mosquito come spray
companies
convince everybody that you got to pay
the bill
they convinced all the governments you
have to pay the bill all around the
world and so there's mosquito spray two
stop mosquitoes that they're growing and
releasing right you see this sick sick
world we live in
Stevens Ranch says you give us hope and
strength to heal
amazing incredible yeah
yeah so
the chemical companies providing the
spray and flight patterns do not
purposely avoid Organic Farms
yeah yeah Mac yep
yeah yeah there's a whole bunch of
organic farms ahead of you change your
trajectory
yep just keep on no no don't don't spray
that mosquito spray there's a whole
bunch of
vegans
and animal protein vegetable fruit Eater
people they love their organic produce
Don't Spray that mosquito spray over
there okay right on all right Roger out
no it doesn't work that way every single
organic farm is sprayed
through helicopters in the air dropping
mosquito spray it is not immune to it
they don't just stop they go over every
place everywhere
foreign
cities and towns are sprayed by
helicopter for bugs like mosquitoes and
gypsy moth caterpillars
so see if you can find out the local
schedule and stay indoors with windows
closed at those times but chances are
they won't tell you any local schedules
because they won't there's very few
places in the world
that tell you there's going to be
helicopter spray for mosquitoes some
counties do in some areas of this
country and around the world but it's
rare
and it's not always accurate keep in
mind that scheduling is never a
definitive operation I have it right
here
even if you have the local schedule in
hand it is not guaranteed to be correct
timing is never exact
ly never is very interesting
it's always extremely loosey-goosey
that's a word lucy-goosey and spraying
is often done without forewarning trust
your instincts if you see here or smell
something suspicious
use your Snoop
on IG
nit uh says why do you keep writing so
many books why not write everything in
one book well
that's what I tried to do where's my
other book here oh let me just get it
over here excuse me
this is one book
right there it is
it's the old one book too big too much
information
bookstores don't want a book this big
publisher can't print out books this big
shipping books this big is really hard
and this book's 12 pounds I think I mean
don't quote me on that I don't know but
it feels like it's 10 pounds or
something
and I have to say uncle
because
I have to say uncle to Spirit of
compassion because
these books
take a lot out of me
and there's eight big ones
there's eight books packed with
information too much information to fit
into them
and I just pray to God every day to give
me the strength to listen to Spirit of
compassion and write another book
thank you for asking
if you like going to a public park find
out his particular treatment schedule
too and see if you can wait for a good
Reign between when it's sprayed or
fertilized and when you can visit if
you're sensitive keep in mind for people
who have chronic illness this is this
tips to scale
you sit in a park on the ground
that was just doused with herbicide
and it's woofing everywhere and you
smell it everywhere let's make her break
when you got chronic sickness that's
make or break
when you got chronic sickness set you
back for weeks
when you do go take along a blanket so
you don't end up sitting untreated grass
treated ground
pregnant women should take special care
with all of this direct pesticide
herbicide or fungicide exposure can be
enough to cause pregnancy complications
that kind of intense skull and crossbone
exposure
which is sprayed directly out of trucks
and canisters
on the ground direct exposure to that
spray like if they're spraying and a
pregnant woman is breathing it in it's
getting in her in her face and on her
skin
can be a dangerous thing
June says in IG the area here sprays at
night and if I have windows open I
quickly try to close the windows it's
awful smelling too
I believe you because I've seen it for
years anywhere I've lived in the United
States
here's an interesting part right here
DDT isn't gone
DDT
is in a pesticide class all on its own
this toxin it seems like a problem of
the past because it's in the past it's
still very much with us today it's in
our oceans it's in our Lakes it's in our
streams
it's in our reservoirs
and other water reservoirs agricultural
fields and more
DDT is in all those places plus it's
still in use in some parts of the world
it's still in use
it's in use in a lot of places in in the
world
it's incredible really
plus it's still in use in some parts of
the world and what and wins you know the
wind air
can even carry it from continent to
continent what's more DDT passes along
through Bloodlines from generation to
generation so
if one of your forebears was exposed in
ddt's Heyday that same DVT from back
then could now be in your body and brain
my father
the medical medium's father
he just told me recently and he's told
me before but he reminded me that when
he was a kid
he used to play
right behind the DVT trucks they used to
drive by through the parks and him and
his friends would run up behind the
truck and they would spray
all the kids down
my dad said he was sprayed a lot
he had Direct DBT application all on his
body was just set it up all in his hair
and all over his body
and
that means
he passed it on down to me
so
just being born
I had DDT contamination the medical
media
it's incredible
in farming a lot of fields are recycled
oh wait there's still a little bit more
DDT passes along through Bloodlines from
generation to generation so if one of
your forebears was exposed in ddt's
Heyday that same DDT from back then
could now be in your body and brain
correct
in farming a lot of fields are recycled
almost all the Farmland is in use today
is Farmland from the 1930s 40s and 50s
so this is interesting
almost all of the Farmland we use today
is recycled it's from the 30s the 40s
the 50s and the 60s on IG saved by
plants my father played behind those
trucks too
it's incredible
in 1960s that was heavily sprayed with
DDT so all the Recycled Farms that were
actually eating our food out were spread
with DDT but not just sprayed with DDT
like sprayed with DVT
so DDT is still in the dirt
that's true whether the Farmland is used
for conventional or organic farming
today
organic farming
unless that organic farm
was in a forest
not in a forest it was a forest first
the forest was cut down
and then the organic farm was created
out of that Forest
that's the only time it's possible
there's no DDT
in heavy amounts in the ground but there
still will be DDT in the ground
that's how much DDT was sprayed around
this planet still around this planet and
used to be sprayed here
that's true whether the Farmland is used
for conventional or organic farming
today most organic farm land was
converted to organic from conventional
farming almost all organic Farmland was
conventional Farms
this in an interesting way I just got to
be honest with you guys it's kind of
funny where and I was like all right I
can't wait to tell everybody about
pesticides herbicides and and neuro
antagonists and right and and I was
telling SOC this morning like a five in
the morning when I woke up I was telling
SSC like I can't wait to tell everybody
about this stuff but it's so boring it's
so boring chemicals and pesticides and
herbicides this is boring crap it's like
and I said to associ this morning said
how do I make it interesting and and
what do I do like do I do a dance when
I'm actually saying this dude this stuff
is boring right it's like chemical spray
mosquito spray
foreign
but still it's like my favorite topic
um
by lupier says Balu Piper says been
following medical meeting protocol four
years Advanced heavy metal detox
smoothie
um
the 20-day challenge has
rocketed my healing thank you medical
medium these daily teachings gives us as
much as the books incredible
The Organic certification
rules
usually state that in the range of five
to seven to ten years without
conventional spray land can be deemed
suitable for organic farming
but those herbicides last a lot longer
than that they're in the dirt
DDT lives many years past this in soil
DDT has a half-life of a good 100 to 200
years
100 to 200 years
all right well
son
daughter
you'll be able to farm that land over
there ddt-free
but you're gonna have to tell your
grandchildren that they're going to be
able to farm it too
and their children and then maybe it
will be DDT reduced
Gotta Wait 200 years Linda Larkin said
this is disappointing not really alive
really this is alive
I'm live right now
I'm talking about all the different
chemical fertilizers and sprays and DBT
and I just read your comment right now
that we're live
sorry
I know it's no fun but exposure to this
stuff is important to know because you
can avoid it you really can avoid a lot
of it
it's pretty incredible how much you can
avoid when you have this knowledge
and that's just crops animals whether
raised conventionally or organically
grazing fields that were once Fields
conventionally sprayed with DDT DDT
still in our bodies we still eat
conventional
conventional animals we still eat
organically grown animals pasture free
range
that people are eating still DVT in them
unregulated fungicide exposure let's hit
this this is actually pretty interesting
right here right here this is pretty
interesting okay
this one is
that's not mine right
did not have my celery juice
I was really busy this morning
just need to sit
fungicides are recent sorry fungicides
are secretly everywhere too
fungicides I hate fungicides coating
more and more items you buy encounter in
daily life if you buy something out
there in the world and and it comes in
the mail or you go to a store sometimes
you'll smell a fungicide you won't be
familiar with it if you're sprayed with
cologne and perfume and you have
plug-ins in the walls of air fresheners
and you use spray air fresheners on your
furniture you probably won't even smell
the fungicide because because your house
is one big smell right
but it's on stuff that we get and you
can smell it many times it's on a lot of
things
there's no warning
it's on items you buy and encounter in
daily life no one's told
this
was sprayed with fungicide no not my
book but this no one was told
by the way I'm reading out of brain
saver that's why I'm showing you the
book right now I'm on page
foreign
but you can stop using a lot of
fungicide
use out there you can like halt a lot of
it when you let companies know when you
order clothes and you say what's sprayed
on here why does it smell
you know and you can actually train
production of you know clothing the
companies and stuff like that to be more
careful
to be aware of it
no one's told this was sprayed with a
fungicide there's no warning on the
package no tag on clothing no
forewarning clothing
is one of the most fungicide sprayed
items we have in our lives
they don't
put a tag on all the new clothing you
purchase from whatever company or
fashion company or just regular company
whatever it is
there should be a tag saying was sprayed
with fungicide
stick in the laundry right away do not
try on unless it's washed
if you tried on these jeans
before they were washed you have to go
shower like they don't put any of that
on there there should be a tag saying
all this
Health queen says I was so allergic to a
new couch but thought it was my
imagination fungicides are really
sprayed on new couches new chairs all
the time
there's no warning on a package no tag
on clothing no forewarning it is a
secret campaign what
what
it's a secret campaign that no one
speaks about
hmm
no one knows about other than big
fungicide companies in manufacturing
it's a campaign
from the fungicide companies in
manufacturing companies
it's actually a secret
it is sprayed on everything they sell
the fungicide to clothing manufacturers
it's sprayed on everything there isn't a
tag or a forewarning which should be on
every single thing you buy
and there is some clothing that doesn't
have it and it's a miracle but it's
getting less and less like that
there is some clothing that doesn't
that's not sprayed with fungicide
it actually exists out there still I try
to choose those Brands where I'm
familiar with them so I choose the
brands that are not sprayed with
fungicide when I get used to them and
I'm like you know what this didn't come
with a fungicide smell it's not making
you sick when I breathe it in because
it's really intense
some stuff can come and it's like whoa
It's got to go in the laundry right away
right the point is is that when I find
clothing that I don't smell any
fungicide on
then that's the stuff I stick with
those are the brands I stick with that's
usually what happens like in my personal
life
yeah but usually I still have to wash
everything
when it comes because stuff will have
all kinds of stuff on it right
okay so let's go into this a little bit
more
what happens is this any corporation
that manufactures a product is sought
out by suppliers
chemical companies will send sales reps
to meet with manufacturing companies and
sell them on the fungicide chemicals
that they want the corporation to spray
on everything they manufacture
Boom the manufacturers then take the
fungicides put them in spray Jets and
spray them
spray these dangerous fungicide
chemicals on every single item and
package
no one's monitoring this
there's no federal law
this is total Rogue contamination
this information is just insane
thrift store clothes are saturated with
perfumes colognes and air fresheners big
time because I know people say well go
to a thrift store man sometimes this
stuff is just saturated mold
fungicide air fresheners
perfumes colognes right gotta look out
that way too
but if you don't mind any of that
whatever then
that's okay if you don't mind any of
that
no one's monitoring this there's no
federal law this is total Road
contamination when you handle items
sprayed with fungicides
nowhere does it say patent number one
seven three two two eight four dot dot
dot applied
nowhere does it show a skull and
crossbones nowhere does it warn immune
system diminisher
with a list of side effects nope and yet
fungicides are in every country
manufacturing plants throughout the
world are sold this fungicide you're not
allowed to be informed of any of this
I'm informing you of something you're
not allowed to be informed with
Sarah Nichols when I worked in fashion
development I got so sick and would open
boxes and boxes of our samples from
other countries I would get so sick and
my throat always hurt Sarah
you're validated
totally
I always worry about people in the
fashion industry I worry about people
that handle all the clothes in the
fashion industry
it's like a life shortener I'd be real
Brave to work in the fashion industry
real Brave
okay fungicides are sprayed on new
clothing and Manufacturing Goods that's
what we're just talking about they're
also applied on crops hospitals are
really doused in the campaign the
private campaign of fungicides
on new used cars and in airplanes and
even applied on garbage cans garbage
bags and the exteriors of some water
bottles
cardboard boxes packaged Foods including
organic packaged foods and beverages are
sprayed with fungicides
how screwed up is that
fungicides are on or in couches
appliances Tech products Lawn Furniture
beds blankets sheets dog shampoos cat
shampoos other pet care products don't
throw any of this out that's not what
I'm saying I'm saying
there's things we can do we're doing an
exposure shot remember the exposure shot
we're doing today day 18 is
pesticide herbicide and
what Fungicide and I'm talking about
fungicide exposure shot
foreign
because we can't just throw all this
stuff out
Lawn Furniture beds blankets sheets Lawn
Lawn Furniture
beds blankets sheets dog shampoos cat
shampoos other pet care products
medication boxes
cosmetic and self-care products medical
supplies health care supplies cleaning
supplies Cleaning Solutions and much
more
basically it's a trillion dollar
business for chemical companies to
produce this much fungicide to sell to
every manufacturer and nobody knows
about it
so wacko
it's unbelievable
they made it a standard of Industries to
grandfather and fungicides against any
ramifications from these dangerous
chemicals let's make the shot I could
just read on I mean there's so much
information in there
so let's actually
there's just so much info in there it's
just packed
that's the shot we're making right here
pesticide herbicide and fungicide
exposure shot right there you guys
but you know
so let's roll it out let's get the
juicer out
I'm excited about this
Loop is free with celery 333 I started
crocheting and my fingers and hands
started to get eczema and after some
research I found that the yarn had
formaldehydes in it so there's there's
one right there
that lumus free with celery 333
pretty amazing
hit the wall
all right you guys
let's make this one so quarter cup
tightly packed fresh
parsley
so quarter cup is not going to be too
too much
so let's just get in here
nice
this horse is really really fresh right
now which is exciting
here we go
next half cup tightly packed cilantro
incredible
half cup tightly packed let's get some
cilantro in here some people like
cilantro people some people don't
there's two kinds of people in the world
people that like cilantro and people
that go
people that are really high in heavy
metals and don't realize it and people
there better a little bit lower in heavy
metals and don't realize it
might put a touch more in here we go
all right next one
two large leaves of kale now I got
really large leaves of kale there's one
I got much larger right there but
there's one right there
you'll notice that's coming out dry
drier than any other machine that I've
used
but I've tried them all it's incredible
this is the mm-1500 it's on sale
20 off
this is a really large
that's a large one right there it's
gonna produce more juice than
someone was just asking about the juicer
there's an mm-900 and mm-1500 you got
the choice the 1500's got a Nutritional
Center
but seriously
food prices are going up up they're
skyrocketing which is like unbelievable
I'm talking about all food animal
products you know beef whatever chicken
everything's going up dairy products
fruits vegetables everything is going up
I endorse these guys you got because
this saves people money so that's the
kill right there
because it's squeezing out a lot of
juice out of here and the pulp's coming
out that kind of dry right there and
it's cold pressed masticating where the
nutrients are preserved
I endorse these guys because this
machine's like incredible
saving people money and that makes me
really happy if you can save people
money when there's like food problems
out there in the world and everything
else it's amazing
it's like
all right
two radishes
our next there's one right here
rad radish went in there all crunched up
two radishes
next one is quarter cup of fresh or
thawed blackberries
I got some frozen blackberries right
here and you want to defrost them and
I'm telling you guys that because I know
that some people will they won't they'll
get frozen but they won't defrost it so
what happens is it doesn't juice
anything out of it because it's making
you're making frozen sorbet so you're
what you're really doing is making a
frozen sorbet somehow
and in this situation
you want to make sure you defrost those
frozen fruits when you're using them in
these brain shot Therapies
one to two
stalks of celery
right there
yep
yep yep yep yep
I'm gonna put one here too
I just had to get a celery stick out of
the fridge you guys
have to one orange peel
okay I'm gonna peel it real quick
there we go
now what's your notice about this juicer
is it's quiet and Juice in the morning
you won't wake up your family if you're
somebody that's worried about that
it's a quiet juicer
the spinning basket juicers and all the
other juicers all they do is throw away
a lot of produce
you've got to have a pretty deep wallet
to keep up with juicing with those
machines
this one right here is about saving
money
crispy perspective says love the juicer
explanation points figuring it all out
yesterday fumbling time was minimal
totally worth the upgrade from spinning
basket crispy perspective
totally worth it because
the amount of produce you have to run
through those other machines is insane
like you need access to like co-ops and
like food co-ops and and produce back
alleys where the produce managers were
giving you lots of produce for free or
something you know what I mean that's
spoiled or something you need access to
a lot of produce with those machines if
you're going to juice all the time
and this right here is squeezing out so
much juice
20 off and it's not like it's more
expensive than anything it's not that's
what's incredible two you know people
are like oh well then what does it cost
well that's the amazing part it's
affordable for a lot of people but I see
people say it's too expensive
right
and
they're but they want a juicer and
they're worrying about worrying about
food and they're worrying about a juicer
that's too expensive they don't
understand that first of all it's 20 off
it's on sale right now second of all
it's saving people so much money
they think it's too A lot of people
think it's too expensive to make juice
they're worried about it being too
expensive to actually make it and what
they don't realize is that with this
juicer you're saving money and that's
the incredible part right there you're
actually saving money
and you can give it a little time and
let it go down
so
I'm going to kind of just massage this a
little bit and get
this comes with a nice screen on top
which I love and you can just actually
push all the juice through it's
incredible when you really get down to
it the amount of juice you can juice
with very little
it's it's really insane
berries are a different consistency
oranges are a different consistency but
if you give it a little time it all ends
up going down there and it's it's
squeezing here's what people don't
realize
it's not about like people are like oh
just make a juice really quick and then
they run all this produce to make this
much juice all this produce through this
thing is squeezing it's got high
compression it's squeezing out the juice
and that is where the money's at because
when you go to the store you have to buy
this much more this much more of
everything in this situation you're
buying less and it's a cold pressed slow
masticating juicer which is incredible
it's still squeezing out juice
Gary Pearson says the mm Omega juicers
paid for themselves and that's what they
do so anybody if you guys are watching
this and you're like well what you sure
because everybody's going to be like if
I'm going to do the brain shot I need a
juicer so um so I'm just showing you how
this works
and the warranty is 15 years plus
powertrain 15 years and parts 15 years
that's unbelievable and there's an mm
you know call hotline number and all
that you know and a mega juicers right
put that there because I'm gonna eat
that later
Lila Collins says Omega has superb
customer service I hear that a lot
that's incredible
and then what you have here is the dry
stuff
right you don't have a pile of wet
sloppy pulp from trying to make a big
basket of juice wet you know the whole
thing it's it's insane this is like the
difference right there
47 Anderson Jay says this juicer makes
the best orange juice and makes so much
out of just a few oranges I know the
reason why I say no because I love to
use oranges I juice like everything in
here I'll juice limes Judith Galley says
what's the juicer brand it's a mega
o-m-e-g-a it's a mega now here's the
thing here right
so in this juice this is the fungicide
herbicide pesticide exposure shot
it calls for a little bit of spirulina
another incredible product I'm just
going to say this okay
this stuff is so incredible but why put
your words where your mouth is man you
know what I mean they don't use the
anti-caking or bonding agents
it's the only company
from what I know out there
right that with the Rishi powder their
chaga powder the barley grass juice
powder the spirulina they don't use the
ant this is crazy you have to know what
this is
like just know what this is
companies have to put an anti-caking
agent that's what they all put in they
just choose to do it and they don't
disclose what it is
people got their green powders and they
don't realize it
their powder has an anti-caking agent
that's not on the list on on the bottle
people have their green powders they got
their mushroom powders they got all
their different powders out there
and they don't realize it there's
anti-caking and anti-bonding agents in
those powders
okay only company that said uh-uh we're
not going to do it we don't care if it
gets clumpy we don't care if some of it
clumps together
we don't care if a little bit of it
we're not going to put an anti-caking
anti-bonding agent in our powders and
then hide it from the public and not
disclose it and that's the difference
that's just one aspect of Imaging you
guys know I endorse these guys because
of stuff like this they continue to
break the mold I love these guys I've
known them for years I freaking love
them I've been friends with them I've
made friends I make friends with the
companies that do the best things for
people
you know make friends along the way with
the Omega people because they wanted to
save people money they're like how do we
save people money like how do we make it
so someone can do what they get gotta do
the same thing with emergy it's a mom
and pop to care about the chronically
ill and for that my heart is always like
you know pouring out to them for the
hard work they put into it they're like
we're not going to use the anti-bonding
agents anti-caking agents we're not
going to use citric acid alcohol under
supplements we're not going to use the
garbage we're not going to do any of
that and they're the only ones that have
said that and they work their butt off
and they're passionate every day about
making sure people have the best stuff
for because they're chronically ill and
chronically sick
and those are the friends that I want in
my life that those are the friends that
I want in my life people that actually
care and
you know so I endorse them I'll endure
some a billion times over since it's
incredible so I'm gonna put a little bit
of this in forgot for a second
quarter teaspoon of spirulina
spirulina spirulina
foreign
[Music]
there and this stuff is amazing
Jill plot women's two women's is some
clean clean stuff they're just wild and
that's it I only adult endorse
a few companies and that's all I get
asked to endorse hundreds and hundreds
of companies out there I just want I
gotta say this right here
I get asked to endorse hundreds of
businesses and companies
you guys
literally
I can actually endorse hundreds they I
get asked every day get the medical
medium support and then I say well what
do you got
this is what we do I'm like uh
uh-uh sorry
it's just it's not it's not cutting it
people don't realize this stuff you know
about me and everything men can make
millions of dollars and millions of
dollars on ads for my podcast
medical mean podcasts to Apple podcast
one of the top health podcasts
a number one Health podcast
could make millions of dollars on ads
but it's what it is is though it's not
about the greed aspect
so running you know running commercials
for uh for a hundred companies it's not
about that I'm not saying anybody else
is greedy or anything I'm just saying
that I want my people to get like free
listening
I get told I'm stupid I get told I'm an
idiot
agencies confront me and said say all
the time like why don't you do this why
don't you do that you're stupid like why
are you doing that
and I'm like because
we're talking about people who are
chronically sick chronically ill you
think they want to hear a commercial
they want answers
same way I don't sell programs I don't
so you know I don't have my own t-shirts
merch I don't have tons of merch I could
sell a ton of merch people don't realize
this
and guess what get the books in the
library for free
I gotta mix this up
[Music]
gotta mix this up a little bit I want
that spirulina
spiralina to get in there nice
all right guys
we're doing we're doing it now with a
killer shot incredible
this is the pesticide herbicide and
fungicide
brain shot therapy
this one's one of my favorites
this topic is one of my favorites
when you actually know what's going on
out there if you know what kind of crap
they're pulling out there
when you know
the kind of game that's being played out
there with the neural antagonists and
you can avoid some of them
some of those neuro antagonists you can
get them out of your life you can avoid
them and better than that too
you can actually do something to help
get it out of the body because it's been
in the body for so long
it adds up it adds up
we get toxic and more toxic as the years
go by and we get more and more and more
of these poisons in US
this one
always hits me about
[Music]
now
right there
you can feel this one working
the exposure shots do something where
it's kind of like whole body
there's a lot of that whole body feeling
going on
[Music]
amazing
and that's one strong
strong brain shot
it is
[Music]
you can feel like you can feel it kind
of really coming on now are you doing
this right now are you actually doing
this job with me right now do you feel
that
some of you guys wait and make it along
with me
right
I mean yeah
multi multi blonde says love energy
incredible
this is amazing do you feel this
[Music]
amazing
bartender
please give me another
time I put a please there I pissed off
the bartender last
day ago was it a day ago I pissed off
the bartender
[Music]
bartender was mad
bartender where's my next Juice shot
foreign
bartender you spilled it
two more days sign up you guys you can
sign up
there it is go to medicalmedium.com sign
up and do a two-day brand shot therapy
cleanse Challenge and guess what it
costs
make sure you've got your pockets ready
guess what it cost nothing it's free
free free download your free grocery
shopping list get your information do a
two day brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge with me if you like
for fun why not okay
and uh you can watch all the other 18
days guess what they're not held from
you guys
they're not held back from anyone I'm
permanently putting it on the website
it's there you can watch the 18 days
before and you can do your own 20-day
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge for
free it's not being withheld it's not
being held back and then brought out
another time and then you have to pay
for it none of that
we're not doing that right now we're not
doing that planning on doing that in the
future it's there for you as a free
resource just know that
medicalmedium.com offers a lot of free
information it's all there plus you can
go to the you can go to the libraries
and get the books if you like also
amazon.com sells the books
with an incredible discount like 42 off
and 50 off on brain saver brain saver
protocols right
Elvis lives now dot dot dot we just need
a thumbnail pose you got it
that's a bad one right there's a bad one
thumbnail pose is it this one right here
thumbnail pose
that now all of a sudden they're not
looking good for some reason you know
when you're trying too hard what's in
the brain shot Ben says I got kale I got
the blackberries right here orange I got
the radish I got a celery stick I got
parsley I got cilantro
and I got the vimergy spirulina watch
about the spirulina information which is
critical you can go back and you can see
what I was talking about before get the
recipe in the books get the recipe in
the books or medicalmedium.com for free
I'm going to send this down one more
time if you guys don't mind
wow
that's so good
turn your lives around with these what
is resource what an opportunity
so good
I mean that is really really potent
think what that's doing inside the body
incredible
all right you guys
tomorrow day 19 be there
I can't wait
I'm excited all right anyway I love you
guys God bless you seriously it was
really fun
and I'll see you guys soon