[Music]
thank you
day eight
are we in day eight
oh my God
the robot you guys doing it
[Music]
who's got a good robot
[Applause]
okay
therapy challenge
let's go
we're here you guys
guilt and shame shifter shot
let's get the music back on get it back
on
we're doing it
um
you guys were day eight
[Music]
let's go
our greatest line of defense
against threats to our brain and
neurological health is our brain itself
our brain that's what it is
okay guys you coming on giving everybody
a chance to come on
doing the brain shot therapy
or working with the brain our brains
so important
you guys got your ingredients going
what do we got spinach
oranges it's a little Tangerine right
there
Ginger
they guilt and shame shifter very
important one actually
so many people dealing with guilt and
shame
mystery guilt and shame that can happen
too so this is an incredible day where
they ate uh the medical medium brain
shot therapy cleanse if you guys just
got in here you don't know what this is
we're doing a free challenge 10 days
just so you know
these are the books right here
so I'm excited about this you guys
having a little Tech glitches but we're
fixing them now
all right let's go into a little bit
so I want to read this quote to you okay
so you guys are you experiencing the
Miracles from these brain shots the
Miracles anybody who just got on here
you don't know where you are what you're
doing right here just so you know
anybody who just got on here
we're having miracles happen from the
powerful brain shots in these books it's
unbelievable what's happening and I hope
you guys are experiencing this if you're
new and you don't know what this is wait
till you try the brain shot Therapies in
these books
just go to amazon.com 40 off both these
books you need both there's 26.29
there's 12 books in both these books
incredible 300 symptoms conditions
14 different cleanses
I mean these books are absolutely packed
a hundred over a hundred recipes
this information is just over the top as
far as what's happening here it's light
years ahead of science and research
when you experience the brain shot
therapy if you're new here you will be
blown away I'm giving you a forewarning
right now
if you do the brain shot therapy
I just don't want you caught off guard
because it's going to hit you
you're going to experience something
you're getting experience results it
doesn't happen in Natural Health Medical
medium books have been giving people
results
and regaining their health
moving them forward getting people out
of wheelchairs all of that right the
medical medium
incredible heavy metal detox smoothies
and cleanses and all the different other
different cleanses right and the tools
and people get better but the brain shot
therapies is like a gift from God
along with all the other incredible
information of course but a gift from
God to be like
let's just add to everything step it up
let's kick it up in a way that's so
profound and so mind-blowing
it's just I can't put it to words I
can't find the words
Jackie says yes I'm gonna have to
continue these shots Beyond a 10. I love
them I hope you continue the shots
Beyond day 10. I'm really hoping truly
you guys
that would be incredible
Jorah says the book is available in the
Netherlands oh thank God awesome
so we're dealing with Miracles here
is what we're dealing with when it comes
down to the branch out therapy
so that's important to know right there
Jane Moore says can we keep doing these
brain shot therapies continually past
the 10 days will we still see benefits
oh my God yes you can the entry level
first of all you guys there's seven
brain shot therapy cleanses in the brain
saver books seven
brain shot therapy cleanses
you can do 10-day 20-day 30-day you
should continue them for the rest of
your life and get the results that's how
powerful they are
I told you guys before when I was
sitting on my desk and I was taking the
information from Spirit of compassion
my mind was being blown
every second
and when I was getting the information
for these brain shot therapies I was
promised
because I was writing the information
down and what I was writing down was and
this is what's incredible about this
what I was writing down
which was so incredible
check this out
I was writing down medical medium brain
shot therapy offers instant relief
I wrote that down
right
because that's what I heard
and so what I said to Spirit of
compassion was oh wait a minute here
I know a lot of people get some instant
relief
pretty quickly when they're doing their
celery juice which has saved a lot of
lives around the world
I know people have gotten relief within
days of the heavy metal detox smoothie
I know they've gotten relief on the
monocleanse I know they've gotten relief
from the medical medium tools and
protocols I know they've gotten relief
from the zinc shock therapy
and the incredible vitamin C shock
therapy instant relief
I know they've gotten relief before but
you're telling me these brain shot
therapies are going to provide instant
relief but not just instant relief on a
way that was just unbelievable
miraculous the ability to even
push away a hundred symptoms over time
so when I heard that from Spirit of
compassion
I had to stop myself I remember I was in
mid flight of writing it down
because I hand write the Books
so as I'm hearing the information I'm
hand so I'm I'm basically like a scribe
and I'm just
hearing the information right
so it's the whole profit thing you're
hearing the information and you're
writing it down that's what it is and so
I'm doing that and spirit of compassion
is telling me instant relief and I'm
like instant relief
more and more more
I have to get the chronic Leo better and
what happened was
I was
hearing
it's just profound incredible
information about the brain shot therapy
and I I couldn't get enough
just writing it all down
and I was promised
that people would get that relief
so I could not wait for you to have
these books so it was like Christmas
morning
knowing like you know it was like
knowing you guys were gonna get
it was like being a kid waiting for
Christmas morning to come
so
for you guys to get the package of your
books
and for you guys to experience this
profound incredible
I mean
can there even be words for him so we're
doing the guilt and shame shifter we're
day eight gilton's shame shifter
now a lot of people Harbor guilt and
shame deep down inside
so I want to talk about the brain shot
therapy for a couple of seconds right
medical medium brain shot therapies
Uncharted Territory now all medical
medium books are they're all been
Uncharted Territory right
but this takes it to another level of
Uncharted
these are special configurations
synergistically combined just right to
crack the code
to crack the code
now you can have a Creative Juice
concoction but that's not what this is
this is medicinals
organized in a way that only above can
know
to crack the code on how to rewire
and reset the brain
I mean when you think about that it's
just like oh my God that's why these
books are the best books in history
hands down they're the greatest books of
all time
they are the greatest books of all time
you can be the judge go pick yourself up
some health books out there from the the
best podcast doctors or whoever go pick
up some books read those and then read
these
you'll find those are empty
unfortunately and you'll find that these
have so much information line for line
you've never even heard or read before
and your minds will be blown to such a
degree it is unbelievable and it's like
that with all medical medium books but
the point is is these right here it's
like I I don't even know what to say
so these are special configurations
synergistically combined just right to
crack the code to reset and to rewire
the brain how powerful is that
these brain shots
are unreal the healing shots of the
medical medium brain shot therapy are
tools that come from above these brain
shots are composed of special
combinations of ingredients working
together systematically for specific
reasons that only a source above can
know
oh my God
the relationships among these
ingredients right no one would ever know
that guilt and shame can be vanquished
just eliminated between these three
ingredients
Mary Lou says when will you be live on
Facebook
I'm live on Facebook now
but unfortunately
yeah
I mean it's not your fault you can't see
me on Facebook
because you're not allowed to heal
people that's why
um on a level that we do with these
books it's just no one's ever seen this
before in history
so Brett says this shot these shots are
my favorite immediate uplifting shift
incredible
the relationships among these
ingredients are intricate and unknown to
anyone so that means when you stick our
this is just today this shot the golden
chain shifter when you stick Orange
and spinach and ginger together just
those three you put something else in
there it doesn't work
you have one of those missing it doesn't
work
think about that
you have ginger missing it doesn't work
you have orange missing it doesn't work
you have spinach missing it doesn't work
you have to have these three and only
these three in the amount it is to in
order for it to actually eliminate the
guilt and shame that's deep within us
to get relief instantly with guilt and
shame
you eat a big old chocolate cake and
you've got all this guilt about it you
get these three ingredients together
and you juice them in the form in the
way that we're talking about here
you got guilt and shame deep within from
something you think you did wrong in
your life something he did you think
that didn't go right in your life
whatever it is get these three together
if you have a past skeleton shame thing
if you have a present guilt and shame
thing
get these three ingredients together in
the order in the way and the amounts
because no one would know ever anywhere
anyhow
any possibility
that when you put these three together
just right
it gets somewhere into here
it drives into the brain
and you know you know where it goes
I'm going to open up this brain right
here this cavity
create a cavity here
into the emotional center of the brain
so only a source above would know that
when these three come together that
Miracle happens
where that energy from these three
ingredients gets driven directly
absorbed into the emotional center of
the brain and unlocks
a condition
in order to heal
rewires and resets
that's how incredible this really is
truly unbelievable
says I just watched a retired Air Force
pilot sharing about UFO their team saw
in the air at night isn't it funny how
after the UFO podcast Anthony shared a
lot more people did the same
it's very funny
so
yeah check out that aliens podcast when
you guys get the chance
Sienna says the obsessive thoughts brain
had a huge impact on my teen daughter so
use so you use the obsessive thoughts
shifter the brain shot therapy
incredible
that means everything
if there is an impact from that
obsessive thought shifter
with your daughter
healing happened that means everything
right there
Winslow says loving the shots they are
so powerful
these shots are really addictive in a
good way because they give you relief
and they start moving the needle fast
and they start getting what needs to be
done quick and here's the crazy thing
when you're doing the other medical
medium tools and you're doing the brain
shots
you don't have to do the other medical
medium tools you just do the brain shots
you get relief but the point is when
you're doing the medical medium tools
and if you're even doing my God
the shock Therapies
not just the brain shot therapy the
actual medical medium shock Therapies in
here there's nine shock Therapies
that alone is just unbelievable there's
nothing out there like that that anybody
could ever touch or see
Gigi says the first one gave me instant
relief
from a scratchy throat and earache
incredible
this is what is needed
is this type of information for what
we're up against today
to get that instant relief
good morning Margaret instant relief the
power to that
is just absolutely incredible
Gigi says the first one gave me instant
relief to scratchy throat okay I read
that one and still they're still coming
up
when you think about it and that's
incredible by the way
really is
Jay Moore says all your information got
rid of my horrendous migraine
where I projectile vomit the pain was so
bad
I am free of migraines this past four
years
I mean when you think about that you're
free of the migraines for the past four
years what does that mean
to someone who suffers from a migraine
condition that means
that means freedom
freedom is critical and that's what
these books are they are freedom
the greatest books of all time provide
freedom
and there's so much to be said about
that
what's incredible you guys and I was
thinking about this this morning I woke
up five o'clock this morning and what I
was thinking about was
if even one podcast doctor or one Health
Guru
had even a fraction of this information
they would probably withhold it and make
sure they would charge thousands of
dollars for you to access it a fraction
of this information it's really
unbelievable but they don't even have a
fraction of it anyway
unless they poach it later which many do
Susan says I want to do the nerve
shifter shot again today wow
it was my favorite so far it gave me a
sense of clarity and energy that's
incredible
of course you can do that one again
Nicole says I slept super good for the
third night after the shots I was
struggling to even get five hours of
sleep before this now here's how it
works
a lot of the like the adrenal right
the adrenal um
I mean like there's okay first of all I
wish you wanted to say wait another one
too Lake says my teen daughter is being
transformed before my very eyes with
these shots I can't believe it
that means everything
Jen says oh boy the shot therapies are
so very powerful loving the results
results matter
they matter when it comes down to
chronic illness
Joshua yes the the books are handwritten
by me with this hand right here
you guys I'm reading the Instagram
comments right now
so I have to so let's go into it a
little bit here let's let's get cooking
let's get cooking
I'm gonna go to page 331.
that's where I'm gonna go page 331
and I am here chronic mystery guilt 341
sorry
chronic mystery guilt
but I'm here now there's over 300
symptoms conditions in the book and
protocols powerful protocols there's
also the medical medium shock therapies
there's nine shock therapies ask your
doctor what's right for you bring the
books to your doctor and ask your doctor
what's right for you now if you Embark
into the shock therapies make sure
you're using the right supplementation
it's critical I'm just letting you know
right there
I talk about you know how I fully
endorsed the vemergy company
fully endorse them because of the four
incredible things that they offer and do
that no supplement companies in my
opinion ever touched upon or do which is
mind-blowing
so check out uh you know my website
medical medium.com supplements directory
so if you're embarking into the
supplement world and you're thinking
about like medical means shock therapies
the problem is
if you use the wrong stuff
it's just their lack of results occur
that's one thing that could happen if
you use the wrong stuff it's also just
other problems too because
there's a lot of junky stuff out there
going to that another day
but the information in this book and the
amount of protocols and the amount of
conditions and symptoms neurologically
is just through the roof including the
recipes and the brain shot therapy we're
doing we're day a of the brain shot
therapy cleanse and we're on the entry
level
mystery chronic guilt here we are
in the emotional centers of the brain
certain areas of nerve tissue are partly
responsible for the way we feel
it's not only the tissue itself
this is incredible
the brain's emotional centers are
intertwined greatly with our soul
and the science of research doesn't know
that
Neuroscience a brain hack
nobody they don't know that literally
that in the emotional centers of the
brain
it's not just the brain tissue but in
the emotional center of the centers of
the brain it's the brain tissue being
intertwined with our soul
if someone feels guilty for something
they've done
and that's appropriate for the
circumstance the soul is tied into this
emotional response in the brain
that that's mind-blowing information by
the way
when you even think about that
if someone never feels guilty even when
they should when it would help them
learn and grow and give others
resolution right
there's a disconnect
for one there's a disconnect between the
soul and the brain's emotional centers
so if someone does something terrible to
somebody and they don't feel guilty
there's a disconnect between their soul
and the emotional center of the brain
I want to read something really quick
quote
right here in the brain saver book
because it reminds me of what we're
looking at now
we all know there are bad people in the
world
and these people have no interest in
protecting us or our brains
only a great agenda to find ways to hurt
us and our brains
we deserve to be wise to this so we can
look out for ourselves and the ones we
love
bad people in the world and they don't
feel guilty for what they do and what
they've done
because there's a disconnect between
their soul
and the emotional centers of the brain
if if someone never feels guilty when
they should
when it would help them learn and grow
and give others resolution
if you feel guilty about something bad
that happened it gives others resolution
there's a disconnect if they don't have
that for one there's a disconnect
between the soul and the brain's
emotional centers the soul has pushed
away from the brain
you don't have to be a terrible person
doing bad things though for that to
happen so that's important to know there
are bad people in the world where
they'll never be resolution for anyone
but you can also be so injured where you
don't feel guilty about something
because you're so injured and your soul
is pushed away from the brain for
another there's usually been some sort
of toxic exposure in the emotional
centers of the brain causing a
disconnect and electrical signal so that
can happen we can get sick we can
actually have toxic heavy metals inside
the brain we can have some kind of
poison or toxin that's actually
interfering with the Soul's connection
to the emotional center of the brain
when toxic heavy metals such as mercury
and aluminum take up residence there it
can interfere with the empathy sympathy
compassion and guilt that are supposed
to arise upon causing harm to others
it can mean that someone never
apologizes for what they've done
Cody says I've been praying for
something like this
I've tried techniques for rewiring the
brain my brain
but I'd get so mad at myself for not
changing
but I'm seeing changes already from
these shots it's amazing and Cody you're
also going to see changes when you read
the information in these books because I
talk about that
I talk about that the brain hacks out
there for rewiring they don't make us
feel good about ourselves because the
brain hacks and the people that create
them don't know how our body and brain
even works so all these mistakes are
made
incredible Adam says the nerve shifter
made the pain from my neck and shoulder
injuries so much better God bless
that's amazing and you can continue
if your doctor's happy that you're over
there on YouTube amazing ask your doctor
what's right for you guys if if any of
you are concerned too you could always
be like I'll take these brain saver
books to the doctor's office
that's because heavy metals can derail
electrical impulses heavy metals have a
lot to do
with our ability not to actually have a
connection to get that disconnect
the soul connects to nerve tissue inside
the brain it's part of the brain that
allows someone to have a heart so
metals can interfere with our soul and
our brain's connection
what about when someone's guilt is
overactive I want to talk about this
next part you guys it's really
interesting
since drinking these shots Atlanta says
since drinking these shots I've been so
relaxed I never remember ever being so
relaxed and I'm sleeping so deeply I
want you guys to know sleep can get a
lot better when you're doing these brain
shot Therapies
because that's how much healing is
happening inside the brain because it's
actually going directly to the brain
fast getting there resetting rewiring
and so healing is going to happen on all
kinds of different levels
I mean I waited all year or more
so you guys can have this information
countless hours to make sure these books
got into your hands I can't even I don't
even know what to say it was worth the
sacrifice every last bit of it so that
you guys had answers and tools
what about when someone's guilt is
overactive when toxic heavy metals
saturate a different area of the brain's
emotional centers they can cause
electrical impulses to Surge into
adjacent tissue and if that's the area
that governs guilt it heightens guilty
feelings so what happens you guys when
we have toxins inside the brain like
toxic heavy metals and it's in the
emotional centers of the brain it can
make somebody overactive with a lot of
guilt
so what I love about the guilt and shame
shifter it's hitting directly to the
emotional center of the brain
basically what I'm trying to tell you
and I'm giving you this really Advanced
information over here
is that for whatever reason why and how
we're experiencing guilt and shame
whether it's something that happened
that's justifiable
and how we feel or we don't know why
we're feeling this or it's something
that happened 10 years ago in our life
15 years ago in her life 20 years ago
five years whatever it is and we feel
this and it creeps up and we have this
guilt about something or we have this
feeling of Shame about something the
guilt and shame shifter can help rewire
and shift and change that that's how
incredible this is
Annette says I am still so surprised I
have been trying various shots since a
few days and today I tried the OCD shot
I got a smile on my face because I know
you're gonna it's gonna surprise a lot
of people because they're just they're
gonna get the results and it was the
first time that I could eat my supper
whoa including some cooked peas and
sweet potatoes sounds yummy actually
without feeling that I want to overeat
and without guilt that it was not all
raw that's amazing I usually only
include cooked on the weekends and my
digestion is better than ever I'm still
in awe and so so thankful that's
incredible
that's incredible
marjorie's uh Marjorie says overly
emotional does this mean what does this
mean the books go into great depth about
that there's an emotional brain chapter
that goes into depth I'm not even in the
emotional brain chapter I mean that's
how much information is is actually
placed around the books
Jenny Jenn says I'm having a medical
procedure next week for a car accident
and I'm so comforted to know that the
information in these books will be there
for me to cleanse after the medical
procedure that's so incredible I'm so
happy these books are there for you
that's what I wanted
wondering Wishin says I've been doing
the speak your truth shot wow that's an
incredible one and it helps me tell
people who talk about their ailments to
get your info amazing before I would get
awkward and then bad I didn't do more or
feel bad that you didn't do more and not
anymore
amazing
this is incredible you guys seriously
Josh
the wisdom shot drastically enhanced my
Consciousness and intuition I love the
wisdom shot I use that one periodically
as well
I need all the wisdom I can get I
receive the information I put the
information in the books
that's what I do but I always told you
guys I'm not a smart guy I'm just a very
good listener it's one of the abilities
I have and I also have another ability
to hear the voice since age four
and hang in there
for the ride because it's been brutal I
have that other ability
a certain level of
I guess
certain level of strength I don't know
what someone would call it
So reading through the comments
also going through here
okay so this is interesting
the littlest thing someone does like
borrowing a penny from the penny dish
did you ever do that borrow Penny from
the penny dish and
in the store the grocery store there's a
little pile of pennies there and you go
and grab one you're like here you go
grab two pennies here you go
the littlest thing someone does like
borrowing a penny from the penny dish at
a convenience store can fill them with
regret I've seen that happen the
emotional center of the brain
you know needs to be rewired because
they have that much regret because they
actually I've seen that actually
for someone feels guilty and they took
three pennies out of the penny jar and
they put three pennies down getting so
busy one day that they aren't able to
call back a friend even if that friend
would completely understand can make
someone feel terribly guilty like you
got so busy you can't call back that
friend or call back that family member
and you just feel the guilt it's just
hanging over you
to the point where it hurts
and they're saddened and depressed like
they get depressed over it like the day
ended and you couldn't get back to
someone
then when something happens where guilt
is is the appropriate response if that
person makes a particular mistake their
attempts to learn from it can be
heightened to the point of obsession or
danger where you make a mistake and you
hate yourself you hate your guts over it
which is really horrible
that someone feels that way where you
make a mistake and you hate your own
guts like you hate yourself over it
that's brutal so many people go through
that
that's really hard
even approaching harming themselves in
some cases where you want to harm
yourself because you feel so guilty
about some things that's when the guilt
and shame shifter have to come in we
need that relief fast because there's
people out there and I feel so bad for
them for some of the for some simple
things too they'll hate themselves so
much they'll have so much guilt
or if something happened in their life
they'll have so much guilt where they
want to harm themselves because they
hate themselves that much it's so
terrible
we have to not let that happen to people
Maria says the adrenal shot was my
favorite the adrenal the adrenal shot is
one of my favorite
so far wow I was suddenly so calm yes
that's what happens with the adrenal
shot the fight or flight amazing
I was suddenly so calm and I was not
into my natural angry mode wow
mind-blowing
incredible Marie I I wish the greatest
and the best
for you with that because it's so
incredible when you get that relief I
want you to have that relief
if you have to rely on that shot as
you're healing to rewire and heal and
reset please do
KP tree says yesterday shot changed my
day turned it into it turned it all
around I was so happy afterwards
incredible
if that person's soul is injured from
abuse so say there's somebody that
they're injured from abuse right
hardships betrayal or trust breakage so
they're they're injured from trust
breakage hardships they're injured from
abuse of some kind
it can compound the situation and make
the guilt reaction worse
or the reaction can go the opposite
direction where the anger numbness
settle in and displace all feelings that
go completely until the numbness and
anger wear off and then the guilt
returns and that person just hates
themselves and that's sad we don't want
that we don't want people experiencing
that the guilt and shame shifter is one
of the medical medium tools now
available to actually help somebody
shift out of this because you can go
down a rabbit hole of guilt a rabbit
hole of Shame
it's terrifying when you think about it
and to actually be able to fix that for
someone to turn that around is is short
I mean as a miracle
so I'm in the brain saver books you guys
just so you know brain saver books just
came out if you're brand new here if
you're here and you're watching this
and it interests you
we're in a free challenge so we're day
eight of the medical medium Branch out
therapy cleanse challenge you didn't
have to pay to get in
I want to donate all the time I have I
want it to be free
and I want to help in any way possible
it's not about banking it's about making
sure because right now with influencers
and everything it's only about banking
now it's sad to say
but that's how the world became and the
world is turning
I want to make sure it's free everything
medicalmedium.com is free download your
free grocery store list so you can
finish the cleanse with us there's two
more days you can join now sign up get
your free grocery store list a whole bit
go to medicalmedium.com and let's finish
out the next two days for free
because that's how it's got to be
so Integrity generation I trained two
the OCD obsessive shot shifters okay
sorry brain today in The Help stay calm
at work incredible
amazing I was trying to read what you
put there
I think it was all short shortened
foreign
oh yeah okay call me obsessive all right
incredible
amazing
that's a cool name for the shot I like
it obsessy
see guys let's see what else we got
cooking let's go
all right we're in this
we're in the shifter shots
um you know what it is you guys don't
want to read your comments today
Courtney Feldman Courtney Feldman oh my
God
I can't wait to do the guilt and shame
shifter with my husband and stepson
incredible
well tell her tell everybody I said hi
please
dear friend of mine
I'm so glad you're here so we're in the
shifter shots
that's where we are let's read about it
a little bit
the world is getting so complicated in
so many ways and we've been pushed in so
many different directions it's easy to
get confused or stuck in a pattern
that is not helpful for the healing
process so when we get the guilt and
shame and it takes over and it becomes
like a
like Madness really because it's such a
Feeling
I had one person describe it to me years
ago where it felt like just someone was
just taking over them
the guilt and shame could not just leave
it just could they could not get it away
from them or out of them
these brain shots are designed to help
shift our Direction fast
so our body can shift and heal and our
emotional frame of mind can break a
pattern
or confinement that the complications of
this world has created so if we're like
confined and stuck in this pattern and
not able to break it we need that
shifter and that's what these are
shifter shots
there's ten shifter shots we're doing
the guilt and shame shifter today I'm
excited because I have a lot of guilt
we are in the middle here it is
intermission it's halftime
you guys want to do the robot with me
Spirit of compassion tells me a lot of
you guys do way better Roblox than they
way better in fact mine are embarrassing
[Music]
the moonwalk one
foreign
[Music]
hey that's our halftime
you guys get a good break Refreshers
Shake It Off Shake It Off
we're going into the information
incredible
Kim Miller says my digestion feels
better than ever on juice
sorry I'm just sorry my dad would it
help if I read them right read the
questions right I'm sorry you guys my
digestion feels better than ever on just
a week of shots after being bedridden
for four years oh my God
you guys by the way
the comments are this small on the
screen
but that's incredible
that's absolutely incredible
seriously I mean that that is just
amazing
I'm just so proud of you guys but just
know that I'm proud of you George says I
love this book I learned so much and I'm
only page 92. there's two books so you
got 1200 plus Pages coming your way so
let me just think here you're page 92
you got 1100 Pages coming your way
incredible when I think about it
now ready there's six books per book you
got to think about it that way because
that's what it is like one book two
books three books four books five books
six books
there's six books in each book
yes
there were many times when I was working
22 hour days 20 I did a 24-hour day
which was stupid of me but which was
definitely reckless in my opinion but I
knew the deadlines were coming and I
knew I had to make sure I get this
information out there
media mediate says our medial says I
feel so calm after the energy shifter
shots
think they changed my personality what
they're doing is let's talk about that a
little bit
like if you're doing the energy shifter
shot
or the obsessive thoughts shifter shot
or your guilt and shame shifter shot or
a stabilizer or any of them what's
happening is they're going into the
emotional centers of the brain but only
a source from above would know the
combination in order to make that happen
it cannot happen if you just do some
juicing it will not happen now straight
celery juice is an incredible Miracle
tool it is for doing all the things I've
talked about in the books
but the brain shots or are another tool
from above
so what we're essentially doing is we're
bringing in more tools that are just so
profound and when you even put some of
these together these tools just forget
it you're moving forward you get out of
bed you get out of wheelchairs you get
you get moving through your you know you
get moving you heal you you grow you
move forward it's just miraculous and
amazing
but what happens is
this is absorbing really quick instantly
instantly going to the brain boom but
it's not just the absorption factor that
happens it's knowing that if you put
these three together there's a quick
absorption rate but it's not just that
there's something in these three
ingredients that actually does something
to certain groups of neurons that no one
would ever know and science can never
figure out
so too says
Anthony a new study about EBV causing me
long covet in Sweden really because they
got it from medical medium
and it was published first
medical media where are you where's
medical medium
so
what happens is when they say that
there's a new study what they're not
telling you situ is what they're not
telling you
is that they took it from a New York
Times best-selling book in a number one
New York Times best-selling author and
they're not giving me credit because the
information is too mind-blowing and too
incredible already published first and
so what they're doing is they're
illegally
plagiarizing or taking that information
trying to get the gold star put on them
whatever
about their Discovery and they're not
saying that it was already published
first discovered already done
and put out there
so
do you call that evil oh yeah
Selena says I'm I'm in such a good mood
since doing the brain shots thank you so
much aw and SOC the info in the books
blows my mind I studied psychology and
medical medium info is way ahead
Neuroscience like a lot and incredible
thank you Selena thank you for being
here and thank you for for that comment
it means a lot and you know what happens
is the medical medium information is
really Advanced so when you see in
mystery chronic illness out there when
they're trying to do a study on
something or something it's already been
done and figured out by medical medium
published already before or spoke about
in lectures or podcasts I already put it
out there
so and this includes Mayo Clinic this
includes other clinics this includes
whatever Cleveland Clinic this includes
um you know Cedars this includes
Whatever Whenever they play around with
viral talk viruses Epstein-Barr anything
like that it was all done before it was
all medical medium and they're not
citing it back
let's do the guilt and shame shifter
talk let's take a look about that let's
look at everything about it
I have a lot of guilt
the guilt inside of me is I just bought
a wine vineyard the other day
and I just spent four billion dollars on
the wine vineyard me and a bunch of
doctor friends
and we're gonna drink wine each glass of
wine cost about a hundred thousand
dollars a glass
that's where my guilt lies
all right you guys let's move on to the
next part here
so we did this we're talking about
the shifter shots
let's head to another department inside
the books we're in the entry level
cleanse let's go into that for a little
bit so we're doing the entry level
cleanse we're doing a 10-day version of
the entry level cleanse that means
whatever diet you're on whatever medical
medium tools and and Foods you're doing
whatever you got going on you can still
keep on doing and you're doing the
branch out therapy or if you're somebody
that just came out of a fast food you
know your your fast food restaurants are
the way you eat for now because that's
just life or you're on some just keto
diet or something and you're starving
yourself of like glucose and things you
need and you want to start going into
this then go into this like whatever it
is that you're doing
you can bring this into that which is
incredible so we're doing the entry
level brain shot therapy cleanse which
means 10 days
but I'm doing three shots a day you can
do three shots a day you could do one
shot a day so I'm doing three shots a
day so today's gonna be right now it's
gonna be the first shot of the goat and
shame shifter
second shot's gonna be later third
shot's gonna be later on so it's gonna
be three shots for me
I don't know what you guys are doing you
could do one shot that's perfectly fine
each day you can do more you can do more
than three if you wanted to
which you can so we're do we're in the
entry level
brain shot therapy cleanser what I love
about it is it says 50 ounces of water
throughout the day minimum so make sure
you're doing 50 ounces of water minimum
throughout the day don't do the 50
ounces or some food or a whole bunch of
stuff right after you send your shot
down so don't send your shot down
and then all of a sudden
[Music]
you're now eating something minutes
after or drinking a whole bunch of water
don't do that let the shot work let it
absorb let it get in and do its Miracles
let it let it do its miracles
which would be amazing so let's get to
the shot
guilt and shame shifter it's right here
let's talk about it a little bit
try applying the shot when
you don't believe in yourself or you've
lost confidence in yourself has that
ever happened
did you ever have that happen where you
don't believe in yourself or you lost
confidence in yourself
if that has happened even in the past
you should try the golden shame shifter
you're losing faith that you're a good
person did you ever have that experience
if you're losing faith that you're a
good person
it's time to get the guilt and shame
shifter out
let it get into the emotional centers of
the brain let it shift your
consciousness
let it work on those neurons and let it
help heal
how about this one
does this ring a bell at all you guys
you're feeling guilt or Shame about
being sick
I know that when someone's dealing with
chronic illness and you guys have dealt
with this your hope many times many
people do I know that if you've dealt
with any kind of chronic illness
we have guilt and shame about being sick
we just do it can even torture us
right I'm seeing a bunch of people on IG
talk about yes that's happened
yeah that happens
to so many people it's like you get
chronically sick you're seeing doctor
after doctor you feel guilty your family
is worried you feel guilty for them feel
guilty for everybody all of it you feel
like you feel like you're just you're
just struggling so you feel guilty about
that
how about this one you experience
insecurity or loss of confidence due to
chronic illness like you experience
insecurity like you feel insecure for
being chronically sick that's a time to
use the golden shame shifter too when it
hits you like waves of it so here you
are you've been sick for a while for a
couple years and all of a sudden you get
a wave of it like I feel like insecure
about being sick I feel like I don't
feel good about it I don't feel
confident about it that's a great time
to use the guilt and shame shifter
you're feeling less than or like you are
not good enough that's a good time to
actually use the guilt and shame shifter
where you don't feel good enough you
feel less than
I think I'm going to take the guilt and
shame shifter for that reason for myself
personally because I feel less than many
times and I feel like I'm not good
enough so I will be definitely taking
that shot shifter
Terry Appleman I'm still amazed that
none of the shots have made me nauseous
with how sensitive my stomach is oh my
God that's incredible
that's amazing I'm so proud of you Tara
so here's one here so Debbie P says to
hell with alcoholic shots these are way
better explanation point
way better 10 explanation points now you
only did one explanation point but I'll
put 10 more
okay
here's one right here what do you think
about this one
is is this a good reason to use it
you can't forgive yourself
for something you may believe was your
fault
take the guilt and shame shifter if that
happens
he showed his healing if someone has
super inflamed nerves in their stomach
and can't swallow many of the
ingredients could they just hold the
shot in their mouth for the result since
it absorbs in the mouth yes
okay so you can't forgive yourself for
someone
sure you can't for something you think
you did wrong
if that's happening the guilt and shame
shifter you see how incredible this is
and listen if there's you can do the
trauma shock loss
you can do the guilt shame you can do a
couple of different ones too you can
they're just so powerful you can switch
it up
here's one right here
you're feeling guilt or Shame about
something you said and can't unsay
now I say all kinds of things
remember when we were doing a live like
way back do you guys remember when we
were doing a live way back and that
person was saying all those terrible
things about me like Terrible Things
they were like trolling and they were
saying all these terrible things and
then Dr Nesbitt
came out and called the person psycho
I felt really bad for Dr Nesbitt
Jackie B says you should say mayonnaise
Clinic I always used to say Manos
mayonnaise Clinic
they make a lot of mayo there what else
are they doing they don't have the
answers for chronic illness
I mean no disrespect I'm sure there's
some good docs there
but either way I think they're making a
lot of mayonnaise there is what I think
Selena
just my opinion I have every right to
have an opinion everybody else has an
opinion against me 24 7 about me
can't have an opinion one time
Selena
psychology is now acknowledging that
toxic heavy metals are in part behind
autism oh my God
oh my God
let's see what the rest of your comment
is
Selena says psychology is now
acknowledging that toxic heavy metals
are in part behind autism did you know
there's no science study that shows
toxic heavy metals are behind autism
did you know there's no study or proof
or any kind of like discovery
it was published almost a decade ago in
the medical medium book here and also
lectured by me many years before but you
say something else but they won't say
what to do to heal because they don't
know and they never knew it was Metals
anyway they're stealing your information
and mixing it with BS ridiculous exactly
that's what they do Selena that's what
they do it's because millions of these
went around the world with the answer in
them
millions of this New York Times
bestseller went around the world
and they had to take the information and
they won't sign it back
I hope when they leave this place
someday I hope
they can find peace with themselves
when they're leaving here
because they really need to because
that's just some wrong going down
all right
you're feeling guilt or Shame about
something you said and can't unsay like
you said something and you can't unsay
it
here's one right here you guys here's a
great time to use the golden shame
shifter right here
you're feeling guilt or Shame about not
being able to Live Your Dream yet
I was feeling that a long time ago and
still do
because I was forced into this by Spirit
of compassion at age four I still want
to do something on my own someday
um Helene says 50 ounces dot dot dot
Does it include the 32 ounces of lemon
water in the morning
yes includes lemon water in the morning
my dream is to make sure the chronically
will get answers and heal that is my
dream but when I was younger and spirit
of compassion was
making me do this
my dream was to just ride my bicycle and
do a lot of other fun things when I was
eight years old five years old six years
old okay
and here's another one here
this is important too you're feeling
guilt or Shame about not being able to
help a friend or family member in the
present moment that's a great time to
use it too
here's one you're having difficulty
forgiving someone else who has hurt you
so you can't you can't forgive someone
who has hurt you it's a hard one to do
guilt and shame shifter
of someone who's of disappointed you or
someone who's upset you here's one right
here you're feeling ashamed or guilty in
any way this shot can help you
understand and release emotional wounds
that are
actually igniting guilt and shame
perpetuating
all right let's work on it now
I'm excited you guys I'm going to move
over the brain a little bit here let's
get going
it's the mm-1500
I mean I got a little guilt that I
haven't been talking about it
for a while
because I've been so busy trying to get
the book done and everything else and
then the juicer sharks came into the
community started selling people the MLM
crap and saying that this is the best
juice or whatever and they didn't
realize it but the mm 1500 and the 900
is what squeezes more juice out of
everything and it saves you money
because the cost of produce is going up
and we want something to pay for itself
so what I find that my personal
experience and what I've seen other
people's experiences
the savings that happens when you're
juicing with the mm 1500 or 900 is you
actually pay for the juicer itself
so that if you ever get a broken part
it pays for the broken part over again
unlike the other juicers when you get a
broken part
it's not paying for that broken part
because all the juicers just break all
the time all the juicers out there so if
you ever get like a worn out part and
you have to get it pays for itself you
want something that pays for itself all
the time so you're saving money over and
over again
so many amazing comments about your
experiences with the brain shots please
share your stories on Instagram so we
can share with the community you guys
know how to do that at Medical medium
hashtag medical medium I want to share
them reels and stories and posts that's
incredible so many experiences you're
having I would love to just
you know would love to actually share
those so you guys we're making the guilt
shame shifter remember the mm 1500 is 20
off right now which is incredible keep
that in mind I endorsed fully endorsed
the company because of what it does high
compression saves people money
the the cool thing which the juicer
sharks don't know by the way when
they're trying to rip people off with
the juicers out there
they don't realize this makes hummus
salsa sorbet ice cream
nut milks nut Butters
did I say hummus again
flawlessly it's incredible on top of the
fact
that it crushes it in celery juice and
crushes it by Saving you money when
you're juicing stuff all right you guys
so many people asking me what are the
best juicers and I haven't been
responding and I feel guilty so I have
guilt and shame about not responding
enough to that
so because I've been too busy but I
already thought everybody knew about the
1500 and 900 but I was wrong not
everybody knows about it okay so here we
go let's make this and get it going
it's a quiet juicer by the way
so half inch piece of fresh ginger
pop that in there
[Music]
that's first
half to one cup of tightly packed
spinach
so I'm going to tightly pack it in my
hand
and I'm going to drop it in here
so that was about
half cup there somewhere around there
get a little bit more
to make a cup
[Music]
incredible I love the guilt and Shane
shifter
half to one orange peel
you want to peel it
so I'm gonna get my little paring knife
right here if you guys are okay with
this I'm gonna do a quick peeling of
this Orange
now don't use a rotten orange ever I
just want to give you that little tip
make sure you don't have like a rotten
spot on your orange like a real soft
spot and then you end up just putting in
a rotten orange that can happen Allison
Saunders says omega's warranty replaces
my parts for free has done it twice with
no problem
and the and the juice you're saving us
money and so what's happening is it's
paying for itself
incredible
I'm Blown Away
I just feel bad when the juicer sharks
and the Sharks come into the community
because it's like
they'll run ads 24 7 in the community
and then they'll get people on board and
try to do the affiliate feed things so
that everybody's pushing them and then
meanwhile people are not saving money
and produce is expensive foreign it's so
sad
Carolina Sago says I have the 900 and
it's precious I love my 900 this is the
1500 but I love the 900. love it
love it the 920 off in this 1500 is 20
off
it says feel already better by attending
here
amazing
so I'm going to
put this half orange in here
if you guys don't mind I'll put this
other half orange there right
put my little pieces in here
I feel better already attending here
I'm around like-minded people Souls
and you guys are much smarter than me
too some around very seasoned experts in
hell because I believe you guys have
been through a lot in your life and you
know the games out there
and you know
so
I'm gonna put this
towel in my pocket
is this possible do I actually have
another shot to drink can this be real I
mean I'm not kidding I sound like I'm
kidding but I'm not that's the whole
point
I'm not kidding I'm not joking I get
excited when I know there's another shot
to drink like a miracle shot
like a miracle blend from above and so I
get these tingles coming it became when
I was drinking them all the time but now
I get them a little bit when it's like
when we're getting there it's just crazy
so I'm gonna I'm actually gonna get this
into my shot
so excited
[Music]
incredible
I am so excited
[Music]
does it help that I spill it a little
bit
no it doesn't
come on now
all right
are you guys ready
I'm about making sure we find relief I
want relief I'm excited
[Music]
here's the first step
okay I'm feeling it on the first set
[Music]
it's incredible really
are you feeling that too are you doing
it with me right now
it's just incredible it's extraordinary
I'm gonna go with the second tip
oh my God
that's incredible
my God
I'm feeling it
bartender give me another
that one's giving me
like a sensation all through my entire
body because guilt and shame
how much you want to make a bet that it
even reaches Beyond guilt and shame
because the power of these are changing
lives like Miracles and spiritual
passion told me that
they do so much more than what I they're
even labeled as
they go deeper into deeper levels
of what we've experienced in our lives
emotionally in the brain rewiring and
resetting the brain
that feels good so much so
I'll have to say it one more time
bartender give me another
because that one right there just smells
so so so good
whoo
I could feel it the sensation everything
about it the power it has I have a
connection to I make that connection I
have a connection a sensitivity in this
sense since I was a child to connect
with what I'm putting inside my body and
the feeling I get and I know what it is
it's just so special you guys have you
guys tried the brain shot with me did
you try it without me that's fine too
what did you feel what are your results
what did you experience please share
your story on a reel or a post or story
or whatever and tag it medical medium
right hashtag medical medium
remember this tons of free resources
free it's free
right medicalmedium.com free I'm
completely enhancing the website I'm
making it literally a treasure Trove of
information and recipes and everything
for free there's no pay walls why do
they do that out there why are all the
you know the the wealthy Elite podcast
doctor-ish people influencers why are
they when they already have a bankroll
in their account why are they making
everything cost something how come no
disrespect I'm not judging anybody but
what the hell can't it be free
medicalmedium.com is free no
subscription so no subscribing
subscription fees my God this feels so
good I actually feel like I'm drunk
right now
this is incredible
it's all free medicalmedium.com it's
incredible I'm doing exclusive audio
messages with information that's
life-changing on telegram tomorrow's day
nine of the medical medium ring shot
challenge
and we're making the nerve shifter which
I already read a couple of comments
about the nerve shifter right
and you guys can you leave reviews at
amazon.com when you get a chance on the
brain books if you get a chance please
leave a review right and you guys know
how to clean your books right take a
dish towel little towel right here
because they come the covers get dirty
when they go through the Amazon channels
so when they go through the Amazon
channels you'll get a little smudge on
them because the conveyor belt's got
grease on them so you got to clean them
off they come out real nice right with a
little damp cloth a little soap on it
remember um leave a review if you can
that would be incredible it helps others
find their way
it's so great and you can re-watch the
replays at medicalmedium.com and you can
watch all eight days tomorrow's day nine
medical medium.com how incredible all of
it right
and
you guys know I'm honored to be with you
guys out here
another thing to the medical medium
podcast at Apple podcast have you heard
the alien episode or just all the
episodes have you heard mind-blowing and
the light infusion meditation wait till
you try the light infusion meditation
that's in this book in the protocols
book Brain saver protocols please check
the books out when you can 40 off
amazon.com get them free at the library
I could care less get them free free
free free free it doesn't matter if I
have to live under a bridge on a pile of
hay with a cardboard box around me for
God's sakes get the books for free I
don't care if I don't get my two cents
just get the books for free please
it doesn't matter go to the library and
get them for free I want you to heal
because in this lifetime that's what
matters to me and that's what it's all
about now the books cost money to print
to actually process the print to put
together to get out there to get in
trucks the fuel that's burned get to the
bookstores to get around the world just
know that the 26 dollars and the 29 for
each book 40 off is going to good use at
least to cover some of that cost
last but not least look out for the
imposters that say their medical medium
and they say they're Anthony William the
medical medium and they have my profile
pic and they say they do consultations I
don't do consultations look out for them
because they're out there trying to scam
everybody along with all the sharks
trying to scam everybody with their
their garbage supplements and juicers
and everything else Under the Sun make
sure
um when you're looking when you see an
imposter I mean if you see the blue
check then it could be medical medium
here because we got the blue check
imposters don't have the blue check but
still look out for the imposters they
are shady as heck out there anyway guys
hey robot
can we do it one last time
what do you think
I know that your robots are getting
better my robot's getting worse talking
robot
protein protein where's my protein
where's my protein protein protein
protein where's my protein
where is it
meat protein need protein
protein robots you guys know what that
is
let's see Yo kinky says do you have
anything to relieve tonight is by any
chance
have you read the medical medium books
there's protocols in them life-changing
protocols
thank you for being here and even asking
I'm honored you have entered
the free brain shot therapy challenge
and you're asking about tinnitus
hundreds and hundreds of thousands of
people's yield their tinnitus around the
world
piano Granny says what is the spelling
of the juicer I'm very hard of hearing
hmm
the spelling of it can you guys actually
put mm 1500
in the comments
for granny
right
[Music]
and you can look at you can look in the
description
[Music]
and see it right in the bio
mm 1500 there it is Natasha said mm 1500
or mm-900
but those those are this is the model of
the mm-1500 there it is everybody's
saying them on 1500.
a couple of 900 too
hey guys
love you guys
[Applause]
[Music]