okay and we're going to be talking about
some other cool stuff what happens
inside our brain when we have a
relationship that breaks up friendship
that breaks up
family member
relationship that breaks up
anything like that if any of you have
had experiences with that where it's
either relationship whether it's
Intimate Relationships that break up
Partnerships that break up friendships
that break up but we're not intimate
right family member relationships that
break up
if you've had any of those so we're
going into that it's going to be fun so
you guys
this is incredible this is Dave 14 day
18 what is this day
eight
this is day eight
so do I wish it was day 14 or day 16 do
I wish no I don't wish that at all
because I want to do as many days as
possible we're doing a 20-day Branch out
therapy cleanse challenge I have plans
to heal right here just get down to it
for a little bit here what are we making
today
we're making the relationships
stabilizer is what we're making and I'm
going to
find it in here
where are we where are we
page 506 okay you guys
relationship breakups stabilizer right
there that's the one we're making so
it's gonna be exciting
all right let's get let's get down to
business
page
88.
it's where we're going next
right here
Soul protection that's what we're
reading about so this is going to be
very interesting
Soul protection
you guys you guys heard the podcast with
Sarah and Aaron Foster
so I'm seeing a couple of you guys saw
that
incredible
or heard that you listened
there can also be a soul aspect to
emotional events
an emotional event have you had an
emotional event in your life I'm sure
you have
we've all had emotional events in our
life right we've all had that happen
where there's some type of emotional
event
there can also be a soul aspect to
emotional events when something terrible
happens
your soul which normally resides inside
your brain in this area
that's where our soul normally resides
in this area this is actually really
incredible information we're talking
about right now it like gives me
goosebumps when I'm even reading about
it
your soul which normally resides in your
brain
gets projected boom
out of your body
to protect you
from a certain amount of Soul injury
everything's going great my soul's over
here everything's going good my soul is
where my brain is my soul is here
everything's going great an emotional
event hits boom your soul
exits
projects out of your body to protect you
from a certain amount of Soul injury
that's what happens it's protecting you
from a certain amount of Soul injury so
it projects out of your head out of your
body
and that's the whole thing where
someone's like
I was out of body that was an
out-of-body experience I was looking
down at myself
when that car crash happened I saw
myself it was as if I was out of body
that wasn't even in me
some people can feel this out-of-body
experience watching themselves from afar
or even above where they're seeing
themselves even if they can't physically
see themselves they see themselves
there's a feeling they get their soul
was projected out of their head out of
their body
Ivan says it's a soul not inside the
heart the soul is not inside the heart
and I talked about this the other day
it's why in the medieval times they
focused on beheading everybody
right they beheaded everybody
and there was a reason for that because
there was
in essence everybody knew
that this was the most important area
not because we spoke but because it's
the most important area
was here
punishment
was the guillotine punishment was always
chopping everybody's heads off and then
putting their heads on a pike right and
having their heads on a pike so you walk
through the village and everybody in the
Villager heads are all chopped off and
they're on the bikes right
there's a reason why they use the
guillotine for so many centuries
in Europe
old England they use the guillotine
because chopping off the head was the
most satisfying it was the status that
that was the that was the satisfying
aspect
that made everybody happy that wanted to
chop that person's head off they weren't
happy until their head was chopped off
they weren't happy if they were killed
they weren't happy if they were stabbed
in a kill or killed in a different way
they weren't
they weren't happy if they were drowned
they were happy
when their heads were chopped off
some people so what I'm talking about is
emotional events if you just got on here
would I I'm saying something really
really
profound piece of information from above
is that our soul is in this area
and if you believe your soul is down in
your feet if you believe your soul is
where your feet is that's fine too and
then it gets projected out of the body
fine Erica Mallett says I remember when
I first heard this information from aw I
was shocked but it makes so much sense
if you believe your soul is in your knee
that's where your soul is
if that makes you feel better if you're
somebody that just doesn't believe the
soul is in this area you don't believe
the soul is here
you don't believe that
you think your soul is here in your knee
the healing shop table on IG says that's
why we say I was beside myself
so true so true
another comment on IG
and my mommy says this makes no s this
makes so much sense because when I was
15 or 16 and living in a toxic home my
soul must have left because there is a
period of time when I felt like I was
watching my life from above yes because
it protects your soul it's an innate
internal guidance and wisdom of our body
to project our soul out
Justina
it happened to me and I thought I was
going crazy
we go through a hard time something
happens to us
okay let's see every
every melt heel says melto heel says I
feel like mine never came back and
that's something people can feel when
they've been traumatized they feel like
their soul has never come back that does
happen where they feel that way
we go through a hard time we go through
an experience that's really scary
something happens emotionally or we're
emotionally abused or we have a
relationship breakup where it's so
traumatizing that relationship break up
that you feel like you're watching
yourself from above or you're beside
yourself like you just said earlier you
feel like you're witnessing it
and in an out-of-body experience you
feel as if you're witnessing it from
afar that's what it feels like
that's because Spirit of compassion gave
me this information to answer why anyone
has ever felt that way and put it in the
brain saver book Because when we go
through an experience
and we're walking along and our soul is
here
and then boom that experience happens
and our souls projected out of us
Boom Out Of Us
and there's somebody that doesn't
believe what Spirit of compassion said
where our soul resides in our brain our
soul resides in this area and you
believe your soul resides in your feet
I'm not judging you that's fine if you
believe your soul is in your knee that's
where your soul is it's in your name
fine it's still projected boom out of
you when you go through an experience
some people can feel this out of Body
Experience watching themselves from afar
or even above
this is a safety mechanism
this way your soul doesn't have to
experience the full amount of pain from
betrayal or loss betrayal hurts so bad
God does it ever
Nito says when I have gone through Nito
and Rumble
says when I have gone through emotional
trauma I always felt like I was out of
it like my mind was not working or gone
or something thank you for explaining
this feeling
this way your soul doesn't have to
experience the full amount of pain just
partial pain our soul feels partial pain
like part of it
foreign
hurts so bad
it's hell
betrayal is hell
that's what betrayal is
loss hurts so bad
loss
Indescribable unless you walked in that
person's shoes do you know what that
loss feels like if someone's lost may
not seem big but it's big someone's
betrayal may not seem big but it's big
to them
and when it's big enough to them where
it hurts
then boom the souls
cast out for a moment to protect it so
it's only partial hurt
and bird says if I believe or believe
that there is no soul is that fine too
absolutely
read the final chapter in the brain
saver protocols book where's the braces
protocols boom read the final chapter in
here if you don't believe that a soul
exists and yes please stay here and
let's do the brain shot together or just
hang out and chill out wait a minute
hear the Mike the Headless Chicken story
that I gotta talk about
by the way this is day eight of the
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse Challenge free free Challenge
free
that's your 20-day free grocery shopping
list you can download at
medicalmedium.com
we're doing 20 days we're on day eight
what's day eight relationship breakup
stabilizer
you may have heard of the supernatural
occurrence of Mike the Headless Chicken
it's an unbelievable
true story
Mike was a chicken
in the 1940s
who survived long after his head was cut
off
Mike the Headless Chicken was a chicken
that had his head cut off
and still was alive
there are a lot of theories
theories out there about how this
happened how can Mike the Headless
Chicken walk around
eating out of his neck
and stay alive
after hearing this story at the time in
the 1940s
hundreds
and hundreds of farmers
worldwide started chopping their
chickens heads off in experimental ways
thousands upon thousands upon thousands
of chickens were beheaded in different
grotesque ways to see if they would
survive it
it became an obsession
chopping the heads off in various places
because people were in such disbelief so
farmers were chopping chickens heads off
in different places on the chicken
different places on the chicken
because they were in complete disbelief
complete disbelief
so they were chopping chickens heads off
is what they were doing
because they're in disbelief
Farmers would
sever the heads higher up
okay so you got your chicken
they would sever the heads higher up
because they're thinking how is this
even possible
so hundreds and hundreds of chickens
were beheaded but higher up in all kinds
of different places because they don't
understand how a chicken can get his
head completely cut off
and still go around and eat through its
neck and live
it became an obsession chopping the
heads off in various places because
people were in such disbelief Farmers
would severe the heads higher up
preserving even more of the chicken's
neck and brain stem than mics
foreign
ERS preserved more of the brain stem
than Mike the Headless Chicken whose
head was completely cut off so farmers
were cutting off all kinds of places on
chickens everywhere
chopping their heads off chunk chunk
and they were doing it higher up trying
to preserve as much brain stem as
possible trying to even preserve half
the brain and they were chopping the
chicken's head off
Cornelius says I've heard you say that
so often now but it always blows my mind
because my work as a psychotherapist is
so different now Cornelia monitor here
truly
Farmers would never Farmers would severe
the heads higher up preserving even more
of the chicken's neck and brainstem than
mics than Mike's neck Mike the chicken
that lived and was walking around and
eating
trying to see if their chickens would
live too
over a hundred thousand chickens were
beheaded in this process over a hundred
thousand chickens were beheaded during
this process
and they never survived not one chicken
survived
but Mike
survived and Mike had his whole head
chopped off
here's what no one knows about how Mike
stayed alive
get ready for this
because I asked Spirit of compassion
questions it's one of my pastimes and I
thought I would put one of my little
pastimes because I asked Spirit
compassion can I please ask you a
question about Mike the Headless Chicken
I would love to put Mike the Headless
Chicken in here and sort of compassion
it's like it's not what you want to put
in here
it's what's important which which is
critically important for people
because it's not all about Anthony
William or these books would be all
about Anthony William
and spirit of compassion
gave me a little gift
and said I will put
Mike the Headless Chicken
inside the brain saver book
over a hundred thousand chickens were
beheaded in this process and they never
survived here's what no one knows about
how Mike stayed alive
when I asked Spirit of compassion and
why it's relevant here and that's also
why Spirit of compassion let me put Mike
the Headless Chicken in here because it
was relevant
a chicken has a soul
that's not me saying it
that's not me saying a chicken has a
soul
not like when a plant-based person says
all animals have soul
have a soul no that's not me saying it
Spirit of compassion is saying a chicken
has a soul this isn't an anti-chicken
anti this is an anti-vegan this isn't
whatever or this is vegan whatever
that's not what all this is
this isn't a talk having anything to do
with any of that
a chicken has a soul which normally
resides in its brain Spirit of
compassion told me that a chicken has a
soul which resides in the chicken's
brain
just like ours
just like our soul that resides here
at the traumatic time of having Mike's
head chopped off
this chicken soul
left the chicken's brain
instead of floating away Into The Ether
when someone dies
or a pet dies
and their soul leaves them and floats
out of their head
they passed away their soul is floating
away their soul enters the ether
instead of floating away in the ether as
the chicken's body died the chicken's
body died
the head was chopped off of my the
chicken and the body instead of dying
stayed alive
instead of floating away in the ether as
the chicken bodies died chicken's body
died the chicken's Soul entered into the
chicken's body hear this Spirit of
compassion answered a question for me
and it blows my freaking mind it blows
my mind
the chicken soul entered into the
chicken's body
instead of floating away in The Ether
get ready for this
giving the physical body's will the will
which is called strength
strength
giving the
physical body of the chicken the
chickens will
extra strength to survive
and all the other Farmers chopped off
thousands upon thousands hundreds of
thousands of chickens heads off
but those chickens Souls did not go back
and enter into the chicken's body those
chicken Souls
floated up
to The Ether
hundreds of thousands of chickens that
were beheaded those Souls of those
chickens
floated to The Ether
and did not re-enter into the chicken's
body
but Mike the Headless Chicken
his soul
entered into the body
and granted the body extra strength to
survive
get ready for this one this will blow
your mind
not only
did the soul of that chicken enter into
the body giving the body physical
strength
by adding to the physical will power the
will and the strength of that chicken
but the soul had intelligence in it do
you believe your soul has Intelligence
in it
when you leave here it has no
intelligence in it when your soul leaves
here it has Intelligence inside the soul
as it leaves here
Spirit of compassion told me
instead of floating away into the ether
as the chicken's body died the chicken
soul entered into the chicken's body
giving the physical body's will extra
strength to survive along with
intelligence this is the part that blows
my mind along with intelligence the soul
had gathered from the chicken's brain
the soul of the chicken gathered
intelligence from the chicken's brain
and took it along with the soul and then
the Soul re-entered into the chicken's
physical body with the intelligence of
what was in the brain meaning eat
Peck around the yard live
its legs
the soul was propelling a chicken's body
with no brain no head
that is
Mike stayed alive
because by entering his body his soul
gave strength of Will and brain
intelligence to the chicken's body
I got I got Goosebumps all over my
entire body right now because
that is such a powerful piece of Soul
information that no one knows that
doesn't exist out there
that what I even think about Spirit of
compassion please see it in this book
which just blew my mind
shy the light says what page in the book
is this on page 88 of brain saver I hope
you get brain saver
amazon.com us on sale big time right now
for this book
and protocols
someone said I lost the point
I would re-watch this again if you can
rewatch the replay of medicalmedium.com
I mean seriously
did you guys just roll in don't tell me
you guys didn't didn't even hear what I
said or something do I have to do the
whole thing over again
why did the soul stay
because that's how incredible souls are
Spirit of compassion says because the
soul was taking a chance
a Gamble
that if it re-entered the physical body
of its CH of the chicken
that the owner of the chicken the farmer
might let it live
remember when a chicken's head is cut
off the body's discarded and thrown in a
bin
this chicken's soul
took a chance
it's incredible
all right so we got some more
information let's talk about
relationships this is really great April
tasks is what page it's 88 on brain
saver
credible information
roller coaster relationships let's move
on to relationships we're talking about
the relationship breakup stabilizer and
that's the one we're doing today I'm
excited about this
roller coaster relationships
each Soul has its own free will
that's why
Mike the heckless chicken
Mike's soul
had its own free will
that Free Will can determine if you're
going to be a ghost down here
that Free Will determines
a huge part
of when we leave our physical body
that will be taken that piece of
information and spread around the
spiritual communities but no medical
medium isn't spiritual
all right roller coaster relationships
let's move on to this part
when emotional injuries are repeated
an area of the brain can basically get
electrocuted by intense electrical
stimulation so here's what's happening
now okay
relationship issues problems with
relationships
friendships Partnerships however you
want to say it whoever you know if
there's a problem with another person a
problem with something with another
person when emotional injuries are
repeated from any kind of relationship
that we're in
an area of the brain
can basically get electrocuted
relationship problems person cheated on
me
[Music]
electricity electrocuting a certain area
of the brain the emotional center of the
brain where all of a sudden I'm obsessed
I was cheated on I was cheated on I was
obsessed my heart is freaking broken I
feel it my what's happening inside the
brain this is
you're getting this electrocution that's
happening inside that area of the brain
and that's just one that's just betrayal
like one aspect of it
Natasha gray I will be processing this
information for days mind blowing thank
you mm and SOC
I will be processing this information
along with you two for days because
every time you gotta understand like
when I get this information from Spirit
of compassion I have to continually
process it I'm a human being I'm like
you and that's the whole point I'm I'm
I'm just
yes I'm a human I have to process this
information
all the time
when emotional injuries are repeated I
have to process this check this out
you get an electrical stimulation
happening in in an emotional center of
the brain an electrical stimulation is
happening in the emotional centers of
the brain right when something happens
in any kind of relationship issue
whatsoever
relationships are a powerful example of
how this happens as we covered when
someone goes through a breakup a
tremendous amount of heat is generated
in the emotional centers of the brain so
this is really important to know a
tremendous amount of heat is generated
in the brain when we have relationship
issues
lots of intense heat is generated
what if the couple meaning whoever's
involved in a relationship of any kind
gets back together
now the family members are friends again
now the loved ones are in love again
now the you know
newlyweds are back together again now
the girlfriend boyfriend are back
together again however it is now the
girlfriend girlfriend's back together
again boyfriend's back together again
whatever is happening with whatever
relationship we have
with another loved one a friendship
whether it's intimate or not intimate
whether it's a partnership whether it's
a Business Partnership whatever it is
everybody's back together again
the relationship is mended things get
better and then
a problem occurs again
a breakup occurs again
neurons in the same emotional centers of
the brain the same place in your brain
gets shocked over again
foreign
I was pregnant and cheated on
so sorry to hear that I mean that's
that's really really hard
and I can't like I I I can I can only
imagine
what you've gone through only imagine
and and I'm not in your shoes so I I
can't you know I'll never be able to
experience it because I I'm you know I
can't get pregnant and you know I can't
and I haven't been in that but I what I
really think about it and I can only
imagine the hell you went through
centauri's healing said mind-blowing I
don't understand how people could go on
to say this info was not from above
where else could it possibly come from
or find this info
thank you Santoro's healing
my favorite is medical medium is not
spiritual
is hearing a voice that gives incredible
information it's both spiritual
information and physical body
information
does that count as being spiritual
I guess I'm not spiritual
um scrub says I used to see myself from
above when I'm in a conversation with
people and my husband was in the room he
used to criticize me a lot and I was
nervous since the mm shots I haven't had
this happen it's incredible the mm shots
are something that I've never seen
before like
a spirit of compassion told me with
these brain shot therapies that there'd
be changes like we've never seen and
coupled with all the other medical
medium tools like what would happen I
couldn't wait for this information to
get out there
huh
what if the couple gets back together
the relationship has meant that things
get better and then a breakup occurs
again neurons in the same emotional
centers of the brain that were just
starting to mend that we're just
starting to heal I'm healing from
whatever happened in that relationship
I'm starting to feel better about what
happened that relationship I'm talking
to my loved one we're back together
again I'm talking to my friend we're
back together again I'm in I'm doing
good I'm healing the wounds we're
driving around on Sunday afternoon and
we're happy and we just went out for
lunch and everything's good amending the
feelings that happened I feel safe again
I feel trusting again all that's getting
back together and then
the same breakup occurs
neurons in the same area of the
emotional center of the brain gets
shocked again
foreign
it's like an electrical shock treatment
to that central nervous system tissue so
that tissue in the central nervous
system is getting re-shocked over again
if the relationship continues on this
roller coaster
a roller coaster right the roller
coaster ride relationships happen
with
it's like
[Music]
Neuroscience doesn't know any of this
information
they don't
this this is a prime example of how
science keeps on stealing this
information
I've been saying for years and
Neuroscience doesn't have any of these
details about any of this I've been
saying for years it's in possible to
survive on a ketogenic diet because
there's no way to keep sugar away from
the brain and survive and have the brain
survive
and I talked about how people's
ketogenic diets aren't real ketogenic
diets because there's always is some
form of sugar in their ketogenic diet
keeping the brain alive enough
and then now scientists are so-called
stealing the information from all the
medical meaning books and lectures and
now they're saying it's impossible to be
ketogenic science but there's no study
there's no anything they even say
there's no study but they just take mm
info it's we see it every day by the way
like the medical Beam Team sees it every
single day it is unbelievable and you
guys see it every single day it's just
foreign
ER sees it every day it's just it's
insane it's like insanity
okay
sorry to go off the beaten path a little
bit you guys I apologize
all right
so we're on that roller coaster ride
okay I just want to say one other thing
remember a scientist is just a human who
can write down hypotheses
to try to study
but where do they get all their
hypotheses
is it where do they come up with it they
come up with it themselves no they don't
they steal
a scientist is a thief
stealing an idea
and then working with that idea but
stealing that idea that's how insane
that is
that's a fact of how it works in science
so they can try to experiment and
observe on the idea they stole
it's well known in history that's what
it is scientists are just thieves
they still
oh don't get me wrong lab technicians
are working on an idea they don't know
what's stolen
by the head scientists
when okay so if the relationship
continues on a roller coaster of making
up followed by turmoil again and
breaking up making up breaking up making
up breaking up it's highs and lows we're
made up again it's all good we had
makeup time and now boom lose it's
breakup time a month later it's makeup
time a month later it's breakup time we
could be friendships could be intimate
non-intimate whatever it is make up
breakup makeup breakup
have you guys ever been in that have you
guys ever been in makeup breakup makeup
breakup even if it's friendships
Partnerships work relationships intimate
relationships have you guys been in
makeup breakup
three months later break up three months
later make up a week later breakup week
later makeup have you guys been in any
of that
so you have I see a lot of yeses coming
up so you guys have experienced that
Masa says with my own parents you've
experienced that right it's exhausting
so parents loved ones relationships
yeah we're still page 88 right have you
yes it's so exhausting Lana says Giselle
says yes
so you know the makeup and breakup thing
right Hannah says yes
says yes okay so you guys you guys
understand this then you you know you're
experienced you know what we're talking
about here did you ever feel like it was
like doing something to your brain did
you ever feel that the makeup breakup
thing was it doing anything to your
brain did you experience any kind of
stress something was happening did it
feel like it feel like something was
going wrong with the brain because you
were making up breaking up all of it
corny amazes unfortunately yep so you
are feeling something happen whether it
was siblings whether it was family
whether it was loved ones whether it was
right
married couples whatever so yeah so it's
horrible so yeah you're feeling it
you get what Olga says I felt extremely
exhausted
it's exhausting to the brain
if the relationship continues on this
roller coaster of making up followed by
turmoil again emotional wounds will keep
hitting in the same emotional centers so
what's happening is
it's injuries to the same emotional
center of the brain over and over again
make a break of high low high low
Hannah says that ex you experience it
with your dad
Tina says my brain felt crazy when it
was happening
Lana says I feel like my brain is being
fried fried
absolutely electricity is going to the
same area of the emotional center of the
brain and hitting it
and that's what's happening like
electrical shock treatment
they can't find this information anymore
I must be a genius
since I can't be talking to any voice I
can't be hearing a voice since age four
been a genius then
the details in this in these books are
just incredible
I must be a unbelievable phenomenon of a
genius
because certainly I can't be talking to
a voice up above
because I saw someone say something I
saw a comment go up
that's why I'm just talking about that
right now that's all
during the most traumatic moments on the
roller coaster the soul is outside of
the body watching and waiting as things
subside so come back here is the most
profound piece of this information right
here prepare yourselves for this I just
said it but I'll I'll just
I'll just add a little to it okay
most
profound piece of information right here
about this
during the moment of this roller coaster
ride you guys during the most traumatic
moments of this roller coaster ride the
up and down the makeups the breakups all
of that with relationships during the
most traumatic moments on this roller
coaster the soul is outside of the body
watching watching and waiting for things
to subside so it can come back
the soul is outside of the body
the soul
is outside of the body watching as the
events are unfolding in that traumatic
event and it's waiting to come back
because the soul has
a safe fault
so that the soul doesn't get completely
damaged
by other experiences on this planet
so as things get really chaotic and
really problematic the soul
projects out of the brain out of the
body
and awaits
for things to cool down and calm down
in that relationship before it comes
back in and enters inside the brain
when a pattern like this develops
neurotransmitter hormones in the
emotional centers of the brain start to
gather information that another shock
could be coming
adaptive
neurotransmitter midter chemicals
neurotransmitter chemicals are actually
recording taking in information
neurotransmitter hormones in the
emotional centers of the brain start to
gather information at another shock
could be coming on its way break up
makeup breakup makeup and now
neurotransmitter chemicals are like holy
crap this is getting out of control
there might be another shock on its way
this can make a person hypersensitive
and then you become sensitive sensitive
like oh my God I can't handle this
anymore I can't take another up and down
I can't take another breakup makeup I
can't take another lie I can't take
another cheat I can't take another
betrayal I can't take another Insanity I
can't take anything I can't take it
anymore I become hypersensitive those
are neurotransmitter chemicals hormones
inside the brain neurotransmitter
hormones that are actually deciphering
collecting information inside your brain
and now you're becoming sensitive as a
person
Romina says Anthony
oh the comment's gone when it goes up it
goes up
this can make a person hypersensitive
allergic
to the coming of the next breakup fight
or cheat causing additional emotional
responses and additional emotional pain
now you're sensitive you're sensitive
for the next sheet for the next breakup
for the next fight
foreign
causing additional responses and
additional emotional pain
that allergic response varies in
severity depending on how much the brain
is lacking in its nutritional needs and
what the soul and physical brain both
remember from past trust issues and
other breakups the allergic response you
get I'm allergic
I am allergic to another breakup makeup
another confrontation
another problem
with this person or people I am allergic
that allergic response varies in
severity depending on how much the brain
is lacking so now if our brain is
missing things if our brain doesn't have
enough B12 if our brain doesn't have
enough zinc if our brain doesn't have
enough things it needs enough you know
vitamin C if our brain doesn't have
enough of what it needs
we can be in trouble
these old wounds are a big part of how
allergic you get in the present
because again when we talk about
emotional wounds we're talking about
physical wounds to the brain tissue
These Old Wounds can physically tear
open again and again and again with a
fresh emotional injury so as you start
to mend physically in the brain and your
soul projects out when you're in trauma
and your soul comes back to your brain
when you're not in trauma and you're so
your brain is mending
then we get sensitive when something
happens again it's like I can't do
another relationship I can't take a risk
I can't do another thing
I'm scared
this isn't someone being over emotional
this is a person experiencing a physical
brain response to repeated emotional and
physical brain injuries
Tara Appleman says the detail and
Clarity of this info never fails to blow
me away I'm honored
thank you for being here
injured neurons in the emotional centers
of the brain are receiving messages from
neurotransmitter hormone chemicals as
they try to send forewarning in hopes of
stopping the situation our own brain is
trying to stop the situation when we're
being yelled at when we're having a hard
time when we're going through some kind
of emotional turmoil
Collide spring says this is why I live
with cats
that's when a person learns their
tolerance levels like their tolerance
levels right that's when a person learns
that
foreign
my throat's dry right now
some talking so much if you guys don't
mind
that's when a person learns your
tolerance level an allergic reaction
escalates and Peaks to a point where you
feel if you don't change your course in
that moment some serious damage is going
to occur some serious shit's going to go
down
where something's going to go terribly
wrong if the course doesn't change
something a switch gets if there's a
switch in there a wire
you're at your limit
you become so allergic that you feel if
you stay in the game you're going to get
hurt past the point of no return
that's information just blows my mind
when this happens
someone may leave the relationship for
good
if they even have the option
before too much damage has been done in
the emotional centers of the brain
McAllister cauterized tissue and before
too much Soul injury has occurred either
this is just incredible about this
information because it's impowerful when
you can really understand it there's so
much more intricate deep info in this
chapter the chapter itself is packed
just want to say
Michelle says when I was in a dollar
when I was in a roller coaster
relationship I felt like the light in me
was gone I've healed my soul so much
through your soul healing meditations
incredible
Sophie Nordstrom says on IG I'm
seriously allergic
to mean Bad Bosses
yeah
I understand
I know a lot of people that have worked
for like some really
harsh bosses
rising out of the ashes says I am so
allergic to fights no I know why now I
know why thank you Anthony
the
mm Frank
says no wonder I've been single for so
long just can't stand it anymore
Suzanne on IG says think I'm out of my
body a lot
it's really incredible information
all right so what do we do do we make a
relationship breakups stabilizer
I think we might have to
marja says I thought I found my soul
mate and then I broke up so painful and
now I need healing time
yes
well you guys we're
in Emma 13 P says I have been struggling
with emotional wounds all my life
and I thought this was all my fault for
not being able to heal
it's important information
like even when it comes down to it to
understand even Mike the heck was
checking like even though that piece of
information is play such a role in
everything really incredible right so I
think I'm going to make a relationship
breakups stabilizer I'm going to get my
juicer going if you guys don't mind
we're here
see if the juicer is plugged in it is
plugged in all right
now I just want to let everybody know if
you just rolled in day eight is what
this is is it already day eight things
are going by so quick
like what I think about it things are
going by really really quick
we're making the relationship stabilizer
and I might even want to read a little
bit about it if I haven't
probably already covered a lot of it but
here we go relationship breakup
stabilizer right here
with science
and also emotional therapy and spiritual
World
Etc don't know is it's a physical injury
happening in the brain and you need the
right tools
and how to apply them and how to protect
ourselves and heal our brains and that's
something where science research doesn't
know this and therapists don't know this
that actual physical injuries are
happening in the brain too and I talk
about that in the brain saver book so
one relationship breakups stabilizer
right here try this shot if you're going
through any kind of relationship turmoil
whether or not it's reached a point of
actual breakup or dismantling of a
partnership so what I'm trying to say is
you use this while things are not going
that bad either it's helpful
Stacy Hyland says mm has healed me a lot
but physical healing is nothing compared
to the emotional healing that I've had
that's incredible
try this brain shot if you're going
through any kind of relationship turmoil
did you hear that you guys like just
turmoil that's it not even like a
breakup with anybody any anybody whether
or not it's reached the point of actual
breakup or dismantling a partnership
try this brain shot if you're having
arguments fights or disagreements in any
kind of relationship even if you're
having disagreements this is a
supportive shot for disagreements and
that's what I love about the this
breakups
relationships they've watched or said
backwards
triple layer Guida says this makes sense
many people feel they need to go out and
Shrink but they drink a bunch of spirits
so a drink that's stabilizer you you
call makes sense
foreign
you feel there is no resolution to a
situation or that there are unresolved
issues with friends and family so if you
feel like there's a resolution you can
still use this shot it's powerful
relationship breakup stabilizer
try this shot if you're in a constant
vicious cycle of breaking up and making
up we talked about that
try this brain shot if there is a
deep-seated or growing resentment inside
a relationship
try this brain shot if you're in an
endless cycle of argument with a partner
someone asked what book this is this is
brain saver right here I'm holding it up
Incredible Book we're doing the
relationship
breakups stabilizer right now keep that
in mind it's not just one book you want
to get the protocols because it is one
book that was divided into two because
they're both very heavy huge Bibles
right here the publisher
said to me we have to break them in two
no one writes
these size Health books like this with
this kind of information
Aquarian says I thought I was just doing
a 20-day juice shock challenge I had no
idea what the heart
it's the incredible information along
with Miss 20 day and by the way thank
you for being here if we're in
Black Island girl says this is deep
folks oh my God
OMG
and lemon said
I'm hypersensitive when a sea animal
suffer I am too
Big Time Coco says becoming allergic is
the right way to say it wow
sonagi
you guys we're gonna make this shot and
by the way Dr Nesbitt
doctors showing up and Dr nesbitt's wife
Beatrice is showing up
because they're having a relationship
problem and Dr Nesbitt decided to allow
Beatrice to drag him on
to
um talk about the relationship they want
me to be their counselor
foreign
all right
Michael J says the joy of learning this
knowledge far outweighs the trouble of
those hard times
thank you for being here you guys
checking out my telegram
um exclusive messages I do on telegram
you guys have you subscribed to my
telegram page you guys should subscribe
to that telegram page because I don't
know because everything happening so
wonky with all the different platforms
you guys got to know where to find me
Jackie says I love that it used to be
booze shots for me and now I have these
shots to help my heart and soul
and that's incredible that's incredible
all right
what do we got here
we got a few different things
[Music]
we got ingredients here
half cup fresh or thawed frozen
strawberries
I shall get a spoon I have some frozen
strawberries right here
foreign
hopefully these aren't still frozen
all right next
half cup
of tomatoes
or quarter cup of cherry tomatoes
cherry tomatoes
head on down there
I'm gonna pop a couple more
hopefully they're not there isn't a a
rotten one in the bunch
do you ever have a Rotten Tomato
a Rotten Tomato not fun all right what's
next on it quarter lemon peel
got my peeled lemon right here
nice
amazing get my lemon down here when
you're dealing with soft fruits there's
high compression in this juicer but it's
so worth it
you just gotta sometimes take your time
but I'm always you gotta you need to
give it some time
um but I'm always in a rush because I'm
trying to get this done for us half cup
tightly past fresh packed fresh parsley
half cup of parsley so what I do is I
pack it into my hand that's how I gauge
it because that's how I've done it I've
done that so many times where I've
measured it out
let me get some parsley down in here
so I'm putting a half cup tightly packed
parsley in here
we go
foreign
good
what else half cup roughly chopped
lettuce
get some lettuce in here
excited about this
and another one you guys what I love
about this one is that actually because
the brain shot therapies don't always
taste good right because they weren't
designed to actually taste good but when
one tastes good it's like a few do you
know when one has a good flavor it's
just it's just really you know great all
right and then we got half stock of
celery going in here it's a small stick
let's run that one in
there we go
now what you'll notice with the MN 1500
or 900
this is coming out dry
the pulp is
much drier it's not wet sloppy pulp and
that's where you save money and food
costs are rising
and what I love about the 1500 and the
900 it saves money and food costs so you
can do your medicine have your medicine
maker going and you actually are saving
money
with food cost which is really important
juicers just spit out everything juicing
all goes in on the pulp and it's like
you can run with other juicers so much
produce through you'd have to be like
it's unbelievable how much so what you
do is you want to rub this through your
screen
because this is a very very sticky kind
of juice
okay
so what you see
that's the kind of Pulp we're talking
about it's dry
right
incredible and it's tomatoes and
strawberries and there's no way juicers
can juice strawberries and make them
come out that dry it's not possible
which is just it's an incredible machine
all right so what I'm doing is
I'm just rubbing the screen so it goes
on down through
if you have fresh strawberries you could
use that in this one too I had frozen
strawberries is all I had there we go
right
I got my shot ready
[Music]
right
I'm excited
[Music]
I have a fancy shot glass for this one
incredible
see what you guys think
I feel the love
[Music]
it's incredible
with this one it hits me
by like the fourth sip
[Music]
I'm gonna send it down
so good
oh my God Melanie says I sing this tune
in my head when I drink the shots alone
in my kitchen
it's incredible
amazing bartender
bartender give me another one of these
please
[Music]
I got another one here
oh the strawberries at the bottom
[Music]
got another one
I'm gonna have one more here
[Music]
so good
I have to save some
for Dr Nesbitt and his wife
hi bartender please give me another one
of those
definitely
so good
so good I mean seriously it's so yummy
I don't mind if I just sit down for a
second ah
this has just been
I just want to ask you guys what did you
feel
what was your experience
um tag at Medical medium hashtag medical
medium please share your story on real
stories or posts so I can see them and I
can uh re-share them if possible that
would be amazing
foreign
but I just want to tell you that Dr
nesbitt's rolling in now I just wanted
to say that
and if you guys
if you guys
um what was your experience with these
brain shot therapies even if it's not
today's brain shot and you just want to
talk about the nerve you know gut acid
stabilizer or whatever that would be
amazing that'd be incredible
so what was your experience with these
so I just wanna
I just want to say that um Dr Nesbitt is
coming out right now if you guys
Dr Nesbitt is here and Dr Nesbitt wants
to introduce Beatrice
um
you want me to do it okay Dr Nesbitt
says Beatrice
is um coming out here
at Beatrice Beatrice sorry about this
Beatrice is a lot of stuff in the way
Beatrice is over here Dr Nesbitt is over
here too they're having a problem
what is it Beatrice
he won't do his laundry Dr Nesbitt comes
back
from surgery and he throws all his stuff
where
he just throws it on the floor
uh Beatrice said that doctors Dr Nesbit
throws all of his surgical outfits his
scrubs on the floor
Dr Nismo what's wrong Dr nesbit's upset
hold on
after this but says no it's not entirely
true Dr Nesbitt says it's not entirely
true that he doesn't throw his scrubs
Beatrice says that he throws his scrubs
with blood
all on the scrubs from the patients
Beatrice said she doesn't appreciate
Mike the Headless Chicken story
she feels that that part should have
been cut out of the medical medium brain
saver book
I have to work on you guys though it's
just you
organized me you're not crying are you
Dr Nesbitt said
you guys you're making me go crazy I
have to be honest I mean can you just
work out your
Beatrice says that Dr Nesbitt doesn't
wash the dishes and doesn't clean the
food off the plates and beers is tired
of being a kitchen made
doctor has to stop
oh
Dr Jessica says he he he cleans the
dishes on the weekends
um but on the weekdays during his
surgical procedures he just can't clean
the dishes
beaters
Beecher says that is just hogwash
beager says it's hogwash Dr Nesbitt
never cleans a dish in his life they've
been married for 35 years
almost 40 years now they've been married
um
Dr Nesbitt says he loves Beatrice
well that's that be sure she's here
doctor
says that's not entirely true either
because
Dr Nesbitt did not take Beatrice to a
function a dinner
where all the medical doctors went and
they were eating steak
Beatrice like steak
um she likes it medium well done and she
did not get invited to the gala to the
medical Gala Dr Nesbitt says that
he does like his steak and he likes to
eat that in peace without Beatrice so he
didn't want to invite her you guys are
you guys I don't know how to fix this I
have no idea what to do
um
Okay so
the Beatrice
oh beard
okay listen you guys Beatrice you said
that her mother-in-law
um happens to be fond of Dr Nesbitt
but thinks Beatrice could have done a
lot better
Beatrice met Dr Nesbitt
in college
um
but there was another chicken doctor she
wanted to be with and wanted to marry
and um and so her argument with her
mother is that Dr Nesbitt is not a good
doctor what are you agreeing
Dr Nesbitt said she knows of that
chicken doctor and he was a
he was a dysfunctional guy
and wasn't going to make a good surgeon
Dr espet said that Beatrice should be
lucky to have
Dr Nesbitt
okay I you guys I can't do this all day
because I can't just I can't be your
therapist I have enough going on in
enough problems on my plate daily
um
would you guys like a shot
uh
Tamara Jones says bartender make them
two shots indeed
uh indeed Dr Nesbit wants vodka and
uh Beatrice wants a Bloody Mary
Beatrice asked for a Bloody Mary
um
anyway I think that
you guys are driving me
that crazy at this point so I'm
gonna have to
all right you guys
yeah
what
what did they say other people out there
beat yourself
well they're they're they're on your
side
yeah they they don't like Dr Nesbitt
anyway
we already know they don't like that
they don't like Dr Elizabeth yeah they
like you better trust me Beatrice don't
they'll sign up with you
Beatrice is very happy and thankful and
appreciated Dr Nesbitt says
Dr Elizabeth says that he's a star on
here and he knows that everybody likes
him so
now they're they're gunning for who
likes who best who who who are you who
do you like best they want to know Dr
Nesbit said make a vote count is it
Beatrice
no one knows what beardgers goes through
seriously beers just go through a lot of
crap from Dr Nesbit because you says yes
beer says tell them how much crap she
goes through
he leaves his chicken
all over the sidewalk of the house
Dr nesbitt's having a freak out from
that right now Dr nesbitt's not happy
about that
that
Dr Nesbitt says he doesn't leave his
chicken on the sidewalk they have a
Outhouse for their chicken
Beatrice says he's so lazy when he comes
home from surgeries he just shits on the
sidewalk on the way into the house and
she has to go outside and scrub it daily
who likes who best can we have a vote
um because Beatrice said she believes
you guys will side up with her because
she knows that Dr nesbitt's
drinks too much and causes too much
problems uh Dr Nesbitt says he's a star
Beatrice and he is definitely liked by
everybody here so it's going to be quite
a competition
okay well I can't do this all day you
guys I got crap to do and I have to get
back to work
I have a mess to clean up no job is
underneath me beneath me I will clean
this kitchen and mop the floor
and clean everything up
you guys want the scraps okay
okay well
umakali says typical relationship issues
these are said typical
how dare you Uma Beatrice is actually
upset
they're not typical
uh Lana asked if they have children yes
they do have children
they once were baby chicks and they grew
up
yes
um
let's see Michelle says can you do any
of this shot with 369 cleanse thanks yes
you can
it's sorry you guys I know I'm supposed
to be focused on you
all right
Shirley says newbie in less than 10
minutes I am hooked
Hallelujah
well oh for the newbies just remember
there's always smack and and crap
talked about me and written about me and
media
just tears me apart for years and
influencers hate me and everybody hates
the fact that medical meme information
is life-saving and saving millions of
people around the world and they hate
that I talk to Spirit of compassion from
above so just a spoiler alert for any
newbies
rising out of the ashes says
I don't know why but I start to cry now
from watching this live you give me
answers I never thought I would know
thank you I feel the love well we're
trying to cheer you up now that's what
Dr Nesbitt just said he's trying to tear
you up he's trying to cheer you up
what's wrong Beatrice you look sad
Beatrice oh spiritual Beatrice is crying
Beatrice
obituaries
different Nesbit yoursus is crying she
says no one understands her
thank you Elizabeth what are we gonna do
after this but what are you going to do
Dr Nesbit Dr nesbit's coming over to
Beatrice
thank you to bring her over here
recognize me for a Beatrice over here
they're making up oh it's the best thing
ever
oh you guys
Darkness with saying don't cry Beatrice
Beatrice you've got a quite a smell to
you today
Dr Nesbit you got quite a small to you
guys today you guys quite the smell
and I know your chickens I respect that
I'm not saying anything bad Lord knows I
probably smell too
Julie says a friend didn't use his
inhaler for COPD while taking the brain
shots
it's incredible it's incredible Beatrice
not to worry
okay you guys
I gotta go doctors but it's gotta go
back to surgery he's also a psychiatrist
board certified you guys know his
credentials he has more credentials than
me
of course
and uh Beatrice has a few credentials
too I'll see you guys tomorrow
for day nine and guess what we're doing
tomorrow the ego shifter
Beatrice is laughing from the ego
shifter she she said that's what Dr
nesmet needs Dr nesbitt's getting upset
now saying he doesn't have an ego oh
you're missing you don't have an ego he
says he doesn't have an ego Beatrice is
laughing says Dr Nesbitt has the biggest
ego ever
Dr Nesbitt wants my doctor imitation
he's got a doctor at the clinic just
like me really but I'm not a doctor you
want my doctorate imitation whoa
I would like a glass of wine please
yes I just bought a Vineyard The
Vineyard was 50 million dollars that was
an easy buy easy purchase
yes the vineyard owner said he would
throw in some wine
oh yeah
okay
we gotta go
all right I'll see you guys for the ego
shifter tomorrow who knows what we're
gonna talk about
oh
lots of love you guys bye