charged at all after they have a night
of sleep how many people only sleep like
three hours or five hours or four hours
yes yes yes oh my God you guys really so
many people struggling with sleep issues
well today we're doing sleep and
recharging stabilizer which I'm really
excited about by the way this is
incredible sleep and recharging
stabilizer yes indeed we're going to
talk about sleeping issues a little bit
what happens inside the brain when
that's happening too which is really
cool
and we're gonna have some fun with it
all I got my ingredients in front of us
we're day 19 believe it or not I can't
even believe it I don't know like
I woke up this morning I'm like what day
19. is that even possible like we made
it this far
how many of you guys have gone 19 days
here and it's okay if you only went
eight days it's okay if you only want
nine days so maybe if you only won 11
days or 12 days or two days that's okay
too maybe you just started this brain
shot therapy corn challenge two days ago
right
now how many of you guys
started like at the beginning and were
day 19. is it just me is it only me okay
am I the only one that started it and
I'm doing it and it's day 19.
anyway all fun questions but I will say
I will say
all kidding around aside
all fooling around aside you did Lisa
Loft House says I did them all oh my God
incredible me Sophie Nordstrom said me
Lana says this challenge has been
incredibly healing we did the whole
thing my God tomorrow's day 20 day 20
tomorrow you guys are pumping me up big
time
Tina Beeb says I've done all the days ah
amazing
incredible incredible so pumped about
this seriously Sonia or it says yes all
days
uh amazing jessalyn thank you for doing
these lives Anthony Caroline 17 days
whoa
Melanie uh 19 days okay okay all right
like seriously like I don't know how
animated it can possibly like what
that's incredible
on IG clean up your diet tag says I
could only do nine days totally cool
nine days is amazing
amazing five days is amazing four days
is amazing all right so please know that
because all of that is incredibly
amazing
Grace now
I really am
we're talking about like what happens
inside the brain a little bit when we're
having sleeping problems
okay Natalia says you make me excited
for com completion right 19 days so you
got 19 days I didn't look at it as my
accomplishment all right oh my God are
you kidding if you did 19 days that was
a huge accomplishment that was huge
are you kidding
19 days of brain shots it's it's
incredible
and five days four days is incredible
I'm talking like this right now for the
moment because we have to think about it
and sit back and realize how far we've
come and what this means and how
exciting this is and how special it is
you actually got these incredible
Healing Foods in your body
leafy greens herbs wild Foods all of it
in your body fruits every single day 19
days powerful combinations that were for
the right problems in the body like this
is incredible
I don't even know what to say
let's see keep the Hope says 10 days and
counting and couldn't get ingredients
but I do double pathogen exposure every
day oh my God perfect you can do the
same one you can do literally the nerve
gut stabilizer acid stabilizer every
single day if you wanted to for your 19
days your five days whatever whatever
you want to do you don't have to do the
chosen ones
The Chosen days of the brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge you don't have
to do that then
it's what you want and that's totally
awesome there's nothing wrong with that
that's the powerful aspect of medical
medium information it's not one size
fits all that's how incredible it is you
can choose the shot you want to use how
about that and do it all 19 days
you can do that because that's what if
that feels right to you too if you're
like no man I got this stomach acid
thing and the nerves nerve gut
stabilizer acid stabilizers is helping
me then yes do it the whole time
how incredible is that
The Challenge videos are up on
medicalmedium.com and it's a free and
you can get the free download and emails
make sure you sign up it's really
important so you can but it's going to
be on the website so you can watch them
all again the 20-day challenge will be
on the website so you can do it over and
over if you choose to you can do one day
you can do three days you could do all
of it anytime you want
yes Kelly Burke says this one tastes
amazing
all right here we are
we are
here
all right insomnia let's do this day 19.
trouble sleeping can sometimes be as
simple as a racing mind do you guys get
racing mind at all does that happen to
you
like you're in bed you want to sleep
you wish you can sleep
but you
can't sleep because your mind is racing
right and there's different forms of
Mind racing that's what's really
incredible right your mind is racing
it's what's happening you want to sleep
but this is happening right here
your mind just going
[Music]
does that happen to you guys
and you you really do want to sleep
that's the sad part about it or the hard
part about it is
you need to sleep you say to yourself
but your mind is just racing Erica Malek
says I take this shot every night before
bed for the last three months and I
sleep soundly without waking up
incredible the shot is so amazing
and let's see it's helped me it's helped
with my insomnia so much thank you aw
SOC incredible
trouble sleeping can sometimes be as
simple as a racing mind that's trying to
solve a problem are you trying to solve
a problem and your mind takes over do
you fall asleep for a little while and
then you wake up a couple hours later
and now you're trying to solve a problem
and your mind is just going right
laughs
it could even be stress creating the
mind to race right you're under stress
it's triggering the mind to race because
think about that your mind is racing
because it's being triggered stressed
you're trying to solve a problem
or just plain old worry in your life
plain old worry
we don't need to stress ourselves out
over a bad night or two
right a lot of you guys are like I had
more than a bad night or two bad nights
when sleeping problems become chronic
that's when there's more going on yes
neurotransmitter chemicals
are the one critical part of being able
to sleep
neurotransmitter chemicals
what I love about what you're looking in
front of you right here okay this
stabilizer that we're going to do the
sleep and recharging stabilizer
is it benefits you in the neuro
transmitter activity area that's where
it benefits it's targeting that
that's when there's more going on
neurotransmitter chemicals are the one
critical part of being able to sleep
electricity is running through every
neuron as we're sleeping
so I think what people really don't
realize is when they go to sleep
their neurons are just as active in many
ways
so as we're sleeping electricity is
still going through all the neurons
if neurotransmitters are diminished
here's what's interesting
if your neurotransmitters are
diminishing weakened kind of broken down
anemic not anemic
not anemic like claridin of whatever
iron all that stuff no anemic just being
very low
I'm on page 354 someone just asked
of brain saver
if neurotransmitters are diminished
electrical impulses have a tough time
traveling throughout the brain
what that means is your electricity
struggles when your neurotransmitters
are down
low neurotransmitter chemicals or
weakened ones can cause the brain to
have difficulty finding balance so you
can ease into sleep and stay there stay
asleep stay there
so low neurotransmitter chemicals
or weakened ones
can cause the brain to have difficulty
finding balance
that means that when you're having
diminished
neurotransmitter chemicals
your electricity is trying to swim
around it
it's trying to stay charged while you're
sleeping
but it's not staying calm and smooth
instead it's more erratic
it's more Rogue
there's a problem
so you're not able to relax and sleep
you're not able to stay asleep long
memory Stubbs says I have no way to make
them where I currently live but I'm
watching and learning until I can do
them it's incredible you don't have to
make these brain shot therapies you can
just listen to the information and
reading out a brain saver some of these
uh lives that we've done in these 20
days in this 19 days just phenomenal
information that's been mind-blowing and
you don't even have to do the brain
shots you can just chill out hang out
someone may also have a sensitive
nervous system due to a chronic
low-grade viral infection so this is
important to know
a large majority of people's sleep
issues is because someone has a
low-grade viral infection
they don't know it maybe they had an
autoimmune diagnosis but don't know
that's what it is whatever's going on
they're sick with something they're
struggling with something
so someone may have a sensitive nervous
system now why would you have a
sensitive nervous system if you have a
low-grade viral infection
because the Epstein-Barr virus or the
shingles
or any of the herpetic virus especially
I've seen Barn shingles which often goes
undiagnosed
releases neurotoxins
neurotoxins are unfortunately one of the
big problems with people sleeping good
I've seen people
okay
that have the worst chronic fatigue
syndrome the worst me chronic fatigue
syndrome or just severe fatigue and you
would think they sleep
they're not sleeping they're not
sleeping good there are people
that are diagnosed with me CFS
they're diagnosed with chronic fatigue
syndrome
but they're not sleeping good
people can't understand it you're tired
you've got fatigue sleep
just sleep now there are people that get
diagnosed with chronic fatigue syndrome
and they sleep 12 14 hours 16 hours and
they can't do anything but sleep but
that can be just a temporary part of
their chronic fatigue that could be one
year and then another year
they can't sleep and they still have
chronic fatigue syndrome they're tired
they're suffering and they can't sleep
you know anybody that's gone for that
that's me Jan Antonio says that's me
that's a big deal and a lot of people go
through that
lots of people
add add me to Anya's okay
so here you are you're tired you don't
feel good
you got chronic fatigue
or you just feel like your legs feel
like sandbags you can't get ahead of
yourself
you can only do so much kitchen work you
can only do so much you know vacuuming
around your house you get wasted easy
you're on mattress Island
you're fatigued
then someone might say to you hey
why don't you just sleep it off
and you're like
I can't
I go to bed
I can't get eight hours of sleep I can
only get four hours or three hours or
five hours take a long nap I can't take
a long nap I can't fall asleep during
the day but you got chronic fatigue
syndrome you should be able to fall
asleep during the day I can fall asleep
during the day though I'm suffering I
could only take a nap here if I'm lucky
I could only get five hours of sleep one
night some nights I'll get seven hours
and then the next night two hours this
is what people go through you guys
probably know this right so you probably
know somebody that's gone through this
so there's so many people
who get CFS or me CFS meaning they get
the diagnosis they're struggling and
they're tired all the time they have low
grade viral infections and neurotoxins
are getting to their brain and
preventing them from sleeping a peaceful
sleep
their neurotransmitter chemicals are
struggling they have neurotoxins in the
brain and they can't sleep good but then
they get picked on and bullied by people
they know friends they know family
members they know they get bullied
because here you are tired why don't you
just get a good night's sleep and get
fixed
and then one night
if they're not on benzodiazepines
because they got they got in trouble and
they're addicted to benzos to try to
like get through their anxiety and
sleeping and their chronic fatigue
syndrome and then one night they sleep a
really long night's sleep a good night's
sleep
and then everybody says to him well you
slept eight hours that night you should
be back to normal you should be fixed
and it's like no it gave me a little bit
more energy that day it made it so I can
function a little bit but I'm not back
to normal and I'm not better yet I still
have chronic fatigue syndrome yes I
slept one night
but then the next night they only sleep
like two hours or one hour and I know
that there's this isn't everybody but so
many people right Jessica Gail says
always feel like I'm tired of falling
asleep and my body jolts back awake this
makes so much sense wish I could get
some peaceful sleep I know so many
people are going through this
so I'm talking about CFS a little bit
too where people get blamed they have
this chronic chronic fatigue syndrome
and they're getting blamed
why don't you just sleep it off and get
better you're so tired it's like no I
can't sleep and there are people with
CFS their first few years of CFS all
they're doing is sleeping and then they
hit the wall they're not better yet and
they're not sleeping anymore it's like
they slept plenty but they're still sick
and still not functioning and can't
sleep good anymore there's that too
talking about viral issues with any kind
of sleep problems since we're what we're
dealing with now
so someone may also have sensitive
nervous systems due to low-grade viral
infections like shingles and EBD and the
neurotoxins that are released from these
viruses are swimming around their body
attaching themselves to the vagus nerves
yes the vagus nerves
s the vagus nerves
you know and I'll say I'm guilty of
saying vagus nerve many times on and off
that's because people don't they don't
hear you when you say Vegas nerves a lot
they'll be like because everybody will
be like vagus nerve that's nerves
there's two of them I'm saying that
because we did a Vegas nerve show right
where the nerves
there's two of them coming out of the
brain stem and they get all saturated
with neurotoxins and that really stops
people from sleeping too
all right let's keep on going
which page Gabrielle says Gabriella 354.
neurotoxins breaking out of the liver
and traveling through the bloodstream
can reach the brain
where they saturate pollute and diminish
neurotransmitter chemicals that's one of
the key points right there
a lot of people have diminished
neurotransmitter chemicals why
why are they diminished
some people might diminish them because
they're smoking too much weed some
people might diminish them because
they're doing Ayahuasca some people
might dim diminish them because they're
doing too much psilocybin some people
might diminish them because you're not
getting any nutrients at all for their
brain and they're under tremendous
stress it's a huge trigger some people
might have them diminished for other
reasons too some people don't have
enough glucose in their brain and that's
diminishing it
but neurotoxins
breaking out of the liver
and traveling through the bloodstream
can reach the brain where they saturate
and pollute and diminished
neurotransmitter chemicals this is
important neurotoxins from low-grade
viral infections which everybody who's
diagnosed with autoimmune has
they don't know it but that's what they
have
everybody diagnosed with autoimmune at
the doctor's office is struggling with a
low-grade viral infection whether the
doctor knows it because they don't know
medical meme information or they do know
medical meme information because that's
mm info I put that out there all these
years
even if they don't if that they don't
test for it or not test for it they got
a glow grade viral infection and here's
what happens with autoimmune you might
not
see a viral issue in a test but five
years later it shows up because it was
the problem the whole time
hence Kathy says not having the energy
to make the shots
I have been alternating alternating
between the lemon balm and shock therapy
and the California poppy shock therapy
helps my sleep and my restless legs
that's incredible that is incredible I
got the lemon balm here
foreign
but yeah
incredible education educating myself
and doctors think these pains are
autoimmune and genetic unbelievable
so what happens is people have these
low-grade viral infections
there is
protocols in here
medical meme shock Therapies
because that's what we were talking
about a second ago right medical meme
shock therapies and protocols first
sleeping issues and all kinds of other
problems too it's an Incredible Book
Incredible Book you can take the book to
your doctor and ask your doctor what's
right for you
neurotoxins breaking out of the liver
like I said traveling through the
bloodstream
saturate the brain and diminish
neurotransmitter activity
because someone has a low-grade viral
infection and if they have a higher
grade viral infection high grade it can
even be worse and more difficult there
are people out there
that cannot sleep for four straight days
they get hospitalized or they have to
induce a coma
because they can't sleep
and I've always told people I've ever
known and run into anything like this
but you can't see it
like you're not sleeping
you have to see it as you're healing and
resting your central nervous system
whether you sleep or not
if you lay there
know that you're still healing
with your eyes shut and you're laying
there there is something called resting
your nerves
and if I'm not mistaken because these
books are two very large Bibles here and
even I
forget which book has what in it I have
to grab these books and read them over
and over again
I'm not perfect
but I'm not a genius
but the information is profound and
unfreaking believable
IG
Hackberry Tomo says experience this
tired and can't sleep I was punching my
wall and yelling begging to fall asleep
very annoying no more after medical
leave information okay then I have
something to say to you
I want to find resting the nerves in
here
I'm hoping it's here
I think it might be in my other book
yes it is of course
I thought that was protocols for a
second silly me let me just do this
that's what's incredible about these
books
can you keep that straight
it's like 12 pounds
all right
it's in the back of Protocols of course
do you guys know the medical meeting
books better than I do I hope you do
that would be a dream come true to me
to know that you guys be like no aw I
know we're resting the nerves is
resting nurse I want to read this a
little bit this is really important
right here so I'm in protocols right
here
and resting the nerves
this is a very powerful centering
technique that reboots the nervous
system
our brains are all susceptible to
becoming weakened and neurologically
sick
if you can't sleep and you're punching
the wall which guess what I've heard
that before
I've heard people Punch walls I've heard
people punch beds I've heard people
kick things I've heard people hurt
themselves in the middle of the night
because they can't sleep I've heard it
all right
and it breaks my heart because that's
like a hell it I've I've heard people
say it's an unbelievable hell
to not be able to sleep in unbelief
insane unbelievable hell
there's something to know if you can't
sleep if you ever run into a problem you
can't sleep or you're not sleeping the
hours you want to sleep something very
critical to know you can still help to
heal your nervous system
resting the nerves this is a very
powerful centering technique that
reboots the nervous system
our brains are all susceptible to
becoming weakened and neurologically
sick this approach is accessible to all
of us
Spirit of compassion
never never stops to amaze me
this approach is accessible to all of us
when we need to give the brain and
nervous system a quick restorative so we
can be stronger for the day or night
you can try it anywhere in an office
chair lying or sitting on the floor bed
or couch at home
sitting at the kitchen table parked in
your car the options are endless as long
as it's a spot where you'll be safe
closing your eyes
that's part of the power here it's so
easy to do
to get started
you're going to stop whatever else
you're doing and if it's in the middle
of the night that's fine you already are
find a comfortable position
if you have a choice opt for lying down
if not sitting up works
now close your eyes and keep them closed
for eight to twenty minutes now if
you're laying there at night in the
middle of the night you can go way more
than eight to 20 minutes
but just know you can help to rejuvenate
and restore your nervous system even
when you got insomnia and can't sleep
I'm on page 540 of protocols Incredible
Book I mean you've got to get these
books
ideally you'll keep them closed for 12
to 15 minutes
that's the most effective window this is
brain saver protocols
you have less time eight minutes is okay
so I'm talking about if you're in the
middle of the day you can do this so you
can just do eight minutes in the middle
of the day this is so incredible so if
you're not sleeping good at night and
you're wrecked you're wrecked from it
if you're not sleeping at night you're
just feel like you're destroyed from it
you can do this in the middle of the day
regardless of where you are
eight minutes is okay if you have even
less time
don't not do it
even three to four minutes is helpful
any amount of time spent with this
technique when you need a nerve recharge
will serve you
when you close your eyes and sit or lie
back you need to remind yourself why
you're doing it to rest
your nerves
to rest your nerves
so you're doing it at night amazing I
just saw somebody in the comment went up
there in IG you're doing this at night
fantastic
when you close your eyes and sit or lie
back you need to remind yourself why
you're doing it to rest your nerves
don't forget that I have to read that
again because I want to tell myself it's
to rest my nerves
you can't sleep at night you're
suffering
you're about to lose your mind
you're about to lose your freaking mind
I've seen people at that stage it's just
so sad Christina says I feel so
validated
eight explanation points I can't count
it's a lot not sleeping is torture and
this is what made broke the camel's back
for me vicious cycle I wish I would have
found medical medium back then straight
away
so happy now problem is Christina
there's large amounts of people out
there trying to prevent people from
finding medical medium now at this point
there's lots of naysayers and haters
just telling people don't
do medical medium don't whatever
like do you wouldn't believe it the
vegan people are bad because
I support people who eat animal protein
because we're not one size fits all
medical medium you can come here and
still heal
but it's unbelievable really and it's
sad because I know so many people that
aren't finding medical medium easy right
now
is terrible
Seeker for compassion energy shifter did
miracles for me I had it today in the
middle day
and no more tired early night as I had
thank you so much so check this out
about resting your nerves
In This Moment you're going to have
thoughts concerns and even worries
projects you're working on and other
reminders of your busy day are going to
come to mind and if you're suffering
laying in the middle of the night you're
so upset you're going to be thinking
about not being able to sleep either
at least that's how it is for most of us
this technique is not here to punish you
for that it's not a thought punishment
it's not a thought Punisher understand
that
this exercise is not a punishment for
your bad thoughts unproductive thoughts
your swimming thoughts whatever it is
that's what I love about mm info from
Spirit of compassion it's not about
punishing people but when
what I have noticed in a lot of healing
communities out there
it's about punishing people they punish
the crap out of people
you're the blame
it's your body attacking itself your
thoughts are making you sick you're
creating it I've seen it all out there
it's just it's insane
someone was actually left a comment and
they were screaming in the comment you
know how when people but you know how
when people put large capital letters
like non-stop like it's all capital
letters it was something like
how dare you tell me medical medium that
genes aren't why I'm sick it's my genes
and it went across like jeans and then
it went like something like
my jeans are bad
that's what science tells me and I
believe science
it's not any kind of viral infection or
this and this my genes are bad and I was
like dear Lord okay okay okay okay okay
okay
if that's what you want to believe then
your genes are bad you were born with
bad genes you're just a bad Gene
Heather Jenkins says the brain saver
book is so amazing each chapter just
blows my mind and it's really
interesting to read at first I was
intimidated because it was so big
but it moves along quickly I am
intimidated by
these books right here
because
it's it's just unbelievable how big they
are and what's in there Lynn Albers I
don't care what any of those people say
I will always follow medical medium only
thing that works thank you Lynn and you
even survive all the smear campaigns and
hit pieces on me over and over again for
years
you even survive all that
incredible
because I'm such a bad person
and everybody's perfect out there but me
everybody's perfect out there
for me
amazing
all right so when you when you close
your eyes and sit there lie back you
need to remind yourself of doing this to
rest your nerves and check this out
this technique is not here to punish you
for any thoughts
you're not doing it wrong if you have a
reactive racing mind
this is not of meditation but yet it is
but it's not it's not about controlling
your thoughts you can rest your nerves
and give your nerves healing like
healing boosts
which is incredible
the benefits of the exercise override
any thoughts and stresses pounding
through your head you can be laying
there in the middle of night suffering
hating yourself for not sleeping you can
be in the middle of the night suffering
and struggling totally wrecked by it
totally upset by it really going through
a lot
and you can work on healing your nerves
you can strengthen yourself to give you
stronger energy the next day this is an
incredible technique from Spirit of
compassion
the benefits of this exercise
override any thoughts and stresses
pounding through your head
there's something pounding through your
head
this exercise overrides it
that's part of its power
I'm on page 541 the Sesame
asking random protocols
that's part of its power as long as you
know the purpose behind it
the second you shut your eyes and tell
yourself that you're restoring your
nervous system any thoughts and worries
that arise hold no authority over your
restorative experience that I want to
read that again
I want to read that again
umakali
love how simple yet powerful this
meditation is thank you Uma
you're a soldier
mirror Warrior
that's part of its power as long as you
know the purpose behind it if you know
the purpose behind this what's the
purpose behind it restoring and resting
your nerves resting your nerves
the second you shut your eyes and you
tell yourself that you're restoring your
nervous system you shut your eyes
and you tell yourself you're restoring
your nervous system
that's what you have to do
and the minute you do that any thoughts
and worries that arise hold no authority
over the power of this restorative
experience
right when you first close your eyes
remind yourself that the purpose of this
technique is to rest your nerves restore
your nerves and give your nerves some
healing time
your nerves are strengthening every
single second
one of the incredible benefits of this
exercise is that when you do it for the
first time and feel and see the
difference it has made for you that
becomes a landmark that helps you find
peace every time you choose to do to do
this exercise
I gotta like Goosebumps all over my body
right now because I know when someone
who's been through hell like freaking
hell with not being able to sleep and
they got the worst insomnia and they're
really struggling and they're really
suffering and they've tried everything
and they do this in the middle of the
night and they start healing their
nerves they start taking over their life
again they start empowering
their being their soul everything their
body again
Monica you promote life aw the society
promotes fear I do Hunger for your
knowledge thank you Monica on YouTube
it's so powerful that you're going to
remember what it has done for you
when Spirit of compassion wrote that
line
I was freaking out when Spirit of
compassion was putting all this in here
right
and I wrote
it's so powerful that you're going to
remember what it has done for you that's
it Spirit had me right
and I knew then
so many people are going to have
life-changing results from this exercise
along
what page is that on in your book get
healing says it is Page 541 and what
book is it pray tell it's brain saver
protocols
the technique gets even more helpful
every time you do it
it's because your brain learns a routine
and this restorative exercise your brain
learns it you do it more you do it a
second time a third time your brain
remembers
your brain doesn't forget this exercise
it gets more powerful it gets stronger
it helps you fix your problems more and
more
it helps you heal when you can't sleep
it can help you get some sleep it can
change your life
Tom Jensen it had helped me
to be more healthy celery juice morning
cleanse incredible on YouTube IG dizzy
Bliss you allowed me to sleep after
months of going nuts from insomnia if
you have trouble please try melatonin
from Imaging and chamomile and
peppermint and lemon balm tea with raw
honey before bed amazing amazing amazing
November's email atonin is insane
I do take the Bemidji melatonin I do I
do I do
it's incredible
what I find in my personal experience
you guys know I endorse these guys
that it's stronger than the Melatonin I
used to use from other companies meaning
it gives me such more of a better
quality sleep which I love because I
can't shut down my mind because I have a
voice talking to me
so it's not easy
it's nothing easy about that it's a
whole other story someday I will go into
detail about that
it's more than what people could even
imagine actually
I write a little bit about it in the
brain saver books and medical medium
Origins but it's way worse than anything
I've ever said when it comes down to
hearing the voice I hear and you may
think well I don't really believe he
hears a voice then fine I'm a genius I'm
a freaking genius then with all these
books and info all original unique info
I must be genius
but I you know I've endorsed melatonin
primergy you know I've endorsed Bemidji
in all their different products okay
because companies put hidden ingredients
in there companies put hidden
ingredients you're allowed to legally
place a certain percentage
of unidentified hidden ingredients in
the products and not
put it on the bottle that's the rules
the regulations Emoji says no we're not
going to do that we're not going to play
that game no caking agents no bonding
agents know nothing hidden
and that's why they're not only just the
highest quality they do things no one's
ever done and there's a reason it costs
more money for the companies to do those
things and it's smarter and the other
companies I don't see them do either
they're not smarter and they're not
doing these things
which is incredible and it's the highest
quality stuff you can check out the
medical meme directory
or just memory.com
and you know any company I've ever
supported if they start changing their
ways and they're going downhill it's
like see you later whatever
all right
thanks for bringing up the Melatonin
I tell like my friends about it all the
time and everything triple Leo says
laugh out loud my ex used to punch me
when he couldn't sleep
then would pretend he did it in his
sleep
I eventually caught on laugh out loud
that's just like that's I feel really
bad for you to go through that I really
do
so many people are
I mean I can tell you that
when people don't sleep the craziest
stuff can happen it just can't and the
most difficult stuff can happen
for years I've seen people like I said
there's this thing where if you
I don't know if you've ever met somebody
that's gone through this but there are
people and I've seen people throughout
the years that can go two days three
days without sleeping and it's in agony
it's a hell it's a torture where
literally their whole body's rattling
and shaking they're literally pacing
it's three days later they haven't
fallen asleep and when they finally fall
asleep it's like literally a seizure
sleep it's like you go into like a
seizure
foreign
this technique gets even more helpful
every time you do it because your brain
learns the routine of this restorative
exercise we're talking about resting the
nerves if you just got on here and then
I I went on some different directions
it's all kind of related when your eyes
are closed
your neurotransmitters will start
strengthening
did you hear that
if you lay there at night and you close
your eyes and you're just resting your
nerves and you're telling yourself
you're resting your nerves
you're strengthening your
neurotransmitters
your electrical impulses will start
calming down
your neurons will start resting from
less activity even if you're still
thinking about your day or you're angry
about not sleeping
the emotional centers of your brain will
cease to have full control over you when
your central nervous system knows you're
taking care of it and giving it what it
needs right then errant Rogue thoughts
can't interfere with your nerve
strengthening minute by minute this
technique is like a quick charge for the
central nervous system the nutrients
from any Healing Foods you've eaten so
far that day can be used that much more
effectively while you rest your nerves
it's this technique also helps
strengthen the immune system
now it's the time you've set aside for
yourself is coming to an end of this
exercise try to get in touch with the
fact that your brain and nerves have now
strengthened
resonate with this realization that
they're stronger than when you started
and that each time you do this it's more
effective
if you're dealing with any okay this is
an important paragraph coming up right
here really important okay very
important
if you're dealing with any sort of
neurological symptom or illness
including mecfs multiple sclerosis
seizures weakness of the limbs tingles
and numbness dizziness vertigo floaters
in the eyes Tremors aches and pains
ringing in the ears
headaches migraines jaw pain owl neck
pain severe fatigue inability to think
or brain fog
this is one of the most powerful healing
techniques for you
you can use this technique throughout
your day throughout sleepless nights
there it is and even throughout your
healing process
foreign
guys we're gonna work on it let's do it
let's make a shot
let's get rid of the brain here
okay
let's get the juicer over here
I think I'm ready for a
incredible shot
[Music]
got all my stuff
multitask
multitasking I'm hoping Dr Nesbitt shows
up tomorrow it's the 20th day he
promised me he would he said that he
would
but he's got some surgeries
and he's doing some psychiatry
all right so what do we got three
quarter cup
fresh or thawed mango nice
this is frozen mango right here
Frozen mango
sleep and recharging
whoa getting some juice out of that
Frozen mango
you know how much Frozen mango you would
have thrown into one of the other
juicers it'd be insane I only put a
little bit in and it's just it's
squeezing the crap out of it
you guys if you read thyroid healing
I gotta get the book over here sometime
if you read thyroid healing people heal
through their Dreams and Nightmare
section you know it's so really cool
right there
and I've always talked about this before
what happens if you have bad dreams if
you have nightmares you're healing
through that
keep that in mind your healing through
those nightmares and those bad dreams
all right let's go next one
eighth of a cup of tightly packed Dill
get some dill in here
it's about good
next quarter cup of chopped cucumber
can't throw that one right
not without hitting the juicer so I
choked on that one
but I didn't drop it on the floor
quarter cup chopped cucumber
let's send the cube through there
foreign
nice get you moving there you go
next after that half cup roughly chopped
lettuce
and more than that
squeeze into tightly packed
foreign
so you want to get that in there and
then a half of teaspoon of pure maple
syrup and here's what's incredible
and I asked Spirit of compassion about
this recipe the spring shot
why would the maple syrup go in there
is the maple syrup going in there to
make it taste good
if that's the case shouldn't maple syrup
be in every single brain shot therapy
you would think so right if the maple
syrup is there to make it taste good the
shot
and maybe the maple syrup should be in
everything it should be in every single
brain shot there but no
it's very compassion told me the maple
syrup
was to get glucose to the brain and then
I said well okay glucose to the brain
that would be good for everything
shouldn't we just be a maple syrup all
day these are the questions I asked
because it's just you know that I'm the
messenger I got to ask these questions
goes down
it's the trace minerals in the maple
syrup and glucose combined with that
form of glucose which is entirely
different inside the mango combined with
the trace minerals and the lettuce
combined with
phytochemical compounds in the
um Dill combined with what's in the
Cucumber it's that combination in the
amounts that does something to the brain
because these are literally an entirely
different situation this isn't about a
tasty juice shot that's why some of them
just taste so bad
it's really really incredible when you
even think about it
what
music
no way
[Music]
love it
amazing incredible
foreign
right away
[Music]
now I'm getting that the like fuzzy
Sensations everywhere right now
I'm going to read you a little bit more
by the way of mind-blowing sleep
information
I'm going to read a little bit more
don't go away after this
we're just going to send this down to
the number to read
I'm going to read you the sacred sleep
window
hmm and you feel that
can you feel that
that's just incredible it's absolutely
incredible
[Music]
so good
bartender
[Music]
give me 10 more
so good
seriously
I'm getting like this funny funny
Sensation that I haven't had with this
one
I feel like
I'm coming down
and spirit says I didn't even finish
this one right he says you still have to
have a little bit of the maple syrup
mixed in
he says if you don't have maple syrup
the mango might just be enough
but he said you have to have the maple
syrup and then it really kicks in harder
[Music]
foreign
to you why dreams are bad which is
really critical information
my dreams are good I'm telling you I'm
actually I'm actually ready to go to
sleep
I'm afraid of the second shot right now
because I'm actually relaxing so much
[Music]
oh my God I'm ready to go to bed
I'm not just saying that
that just calmed me down like in this
insane way
now it's really kicking in because then
I had a little bit of the maple mixed in
there oh my God
but I had maple syrup this morning so I
had lots of it in my lunch dream
ugh
you guys remember when I do the when I
would do the Amazon lives I feel like
this is crazy how I feel right now
remember when it did the Amazon lives
I feel like all the maple syrup candies
you have the maple syrup candies the
pure ones well I had a bunch of those
this morning
okay
and um so I had a lot of maple syrup
already on my bloodstream but what's
really funny right what's really funny
is then I just added a little bit more
to this shot even though I had it in me
incredible all right
I'm ready just to relax
call it a day
take a nap I'd like to take a nap
why bad dreams are good
night we're healing
dreams are the ultimate mystery
they can't be weighed or measured sorry
science to research I don't care what
diodes you hook up to somebody's head
there's no freaking way you're ever
going to weigh or measure dreams
sorry A Thousand Years Ago by in science
you're not going to be able to weigh and
measure dreams one million years can go
by
and you're still not going to be able to
measure dreams
or weigh them what are dreams telling us
we ask ourselves from the time where
children what do they mean
that brain shot therapy is so freaking
incredible
that like seriously
now I know why you know when you
commented somebody commented earlier now
I know why it's actually helping you
sleep for how how long you've been
sleeping now
foreign
we question the bad dreams what's behind
the nightmares my God you take that
brain shot therapy and you have some
memory melatonin
if you do the brain shot therapy that we
just did just now and you throw in
memory melatonin
yeah it's amazing and then the Bemidji
Gaba
forget it
especially we question the bad dreams
what's behind the nightmares what is
behind the nightmares sorry guys what is
behind the nightmares
the anger dreams do you ever get anger
dreams do you ever get like Angry in
your dreams I wanted to ask you guys
that do you ever get anger like an anger
fit in your dream like you're in the
dream you're dreaming and then you're
angry
you're in your dream and you're upset in
your dream
Infinite Wellness says love the Gaba
amazing
go to Cola says I can actually see a
major shift in your energy after that
shot it I'm not kidding I gotta tell you
something go to cola this is so this is
so messed up
all the shots throughout these 19 days
have given me Sensations and have given
me incredible feelings and everything
else right this sleep and recharge one I
mean I don't even know what to say like
my brain everything about it I just feel
so
I'm floating in a good way it's just
incredible
kind of ready for a nap
ER says never had anger in dreams but
lots of distress okay that's it's good
to know actually
it's good to know because a lot of
people have the stress too so exactly
and frustration on IG celo says yes I've
been having a lot of angry sad dreams
about
about Dad
the stress dreams the sweet dreams the
awakened this night
the sweat dream sorry about that
okay the frustration dreams the stress
streams the sweat dreams the wake in the
night screaming dreams
how many people wake up in the middle of
the night screaming
got a nightmare
how can we make them go away
are they punishment can we have some
more blissed out dreams of tropical
island vacations which could be a
nightmare for some people
some people tropical nightmares
vacations
I mean you hear about it out there like
yeah some people go on a tropical
vacation and something terrible happens
like they could be a nightmare
once you understand what's behind those
bad dreams you won't want them to go
anywhere
I just said basically you don't want to
lose your bad dreams once you understand
what's behind those bad dreams you won't
want them to go anywhere bad dreams are
the Soul's way of healing
bad dreams are the Soul's way of healing
when we're awake we're not supposed to
be Breaking Down the Walls of our
emotional hurt
when we are wounded a physical component
in the brain puts up a barrier to
protect us from constantly processing
and reprocessing the pain so that we can
be productive and move forward during
our waking hours so we're not reliving
all the pain see how it works all the
hardships you had in your life the
struggles you had in your life we're not
supposed to be reliving it every single
minute we won't even be able to be
productive right we won't be able to
push through
so there's walls that are up that are
naturally supposed to be there
they're not walls of denial
they're they're walls of divine
protection
these walls these emotional walls inside
of our brain are emotional walls of
divine protection
so we're not suffering every minute all
day long so all of our hardships the
Betrayal the broken trust all the crap
that's happened in our lives all the
losses all the struggles if we live in
that every single second we won't be
able to do anything
so a lot of that gets tucked away it
gets tucked away the old stuff gets
tucked away there is a natural wall it's
not a wall of denial it's a wall of
divine protection
while some conscious processing is
healthy and necessary it's not meant to
haunt us
we're not
supposed to be haunted constantly about
things we've gone through or we're not
going to be able to function so good
there's a Divine protective wall that's
built inside of our brain it's both
Supernatural and natural
the time to process that pain is in our
sleep by the way
when we're sleeping
that's the time to process our pain
when we're not conscious
that's when we process that pain that's
what's incredible this is blowing my
mind over and over again this is thyroid
healing Spirit of compassions put put
this in here years ago this is
mind-blowing information you won't hear
this anywhere else of course but this
book has been out and millions of copies
have gotten around the world so people
could be talking about it now
and not citing it back to thyroid
healing
they're not walls of denial these walls
are Divine protection they're there
so things in our life and in our past
don't haunt us the time to process that
pain is in our sleep your nightmares
your nighttime nightmares your dreams of
sadness your dreams of frustration your
dreams of betrayal your dreams of broken
trust your dreams when you're sleeping
at night a pain and sorrow and loss are
there
for a reason
their time to process those very things
that you have gone through you guys is
in our sleep
when we're not conscious
the emotional walls come down so the
soul can do its cleanup and repair work
when you're sleeping at night the
emotional Wall comes down it's not
supposed to come down during the day
when you're trying to function and drive
a car and live your life and work or do
whatever you're doing
being creative painting whatever it's
supposed to come down the Walls when
you're sleeping so your soul can do its
clean up and repair work
this means that all sorts of difficult
emotions get stirred up and they work
themselves out through our dreams it's
meant to be worked out through our
dreams
we're supposed to heal emotional injury
through our dreams
if this didn't happen frustration anger
fear betrayal guilt experience any of
that I experienced that every day
you ever experienced any of that stuff
yeah I experienced betrayal every day
it's like my being of my existence or
whatever you want to call it
if this didn't happen frustration I
experienced frustration of course anger
sure fear sure betrayal guilt and
humiliation would build up and build up
and build up within us until they
overpower the strength of the walls
holding them in place that means
if you don't heal frustration anger fear
betrayal guilt and humiliation if you
don't heal
the wounds that are behind things and if
you don't heal those in your sleep then
they can come out during the day
that wall comes down during the day you
don't want that you want the wall to
come down when you're sleeping that is
part of the Divine protection aspect of
our design
Spirit of compassion says
if we didn't do this frustration anger
of fear of betrayal guilt and
humiliation would build up and build up
and build up within us until they
overpower the strength of the walls
holding them in place and took over our
waking lives
it doesn't take over my Waking Life life
even though I get betrayed or whatever
it is or whatever's happening out there
there's so much hate on medical medium
and all that it doesn't take over my
life
because it heals through my dreams
that's where the Wall comes down when
you're sleeping
so
during my waking days
people say I'm a pretty happy guy
you know and so what's funny is because
I'm being productive um getting the
information out on working hard whatever
it is
right I don't let those things take over
and dominate my life
I heal those through my dreams at night
like Spirit of compassion is saying we
all do
instead our dreams release them this
nightly house cleaning aided by the
angel of sleep and if you don't believe
in the Angels if you don't believe in
angels
then maybe it's something else a gnome
maybe it's something else of sleep
maybe you just think God helps us sleep
whatever it is that you believe you
don't believe in angels that's okay
but our dreams released this nightly
house cleaning aided by the angel of
sleep and the angel of Dreams many times
when people take melatonin it allows
them to dream when they weren't able to
dream before and that helps people to
heal their emotions in their sleep
by the way
nightmares are not a bad sign
that's a sign that the brain that your
emotional your soul your state is
healing
this nightly house cleaning aided by the
angel of sleep the angel of dreams and
the unknown Angels helps the unknown
angels
the unknown angels
helps us face what's going on in life
without becoming scared by it
sometimes dreams have staying power
a dream can stick to you all day or even
longer even years
can I just ask you guys something
have you been in a situation where a
dream has stayed with you for years a
dream that you had a long time ago a
dream that you might have had and it has
stayed with you for years
these dreams can be confusing we often
dream of family and other loved ones for
example
with the swirl of emotions
even if everything is going fine in a
waking relationship a dream can bring a
feeling of hurt or
loneliness
and it's okay if you don't remember your
dreams either
that's okay too there's nothing wrong
with that
even if everything is going fine in a
waking relationship a dream can bring a
feeling of hurt or uneasiness
or if it's a relationship where there's
been some challenge or distance dreams
can bring up the Old Wounds making us
contemplate what went wrong years ago to
cause the pain
we may wake from a dream feeling like we
did something wrong you were processing
at night so you don't have to do it in
your Waking Life
even if a relationship where there's
been some challenge or some distance
dreams can bring up Old Wounds making us
contemplate what went wrong years ago to
cause the pain we may wake from a dream
feeling like we did something wrong
or like we weren't heard or perceived
right as we painfully try to decode what
it means we can be left feeling empty
all of this is healthy I've heard from
people who told me that a bad dream made
them pick up the phone and call a family
friend
or a friend or a family member they
hadn't talked to in years that's what
bad dreams can do
Juliet says I have bad dreams almost
every night which makes sense since I
have been through trauma and PTSD it
makes a lot of sense
people have bad dreams about an old
family friend or something and they
contact them and it's amazing about how
this works
see
and dash says I did not dream for over
10 years thank you for changing that
incredible
any empty feeling is because toxic
wounds and emotions left us or started
to leave us that's the empty feeling we
can get to in our sleep reducing our
storage of Bank of hurt
even though we think it's the opposite
bad dreams rejuvenate us even when we
think it's the opposite a bad dream
rejuvenates us how insane is that so
cool
they remind us that there are people
places and things in our lives that may
need some attention so we can move on
bad dreams don't close doors they open
doors
I think I'm gonna quote that you guys
think I'm gonna remember that one okay
I'll make a medical medium quota that
bad dreams don't open doors they try if
I'm going to do the quote can I get the
quote right
bad dreams don't close doors they open
doors
I love doing live shows
to create new beginnings
I should add that to the quote too they
create new beginnings
even if you're not aware of what that
new beginning is it's happening
far down the road you can quote all of
medical medium books right like if you
you can turn quotes into like every line
is always but it's mind-blowing
Spirit of compassion did a fantastic job
even if you're not aware of what that
new beginning is it's happening far down
the roads you may have the perspective
to see what opportunity a bad dream
led to you and your way LED
to your life
we wish each other sweet dreams sweet
dreams
sweet dreams
or if you're a mobster or something
sweet dreams right whatever
it's pretty funny
we wish each other sweet dreams
back then all those years ago I put this
in the books but people say I'm just a
fruit and vegetable guy
and the rest of it I've
they have fruit and vegetables man and
then I got it all wrong
but they got it wrong
man do they got it wrong
we wish each other sweet dreams when
really we should wish each other healing
dreams we're not supposed to say sweet
dreams we're supposed to say healing
dreams
I wish you healing dreams
to advance the soul
men the heart and simply
empty yourself or harmful emotions you
don't want every dream to be perfect and
tranquil and Flowery you don't want your
dream
to be a Wonderland
and only that you want your dreams to
have some hardship in them because you
want the good stuff to be happening when
you're awake you want the bad stuff to
happen when you're asleep if our dream
life if our dream lives were total
fantasy sleeping would be the only thing
we'd ever want to do
now there are Sinister people in the
world that have existed throughout
history I love when Spirit of compassion
does stuff like this
or talked about stuff like this and say
things like this these books are
incredible
now there and this is years ago right we
know how the world's getting even more
Sinister I mean
now there are Sinister people in the
world
they have existed throughout history
these cold-hearted people can go through
life without one nightmare
if you look it doesn't mean you're a
Sinister person just because you never
had a bad dream once in your entire life
but there are Sinister people where they
don't have those bad dreams that's an
indication of how cut off they are from
processing negative experiences like
pain and suffering since they don't deal
with their pain while they sleep they
hold on to it in their waking lives and
they want to inflict that opinion on
others which book page is this lag
on YouTube it's page 260 of thyroid
healing
yes on the flip side you can have the
most compassionate generous loving
person who can't go a night without
dreaming something unpleasant
believe it or not this is the healthier
process
because this person is so tuned in she's
a witness to other struggles she
experiences the range of human suffering
and so when she checks out for the night
her brain needs
to protect her from becoming haunted by
it in her Waking Life
this is just I'm trying to re-digest
this information she may dream of
schoolyard bullies and natural disasters
and War zones
and it's all for her benefit so that
rather than waking up bitter that she
has to leave some Fantastical fantasy
dream and face a harsh World instead she
can wake up or leave to leave those
tough dreams behind and ready to
continue Her Sacred work of compassion
here's one of the last paragraphs right
here this is deep this is deep
I was if there's ever a term to use that
would be the term right now
I love this paragraph right here
let me be clear
that having good dreams does not make
you a bad person
let me be clear that's what Spirit of
compassion said that's what I wrote
of course not
it's all about balance in addition to
those memorable bad dreams we're meant
to have beautiful dreams as well the
Angels sometimes grant us dreams of
transcendence and Hope
sometimes our dreams are premonitions or
messages or creative inspiration
some nights some nights we have mild bad
dreams in which we process emotions
though we're spared from remembering
what happened Come Morning other times
we get to visit with we get a visit with
a deceased loved one in our dreams has
that ever happened to you I just want to
ask you guys that
have you ever had
you were sleeping and you had a dream
and a deceased loved one came into the
dream
foreign
just remember to welcome
the dreams that challenge you
they are doing you a great service as
your body heals during slumber
they are not a punishment or judgment
they are helping you become your best
self
what the afterward is your Soul's gold I
don't know if you guys read that
rising out of the ashes says I love that
you say
she in the books
otherwise it's always he and other books
can I say something about that Rising on
the ashes I got a lot of flack from that
one
from what
they say and I can't I can't be quoted
on this because I don't know if someone
did it before but before medical medium
books it said that no one puts she in
front of he
and the medical medium books were the
first books published where he was at
where he was after she where it was she
in front of he
it's her in front of him
and all the other books I was told
and even my publisher said they said we
think no one's done that before we think
it was always him and her
right he and she
or always he and the medical meme books
were her and him
the first time they think in publishing
history that's what we believe I mean
maybe there was one book somewhere that
was 100 years ago I don't know but I'm
saying that's what we we've learned
Lori's page and that was that was really
cool um Lori says yes I a dream I had
for 10 years about my son who came to me
before I became pregnant with him that's
incredible absolutely incredible
not IG
jacquelina
had a weird one last night a message
from my ex-husband
incredible I love I love talking about
dreams and reading about the dream
information in the medical medium books
there's other dream information
throughout the medical mean books I just
love it
I really do the treasure it treasure it
dearly
you guys I'm still hearing about it
every day cold and flu cold and flu RSV
stomach flu now there's a new stomach
flu out there coming around
there's more sea there's more mutations
of C all of that do you have your cold
and flu tool kit go to medicalbean.com
you can download it for free you'll see
seven herbs and supplements to keep on
hand I always tell my friends and family
don't wait for the flu to hit don't wait
for the cold to hit don't wait for the
seed to hit don't wait and then be like
what do I need what do I need oh I got a
fever what do I need I'm coughing I
can't get what do I need oh I gotta wait
I wait a couple days for it to come in
the mail whatever
check with your doctor and see what's
right for you but I tell friends and
family to have those on hand right there
so it's B12 the zinc the micro C the
cat's claw the propolis pure the olive
leaf right the golden seal by the way
tomorrow is day and this is the imagery
stuff you guys know I endorse them
um because the stuff is mind-blowing you
guys know that tomorrow's day 20
okay and there's more recipes in here
too this isn't just the only part of
this download this download is actually
totally
stocked with info right
day 20 tomorrow
that sleeping recharging shot did
something for me I was ready for a nap
right after I had it like I needed to
take a nap kind of thing where I was
just relaxing like relaxing and then
starting to get recharged so I get over
money for like a whole nother round or
something
this is this is amazing Nicholas Russell
does Nesbit take sleeping pills with a
swallow of bourbon
look I don't want to like talk about
nesbit's medical history
but Dr Nesbit does take various
medications
um Dr Nesbitt has prescribed himself
various medications
he won't go to a colleague doctor at his
own Surgical Clinic he says that
his colleagues doctor colleagues don't
like him on so much medication so he
decided to prescribe all the medication
himself to himself
and I'm not gonna say what they totally
are we'll let Dr Nesbitt tell you
tomorrow Dr Nesbitt will be here
tomorrow he's in surgery right now and
he's going to tell you what medications
he's on yes that's what he's gonna do
it's gonna be good
Rosemary McManus what is the sleep and
recharging shot
or what is in the sleep and recharging
shot oh can you re-watch this please you
see some mango there the whole bit of
re-watches okay I gotta go I gotta go
please
guys are amazing
bye
I'll see you guys I'll see you tomorrow
day 20. I can't seem to leave
the sleeping recharging shot I'm ready
for another round let's do it let's do
round 20. now
I'll see you guys tomorrow for 220 all
right
day 20 Medical mean brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge say that four times in
a row really fast
I'll see you guys