we're live facebook youtube tick-tock
clubhouse
day two day two how are you guys
doing that's what i wanted to ask you
how are you doing
on the medical medium mono cleanse
challenge that's what it's about okay
mono eating
for a couple of days for three days
actually three days are you gonna go
four
you can do five days three days okay so
i'm excited about this got the papayas
right here
got my bananas right here okay
got steamed potatoes right here i got
peas over here right deck which i'm
gonna cook up and make the pea hummus
again
that pea hummus is so good it's insane
that's how great it is it's so good
good to see you guys coming on great
great great glad you all guys are here
so how are you guys doing by the way and
i just want to run down one little thing
the
craving the emotional craving could
start
because all those things are out of your
diet the milk cheese the butter the eggs
the chicken the meat
right gone out of the diet right now the
chocolate the caffeine
right the coffee it's out of your diet
right now right
the all the different nutritional yeast
apple cider vinegar all the
all the stuff right all those vegan
burgers and vegan pizzas are out of your
diet right now right
you guys are just taste buds are
recalibrate
right they're recalibrating think about
that a little bit
your taste buds are actually
recalibrating your stomach's getting a
chance to heal your digestion is getting
a chance
to come back and heal think about how
amazing that is
you guys i'm proud of you for doing this
if you just started it and
you're starting it today because you
haven't done it or you started after
this
hey fine i'm proud of you then too
but we're day two i'm doing it i'm
excited okay
so we're gonna run down some of the do's
and don'ts gonna run down on some of
the good things about what this is doing
for us which is so exciting
so good to see you guys coming on
awesome and i'm going to answer as many
questions as i can
and we're going to run through it all so
let's start doing it let's start
breaking it down and
by the way do you have the cleanse the
heel book
do you have this book 51 off
amazon.com us so do you have your school
book
so keep that in mind because that's what
really what it is it's your school book
and the mono cleanse is in here and all
the questions are answered in here in
detail the details matter
so you got to make sure you have this so
important so you guys are you doing your
lemon water
dr fon md good to see you doing your
lemon water 16 ounces to 32 ounces of
lemon water
do it more than once a day so i'm gonna
make some lemon water in a minute too
right are you doing your celery juice at
all
at all kelly roberts said can i put lime
on a salad a papaya banana and greens
yes you can
i think that's fine to do absolutely
could put
lime on there that's okay you could put
a little lemon on there too because
lemon's involved
lime is involved in this mono cleanse
so in this mono cleanse challenge let's
make some lemon water really quick
did you guys do your lemon water i want
to ask
and how are you doing is it hitting you
yet
you're like you know any kind of
cravings any emotional
cravings is hitting you you need to see
somebody says need a juicer
um deanna says please hit the thumbs up
for
anthony that would be really kind thank
you bless your heart for caring
right so we got the lemon so
you guys are you stocked up with your
lemons you're doing you should do lemon
water twice a day
on this you could do it three times a
day if you want as well
okay and you can definitely do that is
there a limit on how much lemon water i
saw that in tik tok just now
there's no limit to it if you want to do
if you want water all day long like the
liter of water
you cause a minimum of a liter of water
and you want to squeeze lemon into that
all day long as you eat you're drinking
it that's perfectly fine you guys
i'm excited about this for everybody
really am
okay 16 to 32 ounces water
there you go lemons going in that's a
part of it
upon waking you're flushing your liver
you're flushing out poisons and toxins
when you use this upon
wait right upon waking you wake up
it's like rise and shine boom you got
your lemon water how incredible is that
first thing okay you need that
then you can wait a little while you can
have your celery juice
shortly after that that's one thing you
can do
and um and we're going to go into that a
little bit so let's talk about the mono
cleanse what are we even talking about
you guys just got or day two of the mono
cleanse challenge as we speak
the mono cleanses and cleanse the heel
okay right here
and i'm gonna take us right in there
okay
so um the mono cleanse is really
important
because people with digestive problems
digestive weaknesses people that don't
even know they have digestive weaknesses
can really use this in their life okay
so people that have h pylori people who
have ulcers people have acid reflux
celiac crohn's colitis gastroparesis
this information is really valuable
ibs cramping bloating diarrhea
loose stools if that's a problem for
someone
constipation that one too polyps
what about the polyps intestinal polyps
right the colon
hemorrhoids it's another one too you
know i didn't mention that yesterday too
that
hemorrhoids is a big deal a lot of
people got the hemorrhoids
and mono eating is a great way to
bring things back and balance and do
some healing
but not just any mono eating
you don't want to just do well i'm just
going to eat meat for
just i'm just only going to eat meat or
i'm just going to eat beans
you know where i'm just going to eat
beans every day and only beans no you
don't want to do that
right i'm just gonna have milk and just
milk
i'm just gonna have cheese you don't
want to do that either
maria says coconut water really is
helping me
it helps it helps with neurological
issues too
it's once again those minerals right
that
those mineral salts that's why celery
juice is so incredible
because of that reason the powerful
mineral salts right so you don't want a
mono eat
something that you shouldn't okay
you don't want a mono eat eggs you don't
want a mono eat bread
right you don't want a mono eat chicken
you don't want a mono eat turkey all
right i'm going to do a mono eating
cleanse i'm just going to have turkey
i'm just going to eat turkey okay you
don't want to do that
you want to do it right if you do it and
it takes a a special blend
information that i've been providing
people for over 35 years from
above so cleanse the heal is where that
information is the details are there
we're going to run across a couple a
couple of those details we're going to
talk about it
so everybody's worried about protein so
i want to hit that right off the running
because i see that a lot it's like
where's your protein where's your
protein
and you have to understand one thing
right everybody's getting a ton of
protein out there they're living off of
protein they got protein coming in every
which way
everybody's on a high protein diet did
you know that everybody's on a high
protein diet out there
even the vegans they're on high protein
diets everybody's on that you're on your
nuts
and your nut butters if you're vegan or
plant-based you're on your beans if
you're vegan
you're just you're on all these intense
proteins right you're on your chickpea
hummus your black bean hummus
okay you're eating your tofu you're
eating your soy
right you know and then
if you're somebody that's animal protein
you're eating your chicken you're eating
your fish
you're eating all the and you're still
having beans and nuts and nut butters
everybody's having their peanut butter
everybody's having their cheese you're
you're eating your protein everybody's
eating their protein and everybody gets
sick
protein has nothing to do whether if
you're gonna get sick or not
protein has nothing to do with you
getting sick with lupus multiple
sclerosis
ra hashimoto's eczema psoriasis
psoriatic arthritis or any other
condition
there is that has nothing to do with
protein at all
very important to know okay you get
neurological symptoms and you get
diagnosed with neurological
neurological lyme protein has nothing to
do with any of it if you get acne
protein has nothing to do with acne
rosacea protein has nothing to do with
rosacea
it's imperative you understand how that
works
where you get sick and if someone says
oh are you getting protein
as if that's some kind of answer or some
kind of solution
to why you're sick like it's a head
scratcher right there
that's a head scratcher uh so is a
protein
bar gonna save me from my
lupus from my heart palpitations from my
weak limbs from my tingles and numbness
and and so
how does that work so that's really
important you know it really is
literally everyone is complaining about
a symptom
a pain an ache a condition out there
everybody now is the new normal is to be
sick
that's the new normal is to be sick so
everybody's got a symptom that's a new
normal out there and protein has nothing
to do with it now if you're going to do
the mono cleanse you got to get the
calories in
you can't under feed yourself you're not
fasting and that's the first thing
people do when they're like oh i'm gonna
do some kind of cleanse or i'm gonna try
to do something and then they don't eat
anything
they eat hardly anything it's like okay
i had my lemon water uh what next
um i better have a banana
yep let's see i'm on the cleanse
ray i'm on the cleanse i better have a
banana
mm-hmm i'm on my three-day cleanse
yep
is that it i'm getting hungry
i didn't realize how spoiled i was
eating everything and anything i ever
wanted
i didn't what if there was like a food
shortage someday
what would i do then i didn't know i was
just
i'm getting i'm getting hungry again i i
need something to eat
i need something to eat i better have
some cookies
i better have some cookies because i
i'm like spoiled i i better have a grill
oh i'm in a mood for a grilled cheese
sandwich today
yeah like i can't do this mono eating
cleanse i'm in the mood for a grilled
cheese sandwich
i i i ordered a pizza i ordered a pizza
a little while ago it's on its way
it's on its way and um so i'm thinking
about the pizza what else can i have
a couple eggs i'm i'm getting hungry
what happens is that people don't
realize how spoiled they are
too instant gratification everywhere
instant gratification just eat what you
want i'm in the mood for some coffee of
course you're in the mood you're
addicted to it you're gonna have to have
it every day
i'm in the mood for some chocolate of
course you're gonna need to be in the
mood for it you're addicted to it
you eat it every day you know i'm in the
you know
i'm in the mood for chicken quesadilla
i'm in the mood for some tacos some
nachos
i'm in the mood i'm in the mood for some
pizza you know i'm in the mood for you
know flavors
and lots of just oil and fat
this is the first time you're off the
fats
this is the first time you're off
the fats you're off the milk cheese the
butter the eggs the bacon the sausage
you're off the chicken the fish the meat
you're off the
the oils the nut butters the nuts and
seeds you're off of it
you're off of the fat you're off of the
soy which is fat
the soy is fat all right it's a lot of
oil in soy
so you're you're off of the fat you guys
and when you go off the fat
there's this you know panic button that
hits too it's like
it's also a combination of being spoiled
too
like eating whatever you want i'm gonna
have my tuna fish where's my mayo i'm
gonna have my grilled cheese sandwich
i'm gonna have cookies later on i'm
gonna have some chocolate oh it's all
organic though
i'm gonna have you know we get spoiled
okay so let's go into the coins let's
talk about it a little bit
let's do that
people always worry about like getting
enough
of the food rainbow right getting enough
of food rainbow
on the mono eating cleanse the larger
amounts you're eating of healing foods
remember this you're eating a larger
amount
of healing foods okay
such as papaya in the way your body
benefits from that
supersedes the need for variety
keep that in mind i'm a big believer in
variety for sure but when we're healing
certain problems and cleansing certain
things going on in the body
simplicity helps us heal
and when we're doing larger amounts of a
medicinal food
that heals us in special ways
we're changing our body's environment
for the positive we're getting rid of
the poisons we're easing up the liver
the liver doesn't have to produce all
this bile your stomach doesn't blow out
all its hydrochloric acid and your
adrenals
have a chance to heal right your
adrenals have a chance
all these things matter okay so
the larger amounts you're eating you
guys of these healing foods such as
papaya
weigh out the benefits man
super seed superseded if you're trying
to get the entire
rainbow on your plate because you know i
know a lot of people are like i'm always
trying to get the
rainbow i'm always trying to get all the
colors in right
if you're only getting this much color
of one thing
you're really not getting much anything
see how it works
keep that in mind this is really
important this is such an important
piece of information you guys i hope you
have your school book with you if you
don't have it
amazon.com us 51 off make sure that
books in your hands someday
you won't be sorry get at the library if
you can for free
you're trying to get that entire rainbow
on your plate right you guys heard of
that
you're only getting tiny amounts of each
food when people are trying to get that
rainbow going
you're only getting tiny amounts one
little piece of tomato in your salad
oh i got a little red in there there's a
little tomato in my salad i got a little
red
it's not enough you have to eat a few
tomatoes like in this medical medium
spinach soup right when you're not doing
the mono cleanse
and you're doing the medical medium
spinach soup you're getting like
two three bigger sized tomatoes in there
but you eat a little salad and you got a
little piece of tomato you think you're
doing yourself good
that's the trick out of that whole
rainbow thing right
a couple of cucumber pieces versus
actually making cucumber noodles
or juicing some cucumbers and making
some cucumber juice right
see the difference the power the power
difference right there
so people are like well no i had some
cucumber i had a salad with a little
tomato i got a check
check covered got a little piece of
tomato
check covered uh no check
no check me you got screwed over by
information out there
because it takes more than a little
piece of tomato and a little couple
little slices of cucumber
it does so when we span out the rainbow
too much and we're all trying to
you know a little bit of this little bit
of that little bit little bit of this
it's not enough to do anything keep that
in mind right
so a few leaves of mixed greens
isn't enough is it enough
well it may give you the full spectrum
it's not like eating the whole bowl of
heirloom
tomatoes you guys it's not like
having a whole head of cauliflower in
one sitting
instead you're spreading out your
nutrients in these little pieces of food
in some cases that can work in the end
if your digestion isn't troubled either
too a lot of people
their digestion isn't tanked yet right
and they can just like throw any
abomination they want in there fried
this fry that or just whatever
you know bake this oils and all this
stuff
but you know it's important to know so
um
look ten i gotta tell you something too
we're gonna go into quantities in a
second i just wanna finish this up
all right now the bottom line is
another thing too when people when they
eat avocado they might have in their
salad a sliver of avocado
and orange slice right and you know in
their food somewhere and it you know or
they have something that's made with
all the stuff and thrown on chicken
breasts right the bottom line
bottom line is how do you get better
if you're not using enough of a
medicinal food
if someone only eats a couple of bites
of banana every three days
or a couple of bites of banana every
week you're not getting enough there's
you can't get enough to do what you need
to do to heal
and this is one of the traps right now
in alternative medicine by the way
really important information right there
that alone is so critical
um quantities let's go into that a
little bit
while we can
eight bananas might not be enough for
somebody definitely not ten bananas
might not be enough for somebody on this
mono cleanse
okay the bananas could be small these
bananas
are bigger all right these bananas are
these are big bananas right here someone
could have smaller bananas
medium-sized bananas you don't want to
starve yourself you
want to eat enough so important lunell
says quantity matters
as much as quality exactly let's talk
about how to do it
let's go let's get working we got work
to do
we do we do let's get on it so
first things first let me run a little
celery juice let's get that going right
now
you guys don't mind first and foremost
did you guys get your celery juice you
need the mineral salts
that's a big deal all in its own you
have to have the mineral salts
very important
so i got some fresh washed celery right
here
one of the reasons why people heal with
celery juice is because
of the mineral salts
it's a complete electrolyte
you can be somebody with a whole rainbow
of foods
you you know you got a a wide palette
you're eccentric can i have this
you're in a you know you're in a juice
bar you're in a restaurant a vegan
restaurant and you're like
yeah can i have that i say
a little bit of this and a little juice
on the side and you're not getting a
complete electrolyte
the reason why people heal is one of the
reasons is that complete electrolyte
which juicer do i use mary this is the
mm-900 hds
it has to be that model if you want the
results
as far as saving money
20 off i think coming up i don't know
when the sale is i think it's now
actually
i knew it was on its way but it's the
mm-900 hds not
another omega juicer it's that one
specifically and
it's the celery juicer and it does other
stuff too
you won't be disappointed i'm telling
it's my favorite juicer i've ever
i'm working with these guys on it and um
with them on this and it's my favorite
juicer i've ever
used so
what this does is it gives you a chance
to cleanse
and heal it gives your body a rest
like no other that's what the mono
cleanse does
it gives your body a rest
when you're healing and cleansing you
may
rest more you may feel like you need to
rest
more your adrenals aren't on fire
when you're doing this keep that in mind
your adrenals aren't on fire every day
we stress our adrenals out it's not just
the world stressing them out we eat in a
way
that trashes our adrenals you guys this
is so important
when you're mono cleansing right
doing the mono cleanse
medical medium mono cleanse i have to
say medical medium because someone's
gonna be like
yeah i'm eating nothing but grapes for a
month and they just rip their guts apart
and they actually hurt themselves versus
help themselves
[Music]
the medical medium mono cleanse allows
for your adrenals to not
have to get overworked so you might get
tired
because you're healing that's how it
works
your body's getting a break you may need
to rest
or take a nap
all of this is important to know so that
in the future
you'll have more energy and more
strength
see how that works you're giving your
body
a chance to heal so that in the future
you're going to have more strength and
more adrenal power
right every bit everybody every day is
trashing their adrenals they don't know
it but they are
they're tanking fats every day because
everybody's on a high fat diet
which tires out the adrenals
they're on caffeine they're on coffee
green tea matcha tea whatever chocolate
and they've got their adrenals
overworked every single day
and then they're intermittent fasting
when things get so out of control
they intermittent fast and then they're
on adrenaline once again because now
they're not eating
so their adrenals are pumping right
[Music]
what this does is it it tells your body
we're healing it tells your body we're
taking a break
see how important that is you may get a
little tired you may need to rest
you have poisons and toxins coming out
into the bloodstream to be urinated out
and eliminated out
your blood is thinning you're getting
rid of all the fat in your blood
your heart's getting a break and so what
happens
is when your heart's getting a break and
your adrenals are getting a break your
heart doesn't have to pump so hard
all these things allow for you to heal
hold on how are adrenals pumping
something's blocking that word oh during
an intermittent fast so hold this on
tick tock
hold on how are adrenals pumping during
intermittent fast
intermittent fast doesn't doesn't give
you glucose so you're not running on any
glucose adrenaline has to replace the
glucose that's why
so here's how it works right
you're intermittent fasting the wrong
way that's what everybody does
okay because they're not getting their
celery juice keeping those mineral salts
going in there they're not getting their
lemon water they're not having
some fruit they're not doing that so
intermittent fasting means they're
holding
withholding from food right when you
withhold for fruit from food
past a couple of hours you start running
on adrenaline because you ran out of
glucose your glucose is gone
your glucose just disappears out of the
bloodstream because you're now
you're not giving yourself any glucose
right you're not giving yourself any
carbohydrates or blood sugar your blood
sugar is just
relying now on adrenaline so when you
intermittent fast you're just off of
adrenaline so you're on a high you're
like wow this intermittent fasting
thing's working for me
and all that does is take you to a place
of trashing your adrenals later on
that's how it works you don't think no
one intermittent fasted before and just
i mean yeah it's been around and it
crashes people
right now it's popular because people
are used to bombarding themselves with
so much food in the morning
that when they take a digestive break
for a little while they pick up
but you trash your adrenals at the same
time
so intermittent fasting totally wipes
the adrenals out okay and that's how it
works
believe it or not that's just the way
the body the body runs
if you don't have glucose you run on
adrenaline
it's one or the other glucose or
adrenaline you run out of glucose
because you're intermittent fasting and
you stop eating
then you better be running on something
and guess what it is it's adrenaline it
takes
place of glucose that's how the body
works the more you
run out of glucose the more adrenaline
rises
the more adrenaline epinephrine is
released more epinephrine's released and
more epinephrine is released and it
happens like that every day for people
and that's how thanks for asking that
questions really good
question by the way the sale is on 20
off for
the mm-900 hds that's bone dry
there's nothing wet in the in the bowl
that's dry
there's no fluid in the bowl there's no
moisture on the bottom of the bowl
this is the hds what this does is it
cuts my salary bill in half i can't tell
you how many juicers
this has probably allowed me to pretend
to buy in the sense where it paid for
itself over and over and over again i
could have bought
50 juicers already with the money saved
that's how incredible that is it's the
only juicer that pays for itself by the
way
incredible so all right
let's move on you guys i'm excited to be
here today
second day of the mono eating cleanse
pick up what you can from any any
tidbits you can and
maybe watch the video again if you just
got here california poppy what's up
i found banana mono good for ptsd
amazing and vagus nerve issues too
absolutely healing the vagus nerve
gentle glucose-rich mineral-rich
foods easy on the digestion allows the
vagus nerve to do some healing
love it love it love it so great so
great
got my celery juice 16 to 32 ounces okay
always strain your celery juice
keep that in mind gotta strain it get
the pulp get the fiber
out make sure it's straight celery juice
really important to know okay all right
what celery juice does for us is it
helps to stop
the cravings really important right
there on its own
helps to kill the cravings there's only
a little bit of glucose and celery not a
lot
but the point is there's a lot of
mineral salts right
there's a difference between salt itself
and then what's in celery
the sodium cluster salts the trace
minerals and celery juice do a whole
different thing
can you do aloe on mono okay yeah you
can
healthful christina yeah you can do
aloe on the mono cleanse definitely
absolutely let's go into the next part
you guys we just did 16 to 32 ounces 32
ounces of lemon water
32 ounces of celery juice check check
got those two down
pumped let's go into some papaya
let's do that all right
you guys you might have the small
papayas you might have the big papayas
now let's talk about the options we
didn't go into that
so we got the book all you guys have the
cleanse to heal
make sure you get a copy sometime when
you can so
important okay this is the mono cleanse
section
amazon's running a sale on this book
specifically 51 percent off
okay model eating options banana and
lettuce
right that's one okay where's the
right here you might be somebody that
just is gonna take the banana
and lettuce option that means
lots of lettuce and lots of bananas
that's your food every day for three
days lots of bananas
and lots of lettuce keep in mind the
mono cleanse
can turn into a long-term diet to help
recover somebody and bring somebody back
and that's what it's done for so many
around the world for so many years
all right so there's that that's an
option banana lettuce
another option papaya
and lettuce that's the other option
keep in mind you don't want to
be frugal in your papaya and banana
you want to eat enough you just don't
want to buy a couple of bananas
and think that you got it down and
you're eating a banana a day
basically what that means is you're
eating 80 calories
60 calories a day
that's what's going to happen it's like
it's in it's you know i notice people
are doing it
it's like they're just doing it you know
just like doing it yeah starting to
start the model eating cleanse yeah
yep i just came back from the store
yeah i'm ready for three days what do i
got i got
a bunch of bananas yeah for three days
um what 80 calories
some of these have 60 calories in them
all right 80
80 80.
um whoa for three straight
days how much does my vegan pizza have
2 500 calories what if i have my vegan
burgers
1800 calories all right what about my
grilled cheese sandwiches
that i eat every day fifteen hundred
calories
in fat it's all the fat in there too
all right well i think i'm gonna be
hungry
let's crack open that papaya let's go
into the other options
then you can do banana and papaya
together
i'll show you how to do that with
lettuce involved right
all the days that you're doing this no
matter what option you're picking you're
still doing celery juice still doing
lemon water keep that in mind
coconut water too that's great as well
still got to do a liter of water as well
too so keep that in mind what's another
option right here
steamed potatoes these are piping hot
just came out of steamer before i
clicked on
the cam so we got steamed
potatoes right here and i'm gonna make
some mashed potatoes for you guys in a
little bit
what's another option peas
peas are another option so i'm gonna
make a pea hummus
as well so i'm excited about these
options right here
and then winter squash is an additional
option if you guys are just kind of
losing it you're like well i want
something fun and different
you can do the winter squash right here
any type of lettuce in particular
butter leaf lettuce is best red leaf
lettuce is your second best and if you
have to use any kind of lettuce past
that i'm fine with it
totally cool you can do that let's crack
open this papaya
so this is a large papaya you may buy
some papayas and they're like this big
right you may buy some papayas and
they're just a little bigger than
this lemon there's papayas that
are small right you're gonna need a lot
of them keep that in mind you might need
to eat
15 tiny papayas in a day
all right okay if you read the book
you'll know like so many details of this
you don't mess up
so you end up eating enough of a portion
or getting enough food so you're not
missing out and you buy two tiny little
papayas
and now you're just home and you're like
how am i going to do this let's start
with the
pie here so
just going to open up this washer and
grab some balls
right so i'm going to scoop the seeds
out of this papaya as you guys can see
right now you can eat papaya seeds but
they're very spicy
and they're very strong right and when
you're mono
eating it might not be something you
want to do you might not want to eat
them they're very
peppery very very bitey
okay very spicy
removing the um seeds right there
so you got a couple of different options
you could just do this
you're doing the mono cleanse just take
a spoon right
and you can eat it so like that another
way here
is i'm going to cut it in pieces
all right little squares and stuff i'm
gonna make
a papaya bowl do that now
now this isn't a lot of food
right so because it's not a lot of
calories
believe it or not people are afraid of
bananas they think it's so much sugar
there's so many calories in there
peanut butter's got the calories people
don't realize that
it's under a different name it's under
fat
so somebody's gonna be like that's not a
calorie fat's not a calorie
fat's fat yeah the system is rigged
so we think that the fat is just really
doesn't really
offer anything like that but what it
does is the fat makes you fat
there's a reason for that fat makes you
fat
why is watermelon making me super
bloated does that mean i have
sibo or candida so
a couple of things with watermelon is i
love a look i love watermelon it's a
cleansing healing food i love
melons in the 369 cleanse the 369
advanced cleanse you'll see
melons on the ninth day right
but what happens is a lot of people have
digestive problems of all kinds
they'll have things going on with their
digestion you know that that anything
they'll have
um they'll have sibo they'll have h
pylori they'll have
uh pockets in their colon they'll have
narrowing
in their intestinal tract so they'll
have all these different issues
they'll have low low hydrochloric acid
because their stomach glands are burnt
big thing about bloating and you should
learn about it in here
honestly if you're bloating for any
reason you should have this book so you
can look in the bloating section and
work on
fixing what's going on inside of there
you don't have that book you
i mean you really should people got the
blown out
gastric lands inside the stomach so the
gastric lamps inside the stomach are
blown out
right watermelon is very healing
very very cleansing right
but what happens is because it's so
cleansing
in its own way it's gonna start flushing
all kinds of crap you got on that lining
see so inside here
you're gonna have
inside your colon right in there okay
okay right inside your colon
you're gonna have all this debris and so
now you're like well i'm gonna do a
whole bunch of watermelon let me do that
let me do a whole bunch of watermelon
and as you're doing that
you're gonna be like flushing
flushing and flush it and then you're
not going to be used to
uprooting all that that protein that's
rancid
that's sticking all on the linings
you're not going to be used to
all that putrified fat that's stuck
in the linings from years and years and
years of eating that
so then you you're gonna you're gonna
get kind of upset about watermelon
we get upset there's other cleansing
foods we might get upset at right
so we'll punish these foods during that
watermelon
making me bloated i'm not saying you're
like you know freaking out but
you know darn that cleansing food it's
you know darn that celery juice
but really it's from years and years
of being fed garbage that's what it is
and and the whole thing is you must
already
had uploading issues somewhere this
isn't the first time you blowed it
and if you're dealing with sibo or
anything else you already have a
bloating issue
right so it's not like you've never
bloated before you're eating your pizzas
and never bloated you're eating your
nachos and never bloated you're eating
your bean burgers never bloated you're
eating your chicken and
rice and never bloated your bread and
never bloated your muffins and never
bloated your bagels had never bloated
so you you're obviously bloating it's
not like you had watermelon for the
first time in your bloating
but watermelon watermelon is a
powerful cleanser too though once you
start uprooting all that crap
you'll have a storm in there you'll
have a shitstorm in there
so in the medical medium mono cleanse
watermelon isn't recommended
okay it doesn't mean you can't use
watermelon it's a very healing food
it's on the cover of the book right here
right
because it's an extremely healing food
i've gotten a lot of people recovered
using melons
so let's let's minus the watermelon
let's move into honeydew melons
cantaloupes right so
for sensitive people i've had them on
melons i've had them on cantaloupes
all right and i've used it but
i'm saying in general when you want to
do something when if you have anything
going on with your intestinal tract when
you've got crohn's colitis and you've
got
ibs and you've got sibo and you've got
all these other problems i like
what's in the book for mono eating which
is your papaya
and your banana your lettuces your
gentle lettuces
your celery juice your lemon water
that's what i
like right there and there's some people
that got pretty strong guts still
you know they're their hydrochloric acid
is still strong
their guts aren't filled with too much
putrefied stuff and they're taking the
watermelon every day it's a great tool
it's a great tool but i'm saying
it's not highly recommended for the mono
eating cleanse
but yet i love melons and i love the
honeydews and the cantaloupes and the
crenshaws and all those
and i love those for the 369 last day
anyway but if you're gonna go
long term on the melon long term
like if you ever choose to do something
like that you go watermelon
you're doing a watermelon every day long
term i recommend you make sure you get
that celery juice in every single day
because you need those mineral salts
that's what i recommend okay i also
recommend
that you should if you are doing it you
should be pretty
hardy when you do it because you might
bump into walls eventually because
there's not
there's not enough calories in most of
the watermelons that are
out there some watermelons around the
world
have the caloric they have that caloric
nature to it they got the calories
most watermelons that we walk in and
just stumble into a store and we grab
one
not a lot of calories in those some of
those aren't like that you'll see
they're kind of whitish inside
they're a little pale inside they're not
deep red with
all that sugar and glucose so that's
another mistake too you just go okay i'm
gonna do watermelon cleanse you grab a
watermelon from the store and that
watermelon doesn't have a lot of
calories because it's not like somebody
else's watermelon somewhere else in the
world
where it's deep rich red all the seeds
in there just keep in mind that that
that's just some of the some of the
things that just to look out for
but you notice the medical medium
cleanse is
mono cleanse is based with based out of
a
papaya so we're doing the papaya right
here okay
and what we do is you can do you take
the banana
chop it up throw it on top of the papaya
if you're gonna do the papaya banana one
so if you're gonna mix them and do i
like the papaya banana
together that's one i really like but i
also like when you know
many times i've had to recommend for
people to do the banana one
just the banana and lettuce to recover
them and get them better and stronger
and healthier
um so you can just literally go this
route right here
grab a fork and now you're having your
banana pieces
so good having your papaya piece
blending papaya is actually one of my
favorite too here's another thing
take your lettuce leaf right
put your banana pieces here put some
papaya pieces in your
your lettuce leaf right and then you got
your lettuce papaya banana
that's not a lot of food
it's one banana and a half of a large
papaya
it's not a lot of food keep that in mind
so
you may need a whole bunch of these from
morning till night okay if you're really
really hungry like you're hitting the
wall you're hungry
you're craving you're hungry if you're
only three bananas in
half a papaya in and it's four o'clock
in the afternoon and you're like hitting
you're just like
you want to scream then you know
you need some more so keep that in mind
how it works very important information
right here
all right all right we got that
that was fun let's go into the next part
so we need to do
i want to blend up papaya real quick
i know i did that yesterday but it's
important to do it again and show
everybody because
it's it's such a great tool
so let's get some papaya in here do a
little blend up real quick
so we're getting some papaya in here
right here
and we're gonna do just a quick papaya
blend
right now you can you can scoop right
down to the skins of your papayas like
right to this you know inner rind
okay keep that in mind you can totally
do that
do a quick little blend
this is probably one of my favorite ways
of doing it
and i'll give you a recap you guys 16 to
32 ounces of lemon water upon waking
okay i i think 32 ounces of lemon water
is smart even if you use a half a lemon
right then you move on 15-30 minutes
later you're on your celery juice
right you got that
and then you're moving on to whatever
food choice you have you don't have to
have your lettuce
in the morning you could save that for
lunch your lunch version
you can save it for the end of the day
version right
and
so i got some papaya that's blended
fun fun fun
all right and what i like to do i'm just
going to move this out of the way real
quick
what i like to do is peel back a banana
like this
i like to cut in pieces
[Music]
and anyway
i got it right there in the in the the
cut pieces
in the bowl of papaya so what i like to
do is dip
it so i take the piece of banana and dip
it
don't knock it till you try it it's that
good
like if you were here right now and i
was like
dude just dip it in there
don't knock it to your stripe that's
incredible
but then again you could be somebody
that's so addicted
to all the bad stuff you don't know what
you're tasting
and that's what i love about the mono
cleanse it brings you
back around so that you might be able to
detect
poison in all your food
because that's what happens everybody's
poisoning themselves
they're poisoning themselves a cow's
milk poisoning themselves with
with soy they're poisoning themselves
with caffeine they're poisoning
themselves with all kinds of different
things apple cider vinegar all kinds of
stuff vinegar and all their food they're
just poisoning themselves
and what happens is when you remove
all the poison right and you keep it
plain and simple you guys
and you get used to that simplicity and
then your body reorganizes
okay your taste buds reorganize your
your central
nervous system connects to the taste
buds right
your cranial nerves go to the taste buds
your cranial nerves
go to all those nerves that that are
there for your senses
and all of a sudden everything starts
changing
because you're getting away from the
poisons for a little bit because
everybody's they're just poisoning
themselves that's what they're taught to
do
right and once you're doing this you get
used to it
and you do this long enough and then you
go to
back to all that poison you're used to
eating
right you go back to all the poison now
you're on the caffeine
now you're on the butter and your cheese
and everything else you go back to it
and the vinegar and everything and the
kombucha tea
straight poison once you go back to all
that you'll be like what
and that's why this is critical to
realign things to get
you back to where you're supposed to be
to be able to heal
too all right so let's keep it moving
if you guys just got here talking about
the different options we just did banana
papaya
just did papaya by itself showed you a
couple different ways of doing it
let's move on to some mashed potatoes
let me grab a bowl i think that's what
i'm gonna do
see what we got oh we got souls here
so rewatch the last two days of lives if
you can if you just got here you should
catch up you should learn how to do the
mono cleanse right
watch it on youtube you can get all this
information
all the questions i'm gonna answer along
the way and everything make sure you've
got your school book
you won't be sorry it's critical to have
it's 51
off amazon.com us
all right let's make some mashed
potatoes
i got some steamed potatoes here if
you're somebody and you're like well i'm
doing the mono cleanse and
i just bought some potatoes and and i'm
gonna have
you know i'm gonna have my potato right
here
this is it this is it for the day
here it is here's my potato for the day
right here
you're just gonna get in trouble it's
not gonna be enough food prepare to have
enough food
that is important so you can mash the
potatoes like this if you want
pretty easy so you could use this
so let's recap a little bit we got 16 to
32 ounces of lemon water is an inside
thing going on here's inside jokes going
on
we got 16 to 32 ounces of lemon water
we got 16 to 32 ounces of celery juice
right okay you're moving on to some of
your options you could do banana papaya
you can do papaya
all right we're doing a potato and
lettuce option let's head there now
okay pick the one you want you can drink
pure
cucumber juice at the end of the day you
can drink celery juice twice
morning and end of the day keep the salt
keep the seasonings like i'm saying keep
all
that out and drink approximately
a liter of water throughout the day you
can add lemon to that water too
all right back on track okay let's mash
some potatoes
now you can put the potatoes in a food
processor right
i wouldn't put them in a blender i
wouldn't
i wouldn't put a potato in a blender i
don't know i don't think that i don't
think that would be a smart thing to do
right so i'm just mashing up these
potatoes
so i'm doing some mashed potatoes now i
get it everybody wants salt they want
butter
they want cheese in here right that's
that's what everybody wants
and remember this is plain
this is plain for reason
this is about sacrificing a little
without having a sacrifice
this is just as healing
as the other medical medium cleanses
it does different things okay
most importantly really gives your
digestive system
a total break which is key
you give your digestive system a break
right i left the skins on this potato
you can take the skins off if you really
wanted to you don't have to
you're getting rid of addictions you
guys
you're restarting your taste buds you're
healing your stomach glands
you're rebuilding your hcl
what i like to do is put lemon in these
mashed potatoes
so dropping some lemon in
here we go we're day two the medical
medium mono cleanse
challenge are you guys doing it
would love to know i know you guys are
many of you guys are
right
so let's just mash these up a little bit
more
all right we got mashed potatoes right
here
now i'm gonna put these in a small bowl
let's do that
now you don't have to have four potatoes
worth at once
you can span those out okay some people
are gonna want four potatoes
some people are gonna want more
throughout the day some people less
you might have a small stomach and
you're not used to stretching your
stomach
because you're used to eating dense fats
small portions of dense
fat right a lot of people do that
they're used to eating
pieces of meat little pieces of chicken
and they get all their calories
from all dense fats so their stomach
isn't stretched
our stomach isn't um it's it's
shrunk right a lot of people have so
they'll eat like a part of a banana and
feel
full they'll eat like half a banana and
feel like well that was too much food
but you can eat more when it comes down
to the mono cleanse okay
you can eat more so that's important so
this is a mashed potato right here
what i like about the mashed potato you
could add more lemon to it too i added
some lemon
okay and
put a little bit more lemon in there
there's no butter in here there's no fat
in these mashed potatoes
there's a reason for that to save your
liver you guys
to save your liver to save your pancreas
so you don't blow out your pancreas so
you don't blow out your liver
okay so you can put a lid over those
mashed potatoes right there in your
lettuce just like that
and there you go
really good that's another option
and i don't want you guys getting
confused about something
yesterday you saw me eating different
things you saw me eating the pea hummus
and you saw me eating the bananas
then you saw me eating the papaya and
then
i think there's some comments out there
there's some people that were like oh my
god i could do the mono cleanse and have
peas and bananas together
no no i'm just i'm just demonstrating
so that's why i'm i'm kind of breaking
the mono cleanse
challenge around a little bit not
supposed to be doing mashed potatoes and
peas
i'm not supposed to be doing mashed
potatoes and banana mashed potatoes and
papaya
so you're not supposed to just pick one
of the options the papaya option in
lettuce
banana option and lettuce the pea option
in lettuce
no potato same potato pops in the
lettuce
so good so good
all right
so you guys
are you guys eating enough that's a
question i have for you guys are you
guys eating enough
so i got the pan on what i'm going to do
is cook some peas
the pan on here no cheese no butter
no milk
all right i know we like the sour cream
in our potatoes i know
we like the cheese we know we like the
butter on our potatoes but you want to
do this i know we like the oil in there
but you don't want to do that
you don't
i got my pan on i'm gonna drop some peas
in a little bit
get my pan hot
so all right so now there is
an option with the mono cleanse
right here that's the winter squash so
the steamed winter squash right
okay you can do that option and you can
combine that
if you're somebody especially if you're
somebody that's like totally freaking
out you're like there's not in
there's not enough options i'm bored or
i can't do this because
i've been too spoiled for too many years
eating whatever i want and i just
i can't do this so you can do the
steamed winter squash
with steamed green beans brussels
sprouts or asparagus
isn't that great isn't that great it is
really i mean when you think about it to
do all the healing you need to do
it's good to know you look you can
branch out with another
option like that and that's pretty cool
this is so good by the way
i know this is so simplistic but when
you're on the mono cleanse and your
taste buds
are going back to where they should be
and you're recalibrating the senses and
you're recalibrating the cranial nerves
right
so you're recalibrating the cranial
nerves to your taste buds
right so all those cranial nerves
stemming out of your brain stem and then
going to
your tongue to your mouth to your
salivary glands right those cranial
nerves
they're getting rewired they're getting
recalibrated and rewired
that's why it's important right there
that alone is really
really really an important reason for
doing this
okay so i'm letting that pan heat up a
little bit and i'm going to have a
little bit more of this because this is
so good
and believe me check this out you guys
right
when your butt gets hungry
when you get hungry hungry
this is gonna taste good
we're so spoiled we're so spoiled out
there
to eat whatever we want that's what it
is tea whatever we want we get so
spoiled
that when you go hungry a little bit
limb bomb love when you're laughing when
you go hungry a little bit
that stuff tastes good plain
mashed potato with lemon on it with
a butter leaf lettuce incredible
bananas if if you're hungry enough
and you took away that garbage and all
that poison and all that stuff right
all that addiction and everything else
you removed it
and you eat the papaya the banana combo
all of a sudden you're liking lettuce
yeah this lettuce tastes good
yeah um mm-hmm
radish lettuce is good it's amazing
oh my god i know this is good
well that potato is good
when your butt's hungry enough
that potato is amazing
if anybody gets a symptom during anybody
gets a symptom
headache or nausea bloating right
tiredness and you're doing the mono in
clean
always be your own detective did you
ever have a headache before did you have
one last week did you have one two
months ago did you have one
you ever get a little nausea anyway oh
you never had nausea ever
ever ever ever 10 years you've never had
nausea then you start eating some
bananas
some steamed potato and you get nauseous
all right just gotta
kind of be your own detective that's
number one and
and um and also keep in mind of like
medical treatments too okay keep in mind
seeing that a lot out there a lot of
people getting new medical treatments
and then
they're just getting all kinds of stuff
and then they're confused like
they don't know where that stuff's
coming from
all right
hold on you guys get some peas
in the pan here
and pathogens that are inside of us okay
just so you know
pathogens that are inside of us
streptococcus inside our gut
okay epstein-barr viruses on our nerves
once you stop feeding them stuff right
you guys
like this
once you stop feeding them right
once you stop feeding those bugs with
all that egg
and all that cheese and all that dairy
pretend this is an organic pie
pretend it's an organic pie it's still
the same you got your dairy you got your
eggs you got all that
right okay and
that's a conventional one all right it's
a conventional one
but someone might be like yeah but i
only eat organic treats i'll eat
organic pies or organic whatever and
organic cake whatever still there's
always these eggs in there there's
always these dairy and a lot of stuff
that stuff feeds bugs it feeds pathogens
it feeds viruses it feeds bacteria
and when you're doing this you're you're
starving all those bugs
you guys are actually doing this bug
starving thing okay
and those bugs are going to make you
want to eat
they're going to make you want to eat
foods you
once ate those bugs are going to make
you want to eat food
that you that that have fed them
okay so when you're eating your pizzas
that cheese on the pizza and that gluten
in the in the crust
that's feeding all your bugs keeping
them nice and happy
keeping them fat and happy those bugs
when you remove all that and you're mono
eating and then you're eating foods that
actually
help starve the bugs and help eliminate
the bugs
those bugs are gonna try to tell you to
go
and get their food so those bugs are
gonna tell you
you gotta go and find their food find
the pizza
yeah you know it's like whoa i'm on
day two the mono eating cleanse
uh-huh what
what did i
did i what
get what pizza is that my inner
consciousness telling me pizza
what is that i gotta i gotta get a pizza
i i gotta order a pizza now
hey pizza place yeah
can you just give me a i'll take cheese
and put a little pepperoni on that too
yeah pepperoni and cheese
yeah i don't know what's telling me
inside but something inside is telling
me
since i've been on this mono cleanse
something inside of me is telling me i
need a pizza so i think i'm gonna go
with that intuitive feeling
yeah i'm gonna use my intuitive eating
ability that i had
all along yeah i'm gonna eat intuitively
and i and i
and i feel there's a craving and it must
be justified and i i want a pizza with
some
with some sausage on it no i'll just go
with pepperoni
okay all right i'll wait for that pizza
are you gonna bring it okay i'll wait
okay good
i'm waiting for that pizza you guys so
hopefully we get that pizza
you know and the bugs inside of us they
want
they want those foods and so they can
tell us to get those foods that's what's
happening they can tell us to get those
foods
because once those bugs are starving
inside of us
we think it's our intuitive everyday
intuitive thing that people are
saying out there
i'm not saying people aren't intuitive
they are intuitive but when it comes
down to what they eat they're not
i'm sorry we've been poisoned so much
with all our caffeine and everything
else we don't know what we intuitively
like or not
we've been trained to like vinegar we
don't know vinegar destroys the body but
we intuitively eat it
are you kidding me like we're
intuitively eating
no sorry we're addicted to all these
poisons and we're used to eating all
these poisons and flavors and that's
what we do right
but what people completely oh the pizza
just came
okay thanks well i appreciate it oh yeah
thank you i i
that's perfect all right good all right
i just got my delivery now i'm in
i'm intuitively craving
these pizzas during my mono eating
cleanse
and so that must mean that i'm actually
i need it right
that must mean i need it because i hear
a lot of people on youtube they're like
i hear a lot of people on youtube
they're like you know like
um yeah i just you know i just eat what
my body craves i just listen to my body
and my body says
i can have that coffee and my body says
i can also have that
muffin and yeah i can have pizza on
friday night
and so i'm doing that right now you guys
what's happening is
i'm just listening to the bugs inside of
me now all those different bugs you can
call the bugs what you want
bacteria viruses whatever
i'm listening to them they want this
pizza white monster mono cleanse i'm
going to put these i'm going to tank
these pizzas later on
after i after i trick you guys out by
pretending i really like this
i'm going to tank all that pizza later
this is actually really good by the way
really good all right cooking some peas
right now
guys keep in mind
keeping that keep keep in mind that when
you get hungry enough
and you clean things up
okay and those toxins start coming out
and those bugs start dying you're gonna
want something bad
keep that in mind you're gonna want
something bad
okay
really important to know okay you're
going to want something bad
and then you're going to have old
adrenaline come out of your liver
toxins that are inside your liver the
old adrenaline
and that adrenaline has information from
any hard times you might have had
you had a breakup with the relationship
many years ago all that adrenaline that
was surging
surging through you when you had that
breakup
that adrenaline stored itself in your
cells so when you start mono eating
and that adrenaline comes out pockets of
that garbage come out
it might have information in there and
you might feel a little sad you might
feel a little emotional you might want
to go and then eat a bunch of
peanut butter and you want them
chocolate you might want to
stick a chocolate bar in a peanut butter
jar
[Music]
so this is really incredible by the way
especially when you
get rid of all that crazy food
and you give your body a chance to heal
and you start getting hungry
this this literally is so good for you
i'm steaming some peas
i'm going to move this over
what you're doing is you're stopping
from chasing the high you're not running
on adrenaline anymore
and you're not chasing the high anymore
what you're doing is you're working on
healing
and that's what's happening now in your
life when you're doing this you're
working
on healing that's where you're going now
you're going to that place and that
place is a very special place
one that you have to respect because
you're healing now and that's what's so
important
so i got some peas going these are just
about done
there we go did you guys try the pea
hummus whoever did the pea option
jenny says i've learned how to translate
my cravings
if i want fat i need calories if i want
salt i need mineral salts
incredible incredible
spoken like a season season person in
health
spoken like a true seasoned person
amazing using medical medium information
learning how to use it learning how to
use the tools so you can actually
just you know make things better that's
incredible
all right these babies are cooked up
i'm looking around for something
oh there it is so
all right let me just do a quick quick
recap
okay let's do that all right
we got your 16 to 32 ounces of lemon
water upon waking
i go with 32 ounces you got 32 ounces of
celery juice
you can do less if you want to
definitely
32 ounces is great you can do it twice a
day you do lemon water all day
celery juice all day okay keep that in
mind
then choose an option okay
banana is it banana and banana only with
lettuce
that's the option right there okay
banana lettuce
that's your option right you got that
going on
papaya and and lettuce that's another
option
then you can combine papaya and banana
papaya and banana that's another option
with lettuce all right
how great is that next you can do
steamed potato i chose the mashed potato
but you're only choosing one option
you're not doing all these different
options on the same day
i know a lot of people are and if you
are it's still amazing
it's still amazing with what you're
doing it's still great
if you're somebody that's if you're
somebody that's like mixed up with it
all
and you're like well i just had some
peas and i had some potatoes
i'm still proud of you okay and it's
still helpful
it really is it's still really helpful
all right add
out a liter of water throughout the day
sip it throw some lemon in it if you
want
you can do an optional cucumber juice at
the end of the day you could do an
optional celery juice at the end of the
day coconut water too read the book for
details
steamed potatoes and lettuce
boom or i made mashed potatoes right
okay all right
you guys
and
what i'll do is on ig i'll run these
peas through a
through the processor on ig
[Music]
you guys i'm really proud of everybody i
just want everybody to know we're day
two
of the medical medium mono cleanse
challenge make sure you
have the cleansing heal book cryptical
really is proud of everybody
i hope you guys picked up all the
different stuff i you know helped you
with today and the details
and listen to the watch the last youtube
if you can
or or wherever you can watch me on i
will see you guys on ig
i'm gonna turn tik tok back on i'll have
ig back on
in a little while and i'll have
clubhouse back on
you guys i'm gonna make p hummus on ig
in a little while love you guys
and i'll see you soon