[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
day one medical medium rage shot therapy
challenge I held my breath the entire
time
negative energy exposure right hold my
breath for two and a half minutes
whoa you guys we're here incredible when
you do the robot you can't breathe you
can't even breathe you have to hold it
the whole time as if you're underwater
it's crazy or you're gonna look like a
human and not a robot you're gonna be
like
I'm a breathing human I'm not a robot ah
instead you gotta hold your breath the
whole time can't breathe you guys
amazing we're here look
brain saver the books changing lives I'm
pumped up can't say enough about it but
it's more than that this is day one day
one of the medical medium brain shot
therapy challenge
cleanse 10 days
10 days day one what are we doing
negative energy
exposure why do we do negative energy
exposure because it's the beginning of
the cleanse and we got to make sure the
energy is right because people spew
their crap on other people they spew
their demons on other people they spew
their negative energy they spew their
anger and hate on other people right
that's what happens you can walk into a
store right after somebody was in there
and they could be somebody that's like
so negative so negative and they sit
there in the store and they talk to the
checkout person and they just spew that
negativity on that checkout person and
then you go into the store and now
you're lined up to go to that checkout
person that checkout personnel has
contamination of all this negative
energy that's how easy it could happen
and then it gets on to you it's crazy
how it works so we're doing the negative
energy exposure shot
I am pumped you received your books
incredible I have my books right here I
go everywhere with them everywhere and
if you guys could see I got my
ingredients in front of me
I got the mm-1500 on sale 20 off saves
people money saves me money because it
squeezes every last bit out of the juice
I got my books I got my information word
day one I'm gonna talk about the entry
level cleanse because that's really what
this is the entry level cleanse I'm
really excited about this you were day
one medical me and brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge so let's go into it a
little bit
so you guys I want to get into the book
come on let's do it let's do it so these
books are absolutely incredible really
I'm going to
right I just want to show you the
negative energy shot right there I want
you to take a quick look right there
check it out
negative energy exposure shot this is an
important one now here
when you take this shot have you guys
done this one whoa like because even
instead of person even if you're
somebody that
you don't let negative crap get to you
you don't let negativity get to you
you're a positive person even if you're
somebody that's like that it doesn't
mean
that there isn't something going on
because we can pick up that negative
energy everywhere in every how it's
incredible how it works
so
let's take a look here so I'm going to
medical me and brain shot therapy right
there
you guys got the book
let's do it let's just talk about it
page 445
in the medical medium brain saver book
right here page 445 right so
let's talk about a little bit medical
medium brain shot therapy offers instant
relief have you felt it yet
have you tried
the miraculous brain shot therapies yet
I know you guys are doing it many of you
guys are doing it but is it not mind
blowing like I'm talking across the
board I'm not just trying to pump this
up I'm this I'm not trying to make
something out of nothing
the power in these shots is unbelievable
I'm seeing with family friends all of it
and it's because of the information
coming from above it's not man-made it's
nobody knows nobody would know
anywhere
on this planet in the health movement
anywhere anyhow that when you put
Orange
garlic
sunflower sprouts
Sage
wheatgrass
together in a certain amount a certain
amount
and create a shot out of it nobody knows
on this planet that it actually knocks
the hell out of negative energy that's
inside of you
even protects you from negative energy
others are spewing and throwing at you
and this is just one of the shots this
is just one of the days we're day one
right now
let's see Allison says I noticed very
real and tangible results from these
shots
oh yeah and I can't wait to take this
shot down because I'm excited I want to
make this thing and I'm going to send it
down
and I can't wait I can't wait because
you know what I'm dealing with a lot of
stuff out there you guys are dealing
with a lot of stuff out there it's easy
to pick up negative energy it's easy to
get thrown
so easy
so I like this because let me tell you
something I need this shot I do you know
everybody does we all need it because
that's how this world works it's great
you just knock it out of you man knock
it away from you all of it I take this
shot before I go on to a phone call with
something that's like no fun or anything
like that I mean I just take the shot
I'm like you know what not going to let
any negative stuff get to me so
medical medium brain shot therapy offers
instant relief while you're working to
fix problems
at a deeper level in your brain but
here's how well there's the incredible
part
these medical medium shot therapies they
build on each other and they start to
heal within the very things
that they're meant to help you with
it's incredible your brain and body have
a quick response to medicinals delivered
in liquid form
your brain
by the way we're going to take brain and
we're going to juice some brain this is
a cadaver's brain and we're going to run
this through the juicer with everything
it's part of the recipe and you know I'm
kidding around
but
the brain
loves getting things that get to it fast
and the combination and what these shots
are
are designed from above
to drive right to the brain really fast
designed to be highly absorbable in the
mouth that's what it is did you hear
that you guys designed to be highly
absorbable in the mouth think about that
for a minute not everything's highly
absorbable in the mouth
not even water is highly absorbable in
the mouth did you know that like water
has a process
water itself has a process it has to
find its way into your stomach and
really get absorbed that way
these are designed to be highly
absorbable in the mouth that's the way
they're designed from above
because when you put orange with these
if you put orange and wheatgrass
together it's not going to be highly
absorbable in the mouth
it's orange wheatgrass Sage sunflower
grains garlic then
that's when something happens we don't
know we don't have the science food
science we don't know anything down here
about what happens with that but from
above
I got the promise that that will do what
it does and it does
like the medical medium books and the
information always have that's always
pulled through but this is something
really important to know
it's the combination
and what it is and then that makes the
difference
so designed to be highly absorbable in
the mouth these brain shots
valuable healing components within them
can reach the brain fast it could reach
the brain quick that's why these brain
shots also work that's a big part of it
because they're designed so when you
guys take these brain shot therapies
that it reaches the brain quickly
that's a huge huge
huge aspect of your healing that's why
we get that relief that instant relief
so important these these specially
formulated shots have the ability to
reset and rewire the brain think about
that for a little bit
do we need a rewire
do we need a reset
you could ask yourself that
because these brain shots have the
ability to rewire and reset
the incredible part about from
information from above to reset and
rewire
and then the absorption level of driving
it right in the mouth it's already
absorbing
to the brain
already absorbing to the brain
just incredible when you think about it
okay these specially formulated shots
have the ability to reset and rewire the
brain but get this you guys to shock it
out of patterns while at the same time
reducing triggers you guys hear about
triggers you can be triggered easy
and when you have the negative energy or
you're getting negative energy from
somebody else you can trigger really
easy
it's easy to be triggered
and the thing is is these brain shot
therapies are all anti-trigger
that's what they are it's another reason
why they work
really work though
like with confidence they work
with Precision they work
Angela I felt that change explanation
points I gave the anger and the mood
shifter shots to my husband that was
having a bad night and it completely
changed his mood from Angry to happy and
joking incredible
here's the amazing part
it's ingredients from the Earth
but no one knew that there has to be one
ingredient that works with another
ingredient nobody knew that I would
never know that in a million years
nobody does there's no Alchemist there's
no person in health that would ever know
this nobody knows that when you take
that Sage
and you take that and you combine Sage
with wheatgrass
and then you combine those sunflower
greens with the wheatgrass and the sage
and then you combine that garlic with
the sunflower greens the sage and the
wheatgrass and then you combine that
orange or Tangerine juice with it nobody
knew ever
that that would knock the heck out of
negative energy
or any of the other brain shot recipes
were the anger
or the EMF exposure or the mold exposure
are all the different ones Kim says I
was already feeling a change after doing
the nerve gut acid stabilizer after just
two days in a row and that one by the
way
that one just compiles on itself and
just gets stronger and stronger and
stronger
on with the miracle of that you know
honestly
like when I was telling Spirit of
Kardashians like these are Miracle shots
these are Miracle shots
really really profound
so it's about anti-triggers it's about
shifting and rewiring with this but we
would never know no one would know that
these are you you cannot just put Foods
together and think that it's going to
stop a trigger
but that's why the information from
above is so critical and how this works
it's really really special
so
I'm in the brain saver book
I want to read a little bit about the
cleanses aspect of this and we're doing
that we're 10 days we're 10 days but
we're on day one and we're doing 10 days
of this
I want to dedicate my time my energy I
want to work with you guys on this this
is a free cleanse
this is a free free free cleanse and I
want to dedicate my time my energy and
everything I got in this is what I want
to do I'll do the robot again I'll do
anything anything I am at your service
these cleanses are imperative for what's
to come in this world I'm reading Right
Out of Rain saver
the onslaught of domestic chemical
warfare
in our homes in our schools in our
institutions in our society today has
reached
an unbelievable level never seen before
in our history
catechismic proportions when you embark
on these cleanse options you're using
your free will we're using our brain
where does your free will come from
did you ever ask that question did
anybody ever know you've heard of having
free will right but does anybody ever
know or anybody know where your free
will actually comes from where
it comes from that Consciousness and
subconsciousness connecting to your soul
and it comes from this right here this
baby right here
it comes from this this is where it
comes from right there
foreign
anybody sure coming right up lots of
free will right here
does anybody have any free will yes I
got some free will it's coming right up
it's my Consciousness and
subconsciousness and soul all combined
that's my free will right there
oh my God I'm like this and I haven't
even taken the brain shot yet
when you embark on these cleanse options
you're using your free will and your
intention to clean and project the organ
that Harbors the knowledge of the past
this baby right here Harbors the
knowledge from the past and the present
do you have do you guys have the brain
saver books they're 40 off right now at
amazon.com us
both the brand saver books I'm just
letting you guys know
get them for gifts friends whoever
that price is just unbelievable
and when you read the words in these
books the scripture you'll just be mind
blown
here's here's what blows me away right
here okay
think about this you're using your free
will to clean and project
present
past and future toxins
check this out you're using your free
will to clean and project the organ that
Harbors the knowledge to from the past
and the present
and soon to be the future of your life
and harbors your soul you're cleaning
out the home that holds your soul think
about that when you're doing the brain
shot therapies and you're doing the
brain shot therapy cleanse we're day one
right now you're cleaning the home
that Harbors the soul do you want the
home dirty where the soul is sitting you
guys can sign up by the way
if you haven't signed up yet and you're
just coming on here we're in the brain
shot therapy cleanse challenge right
here and guess what it's for you guys
medicalmedium.com so you can download
your information that you need the PDF
that tells you the free pdf about your
grocery shopping list and everything
else
right and then the mm 1500 900 they're
on sale right now 20 off and they
squeeze the juice out of things no no
juicers that I've ever found do so it
saves you money
but think about this
I'm just asking guys if you got a second
it's so fun
that's your home
of your soul
there it is
so are we going to have that home dirty
and nasty
and filled with all kinds of stuff
including negative energy which we're
gonna knock the crap out of
you got negative energy inside of you
around you we're gonna knock the crap
out of the negative energy when we do
these shots coming up
like I can't wait to make that shot
knowledge is in the home your soul is in
this home
and we're gonna clean it up the brain
shot therapy cleanses are Beyond just
physical it's metaphysical and that's
what's incredible you guys think
that this incredible information that
comes from above is just for physical
it's for it's for metaphysical it's for
Spiritual it's not just physical it's
why people have instant relief and
results Beyond no other because it's all
of that
it goes beyond just physical removing
poisons from the brain opens the door
for your Consciousness and
subconsciousness to purify
how insane is that allowing you to
achieve enlightenment in a world of
toxic corruption that keeps us from
Enlightenment how do we achieve
enlightenment if we have so much crap up
here and so much crap in here
and that's the home for our soul when we
purify and we clean and we cleanse and
we shock that junk out of our brain we
are creating Enlightenment we're opening
the door so Enlightenment can even
happen right there
it's incredible
Enlightenment check this out
wow
Enlightenment is not about being
all-knowing
Enlightenment is the freedom to be at
peace because you have full control over
what resides in your brain
Enlightenment isn't just about all
knowing
it isn't just about knowing everything
that's not what enlightenment is it's
about having the freedom
the freedom inside our brain
the peace and knowing we have full
control empowerment Enlightenment is
full empowerment when we have full
control of what's Happening inside our
brain
that's powerful
since we don't have control about what
resides around us to the world think
about it you guys we don't control
everything that's happening around us in
the world we don't but we can control
What's Happening Here
and we can use our free will
and we can actually clean and purify the
home in which our soul resides in
this stuff is deep
you know I was getting the information
from Spirit of compassion I was just I
was trying to learn as fast as I can
learn
some of you guys probably learn it
faster
seriously
when you think about it some of you guys
are are reading this and like oh my God
these cleanses purify your brain Temple
you are removing the poisons
from your brain that take away your
Clarity we lose our Clarity when we got
so much poison inside of us and we also
lose our Clarity when we have things
like the negative energy also inside of
us spiritual and physical these shots
are for Spiritual and physical that's
what's incredible about it all when you
even think about it how incredible is
that
pink so so if I don't have all the
ingredients is it not worth doing them
yeah do you do have to have the
ingredients
someone takes an orange and they juice
it with some garlic it's not going to do
what the shot says it does
and that's okay hang around tomorrow we
got nine more days of this we got nine
more days
of the medical medium
brain shot therapy challenge cleanse
nine more days so if you don't have your
stuff now that's okay hang out with us
because we're gonna do this I'm excited
there's 30 different brain shot therapy
options in the books 30. we're doing a
10 day entry level cleanse
and you can do that while you're eating
whatever you're eating you can do that
while you're doing other medical medium
tools you can just do it but this is so
exciting
oh whoa whoa whoa
whoa
you're intuitive
psychic telepathic Clairvoyant skills
will start to surface your your
you guys you're intuitive
psychic
telepathic Clairvoyant skills will start
to surface
you know one thing that's incredible
about when I was taking the information
from above about these brain shots
when SOC told me that and I remember
writing that down I was like your
you mean them
I was like them
I just want to make that clear
and spirit of compassion said yes you're
not me I said not me them
of course them
I said okay okay I'm sorry I'm getting
the information down and it says in this
book you're intuitive so you're
intuitive you're psychic that's right
all you guys all your psychic abilities
all of you
you're telepathic that's right you don't
think you're telepathic all your
telepathic right and you're Clairvoyant
skills
will grow
by the way sunflower sprouts you can use
another micro green Sprout like Spirit
of compassion says that line can be that
Line's okay right there so if you can't
get the sunflower Sprout you can use
another micro green Sprout until you can
find a sunflower Sprout they're easy
also to grow yourself sunflower sprouts
on your counter
but there's there's very little leeway
in these shots that's the one of the
only places where you can have that
little
curve
because there's something in a sunflower
Sprout that really amplifies it but a
micro green still has enough of that
chemical compound structure but it
doesn't happen like that with all the
shots and ingredients they have to be
what they have to be
yes you your Clairvoyant skills you're
intuitive you're psychic your telepathic
skills will start to surface when you're
doing these brain shot there because you
do these brain shot therapies on a
regular basis and all of that starts to
come out and starts to surface
oh man
you will be able to see truth easily and
clearly and be able to express yourself
increase creativity how cool is that
inexperienced joy in the simplest things
that others would not realize are joyful
that's the whole thing experiencing Joy
on any level in ways that others would
never think is even joyful that takes
you to another level right there that
starts to happen when you're doing these
brain shot Therapies
you can use a micro green if you can't
find the sunflower Sprout but really you
have to eventually get the sunflower
Sprout and you can use another Sprout if
you really have to
if you can't get a micro green but
that's the only way we have for the
negative energy shot
it's just incredible
ready for this
you will open your third eye and develop
your skills as a seer
when you rid yourself of poisons from
the industries that were purposely
placed in our brains
to keep us in Chains and keep us down
you know something what I heard that
information and I put it in the books
I was just I was just sitting there at
my office desk and it was I think it was
like 2 30 in the morning
and spirit of compassion was dropping
that on me and I was just like I can't
go to bed I have to I have to keep on
writing this down because when I heard
that
you will open your third eye with these
brain shot therapy cleanses you will
open your third eye with these brain
shot therapy cleanses
and I was I was just saying the spirit
thank you
thank you that's what I said you will
open your third eye and develop your
skills as a Seer when you rid yourself
of poisons from the industries that were
purposely placed in your brain to keep
you in Chains and keep us all down
when I put that in there I was just
I was in Oh My God moment you know aha
moments
I call them oh my God moments
the physical benefits are truly special
and Powerful with the brain shot
therapies with the brain shot therapy
cleanses you embark on removing toxins
and poisonous chemicals from the brain
that should have never been there to
begin with
foreign
I mean
I don't even know what to say
these anti-pathogenic cleanses because
they're anti-pathogen by the way are
designed for what we deal with on a
daily basis everything from deficiencies
whoa burnout to the brain acids to the
brain emotional injuries to the brain
emotional injuries to the brain
yeah how many people walk around with
metaphysically and physically and how
can we shake out of that how can we
actually correct that we can that's the
whole point
these cleanses are designed
for many different symptoms conditions
diseases
the advanced in high-powered options
have the ability to get rid of a hundred
symptoms someone may have
absolutely incredible
see
I couldn't wait for these to be here for
us and this is a very special time
because it's not about me it's about you
guys that's the whole point it's like
you want to create the nicest birthday
party for somebody you can ever create a
surprise birthday party and you work so
hard at it and so hard at it and you
just want the day for that person who
you made the greatest surprise party
ever that you can ever imagine you got
everything ready all the cakes
all the different things all the stuff
on all the balloons everything
and you got it already and that person
walks in and they're surprised so much
surprised but that's what it's about
and it's that feeling you get I want
everybody to have this information and
get surprised when everything starts to
kick in like this
right
so I'm talking about entry level that's
where I am now this is the brain saver
books if you just got here you have if
you just arrived and maybe you didn't
sign up for this cleanse it's free
anyway and you just arrive welcome to
the medical medium
brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
I'm honored to have you here truly if
you got here and you're somebody that's
like whoa who is this guy
entry-level brain shot therapy cleanse
and we're doing the negative energy
exposure shot
now in the entry level by the way if you
have your books you guys I'm on page 520
of of a well over 600 page book
and the entry-level brain shot therapy
cleanse says add these steps to your
normal eating routine
drink one brain shot per day
you can choose whatever brain shot you
want to choose we're doing the negative
energy exposure shot today and we're
going to do nine different shots for the
next nine days this is the tenth day
you have your choice of doing the entry
level at 10 days 20 days or 30 days do
you dare to do 20 days or 30 days
in in this cleanse challenge you have
the option of two or three of the brain
shots daily the same brain shots if
you're doing the negative exposure shot
because that's what I'm gonna do you can
do it now with me now boom that's one
time I'm gonna make another later boom
let it build on itself I'm gonna make
another one later boom I'm gonna do
three for myself
I'm excited about that truly
the negative energy exposure shot is
what I'm doing today you guys are doing
that with me if you're in the cleanse
it's a great way to start the 10-day
cleanse because we're gonna rock all
that negative energy out of us because
we can collect it anywhere you don't
think you can collect it
here's how it works
you may not be the original source of
negative energy
no
are you the original source of negative
energy no
you're not
someone else can be the original source
of negative energy
and their whole life's purpose is
disputing negative energy you guys don't
know but that's possible
an industry spreads negative energy a
person can spread negative energy
any kind of entity or force can spread
negative energy
a group of people can you guys know this
a group of people can just boom boom
boom get together even on social media
and they can spread so much negative
energy it's unbelievable look what has
happened when I put out my PCOS post
like the true cause or my true cause of
something else like ADHD look at it the
people they come in like wolves and
vultures and they're just spewing
negativity because they want to stop
everybody from healing right either way
you you may not be and you're not the
source of negative energy
but other sources out there are the
source of negative energy you have to
figure this out you have to know this
you can be surrounded by negative energy
you can be surrounded by other people's
demons
where they got a demon going on inside
their head and they're saying rotten
terrible things to you and they're
texting rotten terrible things to you
but it's important to understand
that you are not the source and the
creator of negative energy someone else
could be something else could be
but you need to protect yourself and
being able to actually shed any that
could be inside of you Susan says I
tried the burnout stabilizer and it was
mind-blowing
I felt the electricity running through
my brain it felt like my brain was
working at a higher level Susan
because it does after that because it
does work at a higher level after that
shot that's the difference that's how
incredible it is if you guys just came
on here this is day one the medical
medium
brain saver
challenge but it's the brain shot
therapy cleanse aspect of it and that's
what's exciting about it so let's talk
about a little bit more we're in the
entry level
optional you can incorporate as many
other medical medium tools and recipes
as desired
get ready for this
try to drink a minimum of 50 ounces of
water throughout the day while you're
doing this so all 10 days
try to drink a minimum of 50 50 hour 50
ounces of water
throughout the day if you can
that would be really good this is the
entry level
brain shot therapy cleanse that we're
doing right now we're starting with one
shot and we're going to do that shot we
can do it a couple times a day once a
day you can do it three times a day I'm
gonna do three times today myself
so drink one brain shot per recipe this
is the recipe we're choosing the
negative energy exposure
your choice to do this entry level brain
shot therapy cleanse 10 days 20 days 30
days
the challenge is a 10-day challenge
starts today
and there's more in-depth details here
in the brain saver books
so there's one right there there's more
in-depth detail in the brain saver box
incredible
okay
now what's important okay here's a
detail that's critical don't drink all
your water your 50 ounces of water after
you've
shot you know taken that shot down
don't take the shot down wait 15 minutes
wait 20 minutes
even a half an hour is fine
you send your shot down don't just all
of a sudden start drinking water right
with your shot don't do that don't
dilute it
important detail
because I want you guys to experience
what it has to offer
the power it has
incredible
now
why did I pick the negative energy
exposure shot
because I want you to be able to feel
what happens when you release anything
we collect
because we collected it's easy
so there's other reasons let's go into
the negative energy exposure shot now
[Music]
lost my music
all right
let's go into this now
let's find our negative energy shot
now let's go and let's talk about this
for a little bit this is actually
interesting
that was a little intermission
exposure shots that's the category we're
in right now we're in exposure shots
okay
negative energy exposure shot is the one
we're doing it's day one right now
let's talk about this these exposure
shots can be administered before an
exposure during an exposure shortly
after an exposure or even days weeks or
months after an exposure here's the
thing you can have exposure to some
serious negative energy not even know it
now things are going wrong in your life
it's like you're just you're off beat
something's going wrong
you don't remember the negative energy
that you've been exposed to that was two
weeks ago
that was three weeks ago
but it hangs with us
so if you do know what exposure you had
you're like oh my God that person I
talked to they were just like
they had to dump all their stuff on me
it was like I had to absorb it all and
then they finally were cleared but what
did they dump on me did they dump all
this negative energy and they dumped it
all on me and I took it all in
well that was two weeks ago though well
you can still do this negative energy
exposure shot
you can do it shortly after an exposure
say you're driving a car and someone's
like flips you the bird
and throws your game off
right you're driving down the road
someone gives you the finger right some
road rage happens or anything see
someone cuts you off because they're
psycho in the moment like something's
wrong with them and they just they're
just angry or something happens and they
cut you off and throws you off you
almost get into like a little car
accident
it's time to do that shot
Sammy says oh my God I'm gonna need this
shot 20 times a day when I go home for
the holidays laugh out loud actually
that's actually a really good time for
the negative energy exposure shot
because I hear it all the time people go
home for the holidays people come over
family comes over and then your siblings
are all negative and stuff or somebody's
all negative right and you just you just
need to protect yourself that's a major
exposure so you want to do something
about it
yeah
so I'm going through the exposure shots
now now there's 10 different exposure
shots to choose from but we are at the
negative energy exposure shot right here
I'm excited
because I'm gonna start making it
and then we can talk a little bit about
other stuff about negative energy while
we're drinking it so let's do it guys
brand saver books right here
I'm nervous I'm actually nervous
my god I've never been really nervous
but why am I so nervous
it's crazy
but I am
actually nervous
I'm nervous because I don't know what
negative energy I might have collected
because I'm dealing with so much stuff
but man I'm gonna see it leave and I'm
excited so you're gonna juice the
ingredients in order that's an important
way to do this now if for some reason
you skip a beat and I want you to know
this if you skip a beat
and you juice it out of order
we're still okay
but you do want to juice it in order if
you can that does help okay so it starts
out with a quarter cup of tightly packed
fresh Sage I'm just going to gauge it
because I usually have my own methods to
gauge you know what's a quarter cup and
everything else so I have some Sage
right here
here it is
so I'm going to do is get my quarter cup
ready
so I'm taking the leaves
with the little stems
Lisa do you use the celery attachment
with the mm-1500 for these shots I most
certainly do
you guys this is 20 off CMM 1500
I'm just going to mention it for a
moment because the reason why I leave
the celery juice attachment on in this
because it squeezes every last drop out
of that it extracts those phytochemical
compounds like no other juicer does
that's why these juicers are that
amazing if you're looking for a juicer
is any of your juicers on sale now I
just saw Vivi ask the question yes the
mm-1500 mm-900 on sale right now okay
check out the link you'll see the link
in the description
this is the Omega mm 1500 that's the one
I'm using now what I like about these
juicers by the way and I just I'll just
tell you real quick is they save me
money when I'm juicing they save you
money when you're juicing I work with
them by the way you guys know that and
because they put out the best juicer
there ever was it never is that's why um
I know people be like oh I well I like
my just that's fine use any juicer you
have I'm only saying that because they
squeeze so you get more of what you're
trying to do if you're trying to make a
brain shot or celery juice or anything
else that this is this squeezes it out
the attachment is so powerful that's why
and the whole system is so amazing
anyway
on sale by the way if you're looking for
a juicer if you got your juicer just use
your juicer whatever's going on all
right you guys
so I'm gonna do a quarter cup of the
sage tightly packed grabbing a little
bit more
right here
I'd say it's about quarter cup right
there and we're making a shot so I'm
going to stick that in here
the next ingredient is going to be the
quarter the sorry the half cup of
tightly packed sunflower greens
so I'll get that ready as I'm running
this
and then we'll keep on moving through it
all right I'm gonna fire this up
and you can use the Sprouts as well I
talked about that earlier get ready
dropping a sage in there first
boom
now I'm doing quarter cup tightly packed
sunflower greens if you want if you you
could use a
I mean a half cup you can use a micro
green
you can use a sprout if you don't have a
sunflower green but that's the only
leeway we have in this this combination
or it's not going to work
so I'm knocking this in so a half a cup
of those
I'm gonna put a little bit more because
I want to when you tightly pack them
it's a whole other game
okay next ingredient
wheatgrass so here's how it works
I'm using Frozen wheatgrass
for this one
the best frozen wheatgrass is on my
directory at medicalmedium.com and just
letting you know
and I'm adding it at the end
okay if you have fresh wheatgrass like
this I want to show you
you can juice the fresh wheatgrass right
here
so I got the fresh wheatgrass
so if you guys have that on hand use
that for sure
I have a frozen option too because what
happens is most of you and I want to
just talk about this for a second most
of you don't have the option for
wheatgrass for fresh wheatgrass like I
do you don't have that option
so it's so what you want to do is you
want to use a frozen one the best frozen
one like I said is on my directory at
medicalmedium.com
okay now we're going into it half a
clove of garlic
so I'm just gonna clean this garlic up
for a second knock out a clove
foreign
got a little knife behind here I'm just
getting it ready
nice
small garlic cloves so I'm going to cut
this one in half because this was a
really big garlic clove dropping that in
this is the negative energy exposure
shot if you guys just got here it's the
brain shot therapy cleanse we're day one
anybody new coming on I want you to know
what's up
okay if you don't have the wheatgrass
okay the week the fresh wheat grass
and you can you can definitely use the
Frozen for sure
but
you have to have all these ingredients
when you do this so you can always try
to get the ingredients later on try to
you know search for them and make sure
you have what you need to do this
if you don't have it so we're gonna go
with an orange
or Tangerine so you've got the option of
orange tangerine
I'm going to do a tangerine in here
I'm gonna peel it actually
so it's one one to two peeled tangerines
I'm gonna pop one in there
maybe another one
look in the book it'll say still make
the shot if you don't have
the wheatgrass
but at least you know what you're
building to and what you're looking for
[Music]
all right
we got what we need here
so you stir it
when it's ready
put it through a strainer you know like
you got a little mesh strainer there's a
strainer that comes with the mm 1500
right here
up the rest of that one in a little bit
okay I'm excited you guys this is the
negative energy exposure shot
if you have the Frozen wheatgrass juice
stir it in at the end and that's what
I'm gonna do
incredible
[Music]
Anthony if if I can't get organic
ingredients still do it yes still do it
absolutely
100 still do it
all right
there's my shot glass right there but
I'm not ready yet just getting it
getting the shot glass ready so I'm
going to stir my frozen wheatgrass
in here
we go
[Music]
getting ready
I don't know how much negative energy I
might have collected
it's been a hard week
a lot of pushback a lot of throwback
when you're healing people in the world
[Music]
[Applause]
I got shot filled up
are you guys ready you doing it with me
[Music]
[Applause]
sit with it for a second
did you already send us down Spirit of
compassion just told me a bunch of you
guys already sent yours down
you already send it down that's okay
it's hitting you right you feel it
[Music]
just give it a little time
you feel it
because I always feel it when I do it
you had yours before you started
[Music]
do you feel that you feel the tangles
you feel that
[Music]
push that negative energy away push it
away gone
it's not even gonna come back gone you
can't come back that negative energy
that was around you you're pushing it
away
bartender give me another
oh my God that's not an aha moment
that's an oh my God moment
that even might be an oh my God moment
foreign
that's what I'm talking about
and you can feel it just give it a
moment
it's potent I'm going to tell you right
now that is so potent
truly potent
I'm gonna drink my other two I'm gonna
make two more later now if you want
let's talk about some options
this feels so good it feels so good it's
why
that's why I've been just walking around
with these
because
that's why I take these everywhere I
take them into the bathroom
take them to the kitchen of course
I have them in the bedroom
I just have to have them with me
incredible wait 15 to 30 minutes before
you do any kind of food eating or water
drinking wait a little bit wait 15
minutes give it time let it go to the
brain and that's what it's doing
I could feel it right away it absorbs
into the mouth because of the
ingredients and what they are and the
amounts that they are
they enter into the blood vessels quick
right into the blood vessels they get to
the brain fast
and they're working on the physical and
metaphysical aspect of your life of your
brain and your body
they're working on your soul and your
subconscious mind and conscious mind
that's what they're doing
when these brain shots go in they absorb
quickly it's how they work
and then the combination of what they
are well that's age
combination of what they are
allows for high absorption rates
into the bloodstream up into the brain
look I'm whispering now
I'm not even yelling anymore I'm
whispering what did that shot do to me
I'm actually whispering
incredible
when I think about it
absolutely incredible
it's a moment of silence for just a
couple of seconds because
now I really feel it even kicking in
more
and more
absolutely
profound
[Music]
by the way
this brain saver
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge is free
we're due in 10 days
this was day one
we have nine days of this what's gonna
happen
I'm doing three of these shots a day now
if you need to juice the shots all at
once like one at a time while you're
doing it so you juice one at a time and
you do it all at once
or you're juicing them one at a time and
you save them in your refrigerator
throughout the day you can
you can save them in your freezer if you
really have to
it's something you can do as well
I'm gonna juice three times today myself
I'm gonna make this shot with what you
see in front of me right here
and I'm gonna do it again two more times
today
have you tried the brain shots how did
it make you feel did you try the
negative energy exposure shot just now
please share on social media you guys
tag at Medical medium
what was your experience what was the
results did you feel the negative energy
shift did you feel the negative energy
lift
do you feel more empowered and stronger
around negative people later if you run
into somebody who's negative do you feel
more empowered and stronger
please share your experiences if you can
that would be incredible please say it's
the medical medium negative exposure
shot too if you can as well so others
know what negative energy shot you're
even talking about please share on
social media tag at medicalmedium.com
Medical medium sorry and hashtag medical
medium so I can see both you tagging and
hashtagging so I can then see and share
them
because that's how it works you got the
books today amazing
you guys I'm so excited about sharing
this experience in life in this lifetime
now knowing
that we're doing something for our brain
that nobody could even imagine because
it's information above that no one
understands if you if you doubt the
information from above fine try it
anyway try it anyway
I beg of you
to get a copy
of both books brain saver and protocols
if you don't have
the money for the books
go to the library get them all for free
I don't care
I just need you to have this powerful
information I'm desperately needing you
to have
the work from above because as a
messenger I have to do everything I can
to spread the word so you can heal
the brain shot therapy cleanses are on
another level
you will experience them as you guys
already have
anybody new
to this information I'm just going to
give you a quick for warning
they work
and what that means
is its results that happen quick and
it's going to catch you off guard
because you never expected them to work
giving you the forewarning to anybody
new or anybody who tries these so you're
not caught off guard
whew
[Music]
see you guys tomorrow
are you gonna be there tomorrow
day two
of the medical medium brain shot
challenge therapy cleansed
day two
I mean we're doing betrayal and broken
trust stabilizer have you been betrayed
has your trust been broken
foreign
my God
this negative energy exposure shot
has your trust ever been broken have you
been let down have you been betrayed
divorce breakups bad news
people letting you down sometime did it
ever happen in your life well guess what
not only did you knock out the negative
energy but you're doing the Betrayal and
broken trust stabilizer tomorrow day two
and we're gonna knock the crap out of
that stuff
so that that betrayal doesn't sit inside
of you guys and fester for years and
years and years because the brain shot
therapy cleanses work then we're gonna
knock that betrayal out
and we're gonna send it packing
[Music]
I love you guys
I will see you tomorrow
[Music]
fasten your seat belts
you're going for a ride
the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse ride
instant relief absorbs quick drives into
the brain
get yourself the books if you can you
know what you do if you need a juicer
it's the mm-1500 right 20 off
Incredible One squeezes everything out
of it
and the books are 40 off amazon.com us
26.29 and their massive books