of course not
no just live our lives do our thing
whatever
no one gets radiation exposure and no no
no that's not true
radiation exposure is a big one
people are saturated with radiation
exposure
people are glowing with radiation that's
the reality that's the truth but we
don't want to believe that or even think
it's even possible we don't want to
think it's possible to have radiation
exposure how's it even possible
there's no way when you meet somebody do
you go hey how's your radiation exposure
today
No No One's Gonna Do That
but yet yeah there's radiation exposure
anyway what is this day 15
of the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge we're doing radiation
exposure shot
right there this is an important one
because so many people
are exposed and nothing gets done about
it
nothing at all gets done about it ever
and the radiation accumulates do you
think the radiation exposure you get
just goes away
no it doesn't go away
it stays in US
it radiates out of us a lifetime we
collect radiation
why does it matter
because it affects our health it's part
of the death by a Thousand Cuts here on
planet Earth
it's one of the death by a Thousand Cuts
so I want to read a little bit about it
so let's get into it but first of all I
just want to say this is day 16.
of the medical mean brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge I don't know if you
caught me there I said 15 earlier day
16.
is the radiation exposure shot that we
have right here let's get into it and
let's talk about radiation if you guys
don't mind 237 do you have your brain
saver book
do you know what page we're on
if you don't have the book still hang
out let's do it let's talk about
radiation
if you do have the book Incredible
amazing
radiation and EMF section but I'm just
going to talk about radiation today page
237 if you're worried about EMF
Incredible Book to get information about
EMF exposure
so right there it is friend saver
common medical and transportation
technology
airplane travel
people get radiation from airplane
travel right but not just airplane
travel
because they're in an airplane
that's one way
people get radiation exposure because
radiation is in the atmosphere
from World War II
from when the bomb was dropped
froshima Hiroshima the bomb
that propelled
a massive amount
of radiation into our atmosphere it's
still there it's still floating around
when you fly in a plane
and the plane goes up
and it's in it's at that altitude
it is flying through the radiation
and yes we get exposure just from that
alone
another form of airplane travel we're
going to talk about and another form
we're going to talk about too but just
go through the basics airplane travel
x-rays
have you had an x-ray in your life when
was it you broke your ankle when you
were 13 years old
that radiation never went away
CT computerized tomography scans
p-e-t
position emission tomography scans
fluoroscopy so many people are still
getting fluoroscopy
MRI
magnetic resonance imaging
did I just say something stupid
I said something really stupid right
I must be a total dumbass
big time
did I just say MRI and radiation I must
not know what I'm talking about
I'm probably just one of those stupid
people in alternative medicine that
don't know anything I guess
up just screwed up bad
I put in the book here
MRI magnetic resonance imaging
guess I'm that dumb why would I put that
in there when that's not radiation what
was I thinking
a total dumbass
but guess what
it is radiation there is radiation
exposure
MRIs you get radiation exposure
fact you get radiation exposure
with MRIS
incredible right yeah
brain Savers info is amazing
all right
food and water supply we get radiation
from food and water supply
common nuclear exposure current nuclear
weapons exposure and current nuclear
plant exposure need I say this but
nuclear testing is still happening
they still
test nuclear weapons
they still create nuclear weapons
the amount of exposure going into the
atmosphere and into the
environment alone
from where they're building nukes is
unbelievable Untold as far as how much
exposure
I'd hate to be one of those guys right
that's
helping to build one of those bombs and
I'm wearing a hazmat suit and I'm
walking around with nuclear rods
it's like no don't worry don't worry you
got your suit on you're safe those guys
live about five years and then they just
exchange them and put new guys in
continual atmospheric Fallout from past
nuclear disasters Chernobyl anybody
it's still admitting
radiation everywhere right
Fukushima still emitting radiation every
day everywhere
every day it's just going into our
atmosphere every day but we don't have
radiation exposure on any level
nuclear test sites
all right are we having fun yet I might
have to have
a little sip here of lemon balm tea
but here's the way I do my lemon balm
tea now I want to pop a little bit more
in here because I kind of need this
right now I need a commentative
I actually need a cognitive when I'm
reading about this and talking about
this because there's a part of you that
gets so pissed off
that this stuff happens in the world
and no one has control over it nobody
has control over this crap
it's actually demented right isn't why
would we do this
anyway I'm putting some lemon balm
that's the
imagery lemon balm incredible stuff
so if you guys don't mind I'm popping it
in there that's my lemon balm tea it's
way way more potent this way by far
hands down is using the lemon balm
instead of using like tea or whatever
oh
um I just need a commentive for my
nerves
and you guys know I endorse them Reggie
because it's the greatest stuff out
there
um
I just got to get a little in me I'm
sorry about that
this this actually topic always bothers
me you know how there's certain topics
that bother people
radiation is one that actually bothers
me like it just bothers me personally
like I feel
I feel like
I guess you would say just frustrated
about it because we're talking about
like Untold damage on this planet that's
just happening every day and no one's
talking about it they talk about like
climate change and everything they don't
talk about this this should be talk
about every minute it's insane
Smith and pepper says I made my grandma
the trauma shock and lost shot after my
grandpa passed away yesterday
I'm so sorry to hear that I didn't tell
her what it was for after she drank it
she took a big sigh and said that was
just what I needed
Smith and pepper thank you for letting
us all know uh truly truly heart pours
out to you and your family
I think when it comes down to the
radiation exposure it's one of the more
I don't know it affects me emotionally
because I know on a larger scale and
spirit of compassion knows on a larger
scale of the kind of damage that's
hidden away and tucked away
so we're brainwashed and conditioned on
this planet and we're brainwashed and
conditioned to not realize
that all the countries that are building
nukes
that all the plants that have like blown
up like Fukushima Chernobyl whatever
the bomb that was dropped Hiroshima
right
all of this is still spreading untold
amounts of radiation around the planet
and the atmosphere right
and then the nuclear testing untold
amounts and so
why do you think in the U.S alone nobody
owns the land
eighty percent of the entire United
States is off limits to even step on
what same thing around the world
80 of all the other countries land you
can't step on
it doesn't exist where it's not supposed
to exist why
interesting
all right so
Let's uh let's roll let's talk about
this stuff a little bit examples of
radiation exposure so let's head into
this area
I need a little bit more lemon balm
there's some topics that just really get
me
that's one of them
anyway
it's the vemergy it's the best stuff out
there
all right so examples of radiation
exposure
the obvious sources of radiation
exposure are dental exams
Jovana Valencia
I passed I get passed off too is it
pissed off
you know what you um I get pissed off to
aw right there with you where's my lemon
balm tea and Bemidji lemon balm 2.
I have to get some in me
just Elaine good to see you love Emoji
there's a lot to love with with that
company it's just unbelievable what they
do no one can touch what they do it's
just incredible
the obvious sources of radiation
exposure are dental exams we know that
right
even digital ones or the panorama you go
into the panorama
you go in there you bite onto this right
it's like they put a little plastic
thing on there and you walk up to it
right okay I'm standing here oh all
right
all right all right all right we're
gonna clean it out
[Music]
[Applause]
all right put a new wrapper on for the
next person put a new plastic wrap on
there for the next person
that tasted pretty good though
oh there's a celery stuff
can't turn down a celery stick piece
I need to trace mineral salts
intuitively
because I'm talking about radiation and
nuclear waste and all that I needed
some Trace mineral salts and I needed a
combative which is the Bemidji lemon
balm
musette says where can I get the Lemon
Ball
and I do that's the vimergy Lemon Ball
these in Victor I Amazon Mary e r g
y.com
check it out check out the company no
one touches their stuff it's not only
potent but it's clean but what I mean
clean I mean real real real real real
pure like no other
there's a whole bunch of reasons why I
can't go into it right now because I
don't have the time I have to just focus
on what we're doing with radiation but
by far the reason why I support these
guys with every fiber in my being and
soul is because of what they do and what
they've done with their products
I mean if I told you like and you you
learned about how and why you'd just be
like Blown Away
all right
Trace mineral salts cluster sodium
cluster salts for my brain accommodave
for my brain and nervous system please
thank you
the obvious source of radiation exposure
from Dental exams I just gave you the
demonstration
x-rays that's another one too
get a chest x-ray yeah
of course in other Medical Imaging
such as CT scans and even to the lesser
degree MRIs which still has radiation
I'm not a stupid ass after all it is a
radiation exposure I know people will
argue about magnetic resonance in
imaging uh I'm sorry you but it actually
admits radiation
sorry to tell you I mean that's what I
mean people don't realize this right
now what's interesting too is x-rays
if you go and you get a chest x-ray
somebody stands there they're going to
get chest sex right right they put the
apron on the apron is not covering all
the rest of their body properly the
apron is not covering everything the
chest x-ray is centered here right but
it still spreads out everywhere so it's
like when we get a chest x-ray we're
getting hit everywhere regardless
yeah
even CT scans
or frequent dental work that exposure
can build up and have a more extreme
effect over time in our life
our brains sustain a milder effect from
the everyday radiation we're exposed to
from plane flights
cell phones and other devices
contaminated food and water
being near someone who just got an x-ray
or other Medical Imaging tests and I
just want to go into that a little bit
if someone had an x-ray
and we're close to them if you go to the
doctor's office
and three people in the waiting room had
recent CT scans and x-rays
and MRIS
they're radiating
so when you're in that room with them
you're getting that radiation if you go
to the dental office and someone just
had the Panorama they just had all the
digital x-rays
and they're sitting next to you in the
dental office and the seat next to you
you're actually getting their radiation
it's it's incredible how it works
I don't usually say that
let's hope that doesn't become a habit
I pick up and start doing habits like
that our brain sustain milder effects
from everyday radiation we're exposed to
from plane flights cell phones and other
devices contaminated food and water
being near someone who just got an x-ray
or other Medical Imaging tests in the
continual atmospheric Fallout from past
nuclear disasters such as Fukushima
there's also Fallout from current day
nuclear testing and nuclear weapons
developing of which were unaware of
climate climate
climate nuclear production
production in everywhere new clip in
every freaking country nuclear
production that's what they're doing how
about that and how much that's causing
but no people like climate climate
it's like nothing is what it seems in
this world
nothing
there's also Fallout from current day
nuclear testing like I said nuclear
weapons development of which we're
unaware plus nuclear plants leak in
acceptable amount of radiation nuclear
plants leak
they're allowed to leak
because they're not fixable
nuclear plants aren't fixable
I can't fix them well we're gonna shut
down that plant and then we're gonna
re-modify it and redo
the lead lining that surrounds it we're
going to redo that plant and you can't
redo the plant
you can't
you can't take it apart and redo it
so they up the acceptable amount of
leakage every single decade the the
stats for acceptable leakage is upped
so they let more out because you can't
fix it you just can't go in and fix it
now you know why I need the membership
now you know why
here's the one topic today I needed to
come out this Lorraine uh coglinio says
vimergy was very generous and sent me a
free bottle of lemon balm with my order
they're very generous their customer
service is insane
and they're very generous it's a mom and
pop that actually cares about the
chronically ill it's their mission
that's the difference too
supplement companies don't mean they
give a f about anybody
you guys some women companies don't mean
they care just because it's a natural
supplement company out there it doesn't
mean they care
Denver G is a mom and pop that actually
understands chronic illness and they
understand people's suffering that's
that's that that's a big thing right
there Karen Churchill says my favorite
supplements is vermergy Lemon Ball
thanks
laughs
so I talked about the Fallout the
acceptable ranges of nuclear waste
that's leaking out where do you think
the frog with four eyes comes from
you don't think there's a frog with four
eyes out there they find a lot of frogs
with four eyes
that's not a joke it's real Jenny Jenn
says I got an x-ray of my ankle then I
had to remind them of the protective
apron they don't automatically cover you
with it anymore
Jenny Chen 100 correct
not only is your experience 100
validated
and correct and accurate
but they don't they don't apron anybody
really much anymore you have to ask for
it and even if you ask for it they don't
apron you enough though x-ray the crap
out of you and they want apron parts of
you that they should they should always
apron the person down but they don't
where do you think the frog with four
eyes comes from
waterways near these plants
that's definitely not acceptable
we also inherit radiation
so if anyone in your bloodline ever got
an x-ray or visited a sheet store in the
days when they imaged feet using a
fluoroscope
even though hundreds of thousands of
women's legs were amputated because of
using that fluoroscope because women
went to shoe stores a lot more than men
back in the day women went to shoe
stores all the time it was actually
therapy
back in the 1930s 40s and 50s women went
to the shoe store some saying this over
and over again because people don't they
don't believe this
but they did
that was a mat that was a major outing
women trying on shoes back in the day
who still was a very big part of the
world we lived in back then and we
weren't born but we lived maybe you were
you were born Right Said people out
there much older than me or whatever the
point is 1930s
and 40s and 50s it was an event that
occurred constantly you go to the shoe
store you try on shoes all the time and
then you might not even buy them and you
go and you leave but you put your legs
in the fluoroscope
I remember when I broke that information
out quite a while because no one even
talked about it like it never existed
before and I released that info back
into the world about it there are
hundreds of thousands of women around
this country alone never mind on the
planet that had their feet and legs
amputated off
in book one I talked about that in depth
and the revised expanded over here
we inherit radiation so if anyone in
your bloodline remember what I said
bloodline never got an x-ray or visited
shoe store in the days when the Imaging
was about Imaging your feet with the
fluoroscope some radiation likely ended
up in you radiation
gets passed on from generation to
generation just like toxic heavy metals
and Mercury
that is MM info how incredible that
piece of knowledge is it gets passed on
down radiation
so what happens is that we're actually
being born now loaded with radiation
and people don't realize this
it takes time and commitment I got a
comment right on here on what is it
YouTube Zoe Cox snake oil salesman
whoa how smart are you Zoe Cox and how
original are you too
snake oil salesman
the irony is if you skinned a snake and
squeezed out the oil it would probably
be more medicinal than anything you're
doing or recommending anyone
but thank you for the comment I like the
Charlton comments and the snake oil
salesman comments those are actually my
favorite because they're classics
and they're kind of funny
it takes time and commitment to an
anti-radiation protocol namely
the medical medium
heavy metal detox smoothie which is also
a radiation yanker
isn't it incredible
so you can say goodbye to it
that's actually really funny that
SOC put it in this way I'm reading this
it takes time a commitment to an
anti-radiation protocol namely the
medical medium heavy metal detox
smoothie which is also a radiation
yanker to say goodbye to it
that's it
these books are so big and there's so
much information in them and everything
that I like I forget
like
different parts to it and everything
don't worry
Zoe Cox or whatever your name was
you will get sick someday
and you'll go through the merry-go-round
and you'll go through all this crap I'm
gonna hope you don't get sick
but you go through all this crap and
then you'll be at the medical medium
books looking for answers
yeah I'm sure you won't tell anybody
about it I'll still be a dirty Secret
but whatever
medical exam protective measures so
check this out
lead bibs
provide it for dental X-rays provide a
facade of Total Protection
it's not a nice thing for me to say but
to know my daughter went for an x-ray
and I told them to apron her they said
research shows that the apron isn't
needed
foreign
freaking need another one here
I can't tell you how upset that gets me
I can't even tell you're upset
it's just it's just screwed up
foreign
I'm the only person in alternative
medicine and conventional medicine that
actually gives it crap and and talks
about the lead bibs and everything I
know and no one talks about them out
there oh but I'm the charlatan I'm the
I'm the snake oil sales
love holistic health says I had to have
an x-ray to my entire head for a dental
implant and three months later my
reading vision went down the drain
so I'm saying this right here and I said
well I feel bad and I said this right
here lead bibs provide it but it's the
truth so what am I going to do let bibs
provided for dental X-rays provide a
facade of Total Protection they usually
don't provide enough coverage
because it's true they don't cover the
person enough
I'm not trying to be mean to any
dentists or anything of the sort we need
dentists do we need doctors I get it but
but I don't I'm not trying to be
purposefully
mean it's just the truth so I recommend
asking for additional protection and try
to get one bib a little higher to
protect your thyroid
can I have an extra bid please an extra
bib
can I move the bib up higher to my
thyroid please
ajana says holistic dentists are no
better and I agree with you 100 lots of
trendy traps
and still too much radiation ajada
totally totally agree
aim is true if you're getting an x-ray
at a medical facility
whether an x-ray of the chest
or neck
or elsewhere
ask for extra gear for protection is it
my freaking imagination
or can you find all the eat better books
out there because these aren't eat
better books these are way above all
that even in the ebayer books all these
years can you find that who's putting
that out there and what podcast doctor
is even talking about that
oh oh they'll be talking about it
tomorrow though that's right because the
books just you know got out there in the
world and
and they steal information from the
lives and whatever in the videos
and don't cite it
ask for extra gear for protection beyond
what they offer normally for other parts
of your body not just the part of the
body immediately surrounding the area
being x-rayed on IG let's see
Shamrocks and sunflower says you're
helping me so much explanation points
and I think there were four exclamation
points or three
thank you
this lemon bomb is starting to calm me
down a little bit because that's what
lemon balm is it's common if
and
like when you're using something really
potent and really high quality you can
always feel it that's what's incredible
about it
so many sources of medical exam
radiation are hard to avoid
it's part of the process of seeking help
I'm not telling you to not seek help
you break your leg you're going to need
an x-ray
when people are looking for answers they
go to the doctor with a complaint and
the doctor writes a prescription for an
x-ray
CAT scan
or MRI
MRI does admit does admit a certain
amount of radiation
from chess Rex from chest x-rays to
diagnose lung issues such as bronchitis
and pneumonia to arm x-rays to diagnose
broken bones bursitis or whatever in the
shoulder this is where our current
medical system is
and yet rarely if ever in the X-ray and
scanning world do they ever offer a lead
Helmet or protective headpiece
too expensive to order them and buy them
is the medical industry just doesn't
have enough money
the medical industry is too poor
to actually create and Order up some
lead helmets
but no uh they can't afford that
octop Corp
hey there you are the apron is loaded
with radiation as well because they use
the same one over and over laptop
incredible
incredible octop also followed up with
her other comment shortly after that
said pink phone
if the pink phone rings I will answer it
and talk to that Zoe Cox person
still better to have an apron that's got
radiation in it a lead apron that's got
radiation in it then not having one it's
still better keep that in mind
so with the pneumonia and arm x-rays to
diagnose broken bones this is where our
current medical system is and yet rarely
if ever in the X-ray and scanning world
do they offer a lead Helmet or
protective headpiece no so our brains
are left exposed purposely I believe is
it wrong for me to think purposely or do
you think I think with all the signs of
research and all the brainiacs and
Geniuses and scientists that we have
that come out of elite elite Schools
they're so smart do you think they just
somehow forgot no they wouldn't have
forgot that we need lead helmets with
all these x-rays to protect your brain
no so they're doing it on purpose
foreign
ER says sad but true former TSA Employee
here whoa
whoa
I wish I knew what airport you worked at
when you were at on TSA because I always
get help off to the side and they go
through my bags
and I wouldn't need I needed you I
needed you sad but true former TSA
Employee here the sad part is we were
more exposed to radiation than anyone
else big time I lost a lot of co-workers
from cancers and strokes teach
I totally understand I
me and SOC had conversations about it
every time I was in an airport
constantly about you guys and your job
like I always felt for you guys always
did
always did oh my God my family my
friends know because I've always talked
about that very thing that you you know
being a TSA officer
and I wish I knew you when you were
working there at whatever airport I
would have liked to teach here
hey it's TJ it's teach is teach here
she's working today
me tube787 says we produce poisons then
we make more poisons to check for more
poisons than we're recommended more
poisons to combat the poisons what a
crazy world and then we're recommended
to get blood work because we're sick
from the poisons and then we get sicker
from the blood work and they recommend
more blood work because we're sick for
the voices and sick from the blood work
and then they recommend more blood work
and then when we're just about dead and
we're laying there we can't even move
they actually say you're going to need
more blood work because we don't know
why you're dying so they take more blood
out of us and they make us sicker sicker
and next thing you do it
they try to kill us
I'm not anti-blood work done properly
I'm not anti-doctor go to your doctor
ask your doctor what's right for you
I have a lot of doctor friends
I don't know my spot I have to find it
so hang on
SOC saying get somewhere down here
and yet rarely if ever in the X-ray and
scanning world do they offer you a lead
helmet
or protective headpiece so our brains
are left exposed
wild blueberry girl says that was a
surgical tech for six years and they
would sometimes do x-rays in surgery
would just say for us to turn around and
step 10 feet away still in the room
and I 100 percent believe that because I
have heard that before
and I know that's 100 accurate
I wouldn't need to have heard it before
to know it's accurate because I know
you're telling me exactly what happened
but I've actually heard that
unbelievable
thank you for saying that
that's why it's important for us to ask
for additional bibs to help Shield the
areas of the body we can and to work on
the radiation removal protocols in this
book spirulina
or spirulina
a key ingredient in medical medium
protocols is essential for radiation
exposure
foreign
awareness teach I might have put
something in here SOG SOC might have put
some in there
Jackie I need that lemon balm 2aw they
didn't put an apron on my son yesterday
even though I told him to ask crap crap
crap
I totally understand
I'm gonna put a
Chopper full straight in
goes into your bloodstream really fast
Heidi Inman
this knowledge is gold
three explanation points
airport awareness all right let's let's
uh let's get rolling
medical medium information has always
warned about radiation contamination
from airports and air travel
there is so much radiation being
admitted in airports that it would set
off radiation detection technology
what about fear you guys and Chaos this
isn't about fear it's about knowing what
what you're up against so you can make a
decision and have a choice
I think it's critical to have a choice
and to know what you're up against you
can protect yourself at least work on
radiation protocols at least but the
point is that you actually have a form
of knowledge or you've got the
empowerment empowerment is about
knowledge it's about knowing what's
going on
no changes are going to be made if you
don't know what's happening and you
don't know what's going on
can't make a change if you don't if you
can't make a choice
there's so much radiation being admitted
in airports that it would actually set
off detection radiation detection to
technology get the words right aw while
you were while you were walking through
the rows of passengers waiting for their
flights
the device would go wild picking up
radiation from all the freshly scanned
people and knapsacks and carry-ons fresh
off the scanner conveyor belts not now
contaminated that's why it's good to be
aware and proactive okay I just
butchered that paragraph but I have to
tell you something and this is important
first of all people who say I'm a fear
Monger are so off the mark
so are we all supposed to just never
know anything don't know about how to
guard yourself when you get a blood test
don't know how to get radiation out of
your body don't know how to ask for some
protected bibs when you go and get a
procedure done
an x-ray or you know
um not talk about the truth about why
people are sick so you never know why
anybody got sick like am I supposed to
just hide everything not give anybody
any information and so so I don't put
anybody in fear
meanwhile
people are actually working on healing
with the medical medium info
I'm doing in these incredible recipes
and then someone will come along and be
like orthorexia he's making you
orthorexic okay then it's fine to go eat
go eat whatever you want out there in
the world don't think about your your
your sickness and your problems and
don't try to fix it go eat whatever you
want
go do whatever you want
and it's not about that like mm info you
could do anything you want but it's here
for you when you want to partake in
turning your life around when you want
answers and you want to help yourself
heal
for one luggage
okay this is interesting too I just want
to say this
in the airport
if you had radiation technology
detectors
it would be it would show levels of
radiation
elevated radiation
from the amount of exposure that happens
in the airports
for one luggage has to be discarded and
purchased new periodically
that's a medical medium recommendation
you don't have to do that recommendation
but that's a medical meme recommendation
luggage has to be discarded and
purchased new periodically when not in
use keep luggage that has been on a
flight far away from your children and
pets
because the luggage goes through the
scanners
and it's getting radiated heavy radiated
right the luggage collects that
radiation and keeps that radiation long
term so if you store that luggage and
that carry-on in those suitcases
by say your baby's crib or in a Closet
near your child or you know near your
child's bed or whatever it is if you're
storing it you have to be careful you
have to get that that luggage out of
there store it somewhere else if you
don't want to throw it out I'm in page
239 right here in brain saver just
letting you guys know and Airport
awareness
luggage has to be discarded and
purchased new periodically when not in
use keep luggage that has been on
flights away from children and pets for
an for another when you're going through
security
opt out of the full body scanner and ask
for a pat down instead
so there's a scanning machine
there at the airport
it's not the metal detector
the metal detector kind of just looks
like this gray thing that's like this
right it's like a Gateway and you just
walk right through that's the metal
detector there at the airport
okay that has no radiation coming out of
it that's detecting from metal objects
right
but there's a scanner at the airport
where you stand there and the doors
revolve and a scan happens
there's a couple of different scanners
they have their different makes and
models but there's a scanner
now you can do what you want whatever
but I tell my friends and my family
to not do the scanner
to just get a pat down
so you ask he kindly asked tiesters can
you give me a pat down
and they fill you up
they put their hands everywhere
wherever
but the point is is that you you don't
have to then do the scanner if you stay
on the side so they'll ask you well put
your arms up
Sarah put your arms up ma'am put your
arms up
spread your legs
and you spread your legs and they pat
down your body
herbal Society
says I'm I'm here the knowledge and
respect for the work
you do
drop the gems
drop the gems to the people
thank you
bertrude says it's amazing how much you
care for people three hearts
thank you I'm honored
IG let's see Alpha Hoffman says I used
to be a nuclear engineer whoa and
probably got way more exposure
than what they told us so grateful for
this information to know how to protect
myself incredible
there's some smart people in the medical
medium Community I mean you guys know
you're smart just some smart the
smartest group of people out there are
in the medical medium community
Amanda accusing someone of orthorexia
while they're using mm protocols to hell
to heal is evil
I'm butchering comments today I can make
these comments right
I will read that one over though
because that one blows my mind
Amanda says accusing someone of
orthorexia while they're using medical
medium protocols to heal is evil and
that's true okay I want to talk about
that one second
that is true
there are even people that end up hating
medical medium because they want to go
and they want to do the whole shark
thing they want to sell all their
programs and sell all their stuff and
they healed with medical medium
information and then
to lead people their way for their
programs and everything they try to diss
medical media and be like oh he's he's
he'll make you orthorexic come over to
my come over to my feed in my programs
and buy my programs I'm not like him
he's a jerk he's terrible
all right
for another when you're going through
security opt out of the full body
scanner and ask for a pat down instead
it's perfectly safe to walk through a
plain metal detector
it's the airport body scanner device you
want to avoid
as you're waiting for your pat down try
not to lean against the radiation
machine that's being used to examine
carry-ons did you hear that
critical
this is critical teach you know you know
the machine I'm talking about right
you got to know that machine
as you're waiting for your pat down
try not to lean against the radiation
machine that's being used to examine
carry-ons
so you're waiting for your pat down and
they'll be like stand here sir ma'am
stand here right and when they when you
go to stand there you might stand really
close to the radiation machine so you
got to kind of like just stand a few
feet away
try to stay on a few feet or more away
from the machine that's processing and
irritating baggage
this is interesting I want to read this
next part
if you guys are open to it
extraterrestrial space travel
first of all do you believe in aliens do
you believe in alien sightings alien
spacecrafts do you believe in ETS you
believe in
right
space creatures do you believe that
there are real sightings on the planet
do you believe that there are aliens
flying in our atmosphere
in spacecrafts
do you believe in any of that
you don't have to believe in aliens you
don't have to believe that there are
real sightings out there you don't have
to believe the government's been hiding
all these all this information about all
the different alien encounters and all
that you don't have to believe in any of
that right it's okay I'm not saying that
you have to believe in aliens
I'm not telling you you should believe
in them I'm just wondering if you do if
you do believe in aliens in space travel
and spacecrafts
and all that right you guys do never
seen one but yes you guys believe right
a whole bit you guys know I have a
medical meme podcast at Apple podcast
and alien episode you might want to
listen to it if you haven't heard that
alien episode
but I want to read this next part if
you're okay
extra terrestrial space travel
what some might call alien ships
also leave radiation in the atmosphere
as they pass through
isn't that incredible
Who would know that
I haven't heard anybody talk about that
that radiation is increasing because of
alien space travel but I haven't heard
anybody talk about that Spirit of
compassion put that piece of information
in there
of course I was asking for some cool
stuff
I was like Spirit compassion can you
give me some cool stuff
neurotoxins is getting so boring yes I
know neurotoxins caused so many problems
with everybody's illnesses at chronic
fatigue syndrome and fibromyalgia I know
Epstein-Barr creates multiple sclerosis
and all these things but give me some
cool stuff we're on radiation
and snc said extraterrestrial space
travel which some might call alien ships
also leave radiation in the atmosphere
as they pass through
so we're having radiation exposure from
ETS
passing through all those sightings all
the spacecrafts that are on this planet
that are flying around in the atmosphere
they're spreading a lot of radiation
here we are working worried about
climate climate climb climate what no
one's even talking about this
UFO sightings are not totally understood
sure they are the radiation coming from
these crafts
is not the normal radiation we
experience here
rather it's radiation of another kind
that gets into the atmosphere so here's
the Killer part that was mind-blowing
for me it's not just the thought of that
we're getting all this radiation
exposure from the amount of alien
spacecraft travel happening around the
planet
but it's the type of radiation it's a
different form of radiation
then what we're creating down here so
there's two kinds of radiation affecting
us what we're creating down here
and then the radiation
that's actually entering through space
travel
spacecraft
that's incredible really
um JL says aw thanks so much
my sister is now 18 months without
medicated drugs including penicillin and
anti-seizure meds because of the medical
medium books thanks SOC
and you're on YouTube thank you for
commenting really incredible information
um your comments incredible and it's
really inspiring Caroline Grenier says
your info is life-saving I am pumped
doing this live with you today
I tell everyone about you thank you for
the wisdom and healing from above God
bless
incredible
you guys I shall now get into radiation
exposure shot
Branch out therapy
here we are
there's a IG comment that podcast
episode was mind altering mermail says
You must be talking about the alien
podcast episode medical meme podcast at
Apple podcast
the alien episode that was definitely a
really powerful episode
this is a supported it a supportive shot
for circumstances such as airplane
travel
walking through airports or being close
to airport scanners or baggage scanners
being close to luggage that has gone
through airport scanners
medical testing such as CT scans X-rays
fluoroscopy and even MRIS
being around others who have had medical
testing such as CAT scans X-rays
fluoroscopy and MRIS
exposure to computerized devices
I got no exposure to computerized
devices
not I do have exposure to computerized
and this radiation exposure shot is good
after a sunburn
that's another time you can use it
hmm
with all that all the time I have in the
world to just go out
in my swimsuit and bathe sunbathe in the
Sun for hours
I don't have any time to do that but
don't do that for hours that's not a
good idea don't do that for hours
all right
we are doing the radiation exposure shot
comment if really kicked in but what it
has done it has calmed me down so much
because
I took a decent amount in my
hot water here
but it's definitely
really calmed me down
that's my experience in the moment
happening right now CD says hi Anthony
so happy to have you around I wouldn't
be where I am today without you
are all the energy products safe while
pregnant
it's just cut those guys those guys talk
um those guys communicate I mean just
reach out to the emergency company ask
them any questions you need to ask them
but check with your doctor that's easy
because your situation
and she'd always ask your doctor
well
I am excited let's get a shot going on
Jess Celine I usually read your YouTube
YouTube comments and they're usually
like awesome because they're like
thank you Anthony and I'm like whoa
thanks man like good job Anthony
jessalyne always leaves a comment like
good job Anthony or thank you Anthony
amazing live Anthony you're amazing bro
I feel your energy is what I'm trying to
say I feel your energy
[Applause]
foreign
we got the machine running
so I'm starting out with the cilantro
first
half cup tightly packed cilantro
I got my cilantro right here this is
radiation exposure brain shot therapy
is what this is
getting my cilantro down in here
now I'm using
the wild blueberry powder you can do
frozen wild blueberries fresh wild
blueberries a half cup of Frozen or
fresh you can choose to do that you can
do two tablespoons of wild blueberry
juice or one tablespoon of the wild
blueberry powder right here
but I'm going to go with the asparagus
right now
because I want to make sure I'm able to
mix that in because I'm going to go with
the powder
I love juicing asparagus it is actually
like one of my favorites
these are small Spears
it says four raw medium Spears
and I've seen Spears that big like just
large ones and these are actually really
tiny so I'm going to put a few in there
all right one stalk of celery please
such nice celery right here I like when
I have nice celery you know how it can
come spindly lots of leaves and just
really spindly right just really nice
celery right here
we go
we got just enough for a shot
now I can mix in a couple of things here
which is going to be
I'm just making sure this gets all the
juice out
nice
all right then we're going to mix this
in here
right
next thing is
blueberry powder
one tablespoon
I'm gonna get a measuring
spoon here
one tablespoon
this is incredible by the way
so that's the vimergi wild blueberry
powder right there
gonna drop that in
now I'm going to add
some spirulina
spirulina is half
tablespoon I think it's a half teaspoon
I think so let me get that that's
nice
a half teaspoon in there
barley grass juice powder
and bird says hello can I use barley
grass instead of barley grass juice
powder
nope it's it's an entirely different
creature it's an entirely different
Beast it it doesn't work
it has to be
the juice powder putting a little bit of
that in there now too
yep
I'll tell you why because the barley
grass is barley grass it's chopped up
dehydrated grass
so there's no potency to it it's just
straight grass and it's also irritating
for a lot of people with their
intestinal tracts because it's
scratching grass but if here's the thing
it's scratchy dehydrated grass that's a
difference that's barley grass barley
grass is not what this is so that's
really important to know this is barley
grass juice powder it's the extraction
the juice itself the grass the scratchy
grass was left behind this is actually
the juice and the juice only so that's
what it is and then you know and then
it's fried right it's dehydrated so it's
the barley grass juice powder now here's
what's incredible and beverage is the
only company with my knowledge that's
ever done this they don't have the
caking agents they do they don't
apply caking agents or bonding agents
inside their powder so here's how it
works all the green powders out there
all the different powders whether it's
mushroom powders reishi powders chaga
powders
um spirulina powders barley grass
powders whatever whatever powders that
are out there vegetable and fruit
powders all the different powders that
are out there you guys there's hundreds
of companies doing powders now just
powder everything
there there are undisclosed
bonding agents to stop the powder from
sticking together
that means the companies that have all
these different powders out there think
about this
all the different powders have an
ingredient or ingredients that you don't
know about that's a non-caking agent
so it's a non-bonding agent so they put
these these anti-bonding agents and
caking agents into the powders so you're
like oh you know my my you know my
person here told me to do these to do
these powders here and here's a green
powder and here's another powder
and I got the best powder or I got this
powder or chlorella but what people
don't realize
is they put in the anti-caking agent and
the anti-bonding agent so that the
powders wouldn't Clump together but they
don't put the ingredient on the bottle
so when they use the anti-caking agent
they don't put it on the bottle so when
you read the bottle you're like let's
see there's
spinach in here spinach powder there's
beet powder there's
chlorella there's whatever you're
reading all the ingredients but what
you're not reading is
anti-caking Agent
anti-bonding agent and you won't read
that on the on the bottle it's
undisclosed they're allowed to do it the
emergency swore they would never do that
so the beverages powders and it's just
like this across the board with energy
their stuff is unmatched right because
they
choose not to ever put the anti-caking
agents in these powders their mushroom
powders their their green powders they
don't do that critical to know Kelsey
box says can you do this shop before an
x-ray to protect yourself I would
I would if it was me or a family member
and I said I would definitely do it and
after
I would do it after
so I just wanted people to know it's
another reason why I endorsed themergy
and that's critical to understand
because when you think about what that
is it's insane
it's insane
so
who does that
I don't care what anybody says
undisclosed they secretly put they don't
just tell anybody they put the antibody
bonding agents in there the details
matter when it comes down to healing and
that's that's the difference because
memory is thinking about people who
aren't well they're thinking about their
customers or think about all these
things and
they wouldn't want anti-caking agents
and anti-bonding agents inside their
spirulina inside their barley grass
juice powder inside their chaga powder
inside their Rishi powder whatever they
would never want that in there either
but see it's not about that when it
comes down to supplements out there in
the world
it's just about
bottom line
people will say oh this made me not feel
well
so much of the time that they have they
don't realize that they have bad quality
products out there with all kinds of
anti-caking agents and bonding agents
and
and they don't even know but no don't
use barley grass powder
barley grass powder is grass that was
mulched up
and thrown in there
it's scratchy it's dehydrated
it doesn't do what it needs to do that's
not barley grass juice powder
I'm not even going into the quality of
what these are which is a whole other
level I could be here all day and and
the quality is insane anyway I'm gonna
mix this up
I'm just talking about that so if you
see it clumped if you see a clump in the
in the jar in the bottle you see it
plump that's what you want you want to
see it Clump because you don't you know
that's the whole point it means it
wasn't the bonding agents weren't added
in there
the anti-bonding agents all right
we got it
foreign
have I gotten any radiation exposure
recently
yeah I have
I have done radiation exposure
[Music]
friend of mine got out of an airport
gave him a hug
[Music]
got off the plane
saturated radiation
I got some exposure and I knew it
that's why I'm happy about this
[Music]
why does this one taste so good
so good
[Music]
I like knowing I'm protecting myself
um
I want more
[Music]
so good
should I ask
bartender
hello bartender
can I have another
coming right up Mr William
thank you
so good
amazing
[Music]
oh God
the feelings I get when I do the
radiation shot exposure radiation
exposure shot
is an entire whole body from head down
to my toe
like it's everywhere
it's not the normal Sensations I get
from the other brain shot therapies it's
different it's from my head down to the
bottom of my feet but I feel like
there's
an aura going all around me like I feel
like there's energy going all around me
when I take this every time I take this
one because I get exposed
periodically
and every time I get exposed to
radiation and I say you know what I'm
going to do the radiation exposure shot
and I take it I feel like it it right
about out here this far I feel an energy
that's surrounding me that's what I feel
what do you guys feel let me know how
you feel
you know if you do a post you do a real
a story please let me know your
experience with the radiation exposure
shot what's your feeling I would love to
see it tag a medical medium medical
medium Huntress Divine says how often
should the shots be done if you're
exposed to them daily can I just do them
once a week you can totally do them once
a week if you're exposed to radiation on
a daily level because you work in the
field
of medicine or anywhere else you just
take every couple of days then take take
a shot every few days sure
Heidi Inman the blood work chapter and
brain saver is mind-blowing Heidi
it's so mind-blowing it's actually
unbelievably mind-blowing
you can take them daily of course you
know that you can take them daily for
sure I mean there's nothing wrong with
that
so I mean feel free to take the
radiation exposure shot daily there's
nothing wrong with that
yeah
so that's what that is right there blood
training agenda
it is mind-blowing this chapter
is unbelievable
you will not be the same person
once you read this chapter you will not
be the same person you will have
knowledge you won't believe you now
possess once you read that chapter how
to brain saver I'm just being honest
incredible chapter
working on your healing process while
trying to live your life is difficult
when you're encountering stressful
situations and then I talk about boom
this is so important
getting the radiation exposure recipe
out of the book
is great or medicalmedium.com
you go to medicalmedium.com and get lots
of information it's free free no pay
walls no subscription for uh fees me
tube787 says my 13 year old has been
doing the shot challenge too he loves
doing it took a shot to school today oh
my God that's amazing that is incredible
in this Blood draining agenda chapter
chapter 40 page 4 21
critical immune system knowledge right
here you've got to read this chapter
there's a section here not meant to go
to waste and they're throwing all our
blood out when they don't even use it
here's one right here the endless cycle
of we better order more blood
more blood more blood because if we were
just a disposable blood bag
and then there's a section in this uh
blood agenda blood draw agendas training
our brain supplies because we're losing
our brain reserves when we're getting
blood drawn radically like they do
modern day blood leading
David witchen
happy belated birthday my brother
okay it was yesterday was it yesterday
right did I miss your birthday
or was it the day before or was it today
or am I just losing it and if you didn't
have your birthday
if that's true then that would actually
be really funny
nice
this Blood draining chapter is just
insane
practical considerations of blood
testing
quarter and half tubes the standard of
the future because of medical medium
information because of soc how to
rebuild your blood
draw protocols one week directly before
a blood draw
amazing like the information in here is
just insane
seriously
that's just insane
so you guys
check out rain saver and brain saver
protocols please
right there
get on the newsletter go to
medicalmedium.com get on the newsletter
also uh by the way on telegram I do
exclusive messages I'm probably due for
one might not happen today but I'm due
for one pretty soon you can check out my
previous messages they're from the
hearts
and you can do that on Telegram
we have four more days of this challenge
do we really have four more days you can
sign up now and you're in a four day
challenge and then you could re-watch
all the other days
at medicalmedium.com for free
remember the word free
f-r-e-e because that's incredible here
we have four more days of the challenge
you can still sign up and get the
download the free grocery shopping list
right here
which is incredible
no pay walls no pay firewalls
nothing like that go to medicalme.com
it's free everything
get the book at the library if you
choose
okay I realize though that if you buy
asparagus at the store you're gonna have
to pay for asparagus but you're gonna
have to pay for your food anyway and I
don't own all the asparagus farms and I
don't own any celery Farms so I would
love to give all that out for free in
the food we need and all the supplies
and everything but I can't
but I can give you the information and
knowledge for free and not charge three
thousand dollar five thousand dollar
programs and not withhold the
information from everybody and package
it up and sell it constantly
and do that for years and years and I
won't do that and I never have all right
you guys
we are done for today I'm excited about
tomorrow are you ready for tomorrow
because I'm getting ready we have four
days left
don't miss it be there we're going to
cover more topics and I hope
you're okay with the topics I'm going to
cover
because that radiation topic was very
sad and very depressing but I feel
better though because I'm doing
something about it at least for us for
me we are taking that exposure shot
yeah
Mona says love all your books
there are many books or eight books you
got the medical name revised and expand
it which is mind-blowing right you guys
on IG
you guys know the book that's an
Incredible Book right there just live a
rescue
boom
there's cleanse to heal then there's
thyroid healing and there's
life-changing Foods there's the brain
saver books
am I missing one
could be missing one
I just want to say something you guys
I'm proud of everyone here
more than you guys know
on IG Lynn Meyer says my two-year-old
granddaughter crushed her finger ow
my day had to be held hurt I had to hold
her
to get the finger x-rayed they didn't
bib either of them
well this information is so critical
I think over time you know maybe that's
something that will get better out there
maybe the blood draw issues out there
and the radiation exposure issues out
there and all the different things that
are happening the medical medium
information is in these books it's out
there
so like and then they didn't give you a
bib when you were holding your
granddaughter to
when you hold your daughter
has to hold
her granddaughter okay
you guys
I'm proud of all of you take one day at
a time
I'll see you later tomorrow can't wait