[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
look at me
saver
medical mean brain shot therapy
challenge day seven
[Music]
dear Lord
adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer
because when we expect bad news when you
get bad news or you're stressed out
whatever's happening
you need that adrenal fighter blade
stabilizer it's actually really fun you
guys what are we gonna do when the brain
safer challenge is over
what are we gonna do I mean this is
really fun I look forward to the robot
every day I actually look forward to it
so here we are
um day seven
medical medium
yep brain shot therapy challenge
incredible we're doing the 10-day
cleanse fight or flight
fight or fight either stand you fight
right or you you flight man you take
flight it's either one of the other
right that's what it is I'm always I'm
ready for the fight I'm always ready for
the fight
you know
always always we gotta be ready for the
fight
right
you gotta know what hill to die on
though right that's the other thing I'm
always ready for the fight
ing for the chronically ill for over 35
plus years even more since I was young
fighting for the chronically ill so I'm
ready for the fight
but you gotta know what hill to die on
that I do know right you're a fighter
too Hannah amazing good to see you guys
Cold Light spring you're here you made
it you made it on the live what's going
on here so adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer
where are we where are we
right there
one of my favorites by far one of my
favorites whoa I love this one have you
guys tried this one mm School mm school
have you tried this one
it's really that incredible so that's it
right there but so let's read about it
for a little bit do a little reading
about it for a minute right
stress is dominating your life and
you're not getting a chance to have a
break or reprieve
from whatever you're up against
so whatever you're up against
you're not going to be able to get that
break or that reprieve
and that's really difficult for so many
people so that's a great time to do this
if that's happening in your life stress
is dominating your life and you're not
getting a chance to have a break or
reprieve from whatever you're up against
I've been through that always so there
we go boom that's when I take that one
you can still sign up for the challenge
even though we're day seven medical
medium.com get download your free PDF to
get your grocery shopping list and all
of that how incredible
so here's another reason to use the
adrenal fight or flight stabilizer which
is potent medicine man
continual chronic stress is occurring do
you guys like is it just me that has a
continual chronic stress
is it just me
or do you guys have that too
do you guys have that too
right
that means you're doing something right
in your life
incredible continual chronic stress is
occurring these are battling Darkness to
do good stuff how about this one you
feel involuntary reactions when
receiving any kind of news or
information from various people or
sources guys I'm reading out of the
brand saver books
you just got on here you don't have the
brain saver books
lock one down go to your bookstores go
to the library get it for free
go to amazon.com 40 off these things are
as thick as the Bible I mean these
things are over 600 Pages or 12 books
all together in both these books there's
a recipe book over 100 recipes for the
brain to help heal the brain inside
these books too I mean these books are
packed
so
really incredible information
truly
so
you feel involuntary reactions when
receiving any kind of news or
information from various people and
sources
okay how about this one you're
experiencing any type of PTSD how many
of you guys have PTSD
dealing with any kind of PTSD
right kind of look out for that Rodney
Lee says I took it this morning and my
eight-year-old had some amazing
she did not like it at all was
overwhelmed by the ginger
she melted down but it was resolved so
quickly she's been struggling with her
reactions to things and this was such a
help hope to get this in her again
incredible amazing news
that's incredible
Debbie says thank you so much aw
you've obsessive thought shot
helped me quiet down huge lifetime
obsessive thoughts so yeah I love the
obsessive thought shifter that's a
shifter it's an incredible one we're
doing stabilizers today we're doing the
three and all fighter flight stabilizer
which I'm really excited about you guys
okay you ready if you're experiencing
any type of PTSD how many people got all
kinds of varieties of PTSD I talk about
it in the medical medium books talk
about it in these books too and when we
have that PTSD this is a great time to
use
this incredible adrenal fight-or-flight
stabilizer right here
okey dokey you feel like you're on a
roller coaster ride and have lost
control of your life great time to use
this one
it's a perfect time for these renal
fight-or-flight stabilizer think about
that for a minute okay
yes
you ready for this one
you're addicted to adrenalized
activities or drama
adrenalized activities or drama and
you're addicted
how about that because you could get
addicted to your own adrenaline
you can get addicted to drama you could
get addicted to scary movies you can get
addicted to anything and then your
adrenals are just you know your life
could be like a scary movie in the
moment so many people have that going on
time for the adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer how about this one
you've been using sex as an escape
that's even in here
that happens to a lot of people and then
they just get burnt out where they're
just burnt out
that's another time you use the adrenal
fight-or-flight stabilizer how about
this one you're living on adrenaline
without realizing it
such as with intermittent fasting and or
caffeine use
great time for the adrenal fight or
flight stabilizer
caffeine use if you're doing caffeine
then get that stabilizer and they're
critical all right so let's take a look
here
we're into our next little spot
medical medium brain shot therapy it's
where we are now but you know what we'll
switch up
we'll switch things up a little bit
we'll change it up this time
the heat of the
motion right here in brain saver you
guys we're talking about day seven we're
in the brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge we're doing 10 days one to
three shots a day today is the adrenal
fight or flight stabilizer shot I'm
pumped up
okay and I'm reading right out of here
because I see all my little postage
notes everywhere
right
the Heat of the Moment as we go through
life we come across difficult situations
betrayal loss heartbreak loneliness
confrontation all of us experience these
one way or another somehow or some way
we do even if things are going okay for
a while they're going good for a while
and then boom we experience that like
they're going okay for a while going
okay and then we experience it
all of us experience these one way or
another we get emotionally hurt and the
physical aspect of this goes wholly
ignored
no one gives a crap about stuff
happening in our lives and it affecting
us physically people don't care
you can get in a confrontation with
somebody or something or something
happens and just no one cares if it
affected anyone physically I've seen
this over and over again
foreign
when we get emotionally hurt a physical
aspect occurs inside our body but
nobody's like saying oh
sorry about that I hope you physically
aren't sicker because of that really bad
argument we had that we started or I
started or whatever it is no one's
saying hey you know I'm so sorry you're
probably you know physically sick from
this for days
foreign
s to so many people to get physically
sick from all kinds of confrontations
and other kinds of emotional things that
happen it's really sad
we need to address the physical core
strength of the brain
we need to address that so that no
matter what we're experiencing
emotionally or what we're thinking that
inner core strength of the brain can
survive emotional injuries we want to
strengthen the core of the brain so that
we don't get these emotional injuries so
they're not hurting us or not hitting us
hard and the adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer is one of these incredible
ways to protect ourselves
which is a big deal it's really big deal
incredible
when we have a loss or betrayal our
physical brain can become injured people
don't realize that when we're betrayed
we can get these little tiny micro
injuries inside our brain and talk about
that all through these incredible books
right here
especially if our brain doesn't have
what it needs and that's another problem
a lot of times our brain doesn't have
always what it needs and it said part of
what injures the brain is not the broken
trust itself like the broken trust
that causes us to just be like oh that
broken trust
it's the fire that occurs when an event
like that happens so that's what goes on
it's the fire that blows up in our head
when we've been let down and broken
trust has happened it's the fire that
lights up inside the brain that's why
the adrenal fight-or-flight stabilizer
is so critical for people it's why it's
in here it's why it's so powerful
laughs
that fire is the heating up of the brain
in intense electrical Heat
stress loss trauma and betrayal burn hot
as well so if we're under stress it
burns the brain hot
if we had any kind of loss it burns the
brain hot trauma burns the brain up
betrayal burns the brain hot that's what
happens that's why we need this
stabilizer and we're not just talking
about one angry spell of the Year we're
talking about every day frustrations too
everyday frustrations lights the brain
up on fire
every day frustrations heats up the
brain it's being human fine it's what
it's like to be here on Earth human our
brain heats up it lights up
that's
Perfectly Natural but we have to protect
ourselves though along the way too and
that's something humans don't get taught
we're talking about everyday
frustrations for example driving to work
in traffic when you're late slowed down
or stuck in lights causes the brain to
heat up you start getting a heating of
the brain as simple as that you're late
for an appointment you're trying to get
there and your brain heats up if you
can't get there on time these are small
little things but that's how much
heating happens instead of rain having a
difficult conversation can cause the
brain to heat up oh yeah having a
brain heat up that's why we have to give
our brains what it needs
if you are having trouble on social
media watching these lives and you're
getting kicked off and all kinds of
other stuff go to medicalmedium.com I'm
streaming live there right now we are
live at medicalmedium.com and I saw some
of you guys say how you love the medical
medium.com website it's free everything
on there everything's free on there by
the way but I love what I'm seeing
because you guys actually are noticing
what we're doing to the website
doing all kinds of great stuff
so if you're having a difficult
conversation it can cause the brain to
heat up participating in a virtual
meeting can cause the brain to heat up
do you know that
if you're doing a zoom or something else
or any kind of virtual meeting that
causes the brain to heat up as well
it's incredible because video calls
often involve an additional form of
stress there's an additional form of
stress when you're doing video calls
that's incredible
whether from spotty internet connections
that cause delays participants talking
over one another or because we tend to
raise our voice increase facial
expressions or emphasize body language
when we feel the format isn't allowing
us to project our message it's just
meetings just family meetings with
family virtually can also heat up the
brain I don't know if that's ever
happened to you guys the brain heat of
life's challenges is harder on the
chronically ill because they're often
stuck in bed and that's another thing if
you are on mattress island or if you had
a sickness or an illness or any kind of
symptoms or conditions brain heat tends
to get hotter
I mean who knows this stuff I mean when
I was getting this information from
Spirit of compassion it's just it's all
like who no one talks about this
anywhere
so uh people asking about seizures and
other conditions there are true answers
in these books the brain protocol book
you gotta have both critical to have
both books
so let's keep on going a little bit so
the brain heat of life's challenges is
harder on The Chronic Leo because
they're stuck in bed they're too
fatigued to walk it off or go exercise
and that's another thing too
what happens is when you're stuck on
mattress Islander you're dealing with
any kind of chronic illness or you feel
compromised because of a symptom
it's not easy to just walk off any
frustration
that makes it so hard on people
that's why I wanted to make sure that in
these books there's over 300 symptoms
conditions and protocols I want people
better faster and the brain shot
therapies are just miraculous
all of it is
so when you're too fatigued to walk it
off go exercise or distract yourself or
shake it off a lot of people
have a problem where they're like oh my
God I'm like I'm stuck in bed I don't
feel good a lot going on it's hard to
just walk this stuff off so the
frustration can grow
you won't know unless you're in
somebody's shoes that has struggled or
you know suffered or been through a lot
you won't know until you're in their
shoes that's another thing too
a lot of people run from their stress do
you ever see that out there they run
from their stress they burn off the
adrenaline also called epinephrine
created by a mild Stress and Anxiety by
keeping busy with the activities they
like wearing themselves out so that the
thoughts don't keep cycling a lot of
people run a lot of people
they're lucky in the moment
we're fortunate in the moment to not
have symptoms or conditions drag them
all the way down yet
they may be young they may be strong so
what they do is they keep moving
that's what they do
self-care appointments exercising
running around hitting coffee shops
right
staying out late with friends whatever
it is you just keep moving and you keep
running from the stress that's how you
do it right you're young
but then if you get really sick and all
of a sudden you're like whoa now it's
just a doctor's appointments now I got
to spend a lot of time at home now I got
to spend a lot of time on the couch I
don't really feel good I can't really go
everywhere I want to go that's a whole
nother game and then that heat rises
people who are chronically ill don't
have that luxury or option when you're
stuck on the mattress Island
you you can get caught up in your
headspace with the brain fire burning
hotter and I want to tell everybody
who's stuck on mattress Island who's
been sick who's you know got some kind
of chronic symptom who's struggling all
of it I want to tell you guys
that I understand and that you know it's
okay
because we can do things about it
we can protect our brain while we're
dealing with that while we're on
mattress Island while we're like slowed
down in our life in the moment before we
heal
so when you're stuck on mattress Island
you can get caught up in your headspace
and I see that happen because the people
who aren't stuck on mattress Island
they're able to run from their headspace
they're able to run and just couldn't do
this gonna go see this friend gonna go
back gonna go here and if you're able to
run from it constantly until they get
sick and then doom boom they're stuck
with it all right
Lauren oh my God I just saw saw that
incredible
Lauren hashian's so incredible uh to see
you here right here by the way it's an
honor
um to have you here dear friend of mine
so that's what happens to people if you
get too sick
then you're stuck and then the Mind
races
all that comes out and you can't run
from all that
stress it's harder that's why it's
critical to get healthy too and you can
do that with this information even when
you're stuck on mattress Island and you
don't feel good it's about being
empowered and having the information to
heal brain heat can even burn on a
different level
with a different kind of heat
when everything is good and happy so
even when things are really happy and
joyful and great we can burn a lot of
brain heat that's why it's critical to
get what we need inside our brain
so what I love about the adrenal
fight-or-flight stabilizer it's giving
your brain
this incredible instant fast infusion
that ignites the brain
in the right direction giving it the
fuel it needs so so many of us
we're just so stressed out we got a lot
going on and we end up burning
everything good up in the brain and we
need to restore it we need to refuel it
like I talked about the other day
she conscious says I did two burnout
stabilizer shots yesterday in mid
sentence I stopped without trying it did
not make a sentence blunder
it was almost automated incredible
the branch out therapies are miracles
you will feel it they're changing lives
it's nothing that's ever been released
in this world of health and healing
and I'm so glad you guys are
experiencing that
the brain heat of Happiness can also be
exhausting
so even it's like if you play hard
or you have a lot of happiness you still
have to refill the brain it's not just
if you don't play hard and you're sick
or you don't feel good and you got to
refill the brain it's both sides
boots McGee said Anthony I had your
burnout shot today and I cannot describe
it I'm starting to feel hope and
brightness for the first time in a long
time you are a true miracle and
inspiration I'm honored you're here
incredible I'm so happy to hear that
person who's feeling pretty good in the
moment doesn't get
an immunity card when it comes to brain
heat and burning up all of our reserves
we still need the adrenal
fight-or-flight stabilizer even when
we're feeling great or when we're
feeling sick the brain heat still occurs
and burns up everything inside the brain
that's good
but we have to refill remember you guys
I was telling you guys a swimming pool
water's leaving a swimming pool and not
enough Waters coming in so the level of
the swimming pool is going down and
dropping and dropping and as the water's
going out you got water coming in but
more water is going out less water is
coming in and the swimming pool's
dropping dropping dropping dropping
the solution here isn't to stop yourself
from having emotions we all have
emotions we're all human and emotions
are going to create that
that brain Heat
we don't have total control over that
anyway we can make what feels to be a
lot of progress emotionally with
conquering demons we can move mountains
in our emotional state
and that does not mean we will stop
having emotions life is not definitive
mapped out journey we know that our life
is not somebody else's life
yet if we look at the lives of others
they can seem to have a good run for it
for a little while and we think they
must have figured everything out they're
showing their best life's moments in
public behind the scenes though they're
running into emotional quicksand more
than we know and they need help too
everybody needs the right stuff going
back into the brain
hope for healing says this adrenal
stabilizer shot is magical helping me
sleep again I hear that a lot it helps
with sleep and I want to say this really
quick you guys
when you're doing the brain shot
therapies keep in mind
healing is happening on all kinds of
different levels healing that doesn't
necessarily always match up to what the
shot says it's doing for because what
it's doing is it's healing one thing
other things start to heal because
you're healing this one thing it's
incredible what it could do
Arena says since I've been I've been
since
I've been drinking those shots I sleep
so well can't believe it
I'm hearing that all the time
their powerhouses of healing the brain
so when you're doing the shots and you
do them more often and you pick
different ones or whichever one you like
really you start to see that power that
healing
loving healing says anxiety is a beast
this adrenal shot is a legit Game
Changer this is one of my favorites but
you know at the same time I say that and
then all of a sudden there's another one
that's one of my favorites to be honest
all 30 of the brain shot therapies from
Spirit of compassion are my favorites so
it's a tough one but this one right here
this one hits me right smack instantly
and you know I heard you know a friend
of mine took this shot this brain shot
therapy the adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer and it hit him a day later
and it was like his life changed a day
later so it can it can hit at different
moments so just be prepared
MK says good afternoon SOC and Anthony I
just got my books after a week wow the
books are so high quality by the way
they are incredible high quality
and you say beautiful colors and the
important thing is the helpful
information in the books the price is so
cheap versus the quality yes there's 12
books in these two books
and the quality is unbelievable we
probably only paid for the cost to make
the book
it costs more to make the book actually
than what everybody's paying for no
profit here poor Anthony he's working
really really hard to save our lives not
making money on us as others out there
love you both too much for your
sacrifices well
it's true I will say this okay
in soc's credit right which is
incredible
always being I'm always being reminded
right the website free everything no
subscription fees no pay walls and I
agree 100 with SOC on that get the books
free at the library if you want to I
want everything free I want you guys to
heal that's all I care about and the
quality of the books are incredible
Carrie what are the brain shot therapies
and how do we get them or make them hey
I'm glad you're here you just entered
the brain shot therapy cleanse challenge
we're on day seven you can join right
now go to medicalmedium.com get all the
information from medicalmedium.com brain
saver books you do need your brain saver
books right here and here they are get
them at amazon.com us or wherever you
are Book Depository or someplace else
around the world
and what you do with the brain shots are
they're an incredible medical medium
tool that gives instant relief turning
people's lives around these are Life
Savers these are Miracles is what's
happening be the judge yourself be the
judge yourself get a chance to do it
that'd be amazing
I did my first gut nerve stabilizer it
made me high but in a good way loved it
I noticed that some of the stabilizers
will actually level you out so it'll
give you a high
which is incredible that leveling it
does can give you a high some of the
brain shots just put me right up here
and I'm just like buzzing it's
incredible really and it's all
just medicinal food in the end how
incredible but why does it work it works
because of the synergistic combinations
from above of exactly what needs to be
put together to create what it does for
what it's saying it does like adrenal
fight or flight stabilizer it's what is
here so we got the lemon we got the
garlic clove we got the parsley got the
kale got the watermelon rind and the
wild blueberry juice when you put that
together
it's an entirely different thing
Hillary says every time I read the Brain
book I am blown away by the information
so am I
I'm blown away as well by the
information I think a half time is
coming I'm Blown Away by the information
as well for real you guys want to do the
robot with me
I mean let's do it together if you guys
got a second
it's easy
take your hands like this
and just do a robot come on guys do it
with me I bet you can do a way better
one than me
[Music]
come on you guys
is this corny
someone said it's foreign
[Music]
you guys can do a better robot today
thank you
all right cool
try holding your breath though don't try
holding your breath I hold my breath
when I hear the robot so you can stay
perfectly still like
but you got to get air in there
by the end of it
all right
talking about brain heat we're talking
about the adrenal finer flight
stabilizer
we're doing it this is incredible
so
all right we could get worn down
by the little ups and downs and
challenges thrown out our way
we can get worn down by the larger
challenges that come our way
whatever life brings
we can heal the brain critical to know
our brains can burn hot
but we can cool them down by feeding our
brains what it needs think about that
how incredible it is
being prepared ahead of time is the
ultimate defense and protection for our
brain and that's what we're doing we're
preparing ourselves with this knowledge
and information so
if I know I can do an adrenal
fight-or-flight stabilizer
and I can do that one before I go into
the fire the Heat of the Moment
like I got a big day ahead of me on
meetings I got people I got to talk to
you never know what's gonna happen
you want it all to work out
you want everything to be smooth
but life doesn't really work that way we
don't have control over everything
everybody's got their own free will
just like you have your own free will so
life is always going to just throw
something at you somewhere along the way
but if you can be prepared
and do you like a fight or flight
stabilizer that morning before you go
off
or you can be prepared by having the
ingredients of the fight-or-flight
stabilizer at home in your refrigerator
so that when you're having your day and
you come home and you're like you know
what I need a fight or flight stabilizer
maybe you're on the phone with the phone
company maybe you're on the phone with
some other you know company and they got
you on hold for an hour and you're
trying to fix something and you're like
you know what I need that fight or
flight stabilizer maybe you're going to
be an old friend maybe you got to meet
family maybe somebody's in a really bad
mood that you're spending time with
whatever it is that fight or flight
stabilizer is so powerful because the
brain heat rises but we can be prepared
cut it off at the pass we can have our
stuff in hand
but one thing I'll tell you right now is
the instant relief that these
stabilizers bring
is like a true Miracle so you'll feel it
I feel it on the first sip with the
adrenal fight or flight stabilizer
really incredible
little did we know these steps
might not have been appropriate
in our life where we take these steps in
life but we didn't know we were going to
have a pitfall but we can pick ourselves
back up
and we could not only Rectify what went
wrong inside our bodies because of any
kind of stress but we can move ourselves
forward and that's another thing with
the brain shot therapies the adrenal
fight-or-flight stabilizer starts to
build you up so that when you get
another Pitfall you have a stressful
situation you have a hard day you're
already ahead
you do the fight-or-flight stabilizer I
have a doctor friend of mine now dude
the fight-or-flight stabilizer it's been
doing it for like two weeks now every
day for two weeks the fight-or-flight
stabilizer
and now what's happening
is like any kind of bad news this
doctor's getting or any kind of stress
from any kind of family situation or any
kind of stress what's happening in his
life he's like it's not even phasing him
he's doing the adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer every day for two weeks he
says it's almost like he's ahead of it
and he can just shake it off like it's
no big deal and keep on moving forward
and that's the whole point we can
actually prepare ourselves we can make
ourselves stronger so that when we're
going up against something that is
really the way to do it or you can just
like I'm gonna get it out now because
I'm having a day or I don't feel good
I'm not doing that great I feel a little
tired my energy is low I think my
adrenals are having a problem then boom
these Torino fight or flight stabilizer
really incredible
so let's talk about these medical being
braid shot therapy so I want to give you
guys a little rundown especially if
anybody's new right here
medical media brain shot therapy offers
instant relief
so it helps to rewire and reset the
brain
so the brain shot therapies rewire the
brain and actually help to reset the
brain is what they do but they do it
quickly because they absorb in the mouth
instantaneously and it drives right up
to the brain
so the whole point of the brain shot
therapy from Spirit of compassion
was to offer powerful quick relief a
quick hit
strengthening the brain so when you're
dealing with the obsessive thoughts
problem you do the obsessive thought
shifter and it's there to reset the
brain and rewire the brain quickly
when you're dealing with any kind of
stress you're dealing with the adrenal
fighter flight stabilizer it's there to
reset
the brain quickly
when you're dealing with negative
exposure that you think you're dealing
with resetting the brain putting a
shield around you and moving negative
energy out or away quickly
it has to happen quickly you know one of
the things that
you can but quickly means for anybody
could be the next morning
it could be that second you're taking it
down
and usually you'll feel it no matter
what you'll feel something when you're
taking down the shot because they're
doing something
miraculous in the moment but you can
feel the results Days Later Weeks Later
they're really potent
I remember being in my office
getting the information from Spirit of
compassion writing it down about the
brain shot Therapies
and
say well what do I do
how do I forewarn people about this
because in the Alternative Health world
you don't get things
at the snap of your fingers
an alternative health and healing world
it's just not a lot of options people
don't heal chronic illness easy out
there at all medical medium books have
fast-tracked people
in the last eight years with all the
medical medium books people have fast
tracked and their healing diseases
conditions symptoms faster than anything
but what do I tell people I said to SOC
about these brain shot therapies because
I have to forewarn them they have to
know that just like it says in the book
they have to know it comes quick I don't
want them caught off guard
so systematically these combinations of
ingredients work together to help heal
the problem you're dealing with in even
more than that deeper issues too along
with it so the power of these brain shot
therapies is just absolutely incredible
so let's talk about what are we even
doing you guys we're doing the entry
level if you just got here we're doing
the entry level brain shot therapy
cleanse we're on day seven of a 10 day
brain shot therapy challenge cleanse
right
so we're in the entry level that means
whatever diet you're doing whatever
Foods you're doing you can just continue
to continue to do
so whatever diet you subscribe to or if
you're doing medical medium stuff if
you're doing medical medium tools
whatever's happening and how you're
eating you can still keep that and still
do these brain shot Therapies
what's amazing about these Branch out
therapies they're giving you relief
while you bring in other medical medium
tools too because you're fixing other
issues deep inside your body long term
so I like having them both
the entry-level brain shot therapy
cleanse you drink 50 ounces of water
throughout the day as your minimum 50
ounces of water but don't drink the 50
ounces right when you had your shot
don't send down your shot just had my
shot let me do 50 ounces of water now
don't do that
so when you have your brain shot therapy
make sure you wait like 10 minimum 15
minutes really but 10 minutes is
probably the best the closest we can get
but you want like 15 minutes before you
start drinking or eating other things
you want that to get into your
bloodstream and get to your brain before
you Sidetrack it with other food and
things
so when you do the adrenal
fight-or-flight stabilizer make sure you
when you send it down you wait 15
minutes there's
children guidance in the brain saver
books two
and there's breastfeeding questions if
you're okay with taking the brain shot
therapies ask your doctor what's right
for you take the books to your doctors
if you want but it's fine to do brain
shot therapies while breastfeeding
so the entry level cleanse is what we're
doing and we're in 10 word seven of ten
days of it right now
and you can do one to three shots so I'm
doing three shots a day so today's the
adrenal fight or flight stabilizer so
this is the first shot
I'm gonna do a second one later and the
third one tonight
so that's how I'm doing it you can do it
the way you want to do you can do one
shot a day each day you can do two or
three
and you could do the same shot now if
you want to do
your own thing you're in the 10 day
brain shot therapy cleanse Challenge and
you want to do different shots then then
please be my guest and do different
shots that you see there's over 30 brain
shot therapy therapies here and you can
choose anyone you want and you can do
them every day and do whatever you want
to do you can be you and do that it's
totally fine it's amazing
amethyst says 15 to 30 minutes away from
food yes when you're doing the brain
shot therapy
Darcy Lee said I just did three at once
it's actually really funny
day seven adrenal fighter flight
stabilizer let's get into it
incredible you guys
all right so the ingredients are pretty
straightforward you'll see in there but
you want to keep them in order
so what you'll see over here I got
lemons I got garlic
so the first thing I need is a clove of
garlic now it says small clove of garlic
so you don't want a really large one you
know how there's elephant garlic you
guys
you don't want to get the big old
elephant garlic and have like one big
gigantic clove and you also don't want
the largest clove in the bunch
you want to go with like a medium clove
a small clove right so that's the clove
of garlic right there just getting my
ingredients ready before they run I run
them through the juicer
so that's one thing right there the
other thing is I don't have any Frozen
wild blueberries right now so I got the
Wyman's wild blueberry juice you guys
know it well right which is an
incredible tool all on its own which is
amazing and you guys know I work with
Wyman's
to try to keep the stuff out there
because it is incredible anyway what I'm
going to do is I'm going to pour some of
the wild blueberry juice into
the container after I juice the
ingredients so I'm not going to use the
Frozen wild blueberry because I don't
have any in stock in the house right now
but and they got a sale going on right
now they've had a sale going on check it
out when you when you see so go to
Wyman's but anyway that's what I'm using
I got that ready
what else do we need here
I have lemon so let's get that prepared
so it says in the book
peel your lemon right a peeled lemon so
don't juice the lemon rind
so I'm doing a half a peeled lemon in
here
so I'm peeling The Lemon Back
right and you can use a peeler I'm just
using a knife
little paring knife right
now if you have a really large Lemon
like
big old Myers lemon that's going to give
you a lot of juice just preparing you so
try to use a quarter of that big old
lemon this is kind of like you know a
smaller lemon I'm gonna use a half of
this smaller lemon
so it says it says Ginger first
is that what it says okay here's a
question here
what juicer is best so the best juicer
that I have endorsed is the mm-1500
right here
now I know the sharks are getting upset
at me
because I haven't been talking about the
MN 1500 or 900 in a while because I've
been so busy writing the books getting
the books published making sure
everything was all set but this is the
best juicer I know the sharks have
swooped into the medical medium
community and they're pushing their
juicers
but this one squeezes the heck out of
the produce and then you have more juice
when you have more juice
you save money and that's why I love
these only the mm 1500 and 900 can do
that has that high compression but
here's the incredible thing and I see
people are getting upset because they
see me defending
the mm1500
so what you have to know that this not
only juices and saves you money on that
it makes nut Butters nut milks and the
other juicers don't mix nut Butters nut
milks Salsas hummus
all of that
so that's something to be really you
know
aware of because it's incredible so
there's that but the point is is that by
far when you're saving money with your
produce and you're spending less money
on your produce
that's what the mm 900 and 1500 do
no other juicers do that in my opinion
I've tried them all they don't do it
these are designed to actually squeeze
more juice out so that means you're
saving all this money and adds up my
mm-900 paid for itself a dozen times
which juicers can't do and the MN 1500
is paying for itself all the time too so
I'm just letting you know since you guys
are asking the question now I know the
other juicer companies are telling all
their MLM people to fight back
and say oh no our squeezes all the juice
out too no it doesn't or they'll be like
whatever because they're all freaking
out because they had like the Sharks
came in when I was like asleep but I
wasn't asleep I was working my ass off
anyway guys I got the ginger for the
fight-or-flight stabilizer here
that's going to go first
and then
let's cut this lemon in half we got the
half lemon right there
so I'm just getting these all ready we
got the garlic we got the ginger
we got the lemon
so let's keep on going all right the
next thing we need is the parsley
so we need a cup of tightly packed
parsley so what I like to do I have like
little measuring way I do with my hand
because I've done it so many times
versus cups and all that so I get a cup
of parsley here
tightly packed
so I'm all set that's going to be my
parsley excited getting everything ready
so the next is kale a half cup of
tightly packed kale so I'm just gonna
roll this kale up a little bit tightly
pack it up in my hand
so get a half cup in here
so now some of this stuff is a little
juicy so you're going to get probably a
little bit more in your shot
all right
and then we got the watermelon rind so
let's get that going
one cup of chopped watermelon rind so I
got my watermelon right there
let's get up get a rind real quick
don't need much to make a cup of brine
nice
I really love
really love this stabilizer right here
the adrenal fighter flight stabilizer
just love it
gonna send these pieces down as well all
right
we got our ingredients
let's start making some
move the brain
let's go you guys you guys got your
juicers ready you got your ingredients
ready
let's fire it up
let's go
[Music]
now I don't have the Frozen wall
blueberries like I said so I'm gonna add
the wild blueberry juice in the end
so I'm going to start out with my Ginger
now look if your order isn't perfect
because you missed one first or a second
it's okay but you want to get it in
order the best you can it does help
that's what I've been told
my SOC all right
first thing in getting the ginger
okay
second thing in gonna get the clove of
garlic
[Music]
that's in there right there
third thing
it says put the blueberries in but I'm
gonna pour it in after and you can just
pour it in
right from here too if you're dealing
with the juice so I'm gonna pop in a
little bit of the juice right here
it says two teaspoons will go with a
little bit of juice right there
all right half peeled lemon
get that down there
next we're going with the parsley
here we go
I'm actually really excited
you know there's a feeling you get
when you know you're doing something so
incredible for your brain
because you're using your free will and
your intentions you're using your brain
to heal your brain you have to remember
that and how incredible that is we're
going to do some kale next
you're using
your brain to heal your brain
that's empowerment but people don't do
that and if they try to do it they get
the wrong information which doesn't help
if your brain is using the wrong
information to heal your brain it's not
going to help but when you use your
brain to heal your brain and it's the
information that actually works
that's when everything changes
so we're gonna do some watermelon rind
in here
do you guys find any watermelon
a little bit more in here
and what you'll notice with the mm1500
the the
pulp comes out like dust
so dry
incredible
all right
I'm excited and that's the thing that's
real dry pole big difference
all right you guys
let's do it
got your shot glass
I got a bunch of different shot glasses
now
there we go
[Music]
[Applause]
when you use your brain to heal your
brain and you use your soul to feel your
brain and you're using your free will
you're using your intentions
[Applause]
here we go
something special happens inside
you're breaking the rules because down
here on Earth
it's not easy to heal and it's kind of
been set up like that so people struggle
[Music]
and they don't find their way
so many sick people around the world but
we can change that
when we have tools that actually work
and change our lives
turn things around it is another
entirely different story
it's incredible
that's the first step right there
[Music]
Second Step it's hitting
incredible
thank you
that
is so powerful do you feel that
feel it inside
[Music]
incredible you guys
what I notice about the adrenal fight or
flight stabilizer
is it's hitting the brain but then my
brain is sending messages and I'm being
a little bit quiet when I'm drinking
this one because I'm trying to feel the
sensations and I feel my brain talking
to my adrenals where my brain is
actually connected to my adrenals that's
what I'm getting right now and when I do
this
Anna says oh my God I love the taste
incredible do you guys feel that I gave
it a few seconds
and I feel
what's happening inside Carrie said she
just ordered the 1500 amazing
you guys I can feel my brain talking to
my adrenals and making that connection
through the central nervous system
because your adrenals are directly
connected wire to your vagus nerves
incredible right there
you guys have you tried the brain shots
have you tried this one or here with me
what did you feel I'm telling you what I
felt please share your story right
share it on IG or anywhere else in
social media hashtag and tag at Medical
medium right please share your story and
results that would be incredible I would
love to see it so I could repost I want
people to know what this can do for
themselves because what it's doing for
me what's doing for you guys I could
feel it you guys could feel it and you
guys please re leave reviews on Amazon
if you can that would be incredible
wherever you got the books
that would be amazing if you can leave
reviews that would be just incredible
because it it helps other people know
what is in the books and what they can
do to heal and that part all on its own
is so special and remember if you get a
book remember that
all the books are pristine and they're
clean and they go to the warehouses like
Amazon and other places so when you
order one and they throw it on the
conveyor belt you might see some dirt or
grease from their conveyor belt go on
your book just get a little dish towel
or a handy wipe or something put a
little tiny soap on there a damp one
cloth and you just clean off your book
and it cleans off like brand new because
they are brand new all of them and so
you might get a book that's like that
gets smudged because it goes on the
conveyor belt and it goes on down right
and that whole bit so when you order it
just letting you know
but that shot feels so good what it does
is I could see why it's helping people
sleep at night better because it's it's
rejuvenating my brain
but at the same time supporting my
adrenals and calming me down but
strengthening me so I can tell now that
later on today I'm gonna have this extra
burst of energy because everything is
getting recharged my adrenals are
getting recharged what I was doing is
when I was sipping that Juice shot
when I was sipping that brain stabilizer
what I noticed was
it was going to my brain but then my
brain was sending a message to my
adrenals and I was feeling that message
get driven down my vagus nerves down my
spine down my other nerves and just
going down my phrenic nerves all of it
and heading down to my adrenals and my
adrenals were actually getting that
information I could feel that they were
getting that information and absorbing
it and it felt so good and all I can
think clear and feel clear is so much
better tomorrow is day eight
or the medical medium brain shot therapy
challenge we are making the guilt and
shame shifter
I'm actually psyched about that the
guilt and shame shifter
sign up medicalmedium.com for free
download your PDF your free pdf your
grocery shopping list how incredible
we're updating the website constantly
we're enhancing the website we're making
it better it's all free information you
can get like get that information
there's no pay walls all of that you
guys free resources and you can watch
the replays at medicalmedium.com too so
you can watch all seven days and soon to
be 10 days tomorrow's the eighth day
soon to be 10 days we can watch all 10
days on medicalmedium.com learn grow do
the shots all of it which is really
incredible and by the way you guys I'm
doing exclusive audio messages
on telegram every day so make sure you
check that out exclusive messages on
telegram reminder that the wild
blueberry juice is on sale you guys know
I endorsed Wyman's incredible stuff
right there and that is just amazing you
guys know that
and so you know T dot m e
slash medical medium so make sure you go
their exclusive audio messages on on
telegram so that's a great place where
I'm actually doing these messages every
day
that's a real heart to heart too I read
out of the book all of that so it's just
really an incredible time I love doing
those messages I truly do
so all of that you guys how do you feel
with your adrenal fight or flight
stabilizer how do you feel I'm starting
to get light-hearted more light-hearted
after that like my stress levels have
come down it's really incredible really
you guys look out for imposters just
just try not to get tricked by imposters
medical medium imposters they say
they're medical medium they say they're
Anthony William they say they have my
profile they
um try to get a con to get you to do a
consultation uh all kinds of just weird
stuff just look out for that there's so
many imposters right now out there in
social media and they're taking
advantage of people on their medical
medium and postures so look out for that
too if you can please leave a review on
Amazon.com if you get a chance or
wherever you got the books that would be
incredible so other people can find
their way and see the review and all of
that and you guys know I don't do
consultations but the medical mean
postures say they do consultation
somebody's like okay great I can get a
consultation with Anthony William with
the medical medium and lo and behold
it's not so
and they don't have the blue check and
they're not verified so look out for
that so the imposters don't have the
blue check and they're not verified
verified right
anyway all these things matter you guys
trying to keep it all kind of keep it
all going have you tried the light
infusion meditation that came out of the
protocols book have you tried the light
infusion meditation that's on medical
medium podcasts at Apple podcast a free
meditation
that's so powerful it's incredible and
I'll give you a rundown you guys there's
more meditations in the brain saver
books there's information about the soul
that's mind-blowing there's information
about meditations
there's all this stuff and that's not
just that 300 symptoms conditions and
protocols seven different heavy metal
detox cleanses
oh my God Advanced heavy metal detox
cleanse and the extractor
you guys will be mind blown
seven different brain shot therapy
cleanses
an incredible eating disorder chapter
that will blow your mind you won't even
believe it when you read it OCD chapter
Alzheimer's dementia chapter anxiety
depression chapter you name it bipolar
chapter but more than that it's packed
with information no one's ever heard
before no one's ever seen
by far you if you doubt this please be
the judge yourself but
best books of all time best books in
history of all Health you'll see the
greatest books of our time you will see
the medical medium shock therapies are a
miracle the information the books are
Miracle so you guys there what what let
me give you another little tidbit of
what's inside these books you guys know
about the brain shot therapies right
that we're doing like the cleanse but
there's the medical medium shock
therapies take a look at that when you
ever get a chance to when you see those
your mind will be blown they are just
incredible
for people who need that kind of support
so the medical medium shock therapies
because you guys know about the zinc
shock therapy medical medium vitamin C
shock therapy you guys know about those
but when you look
they're expanded SOC expanded the shock
therapies there are now nine shock
Therapies in the medical medium brain
saver books will blow your mind I don't
even know what to say if you're if
you're if you want bring the books to
your doctor ask them after your doctor
ask your doctor what's right for you
inside the books Incredible One wow the
first sip hits you I just saw that
comment the first sit the first sip hit
me but what happened was
I was feeling the first Sip and the
second sip go straight to the brain with
the fight-or-flight stabilizer but then
the reason why I got quiet
was I was feeling a sensation go down my
back
from my brain
and go down through my body through my
vagus nerves and reach my adrenals so I
actually was experiencing so what I was
sitting there I was doing okay I'm gonna
drink this because I can't wait to get
this in me and all of a sudden
it was happening
Sahara said I noticed a shot worked
better when I'm fat free
well you know what happens is people
aren't a lot of high fat diets right and
so you might feel the shot even
fly through your system even quicker if
you're fat free
absolutely
um Suzanne says my whole body was
vibrating oh my what I was feeling was I
was feeling like a surge go from my
brain down to my adrenals I couldn't
believe it Uma Kelly says is Dr Nesbit
going live today
I am sad to say Uma and I'm so sorry but
Dr Nesbitt
he's called out to an emergency surgery
and he will not be today he told me he
can't and I was so bummed out because I
know I wanted him to make the shot Irina
says your website is beyond fantastic aw
I absolutely love it so many crucial
healing tools and everything is for free
I am at your service
thank you very much
At Your Service
Robinson said love those audio messages
so you're listening to the audio
messages you don't want me to stop those
then Anthony your voice is so soothing
the voice of reason great right before
bed so are you okay if I keep on doing
the telegram messages so you you want
those still because I was wondering if I
was starting to bother you guys you know
what because I'm doing them every day
those those private exclusive messages
Eliza says thank you for the audio
messages on telegram so you guys are
okay with it then I will continue to do
those audio messages
if you guys are are happy about it for
sure because I was doing them every day
and I was like wait a minute mine's
starting to get bother you guys because
I'm there every day
right I just want as much free
information as I can possibly do the
podcast okay can I just say this what
you'll notice
is the medical meeting podcast is
advertisement free
there's no advertisers and commercials
at the medical medium podcast
you guys I want you to know that a
podcast that's a number one podcast in
health
to be Advertiser advertisement and
commercial free is unheard of it doesn't
exist it's the only podcast
so I'm letting you know just keep that
in mind
um that's what we're trying to do
and trust me I get crap for that that's
not a you're not allowed to do that by
the way
Gina says just left five star review the
greatest books of all time thank you
Gina incredible thank you
the reviews help if you guys can leave
reviews on amazon.com that would be
incredible it helps so much I don't even
know what to say Maria said the light
infusion meditation is incredible that
oh my God the light infusion meditation
which is Apple podcast Right medical
meme podcast at Apple podcast light
infusion meditation is incredible I do
it morning and night and sometimes if I
have trouble sleeping in the middle of
the night amazing Maria incredible
so I see Wendy says lemon balm shock
therapy absolutely the lemon bombshock
therapy in
the protocols book
is another level ask your doctor what's
right for you
but yeah it's unbelievable really
incredible and just you know and you
guys
go to my directory at medicalbeam.com to
know which lemon balm is the best if
you're gonna do that Irena says oh my
God the eating disorder chapter was so
mind-blowing am I right
when I got the information from SOC and
eating to write the eating disorder
chapter my mind was blown
lorrainelle amazing depression chapter
and OCD Lorraine I saw I saw your
comment on YouTube saying about I smell
like working class and that's what makes
that's what makes the uh
the industry's not like me like you know
they I reek of working class right
Susan says I'm doing the new shock
therapy propolis Goldenseal zinc
incredible Susan make sure you check my
directory for the right propolisync and
all that it does make an absolute
difference Envy Doom says propolis shock
therapy worked great for me probable
shock therapy is one of my favorites of
all time
the propolis by the way you guys I'm
just just saying right now hands down
right the the Emoji propolis you guys
know I endorsed femergy because of the
four reasons because the four reasons
are mind-blowing there's no supplement
company I've ever seen do what they do
there's four incredible things that they
do no no supplement companies can touch
anyway endorse them fully endorse them
right
they're propolis
hands down
in my opinion by far it's just unreal
unreal that's all I could say it's
unreal
you tell other people about it just tell
other people about the membership
propolis it is unreal anyway
incredible you guys
I'm so proud of all of you
oh the robot
you guys gonna deal with me
[Music]
Katrin says
memory is the best it is there's four
reasons why it's the best
it is the best
Lisa Smith wow love lemon balm energy it
is there's nothing like it out there
nothing out there you guys know I fully
endorsed them
because they deserve every single shout
out I could possibly do
Joshua Eldridge honored to have you here
my brother
Liberty propolis rules nothing touches
it it's the only one out there
I'm doing the worst robot right now
come on you guys
hey member protein robot protein protein
protein protein need my protein need my
protein protein protein robot
talking robot Lorraine
[Music]
foreign
I saw your
review on Amazon
you said that your highlighter ran out
of ink
because the books were so good by the
way it was an incredible story your life
story
actually
I got emotional when I read it and then
you said
you ran out of highlighters all right
you guys
[Music]
God bless you guys you guys keep on
inspiring me to keep going I'm gonna
keep on going I'm leaving a telegram
message
two nights
after I had my adrenal part of life
stabilizer
I'm gonna have my adrenal play to my
supervisor
is this for free no it's fifty two
thousand dollars a glass