comes
they smell good too right clones
perfumes
scented candles I love air fresheners
ah
I have a whole bunch of plug-ins right
now all in the walls everywhere spewing
out that
stink
smells so good
ah who wants to ever smell fresh air
again whoever wants to smell nature
again whoever wants to smell anything I
have the best detergents they're scented
they last forever they say right
detergents I use fabric softeners that
smell so good lots of chemicals going
inside of me
yes
I never want to smell anything natural
again outside I don't want to smell
trees I don't want to smell the buds on
the flowers and leaves and trees I don't
want to smell nature and fresh air I
just want to smell toxic
dangerous evil scents that are created
in the chemical industry that's what I
want ah I want potpourri fake smell and
all kinds of
these perfumes and colognes oh here it
is I got my favorite
perfume right here
very good
I am not spraying it this time on myself
because I've already sprayed it all
morning on myself and I got plenty of it
on me
wait a minute this is the cologne I use
actually it's my favorite cologne I use
yes yes see it's the brand the brand
it's the famous one right oh
cheap cologne
I got a scented candle here I was
burning it all morning it's it's a
scented one
it smells like wildflowers yeah made
from a factory somewhere
you guys what are we day 10 we're day 10
medical and brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge
and we're talking about fragrances toxic
fragrance exposure shot today
is that unbelievable we're doing the
incredible
incredible toxic fragrance exposure
shot
I am now
I am getting faint
and dizzy
all this air freshener
plugged into the walls and scented
candles
all the perfume and cologne
has made me so sick
that I think I need to just lay in bed
and curl up in feel position because
it's so toxic in here you guys
a lot of people get really affected by
it they get really sick they get sick
cologne gets into their sinuses can give
them a migraine trigger a migraine
trigger everything
I would
I would say that the world is becoming
one scented bomb at this point
there's domestic chemical Invasion that
has occurred
it's got into our lives in so many
different ways
and yeah our scented oil is bad too yes
they are
sent it scented fragrances perfumes
perfumes fragrances all of it is
terrible
terrible terrible you were talking about
the toxic fragrance exposure shot so
let's just read let's get into it a
little bit word day 10 of the medical
Bean brain shot therapy clinch challenge
can I just say
this is a 20-day challenge if you just
arrived and you're like what is he
talking about what's he doing
you can sign up
to the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge for free just go to
medicalmedium.com and you can download
your free grocery shopping list you can
see the rest of the shots we're doing
you can choose the shots you want to do
all of it you can do them one time a day
three times a day we're doing the entry
level and we're doing a 20-day
and it's incredible I also had the of
course cold and flu tool kit to make
sure you download
go to medicalmedium.com and find that
download that baby right there
so you have the things you need because
yep everybody's getting knocked on their
butt by RSV flus and C they're all being
knocked on their butt seven herbs and
supplements to keep on hand for when
that comes storming through cold and flu
has come storming through so check out
that download and you'll see
it's really cool
nothing worse
than getting hit from the flu and at the
same time you're hit by cologne perfume
and everything else go to
medicalmedium.com and watch this now
live we're streaming this live right now
at medicalmeaning.com how cool is that
you can watch a replay there too
and you can download the cold and flu
toolkit like I said before at
medicalmedium.com
right
fragrances cause families to divide and
fight now
those who can't handle the sense are the
canaries
they become chemical sensitive
they've reached their saturation point
think about it for a minute
there's a whole bunch of people out
there they're like the canaries they've
reached their Tipping Point of being
able to handle those contaminated
dangerous chemical sense produced by
chemical factories around the world
and they reach their saturation point
and then there are the people who love
their sense still they haven't reached
their saturation point and they're
supporting the chemical industry
they say they're for the environment
meanwhile they're partaking in one of
the worst things that's being released
into the environment
the industry is causing families to
fight over this and divide
how can sense be more important than our
health and our families
why is perfume so important why is
cologne so important why is air
freshener so important why is
all the different toxic fragrance stuff
that were up against all the time why is
it more important than our family
members who are really oversaturated by
this chemical and they're the canaries
people go into battle over it it's
really really difficult for so many
people
so what I wanted to talk to you guys
about is this fragrance toxic fragrance
and medicalmean.com right
I actually go to Apple podcast right for
the medical meeting podcast on Apple
podcast and listen to the fragrance
episode it's it's incredible
Aussie oxymoron good handle on YouTube
someone told me I'm weird because I
don't wear perfume everyone smells of
perfume there is no fresh air anymore it
is very difficult to meet people or even
to be outside I concur 100 oxymoron with
that comment more than you even know
actually no you do know what you're
singing to the choir or how does it work
I totally agree I get it
I don't know what kind of mood I'm in
today but I can't wait to get that air
freshener
perfume cologne drink down anti-one down
Erica Malek says I've been housebound
for six months since my multiple
chemical sensitivity has become severe
not many people understand not many
people do understand
they don't
shen77 says what's a canary
it's an old term for someone basically
what happens is that down in the coal
mines
if they lost oxygen and gases from the
earth were taking over they would have a
canary sitting in a cage
and everybody would be working chipping
away that coal mining whatever minerals
or ore and then all of a sudden you see
the canary die in the cage that means
you've got very little time but you've
got to get out of that cave out of that
mine shaft
Canary dies first
Nadia two years completely fragrance
free and I have no sinus problems
anymore it was triggering all your
problems it was breaking down the immune
system and that's what happens people
don't realize it breaks down the immune
system all this stuff
Aquarius on IG I was diagnosed with
asthma in my 20s but it was really the
perfume I was spraying on myself daily
it was making me choke breathing it in
may I just add this
people have no idea how toxic the stuff
really is out there in the world and
they don't know how serious it is out in
the world and I'm going to tell you
right now that
there's all these people in the health
movement right now okay there's all
these people claiming they're into all
natural stuff they got their avocado
toast going on in the morning they're
doing their YouTubes maybe they're an
influencer
but yet they won't let go of the scented
stuff
they go to their functional medicine
doctor they go to their healer
they even do their ayahuasca microdosing
every now and then with friends
and a shaman somewhere
but they have air fresheners in their
car they Light Sent the candles all the
time they spray perfume and cologne all
over them and they support the chemical
industry that creates these deadly
chemicals and puts them into our lives
and they support it
there's a whole group of people out
there that are all into nature and
preserving animals and being good with
animals and
protect the rainforest and don't let
don't let the forest burn down and
they're all about the turtles on the
beach
they're all about the sea turtles and
protecting them but what they don't
realize every time they're spraying
their perfume cologne their air
fresheners their detergents with all the
scents and fragrances and all of the
above
and many more
they're actually supporting Financial
financially supporting the massive
chemical industry which is destroying
the turtles
the sea turtles the trees the
environment our healthy air all of it
and all you see out there on social
media
you see all these
young women and young men
and older women in Old Men older men
doing their thing on social media
showing that they live this
nice lifestyle and they're all about
eco-friendly vegan Shoes vegan leather
shoes you name it
and they're literally doused in
fragrances
literally doused in fragrances if you
were a fly on the wall and walked into
their house and went into their their
closets
it would be perfume cologne
scented candles everywhere in their
house and they're supporting the
chemical industry which is actually
killing the planet
anyway all right let's go you guys we're
day 10 medical medium Branch out therapy
clinch challenge let's get to page 2
210.
I want to get to page 210 in the brain
saver book Incredible fragrance is
common fragrance exposures
plug-in air fresheners
take this plug-in air fresheners and
throw them out boom pull them out of the
wall and throw them out
I was getting a little too out of hand
out of hand on one of the shows
previously and almost a few days ago and
someone commented is there any way you
can just calm down a little bit and talk
really common slow and I'm like what do
you mean I am right
common fragrance exposures
scented candles
yeah how many scented handles are in
your home
I'm not going to name any brands or
anything
but oh my God people are using these
scented candles
it gets into their walls it gets into
the furniture it gets into their bedding
it gets into all their blankets he gets
into every single orifice of their home
and it saturates it for a lifetime they
can live a life be a hundred years old
die and then the home sells to someone
else and that person buys that home or
enters that apartment and rents that
apartment
and that smell will still be there a
hundred years later if that home is
still standing and then that person will
still smell uh all those years of those
scented candles and air fresheners and
everything else it could last hundreds
of years if a home is around hundreds of
years with these modern everyday
chemicals that were exposed of to right
now then it will last every Century
someone will smell what the old
person who lived in it 100 200 years ago
was using it would be all those scents
and all those fragrances it won't be any
natural smells like the natural wood
smell in the house or the natural
whatever house you know would house that
natural smell on the Furnitures and
everything else it would just be
chemicals chemicals chemicals so we live
in a world now and the hospitals are
filled with chemicals too and that's a
scary thing for a lot of people that are
sick they're sick and they end up going
to the hospital because they they
something happened and they fell or some
got hurt they went to the hospital to
get an x-ray and they're breathing in
every single chemical in the book so
it's like chemical fragrances have
gotten into every single orifice
common fragrance exposures aerosol can
air fresheners which are big too
including squeezy bottles spray bottle
air fresheners and Mists it's like
oh this was only made in a chemical
Factory somewhere synthesized made from
a whole bunch of toxic chemicals where
if you were dipped in it you would maybe
not make it
if it was filled into a massive vat and
you were dipped in and had to bathe in
it
God only knows what would happen but
it's okay to spray it around everywhere
and spray it in the air and spray it on
your furniture and spray all that stuff
right
so we talked about the plug-in air
fresheners plug-in air fresheners are
tricky one that stuff puffing out it
Puffs out and puffs out and then it
clings to everything clings to the walls
clings to every countertop every
clothing item clings to all your shirts
clings to your jackets gets into every
part of the house
Finds Its way into your car
all right and I talked about the set of
candles too everybody's lighting the
scented candles who's crazy you know
when the whole the whole sea lockdown
happened right no one was on the streets
everybody was home
no one was out right there was the
lockdowns were going down you guys know
what I'm talking about a few years ago
all that
and then what happened well I'll tell
you what happened
a billion people bought scented candles
and they were all just shrines in their
rooms and in their houses it was all
over every single you know app every
single platform out there everybody was
just scented candles just lighting them
constantly it was like
the scented candle chemical
industry
exploded when C happened and the
lockdowns happened
it was like a boom like no other
so it fed the chemical industry to
produce more and more
deadly chemicals
and that was the result everybody was
bored out of their minds
everybody was sitting in the room and
they had their you know Facebook running
and Instagram running and everything
else running and they're lighting their
scented candles having their little
get-togethers
and the scented candle Arena exploded
billions going into the chemical
industry to create more chemicals
but yet everybody's so like health
conscious too right
eating good having their oatmeal
having their avocado toast and boom just
burning all these scented candles
cologne's an aftershave that's one right
there after a shave let me just put on
some aftershave here okay I'm Steve
a good shave right here
okay
let me stop on the aftershave there
that's great
very good maybe my girlfriend
will like getting that all over her face
when she kisses me
let me get some aftershave here I just
got back from the gym just worked out
let me put some aftershave on
highly toxic crap
migraines are so common and people don't
realize what some of the triggers are
these are the triggers right here
migraines are so common amongst all the
the influencers now they don't realize
one of the big triggers is all these
chemicals I'm talking about it's the
aftershaves
yeah it's just shaving creams let me
just use the
deadliest shaving cream possible with
all the crazy chemicals in it
that's insane whole house will smell
like that shaving cream for a year
said the candles air fresheners perfumes
colognes exploding in their major
migraine triggers
all the influencers are like migraines
migraines going through this functional
doctor migraines migraines I'm on this
drug
let me just put on my aftershave
yeah like you need an aftershave are you
freaking kidding me
you need an aftershave
what
you need some
horrifying stinky ass smelling crap from
a chemical industry you need to slap
that on your face after you just shaved
are you kidding me
huh
all right you guys let's just get
through this because we got a lot to
read and talk about
cologne that's another one clone is so
so toxic
it's an instant migraine for people it's
an instant immune system lower Earth
it lowers the immune system
that's a big one right there cologne you
can smell cologne
on a beach
if some dude was wearing it
and the wind was going the right
direction and some dude was wearing it
and the dude was
three miles
down the beach
SSC said five miles down the beach
five miles
down the beach if the wind is coming
that direction your direction after
blowing past the dude
with cologne on you're gonna smell it
while you're trying to smell salt air
or if you're on a lake beach fresh air
fresh water air
it's crazy clones are a huge one you go
into an airport what do you smell
you don't smell anything but cologne you
only smell cologne you walk into an
airport you smell one thing and one
thing only it's cologne cologne crushes
even perfume
women's perfume cologne crushes it
that's how bad cologne is
you go into an any airport in this world
and all it is is a cologne shower you're
doused when you leave that airport you
come off that plane you come home you're
doused in Cologne you are cologne it's
in your lungs it's in your sinuses it's
in your shirts it's in your clothing
it's in your your suitcases
yeah
people are so loaded with rotting
protein and putrefying fats inside their
guts it's pouring through their cells
it's coming out of their lymphatic
vessels it's stuck in their liver
they're they're so filled with rotting
stuff inside of them that they smell
like ammonia so what happens is
to hide that stink from them being so
toxic it's like
I smell like [ __ ] so bad it's pouring
out of me and people know I stink and
smell like [ __ ] so bad I'm just gonna
use this deadly chemical crap and I'm
just gonna
hide the fact that I stink so bad
but let me tell you I'd rather smell
somebody's rotting putrifying [ __ ]
that's coming out of them because
they're highly toxic their liver is
overburdened it's coming through their
skin
their their bodies thinks their pants
stinks I would rather be around someone
that smells like that at least I know
that that stuff isn't gonna kill me it's
not going to actually get into my
bloodstream and do some damage it's not
like cologne and perfume I'd rather
smell what people smell like I'd rather
know what they smell like I'd be like
yeah you got a good smell to you man
dude you've got a lot of rotting protein
in you did you just fart again yeah it's
definitely pretty bad you got a good
smell to you man I'd rather have that
than
go up to some of the oh my God that
cologne is killing me it's killing me
another thing too Central Oils stink too
and they trigger migraines too
I don't care how authentically natural
or the quality of essential oil they
trigger people all the time they trigger
their lungs their nervous system they
trigger their sinuses they trigger their
migraines
and then they float around and saturated
to the walls if everybody's doing
essential oils non-stop they saturate
the walls and saturate the furniture and
eventually create a mold problem I
talked about this on Rumble this episode
on Rumble with that
I'm not saying you can't use essential
oils I'm just saying that there's a lot
to understand about all this stuff
another thing too is you'll find that
they're taking essential oils and
they're putting it in toxic project
products so it might be like oh our
detergent has essential oil of orange in
it our detergent has essential oil of
lemon in it meanwhile it also has
perfume perfume perfume and fragrance in
there that's not the essential oil so
then you're tripped so there's all these
products now that have essential oils in
it that you think are natural with
essential oil but they're not there's
fragrances in there perfumes and
perfumes in there it's all in there
Health with Hennis is essential oils
episode was amazing thank you it's
really a good one
good information
if you don't want your house to always
smell like those essential oils forever
don't ease them
because someone was saying that
this isn't an essential oil attack I'm
talking about the chemical industry I'm
talking about fragrances and perfumes
perfumes colognes and all the different
fragrances and right the detergents the
fabric softeners and even more than that
right that the household cleaners with
all the fragrance in it oh my God walk
down the grocery store and I talked
about the other day walk by the the
toiletries the toiletries
every time I have to walk down through
that aisle for some reason
with family or some whatever or friend
and I gotta walk down that aisle of
toiletries I'm just like toiletry hell
it's it's it's so highly toxic
you know like I'm thinking this right
right that I don't like the smell or
something and everybody loves the smell
but I don't think you guys like it right
IG comment right here Sarah Valentine
yes some high
so let's see some high-end Japanese
restaurants do it
and send an email reminder fragrance
interferes the dining experience whoa
it kills the smell of food you won't
smell the food that was really good
point you won't smell the food in a
restaurant
you will smell cologne in perfume in a
and air fresheners too and chemical
cleaners that the restaurant uses on the
tables
not going to smell the food really it
just gets into the hypoglossal nerve it
gets into the nerves and the cranial
nerves it gets into all of them
but clear nerve it just gets into all
the different cranial nerves and it just
starts to beat it down those fragrances
the chemicals
beats it down all right
car air fresheners that's a new
experience
that's a really new experience car air
fresheners
yeah car services
Ubers whatever
people's cars with air fresheners
in the vents of the car sitting there
air fresheners I'm not just talking
about the one that's terrible too the
one that hangs from the
whatever the rear view mirror hair
fresheners in the cars and car services
that's a whole nother one whoa
incense that's a big one too
don't even think for a second that
incense is pure
it's just incense
just burning incense
it's a spiritual incense
it has to be pure it's just herbs
glued to a stick
and then you light it and it burns yeah
that's the smell that's the smell of
of you know Spiritual Awakening
don't even think for a minute
that that stuff isn't laced with
chemicals and fragrances because it is
it is
scent diffusers you know centif users
the food diffusers that release the bad
sense right
scented body lotions creams oh that's a
big one right there oh don't worry I'm
just using this body lotion right here
no big deal if they say it's all natural
it's got essential oil in it BS
okay okay I'm gonna you know put the
body oil on I just took a shower and I'm
putting body oil on everywhere right oh
my God people don't realize that scented
body oil
how intensely toxic and how bad it
stinks
it's bad for you it's a major trigger
scented body lotions
scented creams sprays washes I'm just
gonna use this body wash you guys don't
mind right
this is private right here I'm in the
shower right now I got this body wash
going on me
ah it smells so fresh I had a body wash
I just purchased this body wash
with perfume in it perfume in it
everything else in it
with dangerous chemical sense just
purchased a body wash are you kidding
I'm an influencer on YouTube but I want
to show you my collection right here
you're in my bathroom I want to show you
things I have here I have a body wash
from blah blah blah I have a body lotion
here from
I have I have my body lotions I have my
body wash you might want to check out
the link below for the body wash that
companies like really great and it's
really natural I have my body wash I
have my body cleanser I have my facial
cleanser I have my whatever here in the
bathroom
and they all they're really great
companies and they don't smell I have my
scented lotions I have my
all the different things here so
um yes I'm on YouTube I'm doing a
tutorial right now here's my body wash
in my body
lotions
this smells so great
scented shampoos
conditioners gels I don't think I even
started the show yet did we even start
this show yet all right Sandy shampoos
conditioner is jealous and other hair
products
okay bad bad for you okay scented
laundry detergent fabric softeners and
dryer sheets I'm trying to write I'm
trying to move along now
I got lost
cosmetics and makeup so I want to do a
makeup tutorial for you this is my
YouTube channel and this makeup right
here it's clean they say
um does it smell uh yeah it's scented
with every kind of perfume possible and
fragrance
cosmetic and make makeup drier dust
exhaust on the outside air dryer vents
and homes using everything under the sun
conventional laundry products colognes
perfumes scented candles and air
fresheners and here's the thing about
dryer vents it isn't just
the dryer sheet or the detergent you
washed your clothes in that was the
scented stuff that's getting the dryer
tumbling and blowing out get ready for
this it's the perfume the person wears
with it all it's the it's the perfume
it's the cologne it's the air fresheners
in the house saturating everything the
whole thing smells like one big bomb and
that's blowing out of the dryer dryers
don't just blow out your dryer sheet
smell they just don't blow out your
detergent smell dryers blow out endless
streams of air freshener cologne perfume
body lotion whatever every smell you got
that stinks from the chemical companies
and it's blowing out your dryer and
guess what a little bird going by tweet
just want to bother I'm just an innocent
little person that just put a bug and
pig what's the smell chemical companies
chemical factories
the fragrance sector of the chemical
industry is far from innocent far from
innocent man
rap bastards the industry has a set of
goals
one goal is to keep their chemicals in
mass production
to do this they want to keep people
purchasing their chemicals so let's keep
on purchasing those scented candles and
all those air fresheners let's keep on
purchasing all that perfume cologne and
every other thing in body lotion that
scented sure let's feed the industry all
the money they ever wanted they can
produce more chemicals
and kill the environment so every bird
never knows what the natural air ever
smells like again no one cares about
what a bird smells nobody cares about a
hawk and the fact that the hawk has to
breathe in every single dryer vent
spewing out of every single house
when nobody cares
of course not why should we right to do
this they want to keep people purchasing
their chemicals and to do that they want
to condition and train people they want
to brainwash them to believe they need
these synthetic fragrances and scents
you need that synthetic fragrance
and what about the
what about our pets inside the house
breathing in all of that
last but not you know or their pets that
are outside breathing all of that in
outside what about children breathing
all that in
I mean we don't want our children
breathing in all that chemical from
chemical industries does that make any
sense
it's about learning the truth and
getting empowered
because you just don't want the stuff to
keep on getting stronger out there and
growing and taking over the planet
if you know about it
it at least helps you because
it's going to affect us either way
just because look it doesn't make it go
away if you don't know about it if
you're somebody that doesn't want to
know about it and you want to just be
ignorant to it and you don't want to you
want to put a blind eye to it
it doesn't go away it's there it's
tormenting a lot of people and a lot of
animals and a lot of Wildlife
they want to condition and train people
to believe they need these synthetic
fragrances and scents last but not least
they want to take away any future chance
for someone to know what nature really
smells like did you hear that
did you guys hear that get ready last
but not least the chemical industry
wants to take away any future chance for
someone to know what nature really
smells like your children's children
will not know what nature smells like
on planet Earth down the road these
chemicals have taken over
I can promise you your children's
children won't know what this planet
smells like
Spirit of compassion has told me that
it's not my guess
Spirit of compassion has told me our
children's children are never going to
know what nature smells like again
on this planet
Kendall McCargo says knowing the truth
helps make an informed decision that can
change your life and help prevent
further damage
way better said than me
it's better said than what I would say
whether smelling Ocean Air at the beach
smelling the Earth and fresh air of the
forest
or smelling flowers and freshly moaned
grass
As the Wind rustles Through trees in
your backyard
they want to destroy and disrupt the
authentic experience and they will
destroy and disrupt it for your
children's children
Jenny Jenn said my neighbor's cat smells
like drier sheets from lying on her bed
my friend invited me on a
little boating
trip
was like a really small boat
we went out
he said let's smell some fresh air
all I could smell the entire time on
this little boat
was all the scented [ __ ]
that was trapped on my friend's body
and in his clothes
including the chemicals he used to clean
his little boat
including
the bug repellent he sprayed
just a can of bug repellent in the
corner of the boat made it so you
couldn't smell a darn thing
it was the worst wasted outing I've had
I could not smell the water I could not
smell the air I could not see the clouds
and have a vision of smelling like
something good while you're looking at
the clouds roll by all you smelt was
just chemical chemical chemical
and all I did was complain the whole
time
gen Z said Can enough people not wake up
and make a change for the future or it's
hopeless it's a tricky one because when
you see people who are supposed to be
health-minded all over social media apps
everywhere
who are influencers and they're supposed
to be health-minded and they say they're
health-minded and they're doing all
these healthy things with their foods
and no processed foods and they're
choosing vegan leather you know shoes
slippers and heels and sneakers or
whatever
and they're not doing it and they're
totally addicted to their sense and
their their perfumes colognes and all
the conventional sprays and air freshers
I don't think there's hope I try to
spread the word
you know so that people stop buying the
products and educate other people out
there they stop buying all the scented
fragrances and all the different
products and everything
here is IG comment aw you're the only
person that ever described multiple
chemicals sorry
hey W you're the only person that has
ever described multiple chemical
sensitivity exactly as it is I cried
when I read your chapter on it thank you
thank you for being here
we're
Amanda says how do we stop it question
mark times 10 question marks
we're trying to stop it
I put it in the medical medium books I
talk about it wherever I can
you know I'm trying to actually stop it
the key is enough people have to
complain out there in the world and stop
buying the products that are scented so
that the chemical industry sees a
reduction
of their investment into it like they
see a reduction of sales so they start
to slowly push them out you know of the
market
we're coming to a time when we're not
going to know what any of these natural
surroundings smell like we're only going
to be surrounded by contaminating
fragrances
you walk into Whole Foods now
all you smell is everybody's stuff you
think everybody's shopping in Whole
Foods
is health-minded or natural or plant
or sorry Planet saving mind
of planet-saving mind
and health
mindset right you walk in there the
stink
of everybody's sense coming off of them
and blowing off them air fresheners on
their clothes
send the candles all over whatever
everything you name it it's just one big
cologne bath you go into any place now
fragrances are unlike other toxic
chemicals
many toxic chemicals have a shelf life
and dissipate over time
the rain can dilute certain outdoor
toxic chemicals for example thin them
out and make them less harmful the rain
cannot thin out a toxic chemical
that's saturated with fragrance
the rain cannot even thin out
God's nature
the Earthly mother's nature rain
a substance
created from our Earthly mother cannot
fit out
saturated fragrances
fragrances are being created to last for
an eternity
extremely long time and not dissipate
in many cases fragrance can be
unstoppable
Unstoppable
I'm dramatic today we're on the verge of
never being able to smell what The Ocean
Air is like when we're standing on the
beach because we're just going to be
smelling fragrances blowing off of
people
I'm dramatic for a reason because that
right there all of this is so sad it
breaks my heart so I'm really passionate
about you know talking about it because
it's it's just terrible
Jamie the best thing that ever happened
to me is working from home all the
smells in the office killed me
it's terrible
I'm happy you're working at home it
makes me happy
for you
fragrances are unidentified chemicals
even more so than other domestic
chemical industry Invader products
which you'll read about in the next few
pages one loophole in the chemical
industry is this fragrances don't have
to list the multiple chemicals within
them
all they have to list is fragrance
100 deadly chemicals in there just
listed fragrance
when you see the word fragrance in a
list of ingredients you're looking at
corruption
because in that word are a host of
different chemicals that will not be
listed as ingredients in that product
using a product that lists natural
fragrance is not a way out
there are still chemical industry
fragrances in natural fragrances
the chemical industry is allowed to call
a fragrance natural
if there's one single essential oil
added to the mix of the industrial
chemicals that's why my makeup
or that's why my body wash and my body
lotion is so great it says essential oil
oh I'm not really looking at that other
word in there on the bottle that's
fragrance
but it says essential oil natural
if there's one single essential oil
added to the mix of industrial chemicals
they can tag their fragrance as being
natural
what an evil Escape
whether scented products seem
conventional or natural what you'll find
listed in them are fragrance
or natural fragrance
or perfume
you will not see the list of chemicals
in the fragrance or perfume so you'll
miss out on any understanding of how
many industrial created chemicals
go into making that scent even if it
says naturally derived it still doesn't
mean it gets a free pass
there's a comment on IG
I save so much money now anything with
perfumes perfume or natural fragrances
is left on the Shelf boom
boom
amazing
many people in the health scene are
concerned about conventional products oh
this is pretty cool
many people in the health scene are
concerned about conventional products
so they're using clean makeup
clean hair care products
Clean Skin products
meanwhile these products all have either
fragrances or natural fragrances or
perfume in them or any combination
if you were to sit inside a chemical
Factory watching people with hazmat
suits did you hear that
did you hear that hazmat suits
walking around giant containers of
swirling chemicals
and then you saw those chemicals being
put into a fragrance and that fragrance
sold to all the different companies that
sell all these products
with your clean makeup and your skincare
and your body washes and your body
lotions
you would be shocked
off your butt
it didn't say that it said you will be
shocked to say the least
I said shocked off your butt Spirit
compassion said you would be shocked to
say the least
sabotaged self-care let's read a little
bit about this real quick
we're adopting healthier Lifestyles we
are adopting healthier lifestyles
or eating healthier foods yes we are
eating healthier foods out there in the
world you see it everywhere everybody
top five foods
we're concerned about our environment
yes we are concerned about our
environment everybody is
and at the same time we're allowing
perfumes colognes and fragrances to be
inside everything many people are
concerned about climate change
and at the same time they're
contaminating our climate with chemical
industry soups that are highly toxic and
even affect wildlife
one reason we turn to fragrances is
self-care
we're picking out perfumes and scented
candles and scented lotions and scented
everything because they're supposed to
relax us make us relax and put us in the
right frame of mind
we think we're promoting well-being by
using fragrances another reason we use
so much fragrance is that our bodies
have smells and fragrance is how we hide
our stink
it means all these fragrance chemicals
are inside our brain we're allowing
chemical Giants to hurt our brain age
our skin and body age our lungs and age
our organs speed up the disease process
and at the same time age our pets
fragrances are in air freshener scented
candles makeup including clean makeup
skin care Hair Care body care products
weather clean or regular and
conventional laundry products the more
organic or clean we go with our domestic
products for body care and more the more
loopholes the chemical Giants find to
put their fragrances with unidentified
toxic chemicals into these products
what I'm trying to say is the more
loopholes
the more products we have the more
loopholes the chemical industry uses
foreign
we go with our domestic products for
body care and more the more loopholes
the chemical Giants find to put their
fragrances with unidentified toxic
chemicals into these products it's
imperative we get wise to it and avoid
fragrances including perfumes
so you want to read this last little
part here
so
uh end maker says so what do we buy 10
question marks
I do try to put better options on the
medicalmedium.com directory for those
who are asking
forced exposure
we all need to get wise to the ways the
chemical industry tries to expose us to
these fragrances even when we don't
personally use them
for example scented candles and plug-in
air fresheners saturate walls even if
the person using them moves out anyone
who moves into the home or office
afterward has to contend with the
lingering scent
fragrances can become mold harboring a
film begins to develop from burning
scented candles or using plug-in air
fresheners and that film collects on
every Fabric and fixture inside the home
trapping particles of dust and debris
that flow into the air
I'm in brain saver I'm on page 212 right
here can I show you guys
trapped in the film this debris can
Harbor moisture creating a perfect
situation for mold to grow someone often
uses fragrance in the first place to
cover the smell of mold or mildew in a
space in a situation like this where
mold is already present adding fragrance
products such as air fresheners or
scented candles can accelerate the mold
fulfillment centers
Manila says Anthony help I'm so
sensitive to all perfumes perfumes when
I go outside my house
my health is in in horror or my house is
in the horror
check this out you guys
it breaks my heart first to begin with
okay
that anybody's hypersensitive and they
got the chemical sensitivities and they
have to deal with all this stuff
that's awful fulfillment centers and
warehouses are shipping out products
such as clothing that are saturated with
air fresheners contaminating the
products that arrive at our homes and
workplaces so you know what's happening
is the clothing the Fashion World the
clothing companies
it's being saturated because the work
houses
in some of these situations with
clothing right
are filled with air freshener and the
Fulfillment centers
all of it filled with air fresheners
drier dust is extremely toxic when any
fragrances are used in the home which
means that neighbors get exposed this
dryer exhaust is a combination of the
air fresheners in the home plus perfumes
cologne scented candles Cosmetics body
products saturating all the clothes
being laundered
combined with the fragrances of the
laundry detergents and fabric softeners
used all blowing hot air
in polluting the environment
guys let's make the shot let's just talk
about the shot for a second
this is the toxic fragrance exposure
shot we're doing right now here's here's
a comment on IG great information
Vincent says if we don't know
we can't change it
I love smelling the refreshing when I go
out in the bush
cool so when you go outside and you're
out there in the fields
out in the bush many people call it
you're out on the water you're in the
woods you love the smell
frana says sometimes I thought something
was wrong with me because I can't stand
perfume or deodorant it's like we're
we're
if you have a problem with it you're the
problem
that's how they try to do it
oh you can't handle it
you just you don't like the perfume
cologne and air fresheners and scent of
candles and everything else and
detergents and all that stuff you don't
like all the deadly chemical stuff
created in chemical factories oh you're
the problem
it's not me I have every right to put
all that chemical on me and smell any
way I want too bad that's your problem
is this what the world does
sassy at my old place of employment a
woman wore a super strong perfume that
triggers my migraines
it would linger for hours through
hallways Etc I had to get
out of the building
it's like you can linger in your sinuses
for days
and then in your bloodstream when my
neighbor left his house
his perfume is so strong it goes through
my door inside my apartment it makes me
sick
that's another thing too it's like
people think they're making themselves
smell nice right
they get a new perfume a new cologne
when I see like a cologne commercial and
it's something like dude
it's got no clothes on
got a couple of tattoos
it's a hired model
sitting on top of like a Ferrari or some
[ __ ] right and he's and it's a it's a
clone commercial
and it's like oh yeah I can't wait to go
up to you
Mr hot dude because you probably smell
so good so inviting
I'd love to just give you a hug and
breathe in all that delicious cologne
okay check this out right
other people poisoning people is what
I'm trying to say with their scented
chemicals clones and whatever it's not
just poisoning the person they're
actually poisoning everyone around them
including the environment whatever all
else including pets including animals
okay
toxic fragrance exposure
try this shot when you've been exposed
to toxic fragrances and sense through
such circumstances as Gatherings of
people with fragrances coming off their
persons
try this shot if you're walking through
department stores grocery stores other
shops or visiting doctors offices where
exposure to perfume cologne fabric
softeners scented candles air fresheners
and other fragrances could be present
try this shot
if you're recently driving in a car
where air fresheners are installed and
or family members saturated with perfume
cologne trapped in the car with them
laundry detergents and other chemical
toxic scents we're in the car with you
especially the aftershave too
ah
it's nothing like putting that
aftershave on
smells so good
try this shot if you're close contact
with other saturated and hair products
aftershave Cosmetics body lotions and
body oils
you guys know that this is off
like fun and games but I can't tell you
how much [ __ ] I get for putting this
information out there I've been doing it
for decades and I can't tell you how
much crap I've gotten
like for putting this information out
there
bad media
like what happens is
media will like
do a smear campaign or hit piece on me
because chemical industry
will get them to do it
because I do [ __ ] like this because I I
actually put this out there
for years and years
okay
try this shot
when a neighbor's laundry sending dryer
exhaust filled with perfumes cologne to
send it to church with the fabric
softeners enter the air and you're
breathing it in choking on it's get the
shot down
all right so let's do let's make a shot
guys this is fun
I'm gonna get the old juicer out
let's do it
I got my shot glass right here
I got
my containers I got the mm-1500
which a friend told me that he's
actually saving money
he got he didn't believe me with the MN
1500 it's purchased every single juicer
out there
and I said no you got to believe me on
the mm-1500 like
he goes well I'm only going to believe
you because you're always right about
stuff
and you're always straight out with me
that's what he said so I said okay we'll
get the 1500 got the 1500
and he said but he said I just didn't
think I could save that much money
that's what he said I thought I'd save a
little but not a lot so then he was
keeping tabs on exactly how much produce
he was buying to run through the juicer
and then he he weighed that against what
his other juicer was and everything and
he said it was insane it was like it was
like hundreds he's saving a week and
he's allowed to juice now
because of the food costs going up
all right
one radish foreign
I'm gonna cut this radish up in a few
pieces I'm gonna send it down
and radish
I'm looking forward to this one
one cup roughly chopped green leaf
lettuce
okay
this is a green looking drink
foreign
lettuce in here
nice
I'm excited about this one put a little
bit more green lettuce in here
that's about a cup because it was tight
and packed a whole cup of tightly packed
lettuce
you need just a little bit more I've
been down that road before with the
whole cup
okay
all right
next is one cup tightly packed fresh
cilantro this beautiful cilantro right
here
now what you'll see with my cilantro and
you'll notice
this is the cilantro
that grows in the middle of the plant
it doesn't have the leaves it has more
of like the fur Fern kind of thing
looking
I picked it out of the garden
so it's
cilantro
okay there we go
all right now we need a half of an apple
nice
Audra Lynn says I went on a movie date
with a guy he showed up with so much
cologne on I moved three seats away from
him in the theater because I was choking
on the cologne needless to say there was
so there was no second date now I want
to say something about this
how is a guy
you know there's it's like
you go on a date how does the guy expect
the date to work out good
if he's like slathered in that cologne
how can you have a conversation with the
person on the date if they're if they're
not they're just breathing in nothing
but clone I mean how can you even have a
conversation just think about exactly
your situation or anybody that would be
sitting there it'd be like trying to
talk it's like so what do you do for a
living
well
I work for this office in this office
um
why are you holding your hand over your
face your cologne's really bad
let me let me learn about you do you
have any pets
um yeah and I don't want to expose those
pets to your cologne tonight so you're
not coming back to my apartment
all right
you guys
did we do this one
we did this one
I just want to show you
that pulp is dry
so dry
and that I'm sorry I don't see with
other juicers and that's how people save
the money this is the mm-1500
really proud of this machine
for what it does
it's why I endorsed them
dang right
you're gonna save people money
you better believe it
you guys this is the fragrances exposure
shot
might I add toxic fragrance exposure
shots
I'm just waiting see what I feel
start to hit me now I only had a sip
[Music]
why do I get all this cool sensation and
tingles I get a feeling from my head my
whole head
all through my body from these shots
is it because of the synergistically
combined ribbon ingredients in the
phytochemical compounds involved then no
one would know work together to actually
battle or up against and that's what
these things are
from Spirit combustion
[Music]
bartender
give me another
[Music]
what would you like I'm the bartender
here
bartender give me another
I certainly shall give you another one
there
what's your name
William
hey Mr William here's your dream
thank you
so good
bartender give me another
[Music]
really really good
oh my God
[Music]
incredible
I gotta sit down why the incredible
nature
of this
sets in
it feels so good there's a comment on IG
good question are you taking shots on an
empty stomach
well you don't have to take the shots
but try to drink the shots 15 to 30
minutes apart from any other food or
drink it doesn't mean you might not have
a totally empty stomach not like in the
morning when you drink you know lemon
water but you you should have 15 to 30
minutes away from food
Rosita says what's the brand of that
Geezer please
it is Omega but please know that the
other Omega juicers are not like the
1500 they're not like the mm-900 these
are the mm900 and m1500 models that's
the difference it's an entirely
different experience in the juicing
World okay and for a whole bunch of
reasons
the mm 1500 link is actually
um there in the description and in the
profile and Dr Nesbit Dr nesbit's here
by the way
um
Dr nesbitt's here
having a problem here
hold on here
Dr Nesbit
Dr nesbitt's here
okay
you guys okay and Dr Nesmith brought
Donnie the donkey which is Dr nesbitt's
um
one of Dr nesbitt's best friend actually
Dr Nesbitt Dr Nesbitt said Donnie the
donkey is his best friend
he loves Donnie the donkey so much tiny
donkeys
actually
showing how much
he loves Dr Nesbitt Dr Nesbitt
I know you guys love each other I know
what
Donnie the donkey used to wear the worst
cologne ever
the worst cologne and Donnie the Donkey
uh we used to love wearing cologne
because he used to smell
he smells like a donkey but I think
donkeys smell good personally but Donnie
the donkey thought that no one liked him
because he smelled so fast he actually
had to wear
middleware cologne but Dr Nesbitt Dr
nesbit's freaking out right now he's
just he's freaking out because he never
thought he would be on here with Donnie
the donkey you guys know about dining
donkey he's he's in one of Dr nesbitt's
videos
one of his videos stunning the donkeys
in there
okay yeah yeah
donkey uh would like a juice I can give
you a juice later
um would you like some lettuce
hmm diet donkey I don't know how I can I
don't Donnie donkey are you on the floor
right now
donkey wants that piece of lettuce it
just
need
Donnie
mismatch cheering him on
your Desmond is cheering them on what
academies but it's actually cheering
them on
I'm not gonna ask me to calm down
Marissa's spiritual just said calm down
Dr Nesbitt
what
yeah Marissa spiritual said that Donnie
Donnie Dr nesbitt's cheering Donnie on
right now Donnie Donnie dying
Donnie
Dr Nesbitt is just totally freaking out
you just can't believe that Donnie just
stole a piece of lettuce Donnie
Donny stop eating all that lettuce like
this please
all right
okay Donnie
um Barbara Carbone says so the shot
takes out the fragrance toxic exposures
like fresh exposures you just got really
exposed like fresh exposures yeah
Don is hungry
Donnie's bringing the piece of lettuce
up here for Dr Nesbit Dr nisbee you hate
lettuce Dr is it Dr Nesbit just like
steaks and eggs steak and eggs in the
morning with ketchup
and a glass of vodka with it
nope Bloody Mary he likes bloody Mary
with steaks steaks and eggs
you don't like eating cow anymore
Dr Nesbitt is not a fan of eating cow
anymore
um he's going plant-based
he says he's going plant-based
so you guys are you guys going to be
here tomorrow to the next
next uh brain shot therapy which is
tomorrow
um
we have 10 days left
in the medical mean brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge just letting everybody
know okay this is day 10. tomorrow is
day 11.
Donnie don't spit out that lettuce
Donnie loves the lettuce
he does love lettuce okay you guys
we got 10 more days Zuma
keep that in your mind there remember 10
more days
I'll see you guys tomorrow
Donnie
wait a minute you guys
what was your experience
what was your experience can you post
can you post a real story was your
experience using the brain shot therapy
cleanse
um shots what was your what were your
results I would love to repost them in
any way so let me know what your
experiences are what's going on tag on
medical medium medical medium so I can
see it of course give this video a
thumbs up too
check out telegram I'm leaving exclusive
messages and look out for imposters
postures that are not me report the
imposters at medicalmedium.com
okay you guys Dr Nesbitt just just relax
don't worry
I just saw someone say is Jesus coming
back that's another discussion on
another day
um imposters are dming people saying
that they're me
all right you guys
I will see you guys soon take care