that in mind
that it's possible their ego could rise
up there's a lot of people out there to
be like I don't have an ego
no way I I'm totally not eager I don't
have the ego and then
there but then
you can see it it'll rise up it'll rise
up this is another thing the ego that's
it that's in everyone can be dormant
someone can have a dormant ego
isn't that interesting I swear to
compassion told me that that
ego can be in its dormancy
in someone
how incredible that piece of information
is alone that's for the compassion uh
has taught me it's like what do you mean
in its dormancy what do you mean by that
like how is an ego in its dormancy some
someone please tell me right like what
and
Spirit of compassion was like
dormancy meaning
it's in its infancy in some people too
that's incredible so an ego can develop
you mean it can actually be in it in its
infancy
and then
develop as time goes on
so it's one way somebody's ego can grow
another way is they can have
strong ego deep down inside
but it doesn't get Unleashed
until a trigger moment so that's another
thing too someone can have this
big
dark ego deep down inside
and it's there
and it doesn't peek its head out and
then it experience or a huge trigger can
occur
and then it just gets Unleashed and just
explodes
interesting right
someone said
fiddle stick said so true
okay so I'm reading out of brain saver
so I'm going to read some cool things
out of here I'm excited this is day nine
of the medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge day nine can you
believe it we have 20 days
we're doing a hundred day brain shot
therapy ones challenge no we're not
we're doing a 20-day and this is day
nine
now we're going to be doing the ego
shifter
and I'm going to read about the ego
shifter a little bit later so hang on
for that because it's going to be fun
we're going to read a little bit about
the ego shifter
all right
so let's get into it I'm excited about
this I'm gonna go to page
576. you guys 576 of brain saver here I
am
when everything changes
the not so sick
fall every day and become the sick
do you know anybody who's the not so
sick I just wanted to ask you guys The
Not So Sick is someone who they're not
chronically ill
but they might have a chronic symptom
maybe they get a headache once in a
while maybe they feel kind of low once
in a while maybe they have a mild mild
depression maybe they have a little bit
of acne maybe their stomach bloats up
and they get a they get a stomach bloat
here and there
and then they go to their functional
medicine doctor and they go to another
guy and another guy and they get a
little tune up they get told stay off of
processed foods then they're back in
Action right then they're trying this
and trying that they're doing cod liver
oil they're doing whatever fish oil
they're doing microbiome stuff whatever
it is and that's the not so sick you
know there's different degrees of not so
sick keep that in mind there's different
degrees of not so sick
and then there's the sick right
chronically ill that's when we're sick
there's that's a whole entire level of
degree that's when we're like sick right
so when everything changes so I'll just
read a little bit of this The Not So
Sick fall every day
and become the sick and that's the thing
that you got to think about you'll see
people they're not so sick they're not
so sick and they weigh back and forth
and then their scale tips
and when they're scale tips
they get sicker they get sick so they go
from not so sick to sick right they
start out with some acne and they get a
couple of bad colds once in a while and
they feel a little bit of fatigue and
then comes the day when they're like
neurological problems aches and pains
tingles and numbness barely function
brain fog in the worst way and now
they've gone from the sick the not so
sick too sick
that's commonly when the realizations
come
interesting I've seen people that were
just not so sick
and then they get sick and then the
realizations come
the fall they take brings them to a new
Awakening about how they perceive the
world
interesting right you take somebody
who's seasoned you guys know take
somebody who's really seasoned you've
been there you've done that how many
doctors have you been to how many
practitioners have you been to how many
different things have you tried
how sick were you were you really sick
severe migraines aches and pains
depression panic attacks heart
palpitations tachycardia afib this
cardiologist this cardiologist this
doctor to numbness on the body right
your legs feel like sand bags you got
the worst brain fog you got twitches and
spasms and ticks you got vibrations and
Tremors and you feel like you're just
you can't get like in your own way
because you're just you're you can't
even move
how many people have been through all
that sick as a dog right I just saw that
now in IG sick as a dog been through so
much okay
so
you know how you perceive the world you
know what you're seeing in the world
your Seasons you've been there you've
done that you've been through a lot
you've been kicked down you got sick
could not find answers you've been
everywhere there's that crowd right
wondering wishing says yes a lot of my
neighbors are not so sick and can't
believe our kids do brain shots seller
juice dot dot dot
I totally understand
Phyllis Lombardi I used to be the not so
sick in absolutely different degrees
different degrees of not so sick this is
an incredible topic really Hannity oh
man I remember the day my scale tipped
exactly
the scale tips Everything Changes it
changes how we perceive the world this
is a big deal educating myself says it's
a real humble sandwich
so true so true Hannity says I was I was
not so sick for years the fall was
absolutely my Awakening this is so true
it is isn't it the words in here they
match what you guys experience and and
and have felt so one thing about Spirit
of compassion knowing where people are
and what happens with when we get
chronically sick
the fall The Not So Sick take
when they become sick brings them to a
new Awakening about how they perceive
the world and then
that's when it's like what
until then The Not So Sick may feel safe
and secure I mean you see it out there
right The Not So Sick they feel safe
they feel secure and I'm glad they do I
want them to feel safe and secure
they're not so sick they're not so sick
you know where okay they get a UTI they
run to the doctor they get an antibiotic
they're a pastor UTI okay up and running
again
they get
um a migraine once in a while right and
they're like oh okay but back in Action
all is good
they you know
they get some acne
they catch a cold they get a cough
that's temporary right whatever The Not
So Sick are or they get a rash that's
really mild
and it waves from going back and forth
waivers from going back and forth from
worse to to not so bad whatever The Not
So Sick are up against
I'm in the page number 576 on medical
meaning brain saver that's where I am
and I'm in
until then The Not So Sick may feel safe
and secure in how they've gotten
they're minor or temporary symptoms
under control are solved
I solve that symptom my brain fog's
better
it wasn't that bad to begin with but my
brain fog is better I solved that
symptom I'm feeling stronger my adrenals
feel stronger I went to a doctor a
practitioner they gave me some vitamins
told me to eat better and get some rest
I got my you know aches and pains better
I feel I'm normal again
so until then The Not So Sick may feel
safe and secure in how they've gotten
their minor or temporary symptoms under
control or solved they feel confident
because they tend to find some help in
the form of a functional medicine doctor
or practitioner or chiropractor who
purports to specialize in more advanced
Natural Health Care so they go to this
guy and it seems like hey
you know they're they're um they know
their business this functional doctor
knows their stuff
this this chiropractor knows his stuff
he purports to be a expert in the field
of of chronic conditions and I went to
him and now I'm better and I want people
to go see their doctors of course and I
went to them and they're better
I'm better
when they find these Health Care
Providers the not so sick people are at
the beginning of the learning curve
isn't it interesting on IG I see
something from Elena this is this was me
until one day everything changed
completely understand
when The Not So Sick find these health
care providers
the not so sick people are at the
beginning of the learning curve the
beginning of the learning curve
you're getting symptoms for the first
time you're not so sick you find a
health care provider seems to know his
or her's business really good you go
there you start perking up your body
recovers
you're moving past it
and what they learned from their doctor
or practitioner is new to them
whoa vitamin D I can take a high dosage
of vitamin D doctor so and so well
that's new to me oh wait a minute krill
oil instead of fish oil that's new to me
Dr so-and-so
um oh this microbiome test oh it shows
that my bacteria isn't that great but my
microbes are okay here but not here oh
that's new to me Dr so-and-so
they're not sick enough these not so
sick people are not sick enough yet to
find out these may not be the answers
because their scale hasn't tipped
just slain
I just got some x-rays last week of my
spine as I was years ago I would need to
see a chiropractor perpetually
now he told me I am 90 better all since
having changed to Medical medium diet
and protocols God bless you I'm so happy
you're here and happy you're you're
doing better truly because that's what
it's all about
the not so sick
ngoc says I was a not so sick suddenly
celery juice and lemon water is not
enough
totally I get it when that happens now I
am taking around 15 Bemidji vitamins it
made such a difference with the brain
shots
I'm not addicted to coffee anymore and
people ask me what do I do like what do
I do
I don't want to become a not so sick
person
I don't want to become a sick person
can I become a sick person
I burn myself to the ground
so anything's possible
because the amount of stress I'm under
the amount of fires I have to die out
I'm up against so much that people don't
even know the communities don't even
know the medical medium communities
don't even know
and
so I take care of myself right I have to
I have to use medical medium tools
that's what I have to do
like when I when I put together the
brain saver books I was doing 20 22 hour
days
and I'm exposed to pretty much
everything else everybody else is
exposed to breathing in Kate chemicals
from Neighbors blowing out of their
dryers to chemicals falling out of the
sky I have exposure just like anybody
else has exposure I um and you were
saying you think 15 of energy
supplements I take the zinc every single
day
I mean I took this this morning
fluser going around colds are going
around
I take the propolis from Imaging and you
guys know I endorse these guys I take
the propolis from Bemidji every single
day
I mean every day I don't miss a beat
with the propolis I'm proactive I have
to be proactive I'm doing the brain shot
therapies you know I have to be
proactive I'm not just doing celery
juice like if you want to know like
medical medium I'm not just doing celery
juice and that's it like I take the
micro C from Bemidji every day I take
the golden seal from Bemidji every day
these are just sitting here because I
take them
I'm in my kitchen all the stuff's
sitting here and that's what I take too
many flues going around Seas going
around
RSV is going around I'm under pressure
I'm under stress like nobody's business
like oh my God like right so yeah and
I'm working my butt off Agostino says aw
must be spiritually challenged by
Darkness often
word
Agostino word
and me I'm burning through electrolytes
I'm burning through minerals
I'm eating minerals up like burning
through them
my brain is like going I hear Spirit of
compassion every minute
the stress of that
I'm thinking
because I'm My Own being it's not only
do I hear Spirit of compassion
and the wisdom and the words and spirit
of compassion I'm my own self I I have
to hear my own brain like everybody has
to hear their own brain
I'm not just going
to self-care appointments all day long
I'm not getting massages
I'm not getting facials I'm not relaxing
in a spa ah I would love that nice
facial I would love that nice massage
I'm not on the beach
you know getting some Sun every day
the point I'm trying to say is that
I don't want to be a not so sick person
and I don't want to be a sick person I
want to be strong I want to make sure
that I keep myself
above board up to par so I can deliver
and be the messenger that I have to be
and so I know when I read your comment
you said you celery juice wasn't enough
you were not so sick and then celery
juice wasn't enough anymore you had to
venture on and I'm I'm really proud of
you by the way you had to venture on
into customizing and doing medical
medium protocols and moving forward and
you said you had to do 50 you were doing
15 Bemidji supplements I'm doing that
too because of all the reasons I was
just explaining I don't want to be I
have to be Pro proactive I don't want to
be a sick person and I don't want to be
a not so sick person either so I don't
want to be that either so that's why you
know these are here
that's why they're here and that's why
I'm taking them I take them in the
morning and everything and
at night
when The Not So Sick find these Health
Care Providers out there when they're
not so sick okay they can get some tips
and tricks stay off of this stay off of
that
get some more rest here's here's some
vitamins
not so sick people are at the beginning
of their learning curve that's the whole
thing they're at the beginning of their
learning curve
and what they learned from their doctor
or practitioner is new to them and like
I was saying before also krill oil is
better than fish oil cod liver oil okay
I'll take krill oil I just learned that
oh vitamin D I can take a whole bunch of
vitamin D okay good I'll take that right
and they learn their their newbies right
and they learn these Basics which is
really interesting how it works they
learn these basics
and it's like okay and they start
feeling a little better because they're
starting to take care of themselves a
little bit right oh stay away from fried
greasy Foods all right that sounds good
I won't eat as much pizza I won't eat as
much whatever I'll stay away from
processed foods so they're not so sick
it's a learning curve they go from that
conventional mindset and now they're
like they're starting to do that they're
not sick enough yet to find out these
may not be the answers because the
problems they're dealing with are
manageable did you hear that you guys
manageable the problems that they're
dealing with are manageable
think about that
so they're manageable problems
when you get too sick in the scale tips
the problems aren't manageable so much
anymore that's something people don't
realize
because the problems The Not So Sick are
dealing with are manageable isn't it
interesting well Macaulay neurological
symptoms are so humbling oh my God
neurological symptoms
are so humbling
they
beat the pants off of people
they are so humbling Corinne Angelina
says I'm the Newbie laugh out loud
Corinne thank you for being here
I welcome newbies hang in there
I won't bring Dr Nesbitt out
Kareem Angelina says I'm slowly starting
to feel a lot better thank God Karina I
won't bring Dr Nesbitt out because Dr
Nesbitt will make you probably say I'm
not following medical medium anymore
all right
so someone said what's propolis good for
I mean I can only tell you this
about I don't want to I don't want to
make this about propolis today or
anything like that I mean I know it's
critical to talk about propolis it's
critical to talk about zinc
it's critical it's critical to talk
about that people are sick and getting
sicker and we can talk about it later
today or on a telegram or something go
to my telegram I could leave a message
there for everybody exclusive message or
something
The Not So Sick are not sick enough to
find out that there really aren't good
enough answers yet because the problems
The Not So Sick are deal faced with are
manageable I know I said that but I have
to say it again because it's so true
Michelle says mattress Island here
mattress Island
they're manageable enough that they seem
to be partially or even temporarily
solved by what seems to be smart Cutting
Edge thinking and Alternative Health
it's so smart Alternative Health it's
Cutting Edge the problems that they had
were not that problematic so they were
manageable and even temporarily fixed so
now alternative medicine is literally
like the gold star it's like it knows
everything it feels when you're not so
sick think about that
Jennifer Cockrell says my daughter has
migraines almost daily I'm so sorry and
she just refuses to do anything about it
it's just become normal to her like it
was for me until I found mm
check this out you guys you may you may
be told
here's a product for your microbiome
because everything stems from your gut
or you may be told this
here's a remedy and a powder a
multivitamin and an herb complex all in
line with a no sugar diet
you may be told this do some lean
proteins
stay in a keto direction or well we'll
get some stool samples and check out
your gut balance
here's a probiotic you may be told or
we'll do some blood work
look at your nutritional profile
see where your deficiencies are
the not so secure that all the time
okay and if they're not so sick they've
got a manageable little problem well
that's all great Cutting Edge science
everybody believes but man
it's not reality to what really happens
when you're really sick
because that isn't the Band-Aid that
fixes things when you're really sick
when you go from not so sick to woo to
sick
all the above it yourself
when you're hearing any of this for the
first time
you can feel satisfaction in the advice
you're getting
wow I got a smart practitioner
they know so much
they want to get me on a multivitamin
they're checking up my gut they're
getting me on a probiotic they're
looking at my microbiome they want a
stool sample they want to make sure they
do a little blood work they want to
check out my nutritional profile
gobsmapped wow godsmacked like boom
right it's like that learning curve
it's like whoa brand new learning this
is great they're Geniuses when you're
hearing any of this for the first time
you can feel satisfaction I Feel So
Satisfied
I'm being cared for
I Feel So Satisfied it's ridiculous I
had this little kind of headache and
this little ache back here a little bit
it wasn't really bothering me that much
but I got this great guy and he's doing
all this stuff for me and taking a
little B12 now and whatever and some
vitamin D and it's manageable I'm like
I'm satisfied
in the advice you're getting you feel
Direction I have Direction I'm confident
I'm confident confident in alternative
medicine I'm confident in the in The
Cutting Edge science
I have these problems and they're being
addressed
you feel a Direction
you find resolve that you could make
little changes that could be helpful I
could do that I can switch to a keto for
a little while and exercise a little bit
more
I get exercise a little bit more take a
little bit of a break maybe I'll take
another day off
maybe I'll like take care of myself a
little better I won't do the processed
foods I'll get my gut microbiome checked
out I really like this doctor I'm on a
lot of vitamin D everything's looking
good he wants to give me a good
probiotic
you feel Direction you find resolve that
you could make little changes that could
be helpful feels so good
it's all confidence boosting because
you're not so sick it's confident
boosting because you're not so sick
that's the reality right there you can
still exercise
you can still exercise why am I hanging
on that one note right there how come aw
why are you sitting on that you can
still exercise
because we you know why because when you
get too sick
you can't exercise no more
Cindy lamence says my natural path had
me eating three eggs a day and on the
keto diet then I got really sick and
thankfully found medical medium
information that's what I'm trying to
say here
all this seems like a great thing for
the not so sick and a lot of them bounce
back but when you get too sick this is
not a great thing
Sandra Sheehan says medical meaning
protocols have decreased my 25 years of
migraine significantly that's incredible
by the way it has taken a few years but
so worth it hang in there that's what
Sandra said
people are asking about migraines
right and I talk about migraines and my
migraine protocols in the protocols
groups oh
but you need both books it's critical
because they talk about it in both books
all right
you can still exercise sorry you guys
you can still exercise
you're still doing caffeine
they're not so sick you're not a canary
you're just a not so sick you can still
do caffeine every single day you can
still exercise
every single day you're not a canary you
haven't been brought down yet
you're strong
and now you feel your unhealth expert
now
you're at this place in your life where
I'm young I'm in my 20s
I went to this naturopath I went to
dysfunctional guy I went to this
acupuncturist and I love all doctors
I have respect for acupuncturists I have
respect for uh chiropractors I have
respect for
um uh Do's I have respect for MDS I have
respect for naturopaths I have respect
verbalists you have to understand that
total respect for all doctors looking
out for their patients they care about
their patients they have compassion for
their patients
so I need that up front and we have a
lot of practitioners in Med in medical
meeting communities we have a lot of
practitioners and doctors and so forth
lupus free with celery33 I was just sent
an article that vegans have a higher
rate of Strokes I laughed and said not
all vegans only those that eat all fat
or high fat diets they never know the
cause yet caution you lupus free seller
you're spot on
it's not just Strokes vegans
get sick
and the fats are just one problem
and like you said the other problem is
they don't know why they're even sick to
begin with that's another problem and
they have so many more problems right
and medical medium information talks
about
and I'm pro-vegan
provegan Pro plant-based
times 10.
and I'm also supportive for anybody that
wants to eat animal protein too
because they do it wrong too it's not
just the vegans that do it wrong the
animal protein people do it wrong
and I wouldn't know what anybody did
wrong I would be
in the mix of all the health world
that's where I chose my path to be
and I would never know what anybody was
doing wrong I'd be like everybody else
just pissing in the wind and throwing
darts at the side of a barn
but it's because of soc do I know and
it's because these incredible books
do I know right
other than that I wouldn't know what
direction to piss in
um
in the Wind
so healing is a party said my old job
had tons of air fresheners in the office
oh that's so rough and it triggered
migraines they got way better with
medical medium heavy metal detox
cleanses and brain shots because you're
battling the exposure
you're battling the exposure you're
cleaning it up
something else on IG to read here what
do white spots mean on the brain you're
in luck white spots have our eyes for
white spots and dark spots and all that
I'm the only one that has talked about
the meaning of all those spots
out there in the world of Health
and it's in the books here so it's in
that book and this book here
by the way you guys just want to make an
announcement really quick I'm so sorry
but I know we're talking about some
incredible information
but the books
are 50 off and 42 off at amazon.com us
right now incredible
it's unbelievable price is
22.28 how insane is that I'm just
letting you know
foreign
the twenty two dollars go to the library
and get it for free I don't care I just
want you to have it
I never thought they would be this low I
never ever ever thought they would be
this low in price they're both over 600
pages each they're heavy they're two big
Bibles it's one big book
okay
forgive me I am going back to the
reading
when you're hearing any of this for the
first time and you're not so sick you
can feel that satisfaction I talked
about you're strong
and now you become a health expert how
many times have I seen it and it's not
just young people but you'll see people
they're like 25 years old or 20 years
old or whatever right they have a not so
sick problem they have some acting
that's really Mild they get a little bit
of brain fog they go to a naturopath or
a functional medicine doctor they get
taught a few tricks they get off of
processed foods now they're on their
page and they're teaching about it right
and they're talking about it now they're
a health influencer but they don't know
the difference they don't know that
somebody might not be a not so sick
person somebody might be a very very
sick person and they're listening to the
not so sick person and the sick person
doesn't really know that the not so sick
person never really got sick
so they don't know so like oh krill oil
that's great oh sodium bicarbonate oh
that's great oh whatever vitamin D and a
really high dosage oh that's great and
they just don't know
and so the confusion happens right there
right it's almost like and I'm just
naming a few things just off the top of
my head
but the point is is the not so sick
person is now an expert
because they got rid of their mild not
so sick symptom and they're really
strong and their scale hasn't been
tipped yet and they're young but now
they're an expert so now they're not
only doing say fashion or sports or
something on their IG page or IG account
now they're doing health and they're
doing like what I eat in a day and
everything else
because they become they think they
become an expert they were not so sick
to begin with and they think they become
an expert so now they're teaching
as if they're experts and there's a
million of them out there right there's
a billion of them out there that's how
it's done now
by the way we're live right now at
medicalmedium.com you can watch it
streamed there if you're having trouble
on Instagram or anywhere else
some of the not so sick
people today do believe they are experts
on anything they've experienced with
their health
if a not so sick person
experienced a symptom or two
they believe they're experts now
they had an acute problem or condition
or intermittent symptom that was
perplexing them they got some help
learned what it feels like
Cutting Edge information
seemed to overcome it or Managed IT and
now suddenly they're Health experts
they're given advice on their platforms
they're giving advice on their platforms
giving guidance to other people who are
far more sick
when you're not so sick you can play in
the world of reading new theories or
trying new supplements in alternative
medicine like Pearl powder
or whatever go back to chlorella which
is really toxic
Sophie Nordstrom said first person at
work today who didn't comment on my
lunch of potatoes and salad I'm getting
hungry now I think I might have potatoes
and salad later but she comes from a war
country and is a very humble person
is that what it takes question mark
unbelievable I totally complete that
that's a very interesting interesting
and
powerful comment
insightful
so when you're not so sick you guys you
can play in the world of reading new
theories or trying new supplements and
alternative medicine or read about old
techniques that have been around for the
last decades or two
you know what old techniques I'm talking
about like alkaline IMS or water
machines
those things will make you go insane
down the road you will go insane and
lose your mind
people don't realize that that's just
one old
Theory right
I mean you know that people use old
tools
you read about old techniques that have
been around for the last decade or two
little do you realize as a not so sick
person these theories and supplements in
Old techniques are ones the sick have
already tried
charcoal bentonite clay alkaline ionizer
water machines
folic minerals
humic acid humic and fulvic minerals
everybody tried those they don't get
anybody better
they don't the list goes on and on and
on
and N M Venus said I just want to tell
you Anthony that I used
propolis pure on some psoriasis on my
skin and it has now gone I'm so amazing
that is so amazed that's incredible so
you use the
propolis pure
you have to understand something
you guys
this existing in the world is very
special I'm taking this off topic but
only doing it because
I am so grateful that something like
this exists
because of what it is
no company there's no industry there's
no anything that can produce
what memory has done with this propolis
the energy everything about it is mind
shocking blowing anyway like
I just pray that that that
you know that that stays available to us
and is here for us I pray that it
doesn't go away I pray that memory can
still do it is what I pray because I
know
the potential in what this is
so second about
Luke Rogers propolis move the needle for
healing Wellness rate of colitis amazing
stuff
I could do a whole show only on that
purpose pure not propolis that propolis
pure
and I could do a whole show on that for
hours
talking about really what that is
they just I don't have the time I don't
have enough time in the day crispy
perspective said ionized water machine
doesn't even filter out anything other
than chlorine correct was never
convinced of health benefits of those
thank you for confirming awsoc I can
also confirm this
that that will rot somebody's brain
that's what I can confirm it
at least uh in my opinion in my opinion
Lisa Tesco says memory propolis is so
amazing honestly I mean I know I'm
taking a soft topic I can't help we're
talking about the not so sick and what
they go through and the sick and what
they go through soon Melanie says I got
rid of my canker sores with them as you
propolis
and so has so many people
so has so many people
from what I'm hearing from Doctor
friends from what I'm hearing from
people and family and and other people
out there families friends and stuff
like that yeah
but it's not just propolis the thing is
is people can't get this confused though
if you don't know what we're even
talking about if this is kind of like I
feel like this is an inside thing right
if you don't know what we're talking
about and you just got here and you
don't even know what we're saying this
is the beverage propolis cure so no
one's confused because propolis won't do
that they're not the same
um but that's the propolis pure from
emoji so anyway the V is in Victor i m e
r g y you guys know I endorse these guys
wholeheartedly
yeah
make a wholeheartedly
deservingly so
deserving Lisa
all right
little does someone who's a not so sick
person
who thinks they're a health expert
realized that the theories and
supplements and old techniques are the
ones the sick have already tried
trendy products trendy machines the sick
have tried them all and they've only
gone downhill they have experience of
charcoal bringing them down and not
realizing they have the experience of
things bringing them down and not
realizing they've tried everything
meanwhile The Not So Sick can play in
these trendy places they can play in
this they can play Reindeer Games The
Not So Sick they're not sick enough yet
there's their scale hasn't tipped
and even they can even revive old
techniques and theories for other not so
sick people to play in they can do that
too and they're not so sick actually
revive
old
tools products and theories that were
bad
but the not so sick can revive those
because they're not sick enough yet to
realize those are really bad
and they do it for the other not so sick
people to play in oh I tried this I
tried that I tried bentonite clay
um I tried this right in the whole bit
they end up making them popular again so
it's like
hell comes back to haunt
people Michelle L says I needed this
today
so meanwhile the not so sick influencers
or the not so sick people out there that
think they're Health experts revive
things that should have been put to
sleep a long time ago
and they revive them through social
media and other media sources for the
other not so sick people to play with
but what happens is the really sick
people who haven't tried that yet end up
trying it and go down even further
The Not So Sick don't realize that as
they get sicker down the road because
their health scale has finally ticked
and that's what happens there's a whole
bunch of not so sick people out there
right now
and down the road their scale is going
to tip
there's millions of not so sick people
right now millions and their scale is
going to eventually tip
the approaches they were trying for
their health will show themselves not to
be useful
the recommended diets from their health
care providers direct amended tools and
techniques and supplements from their
health care providers all of it will
prove not as helpful as they as the
scale tips and they get sicker and
sicker and sicker
I mean I believe in doctors of course I
support doctors do what's right for you
and go to your doctor and and do what
your doctor tells you what they were
invested in or guiding others should do
was not ultimately helpful do you see
that now you know I've seen this with
YouTube I've had people tell me about
people's YouTubes right out there
where two years ago they're like
promoting all this stuff right they're
not so sick they're like oh here I'm a
health expert on YouTube and they're
promoting stuff and then they're not
promoting it anymore and they're not
eating that way anymore what happened it
wasn't working for them so now they're
trying something else they're not so
sick and they're trying something else
like it's this crazy thing
nothing's consistent
over here in Rumble since I've been
listening and reading books I began to
understand my body's soul and spirit
thank you for reading the magazine books
incredible
here's one on Rumble back in 1999 just
you you hate when comments go up and up
and up and then you can't catch them
let's see if I can catch a new one
they go up
see if I can catch this one oh my gosh
that's the truth explanation points when
I couldn't exercise that was when it was
a steady down
The Not So Sick and exercise The Not So
Sick can go into the gym and they could
Groove and move not so sick because
they're not sick really
they can exercise their scale hasn't
tipped they don't know what it's like to
be on mattress Island they don't know
what it's like to be whoa cut short
if you're on YouTube right now or Rumble
can you give this video a thumbs up or
whatever like a thumbs up or rumble or
whatever that would be amazing
before that day comes when their health
worsens the not so sick person when the
scale is tipped
before that day comes it doesn't take
much for a not so sick person to feel a
benefit from a health technique
when someone's not so sick they can feel
a benefit
from practically any toxic Health
technique
is that crazy
when they're not so sick because their
body is overcompensating it constantly
because they're really not that sick
their bodies over compensating it so
they overcompensate that Health
technique even if it's toxic even if
it's problematic
Michelle says or they lie about using
medical meaning while misleading others
actually that we have tremendous amount
of proof that that happens Non-Stop
that people are using mm
all the supermodels are doing celery
juice
they're not talking about it look
everybody's like the amount of medical
meaning being used where do you think
the zinc thing blew up how zinc blew up
both in the conventional world now of
Health like it's like it's it's
unbelievable
Karen Karen Hartman said oh my God it's
like you're talking about me I did the
charcoal bentonite clay humic and now
feeling like I am at a Tipping Point
thank you for your information and what
you do Karen completely understand I do
before that day comes for the not so
sick person when their health worsens it
doesn't take much for a not so sick
person to feel a benefit from a health
technique that's toxic
many of these people are only
intermittently sick they're only
intermittently sick with a mild symptom
that comes and goes on its own
no one realizes they are just an
experiment for the Alternative Health
world too at the same time
so dealing with a mild symptom that
comes and goes on its own seeming to get
better with a little bit of sleep
you know
you know what
a sick person knows do you know what a
sick person knows that's been there and
tried everything
they know
that if they get a little bit of sleep
it doesn't mean they're going to be
fixed the next day
well you know nons not so sick people
all not so sick people have to do
depending on what degree of not so sick
they just need to get sleep for a couple
days
that's all
but the scale tips eventually and then
they're not they're not in that position
The Not So Sick seemingly get better
with a little bit of sleep a new vitamin
protocol cleaning up their Foods
intermittent fasting lymphatic massage
sauna routines I'll keep on going in a
second here octo
octop Corp I love the pages
that are in the newsletter
the brain shot therapy challenge emails
you signed up for have the page numbers
we are covering for the day so you're
seeing how we're you're seeing the work
of my team
you're seeing the hard work the medical
medium team does
it's pretty cool I'll let them know
you have to sign up to get them though
all right this part's really important I
have to I have to read this part to you
this part's really important
foreign
people are only intermittently sick with
a mild symptom that comes and goes on
its own seeming to get better with a
little bit of sleep a new vitamin
protocol cleaning up their Foods
intermittent fasting
lymphatic massage sauna routines
breathing class or workout class
they think they have the Panacea they're
not so sick
that's all they needed to kind of like
ebb and flow with their symptoms they're
not so sick
the land of Alternative Health games is
filled with many trendy options
The Not So Sick have the freedom to play
in this fairy tale land waffle about
latch onto something of interest to tell
others about and remain disconnected
from the difference between being a not
so sick person
and being so sick
that last part is really incredible
and remain disconnected from the
difference between sick and not so sick
since the not so sick who's waffling
about in a little bit of Breath class
and a little bit of workout class and a
little bit of yoga class and try in a
little bit of intermittent fasting and a
little bit of this and a little bit of
that that person
that not so sick person is completely
disconnected between the difference of
being a not so sick person like
themselves or someone who's been through
it all and they're really sick and
they're chronically ill now the medical
me in community is for The Chronic Leo
and yes it's for a not so sick person
and yes it's for anybody who's feeling
good and wants to come and partake in it
but it's for the people who've been
through hell and back it's real answers
for the people to to have a chance to
rise out of it
being sick
sick
is an entirely different space
the sick have left the realm of play
correct me if I'm wrong if I'm wrong
tell me if I'm wrong then then my bad my
bad
the sick have left the realm of play
you get too sick
you leave the realm of play
the sick are seasoned
the sick have already done the
probiotics
the fish oils the whey protein powder
and other protein powders the charcoal
the oil pulling the neem oil the
L-Carnitine the chlorella the
diatomaceous earth particles the sodium
bicarbonate the gut powders the
Bentonite Clay and other Clays the
zeolite the fulvic acid the humic acid
right the deer antler the colostrum the
collagen the protein bars the MCT oil
the Kombucha Tea the chocolate the green
tea the apple cider vinegar the
chlorophyll the alkaline ionizer water
machines and dozens more the sick have
become seasoned too from visiting dozens
of doctors and trying everything
including fecal transplants
I'm not telling you that you shouldn't
do what your doctor wants you to do if
your doctor wants you to do a fecal
implant and that's what you're doing I'm
not telling you different but I would
never do it in a million freaking years
I would never do it you think they can
actually figure out what viruses are in
somebody else's fecal they're not even
looking for those viruses they don't
even know what they look like
and they're going to implant it in
somebody else
it's absurd it's insane
Saint Sue says so wait I'm confused
again how does this ego shot relate to
the info with the not so six sorry my
brain and neurons are not firing your
brain and neurons firing because it's
about also dealing with it all it's easy
to get pushed off your healing path with
all the misinformation
and you can get thrown off track by
other people's egos because the not so
sick tend to have some raging egos out
there they think they found it all they
think they know it all they think that
their little keto diet and their breath
class is why they're not sick they're
not sick from other reasons they're just
not sick yet their skill hasn't tipped
it's to keep you unpa it's to keep you
on path of the information because
because if there's so much
misinformation out there propelled by
the ego based communities in health
Alternative Health is one big huge ego
out there it's a massive ego proportion
people don't even realize this is to
help you stay true to yourself and keep
you on track you can also
um you can also give the the ego shot to
your friends and so forth
but it's really fun anyway
if that made sense at the end all right
the sick have become season two from
visiting dozens of doctors and trying
everything including fecal transplants
what a stupid experiment that is but if
your doctor tells you do what your
doctor tells you I'm just saying but I
would never do it
bee sting therapy
would a disaster bee sting therapy is
I mean I know why
I mean I'm not going to explain it all
in this moment
but yeah
all the all the the bee sting therapy is
is used is self-medicating with your own
adrenaline because your body's in a
cytokine storm because you've got a bee
sting it's really a bad therapy
urine therapy another one that's absurd
urine therapy is absolutely ridic
it's ridiculous
coffee enemas dangerous
I'm working on a coffee
enema
podcast and I couldn't get it done
I've been working on trying to finish a
coffee animal podcast a while ago and I
never got it finished but anyway
Rife machines stem cell therapy UV blood
irrigation radiation ozone
cold therapy and more the seasoned sick
have been there and done that if you're
not so sick you can play around in OZO
land you can play around in cold therapy
if you're not so sick you can play
around with UV blood right
a radiation you can play around with
fecal transplants you can play around
bee sting therapy if you're not so sick
you can play around with anything you
can play play play bentonite clay and
everything else and charcoal and all
these combined plus ionizer water
machines and anything else that comes
your way you can play in it on IG
create happiness says my mom used coffee
enemas and she died soon oh God
bless your heart and just know that my
heart pours out to you
the not so sick
when they get their first symptoms May
believe the health world is their oyster
as they stumble across remedy after
remedy
I'm not so sick
oh my God charcoal it says it does
everything for you activate trouble fish
oil is what I need for my brain
it's a Panacea out here human can folic
acid
or would a doctor friend of mine call
shlat
then he's from India and he calls it
shalat
anyway shillajit
right so you said what page am I reading
from
page 578 brain saver
Sonia says um what page are you reading
from oh my God information
Terry Appleman says I have no idea
people didn't really know anything about
why I was sick until everything let me
down and I ended up sicker than ever
bless your heart
so it feels like you just it feels like
you just
landed in a tropical Paradise when you
first when you first get a sim number
two and you see there's a Panacea of
alternative therapies everywhere and
they all seem to make so much sense
because the people talking about the
alternative therapies are so smart and
it seems so smart
even though it doesn't if you really
crack it a coffee enema is the worst
thing that you can do to your adrenals
in your liver but nobody does it's like
it's crazy right
did not so sick people when they get
their first symptoms May believe the
health world is their oyster as they
stumble across remedy after remedy with
confident practitioners who haven't gone
through a major Health crisis themselves
and that's another problem
if I ever get sick
and I need the help of a health care
provider
I want to make sure that healthcare
was really sick
really sick
hands and knees
praying to God
not knowing what the hell's up or down
been through hell and back
burned to the ground rose out of the
ashes
and was back practicing
that's the healthcare provider that I
would want me personally
I mean but I'm not saying keep your
health care providers don't look for
that if you got a good one I'm just
saying that's what I would want
the search for a way to heal starts at
the most basic tier the sicker you get
the more you've sifted through what's
offered out there
there's tears the sicker you get the
more the right the more you sift it
through the sicker you get the more you
sift it through the not so sick many
times the not so sick we're talking
about now think it's impossible for them
to ever get sick with a chronic illness
I can't tell you how many times I've
seen that the not so sick
thinking it's impossible for them to get
any sicker to get sick with a chronic
illness they will never believe they can
get sick with a chronic illness and not
so sick
they don't want to think they could ever
get there because that's frightening and
their health approach must be the answer
the health world is so full of
misinformation I like this shot to keep
us on the humble path keeping true to
ourselves and able to access our soul
and not the brainwashing we've received
down here our subconscious and
Consciousness can be brainwashed we want
to access our soul knowledge the ego
shift is really helpful in general for
all this stuff not just this with this
but just everything
the not so sick people don't want to
think that they could ever get sick
because it's frightening and their
health approach must be the answer of
course they're still doing their
workouts so it should be fine they're
still able to work out
they're still having their cheat days
right the not so sick still want to have
their cheat days
and they want to be quick to call
somebody orthorexic oh you're taking
care of yourself too much oh you're
orthorexic I noticed that the not so
sick people that's a Telltale sign
right there
that if a not so sick person's claiming
they're really sick
or they've been really sick and now
they're a coach a health coach or a
practitioner or whatever if a if a this
is proof If a person claims they were
really sick with some kind of
life-threatening disease they were
really down in in the in the depths of
hell and they crawl out of it they claim
and then they say
that if you're eating that way or this
way you're orthorexic or that
and men can make you orthorexic or that
whatever then they were never really
that sick it's it's
shines a light
because you know
it shines the light because when you're
really really sick
you would never
call anybody orthorexic when they're
taking care of themselves
and they notice throughout the years I
see this all the time
it's so strange
see the minute you start taking care of
yourself and eating better and all this
stuff then someone pops up and says oh
you have orthorexia or your orthorexic
it's like are you kidding just because I
want to live and I want to heal and I
want to do the right things
they have their cheat days they feel
like they're keeping balanced practicing
moderation intuitively living their
lives they believe that person who's
really sick that's not me that's not
going to be me I'm never going to get
sick I'm just gonna be where I am
then when you come across then when you
cross the threshold to being very sick
Everything Changes
it's a different world
one of survival
your goals are different from the goals
of the Not So Sick Things change in your
life
even relationships can change it's a
whole other world of understanding
Health what I'm trying to say is
if you pass the point of just being not
so sick
into the land of sick at some point in
your life then you know things change
your perspective the world changes
you're humbled your ego gets kicked down
that's why I'm talking about this too
your ego gets kicked down someone asks
what about chlorella make sure you grab
the macrobium brain saber books and read
about chlorella in the books to know
what to be worried about with it
all right guys
I'm gonna pop along to
I'm gonna pop along to this we're doing
the ego shifter I want to read a little
bit about that okay
here we are
it's a big book you can flip around in
it forever
anyway that's the ego shifter right
there
this shot is ideal and those moments
when you feel like your ego has taken
over your senses
or your Common Sense and Sensibility
there's a moment in all of our Lives
when we
can feel it's not just confidence we're
working with but our ego is kind of
taking over
there's a sense that it's there in the
background
so there's ego and then there's
confidence
they're two different things
and they can get mixed up
someone can be really confident
but their ego is
kind of behind it all
and that's a great time to take the ego
shifter you want the confidence you want
the ego to kind of chill and drop
so you can take the shot when you feel
like your ego has taken over your senses
or your Common Sense and Sensibility
take this shot if you feel like you're
losing your true self
losing sight of what's truly important
so even if you don't think it's ego
related on any level
that's what's incredible about this ego
shifter forget ego just move that aside
for a second right
taking this shot when you feel like
you're losing your true self
that's interesting because ego can play
a role in pushing out your true self
right the ego can actually
push and Propel your true self out so
that's a great time to do it
take this shot if you feel like you may
have been a little too self-absorbed
you know when I think about
self-absorbed
oh like I don't see
a huge part of the medical meme
Community being self-absorbed not at all
you guys are working on your healing
process you're working hard
self-absorbed is kind of another thing
that a lot that people do out there they
get really self-absorbed that's
something that's a time to do the ego
shifter
you that's when you're kind of losing
sight you're so self-absorbed you're
losing sight of other people's pain and
suffering you're losing sight of what's
around you you know you lose that vision
try this shot
if you realize you've been completely
self-consumed without caring for others
even if you don't have the ability to
care for others because you don't have
that ability
or strength
if you just don't care at all that's a
good time to take the ego shifter
use this shot if you feel as if
something inside of you is controlling
your life
and decisions while you watch from above
whoa you know when Spirit of compassion
put that in here
it's like what
I mean seriously I was blown off my seat
you feel as if something inside of you
is controlling your life
and decisions
something inside of you is controlling
your decisions while you watch from
above it's like no don't do that no
don't do that oh my God what is
happening why would I do that and you
kind of watched it from above like why
would I do that
try this shot if you have a friend or
loved one who has a very large ego do
you guys know anybody who has a big ego
besides
besides aw just kidding
do you do you have do you know anybody
who has a very large ego
and doesn't believe
they do
they don't believe they do
everybody has an ego
how about this one take this shot if you
feel you need to take control of your
life and override
the drive to harm yourself
so there's there's a lot of people out
there that they have this drive to harm
themselves
toxic heavy metals play a role the ego
shifter has something in it to shift and
rewire
try this ego shifter if you need to Free
Yourself
so your authentic Soul shines through
and benefits you and the ones around you
we also get brain let me just say this
we also get brainwashed in harming
ourselves too without even realizing it
like that's another thing too
conditioning
so planet Earth
has a way of conditioning people's minds
brainwashing their minds
so they harm themselves without even
realizing it and they don't even realize
that's what's happening
anyway let's make the ego shifter
Let's Roll
got the Medicine maker here
and let's crank it up but it got some
comments I'd like to read real quick if
we can
eloya says I'm a silent Watcher but
today I just want to say this is great
I'm honored
I am trying to declutter and heal my
mind from an sad lifestyle
lost spouse to chemo 13 years ago and
since I started doing
sorry and since I started going to
doctors I'm worse
well thank you for speaking up you're on
YouTube Eloy Loya and um
thank you for being here and thank you
for speaking up seriously
I know we have some silent Watchers out
there and
I'm honored
Elvis lives thank goodness Anthony
invented the term mattress Island just
having that term at our disposal makes
us feel we are not so nuts and also
helps convey to others what we're going
through and Elvis lives make no mistake
mattress Island will be stolen and
talked about in the other health
communities while they never cite or
mention mm
so no one will be able to get all the
information to get them off of mattress
Island
they'll know the term mattress Island
but they won't have what it takes the
information to get them off of mattress
Island
which is a very good point half time
before we start the shot you want to do
the robot
[Music]
can you the robot you guys
think my robot got worse
did it get worse
could it
and just don't hold your breath the
whole time like I did try to breathe
okay
turn on the machine
half inch piece of fresh turmeric
let's see
all right says aw I wouldn't already
love you for saving my I if I wouldn't
already love you for saving my life
I would have fallen in love with you in
yesterday's live yesterday's life you're
acting with oh you're acting with Mr
Nesbitt and his wife was so funny it
made my day
well I'm gonna tell you right now I
wasn't acting
that was Dr Nesbitt and that was
Beatrice
and I I have to say this too which is
interesting
um I don't think Dr Nesbitt Beatrice is
going to like that because they don't
think they're funny
they were really looking for guidance
and counseling so now that we're all
laughing at Beatrice and Dr Harris but I
don't think they're going to be too
happy about that Jess Elaine
said
creatine robot protein robot protein oh
my
all right all right okay okay okay okay
okay
all right I'm getting a little out of
control here let's get this
get this little piece of turmeric in
here
half cup chopped peeled kiwi fruit oh I
didn't peel it bring it ready
a half of one or is it half cup half cup
a chopped peel kiwi fruit
cheese
I have to peel this kiwi as fast as
possible you guys
I hope my ego can handle it
you guys I'm such a fast peeler
no one can peel as fast as me on this
planet
I'm the fastest peeler in the world
yeah that's right
we'll drop that in here
is my ego working
all right you guys I'm I'm peeling this
uh kiwi just bear with me I'm dropping a
couple links I need a half cup so I'm
just dropping a couple in here
nice
feeling it back
thank you for your patience
I'm running some kiwis in here
did it
all right let's go to the next thing
one tablespoon
of uh fresh or frozen wild blueberries
where you can use a little bit of wild
blueberry juice or wild blueberry powder
drop a little bit of that in
I was one tablespoon of wild blueberry
juice
you can add the juice in at the end if
you like
let's go to the next
um item
quarter cup of chopped portobello
mushroom
why am I yelling the juicer's quiet
that's what's incredible about this
juicer
on IG Michelle Scott I'm struggling to
get fresh turmeric can I use
the powder
you can always do another shot and not
the ego shifter
it's always best to use the fresh
turmeric for this one
okay quarter cup chopped portobello
mushroom quarter cup
I got a portobello mushroom right here
you guys
let's start sending it down
you know when Spirit of compassion said
that a portobello mushroom is used in
the ego shifter I was just like what
it's gonna be really good
quarter cup tightly packed roughly
chopped kale quarter cup of freshly
packed roughly chopped kale
nice
let's get the kale down in here by the
way you guys this is the mm-1500 both
the mm 1500 900 save people money food
costs are going up it's an incredible
machine call it the medicine maker
it saves money people actually save
hundreds of dollars and thousands of
dollars over time because squeeze is
more juice out
anyway it's on sale right now
all right let's go
we got uh and you guys know I endorsed
these guys
quarter cup tightly packed
half cup tightly packed parsley
need a little bit more than that
okay
got some parsley stems I wanted to send
down there
there's some juice in those parsley
stems
just going to put a little more in here
and we're good that's all
right
and a half stalk of celery
okay here we go
foreign
here we go
I'm gonna shut this down
Nicole comes out so dry it just freaks
me out every time
just comes out like dry all right let's
get this going we got some music
foreign
[Music]
this is the ego shifter
I do not have an ego
or do I
[Music]
my ego is going to like this
seriously kind of nervous because
they're rely on a little bit in my ego
and I don't want to knock it out
I want to keep it
I don't want it to go away
I kind of rely on that little bit of ego
gives me my confidence
no it doesn't
it's time to knock it out and crush it
let's go
[Music]
I'm just trying to see how I feel
why why
when I take these brain shots do I feel
crazy feelings
I mean you guys know that right you're
feeling them too
I mean the feeling I get to get tingles
but healthy ones going up and down like
my head my neck Goosebumps I feel cool
Sensations I feel cool Sensations as if
I ate a Peppermint Patty or some
something like I swear to God like
it's
I don't recommend to eat
but the point is that's what people
always say
I feel these Sensations like the
coolness come about me but he goes gotta
be leaving
[Applause]
[Music]
to feel the feelings when you do the
brain shot Therapies
every one of them some
crazy sensation comes over me for me and
I feel these funny feelings and
everything
it's because synergistically nobody knew
the combination of the chemical
compounds working together to conquer
something to rewire the brain it's a hit
an instant hit to the brain is what it
is where the compassion came up with
these concoctions not me these aren't
supposed to be tasty this one actually
doesn't taste that bad though but
they're not supposed to be tasty they're
supposed to work actually work
[Music]
bartender
give me another
oh Dr nesbit's missing all the fun and
sews Beatrice
Maria on YouTube I always read your
comments on YouTube every shot makes me
feel something it does it makes me feel
something gets the craziest thing and
it's a feeling I can't like it comes
over me
ah
you know I mean honestly it's like
I have to tell you guys like
I don't think you guys know something I
don't think you know how much respect I
have for you like
I talk about it all the time in my
private life right meaning the sense of
my life where I'm just like
whatever waking up
going to bathroom
taking shower
whatever just going outside
you know wherever traveling whatever I
have to do the point is working sitting
in my office I think about
something that
that I don't think a lot of people
realize and and how much respect I have
for you guys in the medical medium
community
more respect than
I think anybody really knows because
I know what you guys have gone through
to get here and and it takes like faith
it takes a certain amount of faith for
sure to
trust in this information because it
comes from above and
I just have to tell you that since I was
a child and I've always
wondered
and I would say the spirit of compassion
who would even want to listen to me
doesn't matter if I have an answer or
whatever who would want to listen to me
and
Spirit of compassion said look
you know
there are people that need this
information and
you're gonna
you're gonna meet them someday and
you're going to see them someday and
you're going to know them someday
and
they are souls that are unmatched out
there
Spirit compassion would tell me when I
was younger and I love you guys and I
have tremendous respect for you please
know that how did you feel with this
shot please post about it do reels and
stories and posts
tag at Medical medium and hashtag
medical medium if you can what was what
what was your experience what were your
results please let me know so I can
watch your reels and your posts and your
insta stories and then I can repost them
but you have to hashtag and tag me so
that I can see them
check out telegram I'm leaving exclusive
messages I left one recently called I'm
sorry on telegram subscribe to my
telegram account
for all I know down the road it's the
only place you're gonna even be able to
find me so
another thing too is
check out the podcast I did with
um
the heel on the heel podcast it's not on
my podcast but it's on the heel podcast
with Kelly Noonan Gore's my friend
She interviewed me please listen to that
podcast episode if it just has powerful
information in there if you can
um so it's
it's the heel podcast
you can just listen to it right
um
so check that out at Apple podcast the
heal podcast at Apple podcast and listen
to that one
but I also did a podcast I also was
interviewed by Sarah Foster and Aaron
Foster
on the world's first podcast it's called
so the world's first podcast at Apple
podcast I did an interview with Aaron in
they interviewed me Sarah and Aaron
Foster that one was also really
informative lots of great information
check that out when you can please
listen to these
um support for them would be great and
if you can even leave a positive
or whatever
a review on their podcast too that would
be great too because incredible if you
leave review for them on their podcast
showing support for medical meme
information and all that so on the heel
podcast and um Aaron Fosters and Sarah
Foster's podcast okay
and check out medicalmedium.com where's
my ego where's my ego get my ego reading
up where is it gotta find it
gotta find it
I'll tell you the brain shot therapy so
I just they really do some serious
rewiring like I noticed that
it's just it's unbelievable really
anyway love you guys
I'll see you tomorrow for day 10. will
you be there day 10 and guess what
10 more days after that
what is wrong with me I'll tell you we
gotta do a 20-day and we're gonna do it
I'm excited guys I'll see you