we're talking about the nerve gut acid
stabilizer that's what we're making and
we're talking about the vagus nerves so
even if you're not doing the brain shot
therapy right now many of you are we're
going into vagus nerves you might want
to stick around because it's really
powerful information I'm reading it
straight out of brain saver right here
Vegas nerve information applies to so
many people with what's happening in
their health a lot of different
mysterious symptoms a lot of
neurological symptoms connected to the
vagus nerves we're going deep into the
vagus nerves on this trip okay and we're
making the nerve gut acid stabilizer
and someone asked yesterday they're like
is this alkaline is this alkaline look
in front of me right here what do you
see you see parsley
you see parsley
you see cilantro
that is alkaline that's alkalinity right
there
at its best really so anyway we're going
into it right now by the way we're day
three hello everybody day three of the
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge we're making the nerve
gut acid stabilizer which I'm gonna go
and find right now let's see page 496
and we are going to get there I'm
excited about today I got to be honest
with you guys
I was really looking forward to this
right here
all right
nerve gut acid stabilizer right there
check it out
that's the one we're doing let's talk
about it for a second like why are we
even doing this all right let's go
use a stabilizing shot
if you're looking to strengthen your
vagus nerves so if you're actually
looking to strengthen those vagus nerves
giving people a lot of different
problems tightness to the chest
tightness of the throat intestinal tract
discomfort all of it
this shot is really helpful so you're
looking to strengthen your vagus nerves
use a stabilizing shot
if you're dealing with gastric spasms
flatulence anybody have flatulence
flatulence issues
uh chronic gastritis
mild acid reflux
or other digestive disturbances for
acute and reflux relief right see aloe
vera shock therapy that's another story
but that's incredible there's so many
Tools in here it's insane
use this shot if you feel your food is
not digesting breaking down or
assimilating so many people like I'm not
assimilating my food I'm not digesting
my food I'm not breaking down my food
and so what I love about the nerve gut
acid stabilizer is it's for that
application
here's one right here use the
stabilizing shock if you feel your poor
nutrient absorption
so if you feel like you got the poor
nutrient absorption use a shot if you've
been told you have a microbiome or gut
microflora condition or problem
so if you've been down the whole Road of
hey you got a microbiome problem
microflora problem that's what you got
you're going in this doctor that doctor
whatever bring your bring this to your
doctor show them the nerve gut acid
stabilizer say doctor can I use this
okay
also you can use this nerve gut acid
stabilizer if you feel as if you're
toxic
or your blood is toxic
so you feel you're toxic or your blood
is toxic
use this nerve gut acid stabilizer if
you feel that your liver and lymph are
toxic stagnant and sluggish so your
liver lymph or toxic stagnant and
sluggish use this
stabilizer
all right how about this one if you're
feeling an acidy stomach
acidy Sensations
in your throat acidity Sensations in
your throat acidity Sensations in your
mouth in your stomach or acidity
feelings throughout your body where you
just feel like you're so acidic you're
really acidic realiacity so you can use
this nerve gut State acid stabilizer for
that
foreign
use this nerve gut acid stabilizer if
you're dealing with chronic nausea or
chronic bloating so many people are
dealing with all this chronic nausea and
chronic bloating where they're all
bloated out to here they got the chronic
nausea right it's another reason for
this incredible acid stabilizer
last but not least
you're trying to repair acidic body
systems and make your body systems more
alkaline
I love that
so you're trying to repair yourself
you're trying to repair an acidic
environment you're trying to repair an
acid environment an acid body
and that's what you're up against and
you would use this for that
all right
let's go into this we're hitting page
102. you guys got your books at all if
you don't know what book this is this is
the brain saver books I'm in brain saver
right here I'm in page 102.
we will be making the shot later which
is going to be really fun but we're
going to be talking and discussing about
the vagus nerves so check this out this
is what we're talking about today page
102 in brain saver I hope you guys
um read along I hope you have the book
in front of you if not just hang out
hang out for the ride relax we're going
to talk about your vagus nerves which is
actually a really exciting topic
all right
Catherine Elizabeth
says hi YouTube isn't notifying me that
you are on surprise surprise surprise of
course not I've been kind of like
wondering too about that for quite a
long time
because I don't think they notify
everybody but that's pretty much
everywhere Carol says what do you mean
by toxic blood or whenever we feel like
our blood is so toxic we can sense it we
have intuitive nature inside of us where
we're just feeling like just not
you know not like clean inside or
feeling acidy and toxic I've written
about it in the books this is Liver
Rescue dirty blood syndrome so check
this out if you have that question look
into dirty blood syndrome in here you
can learn so much this these books are
so packed with information
if you don't have these books you might
want to get these books Renata vanada
says you were the only one who could
explain to me what happened to my vagus
nerves and finally help me understand
the source of my suffering forever
grateful and we're not you said vagus
nerves
with the S exactly we have two vagus
nerves not one and I noticed that the
people out there in the in in the health
World always say one but they act like
they know everything about it but they
say one when they don't even know
there's two we're not at your spot on
foreign
this shot is slowly giving me my life
back
see I believe that because I have a
friend that's doing this shot right now
and I'm watching a friend of mine get
their life back so that that's just so
powerful and I know this shot works the
spirit of compassion is information but
it's so it's so incredible all right so
let's read about the Vegas Nerfs I'm so
glad you guys are commenting I want to
read some comments I'm excited about
this the special time we're day three of
the medical and brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge
the vagus nerves are made up of tiny
strands and strings of nerve cells that
run the length of the nerves
a vagus nerve is not just one solid
nerve
yep that's interesting why do I care
about that why do I even give a crap
about that because the industry thinks
it's just one solid nerve
I mean it's not it's not one solid nerve
a vagus nerve is not just one solid
nerve it's a complex weave of nerve
cells
but it's a weave of nerve cells
this is similar to how the other cranial
nerves work although not identical
this complexity Works in our favor so I
want to talk about why vagus nerves this
weave construction that they have this
weave design that they have why is it
beneficial for us if you just got on
here we're talking about vagus nerves so
what that means is
a lot of mystery symptoms burning
burning feelings inside everything from
like intestinal spasms and cramping
gastroparesis to tightness of the chest
to anxiety to all kinds of different
things the vagus nerves play a huge role
I just saw Dr Fond go up over there on
IG
hello hello glad you're here
this complexity Works in our favor when
vagus nerve inflammation occurs you guys
and that's the big thing right there
vagus nerve inflammation
the health industry never knew that when
vagus nerves are inflamed we have
problems
I hate sounding like a broken record but
it's a medical medium info about Vegas
there's becoming inflamed by pathogens
and toxins and what that does is it
inflames your vagus nerves and the
winter vagus nerves get inflamed we get
all these symptoms but nobody knew if
you were around in this industry looking
for help 10 years ago you would have
never found that there it just doesn't
exist you just get told oh it's all in
your head you're crazy or you're not
sick or
or whatever it's something else
when Vegas nerve inflammation occurs it
may affect multiple strings within a
vagus nerve yet yet yet not every single
string of the nerves I want to talk
about that so when our vagus nerves okay
when our vagus nerves are inflamed it
doesn't mean all the strings inside your
vagus nerve are inflame and that makes
up all the complexities of your pain
your stomach gastric pain your
gastroparesis your tightness of the
chest here your tightness of the abdomen
up here you can't take a deep breath
down here but you can take a better
breath up here
it all depends on where the inflammation
is on the vagus nerve medical research
and science has no idea about this about
the complexity about where in the in the
vagus nerve is the inflammation or vagus
nerves which leads us to one other thing
what if you're inflamed in the vagus
nerve but not in the other vagus nerve
what if you're inflamed in one part of
one vagus nerve but inflamed in another
part in another Vegas nerve the
complexities are insane that's why no
one's symptoms are identical it's
impossible to have an exact identical
symptom even though it sounds identical
seems like it it's still going to be a
different sensation than somebody
because of all these different
complexities
the very the variables the variations
this complexity Works in our favor when
Vegas starts inflammation occurs it may
affect multiple strings within a vagus
there but yet not every string of the
nerve which saves our butt
it's how we survive if our vagus nerves
are inflamed
if they're inflamed we can still
function many times because only some
strings in the vagus nerve are inflamed
only some so it makes it so we can
function and live our life but even
though we feel broken and that we're
sick
Renata says I feel mine inflamed in
multiple different parts due to symptoms
is that possible notice that the whole
thing so many people have their nerves
inflamed in so many different places
this means inflammation does not take
over an entire vagus nerve because
that's how we survive if inflammation
takes over your entire vagus nerve then
you're going to be in trouble
you're really going to have some harsh
symptoms but even if that happens
there's a chance the other vagus nerve
on the other side okay of your the other
cranial nerve the vagus nerve is not
completely or fully inflamed so this way
you're still hanging in there
it also means symptoms can move and
shift if nerve-strand inflammation moves
and shift and that's another thing so
many people are like well I had all
these symptoms but they're different now
had all these symptoms but they're
changed
I had all these symptoms but they're not
the same symptoms but they kind of are
the inflammation is changing within the
vagus nerves
so it's actually changing with the value
stirring Sharon says I searched for
years for an explanation why I could not
take a deep breath
teach wow incredible on IG you should re
then you must have read this to find out
why the information is so so intense
Health with Liz good to see you on IG
I've been doing this brain shot for the
past three days and it's gotten rid of
my acidy Sensations I have to tell you
this brain shot
right whether you do all cilantro as an
option or all parsley is
unbelievable unbelievable
while blueberry dreams I have multiple
sclerosis and medical medium information
is helping me restore my nerves I was
going to have a shoulder surgery and
turns out I didn't even need to have it
so thankful I didn't go through with it
oh God bless you amazing that you're
doing so much better I'm so so happy for
you
I really am
Susan Blondo says love that informed us
love that informed us about our two
vagus nerves learn so much from you you
are a great teacher thank you thank you
I try to message the information
the spirit of compassion
and knowing about these two nerves is
critical so I am a messenger and happy
to message
okay
it also means symptoms can move and
shift if nerves Rand inflammation moves
and shift
if the cause of inflammation is
aggressive
inflammation can breach onto other nerve
strands so if you've got some really
intense inflammation in the vagus nerves
okay it can breach into other strands
inside of the vagus nerve signs of
research doesn't have any of this
information about any of that about how
inflammation works in the vase nerve
this is this is literally groundbreaking
life-changing information that doesn't
exist out there
let's see Spirit filleted kitchen says I
always knew it was my vagus nerve didn't
know it was nerves I was researching and
researching about
you're the only one who knew this
so let's keep on going a little bit more
you guys if you just got here we're
going to be making the nerve acid but
the nerve gut acid stabilizer it's an
insane
brain shot therapy it's incredible I'm
just really pumped up about it I've been
telling people about Vegas nerves so
what symptoms are caused for over 35
years
was called the vagus nerve guy years ago
just like us called the Epstein-Barr guy
guess what it was called the zinc guy
which is why everybody's like zinc Zing
for everything now hooting C
and the whole bit Wild Heart kitchen
says I'm a naturopathic practitioner
cool and am learning so much from you a
lot which blows what I've been taught
out of the water I love it incredible so
so wild heart do you have the brain
saver books do you have liberal rescue
do you have cleansed to heal the
information blows my mind every day it
just does
and thank you for actually reading the
books and learning
France's family chef says I did this
with all parsley had the family take it
too helped with more than I could say
it's it's probably one of my favorites
favorites but there's so many medical
medium tools that blow my mind and offer
so much relief and so much movement
forward for people it's hard to say
which ones are my favorite it's just
hard I mean
heavy metal detox movie is insane the
cleanses are insane the monocleanse the
whatever 369 that nerve gut acid
stabilizer like all of it but we're
doing brain shot therapy so I'm not
going to get carried away with myself
right now
game
if the nerve strand inflammation moves
and shifts you guys we're talking about
nerve strands inside your vagus nerves
being becoming inflamed
if the cause of inflammation is
aggressive inflammation can breach onto
other nerve strands where inflammation
can go up and down
slightly pressuring
pressurizing and pushing different
strands of nerve cells within an area of
a vagus nerve leading to Milder
phantom-like symptoms that come and go
so someone could be like why is my
symptoms moving around
why are my symptoms moving around
why
I'm telling a doctor it's kind of here
now it's kind of here
I'm telling my doctor it's kind of here
but now it's kind of here
telling my doctor it's kind of here now
it's kind of here
but now it's both but now it's not
anymore it's kind of here
vegaser of inflammation strands becoming
inflamed
inside the vagus nerves and moving the
symptoms around the sensations and the
feelings you're feeling moving them
around
this makes a lot of people feel crazy
have your vagus nerves symptoms ever
made you feel like you're losing your
mind I just I just want to ask you guys
you're not losing your mind we know that
but did your Vegas their inflammation
symptoms make you feel like you were
crazy you're losing your mind seriously
Michelle says mine stay in my stomach
Cynthia says thank you for sharing this
information I am a doctor and I have all
your books learning so much thank you
Cynthia totally honored that you have
the books on that you're here and you
know when I say things like you know
what I mean where I'm making fun of like
the doctor that buys the vineyard in
Napa Valley
and I make fun of doctors and all the
way it doesn't mean I don't have respect
for doctors Dr Alejandra younger an
amazing doctor incredible medical doctor
you know wrote the forward on the on
these brain saver books
it's you know the point I'm trying to
say is
um definitely honored you're here I talk
to doctors a lot
for years
providing information
for their very difficult cases
all right still these Phantom symptoms
any person's
and a person's main more definable
symptoms are less severe than they would
be if inflammation were taking over the
entire nerve and creating more severe
symptoms that would complicate someone's
suffering further so what I'm trying to
say is your vagus nerves you got two of
them
both can be slightly inflamed in
different nerve strands inside the vagus
nerves
you can be getting Sensations everywhere
you can be the most confusing patient to
a doctor really confusing burning skin
twitches and spasms
tightness in the chest you can have the
vagus nerves inflamed in all various
areas and then feeling like you can't
digest your food at all feeling like you
can't digest anymore could even be
involved
The Details Matter
all these details can give you peace of
mind as you are confused and going to
your 10th Doctor neurologist this is
information brain care doctor the point
is is it brings peace of mind because
when we don't know what's wrong and we
had everything checked out and
everything looks okay but we don't have
an answer having an answer is a huge
relief it's a big deal
that's the difference between medical
medium and everything else you can get
out there the details are in here about
it so if you hear about Vegas nerve out
there you can't get the details about it
all
you can't learn about the different
strands but not just that the different
symptoms involved and not just that
what's inflaming the vagus nerves heck
that's the most important piece of it
what's in flaming your vagus nerves
answers and details on how and why to
heal your vagus nerves that's the other
point
kind of getting carried away I'm getting
ready for my nerve gut acid stabilizer
matter of fact
Elvis lives I really liked Elvis and I
like Elvis's music so that's pretty cool
Elvis lives this explains so much my
strange nerve Sensations move around too
so your strange nerve Sensations are
actually moving around
yes that's how it works it explains it
lupus free with celery33 I used to choke
on food easily until I started medical
meaning protocols which means you were
healing the vagus nerves you were
healing the cranial nerves that's what
you were doing using medical medium was
healing the vagus nerves
endocranial nerves
anybody watching this take the books to
your doctors
pray daily says I feel I'm still alive
because of you and compassionate spirit
compassionate Spirit indeed
I try my best throughout my life to be
as compassion as possible
and any way I possibly can because I do
know one thing that when you're sick and
you're down and you're suffering and
don't have an answer and you tried
everything and you feel like you're
losing hope
it is hell and then some and what I do
is I think about that I think about what
it's like to be in your shoes if you
have all these symptoms that means
you're suffering if you are struggling
and don't have an answer and you feel
these symptoms I have to realize and I
have in my life that if I try to really
connect with that and say Anthony
aw
you're not sick you don't have those
symptoms
but
what if you did feel those symptoms
now connect to that person psychically
connect to that person
telepathically
you know connect to that person listen
to Spirit of compassion on how bad that
person's suffering and
connect with that
and feel that and what would it be like
in their shoes and when I think about
that
and I feel that it's like
you you could see everything you know
especially if you're psychic right you
could see everything you can see
the phone calls they always have to make
how they're not well enough to get out
of bed how they're always like they need
help how they need help they need people
to bring them food how like
how nobody believes them around them how
they're they they hate themselves for
having these symptoms like I feel it all
and I understand it all and and I'm just
scratching the surface
all right
because of the vagus nerves size and
reach when inflammation occurs in the
brain stem that affects the vagus nerve
Grapevine
the vagus nerves can exhibit a wider
range of symptoms on the whole than
other cranial nerves so what this is is
this is a medical textbook right and I'm
just a human being like everybody else
I'm not a doctor
but I have to take the information word
for word doesn't matter how complicated
it is it doesn't matter
how it works I have to take a word from
a word from above to get it in here and
then I have to learn it just like
everybody else someone made fun of me
a couple weeks ago and it was a couple
weeks ago or a few weeks ago I saw it on
social media and they made fun of me and
they said the guy doesn't even know his
own information are you kidding this
eight eight huge medical books with
complicated detailed information I'm
only human
I have to learn it like everybody else
who gets the book If you go to the
library or buy the book somewhere and
get the book from the library and you
have the book in your hand you have to
learn this information I had to learn it
writing it down I still have to learn it
every day someone was making fun of me
like
he doesn't even know his information
when he reads it you should see it's
like are you kidding me
eight volumes of medical medical books
and detailed information yeah I have to
study it
yeah I have to read it
brain saver and brain saver Protocols
are two huge books they were written as
one book Health authors do not do that
they were released at the same time and
written over a year ago
okay mostly written in one year
basically and we had to split it in half
because the publisher said there's no
way to put anything out like this so I'm
just saying
right
you guys were talking about Vegas serves
let's get back to that and I want to
make this nerve good acid stabilizer
when inflammation occurs in the brain
stem
then we get in trouble if somebody has
brain stem inflammation it can affect
the vagus nerves or one of the vagus
nerves in a different way than just if
the vagus nerve itself was inflamed a
lot of people have brain stem vagus
nerve inflammation you don't hear that
out there anywhere but it's but it's
incredible when you think about this
information these Vegas nerve symptoms
okay
can result from an inflamed brain stem
and that could be like not just
tightness of the chest
not just a gut pain or spasm
but you can have like or you feel like
you can't even breathe you can't swallow
you're getting ticks and spasms
everywhere I mean you can have
brain stem
vagus nerves inflammation
these vagus nerve symptoms that result
from an inflamed brain stem could
include tightness of the chest tightness
of the throat mild dizziness and
imbalance to feeling an imbalanced
feeling like you know like you're on a
boat that whole thing
vagus nerve inflammation closer to the
brain stem giving you that boat feeling
that vertigo feeling as well as anxiety
pressure in the chest do you ever feel
you get pressure in the chest difficulty
swallowing even if mild a hard time
taking a deep breath can't keep a deep
breath can't get a deep breath
pain in the throat nausea and sometimes
erratic heartbeat where the doctor
checks out fine you wore the heart
monitor and the doctor checks out fine
if you guys just got here we're talking
about Vegas and you've got the heartbeat
erratic heartbeat
foreign
is stemming from higher up like this
ready higher up in the brain stem when
when vagus nerve inflammation
Tire up
in the brain stem
we could have a lot of symptoms mukto
says show please where are the two vagus
nerves they come right out of brain stem
the brain stems back here in this little
brain right here
and down in here and down in here
so it's and what they do is they come
out of the brain stem
right the cranial nerves come out
and they ride down
and they cross and I want to read about
that because it's really incredible
your vagus nerves
have a lot of little nerves that reach
out and attach to areas
intestinal tract
the gut stomach
a lot of people lose peristaltic action
they get gastroparesis because their
vagus nerve is paralyzed
you can have mild dizziness imbalance
feeling a sense of not digesting well
anxiety pressure in the chest difficulty
swallowing even if mild a hard time
taking a deep breath pain in the throat
nausea and sometimes erratic heartbeat
when vagus nerve inflammation is
stemming from higher up like this higher
up it's not stemming from here it's
stemming from up here okay in your brain
stem from the brain stem itself it could
be a little bit of everything there's
people that have a little bit of
everything and they're like why do I
have every symptom there's people that
feel like they have a hundred symptoms
to the do you have 100 symptoms
Maria says I was on a boat for years
thank you aw not anymore
I see your comments on YouTube Maria
people asking about tinnitus there's a
detailed explanation the brain saver
protocols book about tinnitus and in the
brain saver book these two books you
want both I recommend getting both not
just one if you only have one get the
other
if you don't have money even though it's
on sale at amazon.com like a sick sale
like it's incredible on these two books
if you don't have the money go to the
library and get it for free
please
it's okay I don't mind I just want you
to have it in your hands
one possible experience is neurological
asthma so I want to talk about that a
little bit there's there's a difference
between your bronchial
tubes being inflamed
there's a difference between your
bronchial Airway being inflamed
versus
neurological asthma
um
I can't tell you over the years how many
times I've seen pulmonologists totally
confused by this
the person's doing a pulmonary test
they're breathing in the pipe
and then the pulmonologist says wait a
minute you don't have asthma but you
you're acting like you have asthma
you're acting like you have a breathing
problem
in a pulmonologist
doesn't know what to do
so they give you all the steroids
they give you all the medications they
give you the albuterol they give you all
of that and they're hoping that it helps
but yet your bronchial Airways are not
constricted there isn't an actual
blockage from them swelling
so then where do we go what do we do
millions of people on this planet I've
seen so many that have had neurological
asthma which is a term a medical medium
term nobody knew that that existed like
that
so a possible experience is neurological
asthma ready a form of asthma where the
Airways are not impeded by visible
inflammation at the pulmonologist's
office instead neurological asthma is
the sensation of air restriction created
by inflamed vagus nerves it's the
sensation of Airway obstruction
Elvis lives said this is perfectly
explaining the difficulties I've been
having for the last 20 years never heard
anything that so perfectly describes all
of it it's very emotional incredible
Elvis lives I'm honored you're here
that's why I
try to help and get this information out
I pray to God every night
that someone finds their way and they
find this information
gets me emotional
Shake It Off Shake It Off
get reading get reading
Spirit of compassion said keep reading
we got work to do
okay
and by the way we understand
your pain with all of that
so what I was talking about the
neurological asthma which is a big deal
and I want you to know this and I've
taught doctors about this throughout the
years when this when the bronchial tubes
are not obstructed whatsoever on any
level they're not inflamed where there's
an actual obstruction and they can't get
the ear in instead they have a
neurological problem the vagus nerves
are inflamed and when the vagus nerves
are inflamed they're getting a slight
sensation of paralysis that doesn't even
feel like air is even going in so you're
stuck you just don't know what to do and
then you get anxiety attacks and then
you hyperventilate that's neurological
asthma and you can go to a whole bunch
of pulmonologists they don't know what's
wrong and then you're back to another
neurologist and everybody else and
they're just like I don't know what to
tell you I think you have anxiety maybe
you should take some Xanax and that's
what they tell people where benzo or
some other benzo or something
foreign
as inflammation Ebbs and flows in the
brain stem whoa what did I just said say
burning stem
in
oh yeah yep for mild to more severe some
of the inflammation will lessen or
intensify on the vagus dirt Grapevine so
this is what's really interesting right
here
because I'm having a conversation with
SOC at the same time I'm trying to read
comments and and be present for you guys
at the same time I'm trying to read this
this complexity
this medical Bible right here
Susan horn says I feel like crying too
finally I got answers
we should all cry together I want to sit
down and all this cry together life
coaching nurse Kim says tears of
gratitude right now thank you aw
so as this inflammation I'm talking
about Ebbs and flows in the brain stem
which I was saying before like the brain
stem right from mild to more severe for
some people some of the inflammation
will lessen or intensify on the Vegas
nerve Grapevine what I'm trying to say
is the Grapevine the vagus nerves that
run through the body okay that might
less
intensify so your symptoms can change
down here sometimes but yet up here you
can have more intense symptoms when it
comes down to Vegas Stars
inflammation can come and go based on
whether someone is getting more sleep or
is lacking sleep do you know that now
listen listen
I know I hit a chord
if you can't sleep good it's okay
so I'm going to tell you something I
talk about it in
protocols
there's a piece of information in here
that's so powerful in the protocols book
it's a technique
it's absolutely just profound and
mind-blowing it's about resting the
nerves
okay
and
you can rest the nerves even if you're
not sleeping and have those nerves
heal
even when you're not sleeping so I don't
want anybody upset if they don't sleep
good
Michelle L says all I do is sleep
that's a good thing
meaning like if your true body's trying
to heal and it's allowing you to sleep
that's amazing
as inflammation Ebbs and flows us
talking about the Grapevine can shift on
symptoms so if someone is lacking sleep
or getting more sleep it can shift the
symptoms they can so if someone's
sleeping more symptoms can shift if
someone's not sleeping as much as
symptoms can shift because when you
sleep your body is trying to heal
inflamed nerves and your immune system
is going after bugs
inflamed vagus nerves
big part of that are pathogens like
Epstein-Barr right these pathogens
are in are releasing poisons and toxins
and it's inflaming our brain stem and
vagus nerves our immune system is trying
to clean up the pathogens so when we
sleep our symptoms can lessen in many
situations because pathogens are trying
to do their job while you're sleeping if
you can't sleep you can still heal
nerves and get through it I've talked
about that in the books
other factors that affect inflammation
include whether someone is less stressed
or more stressed whether someone is
eating better than normal or a little
bit of out of control with their foods
and whether someone is exercising more
or less these changes matter
you do
on a day with lower inflammation you may
still have the tightness of the chest
yet less pressure or pain in the abdomen
region
so one day
you're like why am I less pressure on
the chest but more tightness on the
abdomen like why is that happening why
am I less pressure somewhere
and then less anxiety and then sometimes
worse anxiety less vertigo and more
vertigo and some days balance issues or
dizziness if the brain stem inflammation
becomes more pronounced it can feel more
drastic with all of the symptoms
combined at an advanced level
so when the brain stem is inflamed all
of these symptoms can feel really really
intense
I mean there's so many of you guys that
had like a hundred symptoms and you're
knocking those symptoms down as you're
using medical medium information
viral inflammation combined with toxic
heavy metals and everyday toxic
chemicals
that are inside the brain stem located
close to the vagus nerves there can
create most every vagus nerve symptom
with different variables and to
different degrees at the same time so
when people have low-grade viral
infections and I'm on page 103 right now
low-grade viral infections and lots of
metals and toxins that can have vagus
inflammation in various areas of the
nerves from the brain stem down to their
gut
so I'm in brain saver by the way Page
105 103 sorry in brain saver
you guys we're going to be making the
nerve acid gut stabilizer I am pumped up
about that but I'm just reading about
some Vegas nervement the vagus nerves
inflammation talk
in many cases of brain stem and cranial
nerve inflammation the infection is not
in the brain stem or nerves themselves
doesn't mean you have the Epstein-Barr
virus in your brain stem
the viral infection such as such as
Epstein-Barr or shingles herpes simplex
1 or Herpes Simplex 2 is inside the
liver or inside the spleen
wherever a viral infection is in the
body if it's releasing viral neurotoxins
those neurotoxins can travel through the
bloodstream and land on your vagus
nerves and inflame them in all kinds of
whack-a-doodle places
making the Vegas their Grapevine
inflamed creating additional symptoms
whenever neurotoxins inflamabagus nerves
I want to talk about that what's a
neurotoxin you guys know medical medium
byproduct released from a virus like
Epstein-Barr
and that byproduct is neurotoxic it's
it's an allergen to a vagus nerve
cranial nerve trigeminal neurofascial
nerve hypoglossal nerve right
wherever neurotoxins inflamabase nerve
they create inflammation a hot spot
so a hot spot
gotta think about this you got your
vagus nerve and in that Vegas they're on
that Vegas nerve there's going to be hot
spots most people walking around sick
and visiting their doctor's offices have
these hot spots on their vagus nerves
hot spots or are inflamed areas of your
vagus nerves guys I'm reading on a brain
saver you guys don't have these books
saw somebody say what book is that you
want to get these books
G2 Vision says you saved me I'm so
familiar with all of these symptoms I
had lots and I have I had a loss and
stress
before ended up with spasms and crazy
heartbeat I got on the protocols for the
vagus nerves symptoms gone
hearts and praying hands
I was on IG
some of these hot spots
that's incredible by the way
if a virus attaches itself to a higher
section of events so first of all I want
to say something
foreign
I'm proud of you
because it takes it it takes a certain
person
to know what this is
okay
it takes a certain person to know what
the heck this whole medical medium thing
is
takes a rare person to know what all of
this is
like the books the information from
above
the protocols
the mission
this whole thing is a mission
to help the chronically ill heal
it takes a special person to understand
that
push through
and try to do this with all the Flack
they get in this stupid that they
get for doing it
and for all the naysayers and bullies
and discriminators out there
it takes a certain person to know what
all this is that we're doing
Gabriella says my inflammation has
reduced after the light blast
that's music to my ears
if a vagus nerve attached if sorry if a
virus attaches itself to a higher
section of a vagus nerve someone could
experience a severe bad vertigo where
they feel stuck
if you ever had that vertigo where
you're barfing in a bucket and your head
is spinning around and you're laying in
bed and your head's doing this
like feeling like it's doing this like
you're laying in bed and your head feels
it's going like this
I'm talking like the vertigo the crazy
vertigo right
if you ever had that kind of vertigo
that's when that's not a neurotoxin
anymore coming from Epstein-Barr that's
not a Epstein-Barr neurotoxin anymore
giving you a hot spot on your ve on your
vagus nerves or vagus nerve
that's the Epstein-Barr virus attaching
itself to your vagus nerve up high near
the brain stem
so if you had that vertigo where you're
like holy crap and it's just doing this
and you feel like your head's doing this
and you're like oh my God and you're
laying in bed and you're in in torture
land with that vertigo
that's the V that's the Epstein-Barr
virus attaching itself to the vagus
nerve that's not a hot spot anymore from
neurotoxins
by the way we're day three of the
medical medium brain shot therapy
cleanse challenge we're doing 20 days
we're doing the nerve gut acid
stabilizer in a little bit we got our
stuff in front of us
okay let's get back to business
the vagus nerves are channels for
information delivery to the lungs heart
stomach and intestinal tract your Vegas
nerves what are they their channels for
in information
in formation
Elvis lives
Anthony Dot
could emotional trauma be one of the
causes of Vegas nerve inflammation and
could it be stored there for years and
years with the trauma constantly
attempting to release itself the problem
is with trauma is it it lowers our
immune system
trauma
crashes our adrenals and our immune
system
and then
viruses that were dormant
have a field day
that's mostly I'm not saying trauma
can't
give you PTSD and all kinds of other
injuries in the soul and in the physical
brain I talk about how trauma can create
physical brain injuries in your neurons
and I talk about it in detail and brain
saver Elvis lives you have to read the
emotional brain chapter please it's so
in depth it's so adapted that at all
the vagus nerve the Vegas nerves are
channels for information hey smoking
Paradise and that information travels
through the
vagus nerves but the cause of Vegas
nerve inflammation is viral and toxic
heavy metals and toxins it's that's what
it is
okay I talk about this also invite
what's incredible about this book
there's a section a chapter called viral
brain and then a chapter called
emotional brain you'll see where
traumatic loss in everything can injure
the brain yes and I talk about that but
you can see where how it does it and
then how other things injure the brain
when our brain's neurons get
contaminated with toxic heavy metals
caffeine MSG petrochemicals chemical
fragrances viral neurotoxins or other
brain betrayers they can disrupt this
flow of information so what I'm trying
to say is information is going through
your vagus nerve and traveling through
but if there's enough going on it can
disrupt this traveling of information
that that is contaminants interfere with
the signals that neurons send down to
the brain stem
neurons are sending signals down through
the brain stem down out of your vagus
nerves
which in turn affects the signals that
cranial nerves such as the vagus nerve
are meant to deliver on rare occasions
brain tissue becomes inflamed from
direct viral infection like I talked
about and this can interfere with neuron
messaging too so what I'm trying to say
is your neurons have information in it
and then that information goes out of
the brain stem and goes
out of the cranial nerves like the vagus
nerves
D on YouTube this is answering question
I have about my son the things you
describe are amazing
when contaminated messaging travels from
the neurons down to the vagus nerves to
the organs such as the heart and
intestinal tract it's a skewed erratic
electrical signal with skewed
information okay you guys hear what I'm
going now do you hear hear what I'm
going on this check this out
that piece of information alone blew my
mind when I had to
um transcribe it
we're in spirit of compassion and get it
in the books right
when contaminated messaging travels from
the neurons you got contaminated
messaging MSG heavy metals fragrances
chemicals from chemical companies all
that stuff drugs whatever
Pharmaceuticals all that stuff is inside
the brain right the messaging from those
neurons can become skewed
and that messaging
can become erratic
it's a skewed erratic electrical signal
with skewed information all because the
neurons from which the information
originated were contaminated
this is how someone can have an
electrical heartbeat issue without any
impeding or obstruction issue okay so
here's how it works someone can have no
problems with their heart
they've been to so many cardiologists
and they have had no problems with their
heart
their valves are good their ventricles
are good
they're not having bleeding in their
ventricles
they don't have a blockage in their mic
their small blood vessels and arteries
in their heart the heart is checking out
fine
the doctors like you don't have a heart
problem
foreign
but listen it's an it's a skewed erratic
electrical signal with skewed
information all because the neurons from
which the information originated inside
the brain were contaminated this is how
someone can have an electrical heartbeat
issue without anything impeding or
obstructing a heart valve or having any
other heart problem ventricle issue or
other issues with the heart
Soul Angel says thank you for all these
life-saving tools it's been a full
blessing to me and my autistic twins
recently diagnosed with celiac disease
they love the HM detox smoothie have
metal detox smoothie your life saving
thank you for being here Soul angel
foreign
so there's a whole bunch of people
walking around with monitors but they
don't have a heart problem they're told
maybe it's tachycardia maybe it's afib
it's aphid it's tachycardia yeah
electrical
electrical signals that are actually
skewed but here's the thing medical
research and science don't know that the
reason why the electrical signals are
skewed coming from neurons in the brain
is because of some kind of contamination
issue in the brain but they don't know
that
Advanced information
another way an electrical heartbeat
issue can occur is if the brain stem is
inflamed where the vagus nerves exit
if you have inflammation where those
vagus nerves exit out of your brain stem
boom you're hurting too
Danielle Mangini says wow amazing that's
what I have low voltage in one chamber
will the low volt that's how it works
low voltage I've heard this a billion
times too well I'm exaggerating it's not
a billion times
but I've heard it I mean thousands and
thousands of times over the years right
that
um that that low voltage should have
heard that it's like why is that
happening
contamination inside the brain I've told
lots of doctors that bring the books to
your doctors
Bode Katrin says the chapter on
emotional brain is so mind-blowing
honestly
every time I read the chapter on
emotional brain inside brain saver my
mind is blown over and over and over
again I'm surprised I even have a mind
left it's been blown too many times
and not by psilocybins
and Ayahuasca or anything because I've
never done anything like that or weed I
don't smoke weed never did Kimberly all
good I'm not judging anybody who has
at all I'm just saying I don't Kimberly
all good I had heart palpitations and
drinking celery juice every day stopped
that issue
amazing you got all those electrolytes
sodium cluster salts to your brain
guys where am I I'm lost I'm lost in the
chapter now I don't even know where I am
messaging from neurons in the brain gets
momentarily blocked in the brain stem
builds up and then exits with high
intensities sending signals down the
vagus nerves that hit the heart oh whoa
which can cause heart palpitations and
spasms in other places this is insane
this piece of information is absolutely
unbelievable
what this book is saying
yes Spirit of compassion what you're
saying
is
that mess what happens is an electrical
electricity can get stuck
in the brain stem
if the vagus nerves right on the coming
right out of the brain stem are inflamed
electricity could get stuck and then it
can get released in a bigger pal and
when it's released in a bigger pout
it can intensify sending signals down to
the vagus nerves that hit the heart
which can cause heart palpitations and
spasms in other places that are unknown
to why it's happening why am I getting
heart palpitations when my heart is
checking out fine it's because you're
getting this electrical shot that's
coming out of your brain stem
and running to your heart and hitting it
faster and harder
it's a shock to the heart
my God this book is packed
this is
Sarah
feinstra says you said it takes a
special person to accept this
information
does Darkness attack us
strategically or is it random does
Darkness know our potential more than we
even we do
I'll do a big talk about that maybe I'll
do like I'll do a separate show on that
after we get through
the incredible 20-day brain shot that
everyone's Challenge and then we'll talk
about that I do know this
darkness in the world does not want this
information out does not want
you know credibility to this information
does not just wants people on
toxic crap
and you know and not having answers I
mean it's no it's no mystery that the
industries want people in the dark
me media only says bad things about me
and remember this remember this okay
anybody who's here right now
like media
most most of the time always just send
says it says crap about me and
you know because it's like it's like
it's like smear campaigns and stuff like
that and hit pieces like constantly I
mean that's what it's always been it's
like
because it's like they don't want people
getting this incredible information
so the lie because that's what maybe is
allowed to do they're allowed to lie by
the way I don't know if you guys knew
that but they're allowed to just say
anything they want right
and
you'll never see media share all your
unbelievable healing stories that are
mind-blowing
that would literally
each one of your healing stories should
make People magazine
that incredible each one of your healing
stories should make Time Magazine
that's how unbelievable your healing
stories are
you know and and the media won't share
like healing stories like that because
you know and the media won't share the
fact that science is taking the medical
medium information
is that unbelievable
but that's how this world works
and said they'll write a smear campaign
instead of like showcasing
like I gotta tell you something right
a famous TV show but but also to the
credit of like TV Land and stuff I mean
I am offered
the medical medium like TV series and
stuff like that but I don't want to I
don't want to do that I don't want to
cookie cut and make it all about me
and then not do the work I I've I've
been
um chosen to do right
but what's interesting is like a really
well-known show TV show
having a tech problem on tick I think a
really well-known TV show
asked me to come on
to talk about medical stuff
and
so and they said well you can bring
a healing story a person on there that
healed or multiple people that healed
with medical meme information I was like
you know what
that's incredible
so
the TV show reached out to a whole bunch
of people like 10 people
to say hey do you want to come on the
show
to be there and have the medical medium
in you
talk about your sickness and what you've
been through and how you healed this
miraculous story that you have like how
you got out of the wheelchair
and and stories like that and so
people said I would love to
so then it got close to airing the
to filming the show
it got close to filming the show on a
major Network
and when we got close to filming the
show The Producers then reached out to
me and said by the way you're coming
today right
I said yeah I'm coming today
I'm excited I got my lunch lunch packed
I'm ready to go
and then they said
okay great I said how's everybody else
doing did you contacted and that we're
all excited that you told me about oh
we're not having any of them on
I said why
and they said the producer said the head
producer said
we just thought it wouldn't be a good
idea having those 10 individuals on who
got out of wheelchairs who got who
healed and everything else we just don't
think it would be a great idea
and he said but we'll see we'll see you
in an hour I said you and I hung up
all right let's keep on going
all right let's go
so on that note
is that an unbelievable story
it's like what
because I I felt so bad because people
were called
and they're all excited from what the
producer said they were going to talk
about their incredible healing stories
about how that got out of wheelchairs
two people were got out of wheelchairs
two of them out of the ten
the other eight
one person right one person is a cancer
survivor
using mm info another person
um the other person was had ALS
and then got better and another percent
Alzheimer's and got better
and there were a few others and they
didn't they didn't what happened was I
think the the producers
we're like holy crap we're gonna put
somebody on that got better from
Alzheimer's we're gonna put somebody on
that he knew 20 years ago that got
better from ALS and they were they like
and they're still here and they're fine
like they were actually like their minds
were blown
and they had it all scheduled
and then they said medical medium come
on in we're just we're not having any of
those we're not having the ALS person or
the Alzheimer's person come in we're not
having the woman who had four babies at
age 48 years old when she couldn't get
pregnant her whole life and she did all
the medical medium and got pregnant had
her four babies we're not going to have
all of them on and and I just couldn't
believe it Michelle L says they used
that to reel you in so they could
sabotage you correct
correct correct
all right
sorry about swearing earlier
okay
you guys needy does it all the time and
that's why I don't take interviews
anymore
all right let's go
but yeah
it's the craziest thing all right
so this is incredible information about
the Vegas stairs let's have a half time
do you have to you guys want to do the
robot with me
maybe the maybe they didn't like the
robot and that's what they didn't like
[Music]
robot try holding your breath don't
don't try holding your breath the whole
time because
I decided to hold my breath because
that's how you do the best robot where
you don't breathe
you gotta hold your breath but don't do
it
[Music]
you don't breathe
all right
you guys let's make the Durham cut acid
stabilizer we there's more Vegas there
information in this brain saver book
and
we're ready to do it come on let's do
this I love this shot I'm not kidding
the shot is so amazing
and like what health with Liz was saying
that like she's been doing it the last
three days is that what you said Liz
incredible
all right so
I'm pumped up
now this is the mm-1500
the mm900 mm-1500 are on sale right now
incredible juicers they squeeze
the crap out of the juice people are
asking me all the time and I can't
answer
a thousand DMS on what's the best juicer
I just can't do it right
so I try to talk about it when I'm using
the juicer
anyway I'm gonna okay first of all let's
talk about the nerve the nerve that acid
stabilizer let's talk about that one a
little bit okay
when I see another comment first of all
when I see another comment say say after
the sales over for the mm 1500 900 I see
a comment saying what's the best juicer
in the sales over I want to cry
I want to cry and then if I don't talk
about the juicer for like six months
and I think everybody knows what juicer
is the best they end up with a spinning
baskets user or something else that they
got sold into and they're buying they're
spending dumping all their money into
produce because it's not squeezing
enough juice out and they're throwing
money out the window
it's insane right
anyway here's the thing about the nerve
gut acid stabilizer that's cilantro
right here
that's parsley this is curly parsley
right here this is flat leaf parsley
parsley right there
so we have three different things here
now here's the thing I'm not going to
combine
cilantro with parsley
I'm not gonna mix them
but you can do either a cilantro shot on
its own as an option
so many people
love to hate cilantro
they hate cilantro they love to hate
cilantro right
okay and then you can do parsley on its
own too you can pick each one right
you can pick each one
keep that in mind
you might be somebody that's high in
toxic heavy metals
and you're doing the cilantro nerve gut
acid stabilizer
but you can choose either or
parsley one is knock your socks off like
for real love so let's get started I'm
gonna run some there through here okay
high in toxic heavy metals don't like
Taste of cilantro so what happens is
people who are high in all those toxic
heavy metals tend to not like the taste
of cilantro
where it it does something in their
mouth it makes their mouth start doing
some crazy stuff where they despise The
Taste completely and then when you start
getting Metals out over time or bursts
of metals out in different areas of the
organs as they're coming out over time
it can waver where you actually can
stand cilantro or you actually don't
mind it or to the point where you
actually love it anything can shift and
grow and change
we're doing though the parsley shot
so I'm gonna run
my parsley fruit
right now
I'm using flat leaf and a little curly
but I'm gonna just go with more flat
leaf
I mean personally you can have either or
okay
but personally flat leaf parsley is my
favorite
foreign
so
these are really big parsley stems
they're huge
people are asking the difference between
parsley and cilantro all the time I can
tell you this
okay
what I recommend is don't always just do
one
forever you can
but if it's everything I'm talking about
with the nerve gut problems that people
have
that I read about in the book earlier
switch off
do the parsley shot
do it for a while and then eventually do
a cilantro shot
for like a week
so I'm putting this incredible parsley I
get mesmerized by
beautiful flat leaf parsley what about
you guys
sending it right through
just that I don't usually have flat leaf
parsley so but today I do so I actually
really want to focus on that it's fun
very fibrous
extremely fibrous
parsley juice almost becomes gelatinous
it's the craziest thing
so I'm gonna be honest I have enough for
a shot I think
I mean you almost can spoon
that parsley juice out it's crazy how it
works
it's just crazy
all right we got a parsley shot right
here
Lori asked how long will will the sale
last
It's Gonna Last to the end I think of
the brain set challenge possibly maybe a
little after I'm not sure
Sarah how do I get one of those juicers
in the information do you have
to get one of these
link is in profile link is in the
description there's a medical medium
customer service line at Omega by the
way
you can easily talk to them anytime
by the way this mm-1500 I just want to
say does a lot of stuff so it's the
mm1500 is what you're looking at you're
not looking at the 800s or anything else
you're looking at the mm-1500 or mm-900
um
so I want to show you something okay
this is dry
this is actually dry
is what this piece of rope is
this thing was completely cold pressed
masticated
and it's it's dry right the mm 1500 900
you'll buy less parsley you have food
costs are going up you'll buy less
parsley
for your parsley shot there's no juice
dripping off of this it's basically
drying out like rapidly because it was
so so dry right
I mean it's a joke really the
centrifugal juicers and the spinning
basket juicers and all that it's it's
all this juice comes out in the pulp
it's wet and sloppy
right so the juice comes out in the pulp
you lose your juice it's like wet and
sloppy it gets discarded people complain
there's not enough juice
so people who actually buy those other
juicers like the like the spinning
basket ones and the centrifuge ones
where it's easier to use it you know
because you're just shoving everything
in the reason why it's easier to use
that way is because it's not juicing all
the juice out it's just spitting it all
out in the pulp so you don't get dry
pulp but if you're rich it probably
won't matter because you can buy a
hundred heads of parsley
and just spit all that juice out with
those because you're not worried because
you're rich you can buy 100 heads of
parsley all the time but if you're not
someone who's got
you know big big money and you're not
like wealthy or anything or well off
it's best to have a juicer that actually
squeezes the juice out so you're buying
less parsley so you go and you buy you
know five heads of parsley instead of 15
heads of parsley you know you buy like
six Bunches of celery instead of 20
Bunches of celery you know what I'm
saying
all right now parsley juice
turns into like a gel I'm just letting
you know if you let it sit long and I
let it sit
I let it sit long
okay I see daily I see daily people
struggling and commenting about the cost
of food and produce and all food right
people are having a hard time the cost
of food is going up the mm-1500 and the
mm-900
save people money so when they use these
medicine machines they use these
medicine makers it's squeezing out more
juice and they're buying less produce
that's where you save money so the
juicer pays for itself
and the other juicers don't do that but
here's the other thing the other juicers
people never really Juiced a lot with
it's like a juice once a month they use
it for a couple months and then put it
in their closet right so that's what
those are really for people who really
don't care
people that have a lot of money they
juice like once in a blue moon the
medical medium
um endorses the 1500 and the 900 because
it's for the people who juice all day
long like nobody else does like they
juice every day three times the juice
the medical the medical medium Community
juices like nobody does like nobody does
they juice every day they're celery
juice they juice celery twice a day they
juice at least once a day the medical
medium Community people you guys know
you guys know all about it you guys are
juicing and they juice all the time so
these machines
are made for that the other juicers if
you try to juice like that with the
spinning basket machines or those other
juicers
it ain't gonna happen and those
warranties aren't like the warranties on
the 1500 and 900 which are for 15 years
Parts included it's just unbelievable
those other ones they stop warrantying
the parts after like two years two years
or something anyway I got my shot right
here
[Music]
did you guys have yours already
so during this juicer explanation
right whoa
whoa
I'm sorry
but that is a parsley shot
and that baby is totally a nerve gut
acid stabilizer neutralizer
this is
serious
like serious
all right man have you guys had your
shot
I'm about to sip it
Michelle says the mm t-shirts are like
an investment
all right hey guys
I'm gonna take a sip right now a little
bit here
and you just start feeling it
um
so good
[Music]
all right do you have
do you have I start getting all these
unbelievable Sensations
when I'm drinking these shots it's like
something comes over me
and I can't describe it
all right
potent but yummy
yes cheers
[Music]
I'm sending it all down now
says the DJ was a little late
that was so good and once you do it
enough because I do this shot all the
time Allison Saunders says Omega is an
amazing company it's a mega juicers I've
dealt with them with warranty stuff and
they have been Stellar incredible
you guys you feel that you feel the
nerve gut stabilizer
Liz do you feel the nerve gut stabilizer
like that and here's this incredible
it tastes better the more you do it the
more you become alkaline internally the
better it tastes and then you crave it
you crave the nerve gut stabilizer you
crave it
is what you do
exactly
all right the Music's Over
can I just say one thing to you guys
where's the bartender
tell the bartender to give me another
that's all I can say
bartender give me another
yep one to two Wendy 2-2 says I have the
j800
Omega on sale the 300 Before Christmas
nutritional system
you have the warranties but that doesn't
have the high pressure attachment
that doesn't have the squeeze all your
juice out attachment
squeeze more juice out so that you save
money so maybe down the road
you know but that's still a good juicer
maybe down the road the mm-1500 the
mm-900 they're incredible the mm-1500
has also all the Nutritional Center too
what does it do it does salsas
hummus nut Butters nut milks all kinds
of great stuff all right you guys
incredible yeah I'm I'm giddy after that
shot it's that incredible it's there's a
sensation you get when you get that
living Herb in you that was
powerful herb shot is what it was
straight parsley juice going down
and the feeling I get
with it is just unlike anything else
this one gives me a whole entire body
sensation is what it does each shot does
a different thing for me
maybe for you guys too but with the
nerve gut acid stabilizer The Parsley
right what I get is a feeling from the
head down to my toes but a whole feeling
like a whole body Sensation that my
blood is being cleaned
by the way Health with Liz Liz happy
birthday today
happy birthday
and AWS boy at AWS Bar and Grill
we announced birthdays
Liz happy birthday
I'm very grateful you were born
grateful you were born in this timeline
in history
I will definitely say that
wholeheartedly
yes
maybe Dr Nesbit will show his
little chicken head
in another
day we do this because we still have 17
days ago am I crazy 17 days yeah I
probably am it's 20 day range out there
be cleansed but it's worth it
Mindy Yale says where do you one find
info about light blasts go to
medicalmedium.com sign up to the new
sign up to the news letter section at
the light blast find the light blast at
medicalmedium.com there's a section on
my website
Chloe says I feel renewed after the
light blast the light blast is very
special dear to my heart we are going to
do another light blast God willing I am
going to do it no matter what it takes I
don't care
Karen says my inflammation reduced
right after the light blast
I feel so much peace even surrounded by
so much stress
High blast is an entirely different
healing apparatus it is incredible
Nicole I noticed that as well light
blast definitely changed my inflammation
in probably more than I realized you
remember you guys I told you that after
the light blast
it can happen days later even more and
then a month later you can experience
something with it it's truly incredible
Jenny Ann says on Instagram as well I
was instantly drawn to your information
it was like finding water in a desert
and we say Angels might put the book in
front of someone
some spiritual
um Force
working for the light
maybe God sends a message and you see
the book maybe it's a friend that hands
you the book maybe the book falls on
your lap providentially maybe something
happens and people find the information
and then when they find the information
they're like I've never heard this
information before or I heard bits out
there that were taken and then here's
where where it really is you guys have
you guys tried this brain shot the nerve
acid gut stabilized can you please post
any stories post any posts or reels
about how you feel about this nerve Gap
this nerve gut acid stabilizer that we
did let me know let me know what your
results were I would love to post it you
know tag at Medical medium hashtag
medical medium so I can see it you have
to do both of those so I can see the
post the real the story and then I can
try to repost it
or try to
post it on reels or wherever you know in
the stories I would love to do that on
how you're experiencing this brain shot
therapy cleanse challenge how you did
with the nerve gut acid stabilizer but I
feel so good from the nerve gut acid
stay placed
last I feel good
all right guys
I think this is it on to the next one
tomorrow
are you gonna be there you guys going to
be there because we're going to talk
about some other killer stuff some great
stuff check out brain saver check out
braid saver brain saver protocols this
is like
my God so discounted right now
amazon.com us and so is brainsaver check
them out if you can
for warning they're two huge medical
Bibles
I did a couple of podcast interviews
that you will want to check out look for
that okay I did a podcast episode
with Kelly Noonan Gore's the heel
documentary genius and she's a dear
friend of mine incredible check out that
podcast of hers I did an episode I want
you to check it out okay guys
incredible
all right moving on I'll see you guys
see you guys tomorrow