all the time do you know anybody who's
just struggling to keep their mood in
check
they're struggling to keep their mood in
balance
do you know anybody who is just
basically
it's all about their mood
where they can't even get by without
like being focused on it there's people
out there struggling with mood shift
mood changes mood issues mood problems
and we can call it mood but it's even
deeper than that hello I'm Anthony
William the medical medium word day 15
of the brain shot therapy cleanse
challenge can you believe it you guys
day 15 what are we doing we're doing the
mood shifter did you guess the mood
shifter I love the mood shifter
there it is right there I'm in brain
saver right now that's the mood shifter
right there in my hands Chuck it out
the mood shifter is really an incredible
brain shot therapy because so many
people are struggling with the mood that
they're in right because they're sad
how many people feel sad all the time
you know I know a lot of people they
feel sad at the end of the day
I know a lot of people that feel sad
when they wake up do you feel sad this
sadness when you wake up first thing in
the morning did that ever happen to you
in your life
did you feel this sadness in the middle
of the day does the sadness hit you
around lunchtime
does the sadness hit you at the end of
the day
I know people were the sadness
mysteriously Comes This un
diagnosed mysterious sadness that comes
like at four o'clock five o'clock every
single day
I just saw somebody on IG that says I
get angry or easier
so many people are struggling struggling
with moods they're struggling with
sadness
I think
there is a difference
from what I've learned from SOC with
sadness that's mysterious and then just
of course depression and then you may
have both that's the thing you could be
suffering from depression
but also have this mysterious sadness
involved it could be two things like
mood
moods uh problems happening with
depression I mean I've seen it all out
there how you guys doing
are you excited about today because this
is a brain shot therapy I really like I
treasure the mood shifter I treasure the
power it has
and
I'm not saying that lightly I'm not I
treasure the power the mood shifter has
because it does hold something I haven't
seen anything else do friend of mine's
son
was in a really bad mood
um came back from school okay and
instantly she gave him the mood shifter
and usually anything else she tries just
doesn't change his mood and then she
gave him the mood shifter and it was
like a miracle happened so they're doing
the mood shifter every single day
when he comes home from school it's
incredible really
right so let's talk about mood let's get
into it now so
I am in the book
brain saver and I am just so we know
on page 207 I don't think that's the
spot I'm supposed to be in hang on there
let's see where we are
hold on here
looking for page 370.
all right we got it mood changes page
370 in brain saver the book is so huge
it's such a big book I don't think I'll
ever know where everything is I just
don't think I will
all right
we often hear mood changes being blamed
on hormone imbalances okay that's a
question I have for you guys it's really
important is your mood blamed on
hormones did that happen to you
did you go to your practitioner your
doctor your healer your herbalist your
health care provider and they were like
well no your sadness your mood changes
is your hormones
do you hear that all all the time out
there
because that's what people are told when
it comes down to moods it's not about
the toxic heavy metals in their brain
it's not about because of course they
don't know about that out there it's not
about the toxic Metals in the brain or
all the toxic chemicals or all the viral
infections people have it's not about
all that it's about hormones right I
mean pretty much everybody says no it's
hormones are the problem that's why I
have a mood problem right
that's what men always say I just saw
that on IG that it's about women's moods
because of uh hormones we often hear
mood changes being blamed on hormone
imbalances yes we do often hear that
what's incredible is that there's a new
generation and a new generation of women
that are being educated that it's their
hormones
so if anything's wrong with their health
and they're not so sick like they're not
I mean they're not so sick they're not
super sick they're not chronically sick
if they're not chronically sick then
their hormones may not be the blame if
they're just partially sick they got
like a little gut stuff and a little
headache once in a while and they got a
little bit of malaise they got a little
bit of acne and they go to their
functional medicine doctor or whatever
doctor and the first thing that's going
to happen is it's their hormones you're
going to be told it's the hormone so
there's a new generation of young women
right now being trained to think that
every single thing is for hormones and
you see it now with influencers on
social
you'll see like 20 year olds and 21 year
olds and 23 year olds and and 19 year
olds and they're just and they're doing
their thing about like oh it's my
hormones my hormones is why I don't feel
that great my hormones is why I can't
sleep good at night my hormones is why I
have this acne my hormones is why I'm
dizzy all the time this hormones is why
I don't have the energy so it's it's
right now there's a new training
happening since there's a new
conditioning in brainwashing meanwhile
where young women don't understand is
that whoa no you got mercury in your
brain you got aluminum you've got copper
in your brain your liver is getting
clogged up early on when it's not
supposed to you're having all these
other issues you know so it's it's all
of that going on but what's happening is
they're being blamed on hormones is the
big one right now like every functional
doctor every single practitioner it's
still it's your hormones and a whole new
generation of women are being completely
conditioned that it's their hormones so
that they're to blame they're the reason
why they're sick I think it's a
dangerous place to go yes hormones play
a role in a lot and I'm not
anti-hormone belief because I actually
know from a spirit of compassion that
hormones can get out of whack and they
can't get out of balance absolutely but
there's a difference between that
and everything being hormones and
hormones only and that's important to
know because there's this younger
generation of women that are being
trained literally trained every day
right now that their their hormones are
every reason why they're depressed they
have anxiety so if they have anxiety or
anxiousness or panic attacks it's their
hormone
um if their periods are difficult it's
their hormones if they have acne it's
their hormones if they have any kind of
mood shifting against their hormones and
hormones aren't why people are severely
depressed that have anxiety hormones
aren't why people are suffering from
these bad bad periods when they're
younger hormones aren't the reason why a
lot of things right but but there's
you'll see it now on social it's it's
almost like oh my God are you kidding so
they have completely brainwashed and
they're gonna brainwash the entire you
know world of young women that their
hormones are to blame for everything and
that's the new Direction alternative
medicine and conventional medicine but
the New Direction alternative medicine
has gone
and I support
I support hormones and hormone even to
some degree bioidentical I talk about
an idea for women but hormones are not
why young women have difficult periods
There's real reasons happening there's
low grade viral infections there's toxic
heavy metals it's just a couple but the
point is and also adrenal problems which
is adrenal hormones that's an entirely
different thing but they'll blame
everything on hormones for young women
and that's what's going on right now
that's the new normal that's developing
so and you'll see it five years
there'll be another billion sick women
in five years they'll all be on social
like young women will be on social and
they'll all be like it's my hormones
it's why I'm numb in my arms and I feel
like I got sandbags in my legs
and and they won't talk about caffeine
blowing out their adrenals or caffeine
like damaging their brain or anything
because caffeine they want young women
on caffeine the in the caffeine industry
wants young women on caffeine and then
the medical industry would love for
women to just believe it's their genes
or their hormones
and if they're really sick really really
sick then the medical industry will say
well it's your body attacking itself
it's autoimmune so what you're going to
see is on social you're going to see
millions and millions and millions of of
influencer influencers women influencers
like young ones right young women like
21 22 23 in a few years you're going to
see millions of them and they're all
going to be like well it's if they're
too sick it'll be like well my body's
attacking itself it's autoimmune right
which we know isn't the truth if you
know if you know medical meme
information the body doesn't attack
itself or the other thing is they're
going to be like it's my hormones
that's the conditioning of what's
happening today it's to put blame it's
body shame so what I'm trying to say is
that the industries
are teaching
women to shame their bodies
so it's all about body shaming now it's
your hormones that's a form of body
shaming yes when you're 40 years old you
can have hormone imbalances yes you you
could find an incredible doctor that
does bioidentical hormones if you're 45
years old if that's the direction you
want to go if they're really
knowledgeable or something but that's
that's not what this is I'm not talking
about this
I'm talking about
young women that are sick for other
reasons being body shamed and the body
shaming is out of control right now and
it's just beginning
and the body shaming is going to be like
every single 18 19 17 15 whatever 21 22
25 year old woman like every one of them
is going to be if they have a symptom
like a neurological symptom or anxiety
or depression or depersonalization or
OCD it's your hormones
it's your fault your body's bad
your body's faulty your body is not
working right
or it's your jeans or it's your body
attacking itself and that's where it's
going
okay boots Berlin says pregnancy is not
sickness it is he a huge change in the
whole Temple hormones roller coaster
pregnancy is hard on the body and when
women have problems like autoimmune
which is like viruses and low-grade
viral infections when women are very
sick pregnancy is very difficult on a
woman who's very sick with chronic
illness okay because there's all these
other problems why do you see one woman
have a good pregnancy where it was
easier and another woman have a very
difficult pregnancy it was harder
because of other problems going on
pathogens Epstein-Barr infections in the
reproductive system because the immune
system is protecting the baby and the
reproductive system so if a woman is
sick during her pregnancy she's
chronically ill there's other problems
at hand here so that's how it works yes
there's there's hormones related to
pregnancy absolutely and all of that but
I'm trying to show you like something's
really important though so I know you
just want to pass everything off of a
pregnant the woman's pregnant her
hormones are all over the place it's
like let's not kind of insult everybody
because what people don't even realize
is your immune system
is and I'm not saying you're insulting
anybody I'm just saying that's that's
something that happens out there people
are saying that out there they're saying
oh well oh she's pregnant that's what's
going on that's why she's having such a
hard time it's like whoa he's having a
hard time
because there's so many other problems
going on
she's struggling from so many other
different situations
maybe her adrenals aren't strong and one
of them is weakened right that's just
one thing maybe she got the low-grade
viral infections yeah
maybe she's got the toxic heavy metals
maybe there's other things going on and
all of that combined and then being
pregnant and having a baby right but
they'll just blame everything on
hormones so you'll have a mom that's
pregnant
and she's struggling with her pregnancy
and her health and they'll just blame it
all on hormones when wait a minute no
that Mom has a lot of other problems
going on making it really difficult
but that's one topic right there they're
training
millions of young women to believe that
everything is hormones
so if they have one problem it's
hormones whatever that is one symptom
see
um Dreyer woolman says my pregnancies
were the worst especially my second one
I was deep into standard naturopathic
treatments eating way too much protein
and my viruses were out of control
I hadn't found you yet aw my God you
know the information then you're reading
the information and you're learning
that's incredible
it really truly Dr Laura woolman
thank you Dr Laura
thank you for being here so proud of you
so anyway I think that since we're
talking about mood changes I just wanted
to talk about hormone imbalances a
little bit too
and I think that
for to begin with
like Spirit of passion always told me
yes you could have hormones that are
um imbalanced I never said you can't
have imbalanced hormones
you can and the adrenals produce a lot
of reproductive hormones too and they
produce a lot of hormones
but what happens is though there's
hundreds of other symptoms
and these hundreds of other symptoms
don't play any role with hormones
and that's important to know so that
means hormones aren't causing those
symptoms
I just want that out there
clear
because it's so important right now it's
just if you're 20 years old
and you're a woman
and you go to a couple different
practitioners and doctors and you have a
symptom oh you better believe you're
going to be told it's your hormones
people with same hormones out of whack
don't have those symptoms so one 20 year
old
and another one can have two different
experiences
right
so it's incredible how it works because
hormones are not the cause of every
single symptom and condition but they're
going there soon and they're already
kind of there you're seeing it on social
more and more it's just it's gonna be
out of control five years from now
everybody's sick and dying right all the
neurological problems developing and all
these people and all college students
and everything else and everybody's
gonna be on there like
it's my hormones my doctor told me it's
my hormones
Kate says had amazing second pregnancy
on medical medium going mountains
till month nine almost no protein intake
perfect lab work home birth a beautiful
child incredible
I think meant Moving Mountains
incredible
all right so let's let's roll you guys
interesting interesting information
isn't it though but you know where it's
going and you can see it like any
influencer basically not anyone but
almost all young people that are
influencers on YouTube
like they don't know why they have their
symptoms
they have no idea they're like well
I get kind of achy and pains throughout
my body I don't have a lot of energy
some days I feel better some days I
don't and I'm not sleeping that great I
went to my doctor and he said it was my
hormones how old am I 22 years old
it's not your hormones
Trina P iron is a big thing going around
ferritin anemia can you address
well
medical medium info is the only
information that put that was put the
truth about iron deficiencies out there
and so what that truth is is that if
you're missing the iron
and the levels are low
and something is eating the iron
critical to know right there that piece
of information is critical and
I was looking for my little virus
but what happens people don't realize is
iron
is a food source for many varieties of
Epstein-Barr virus
not all varieties of Epstein-Barr virus
but many varieties of Epstein-Barr virus
and so
um
got some iron in your bloodstream
and then a low-grade viral infection
medical research design doesn't know
that the low-grade viral infection is
feeding off of the iron
that's how it works people with serious
iron deficiencies are getting blood
transfusions because they're so high in
a viral load
that the viral load is gobbling and
gobbling all their iron up in their body
so Spirit of compassion always told me
to help somebody get past this someday
in their life they have to get the viral
infections down but if the doctors and
the medical industry don't know about
their viral infection how are they going
to get their iron fixed and they end up
in this vicious cycle
they have to try to change your diet
they try to do different things and some
of it's hit and miss where their iron
gets a little stronger
because they're taking Foods out that
are feeding the viruses as well
and so they get a little bit of a
benefit but if you don't know the truth
of what to really do of what foods to
remove that feed the virus
and how to go after the virus
and how to keep the immune system strong
to go after the virus then the iron in
that person get gets eaten and eaten and
eaten
and then blood transfer blood
transfusions are needed periodically
because
there's a viral infection and the virus
is feeding off the eye
and where'd my line go there's my lime
I'm in such a bad mood today I need the
mood shifter
can you tell I'm in a bad mood today you
guys can you actually tell
I'm not in that bad of a mood
but I would like the mood shifter indeed
um during pregnancy it's common to be
low in iron because Epstein-Barr
infections tend to evolve during
pregnancies if a woman is dealing with a
low-grade viral infection already and so
the immune system is gear a woman's
immune system is geared on protecting
the reproductive system that's not
science research that's medical medium
science right
and it's protecting the the reproductive
system
and uh and then you can have a viral
load that ends up taking advantage of
that and that viral load can be gobbling
up iron all through the body it's just
it's crazy how it works YouTube Jackie
says
uh wow
and years ago they put me on iron pills
feeding the EBV this makes sense I
became worse yes and that that leads me
to the next point I wanted to say thank
you for actually leaving that comment on
YouTube which God bless you
what people don't realize is that so
many people have tried the iron pills
for their anemia and then when they did
the iron pills they got sicker and they
were going back to their doctor like I
can't take these iron pills I'm getting
sicker and sicker and sicker but what
the doctor did not know medical research
design did not know is the viral
infection was feeding off of more iron
so the iron pills were going in and the
virus was feeding off the iron pills and
then the virus was getting stronger and
then person was getting sicker see how
it works
and that's medical medium Advanced
information
extremely Advanced all of it I mean I
cover that in book one medical medium
if you don't have the books go to the
library and get all of them out or go to
Amazon and get it if there's a discount
on all my books right now on Amazon get
the medical medium New Edition
start studying become become an expert
you know for yourself start studying get
Liver Rescue spend time and read the
books get cleansed heal get
life-changing Foods get thyroid healing
I don't have them out here right now get
the brain saver books
Juden said told low in iron two and was
sick for the pills absolutely
uh crystal says yes I was taking on her
pills during pregnancy so okay for okay
here's an example of how incredible
Spirit of compassion's information is I
wanted to say something
Lana Marquis says that must be why I was
anemic when pregnant the only time I
ever was anemic absolutely because when
you're pregnant
almost all your immune system a big hunk
of it is going to the baby
it's protecting the baby in the womb
that means you have less immune system
everywhere else viral infections go up
you go anemic when pregnant
um and here's another thing here's this
is critical like
Spirit of compassion's information is so
advanced
there are millions of women
they go on the iron pills and get sicker
and science research has no idea why
but this info is so Advanced it provides
an answer
just like the blood draw information is
so Advanced it provides answers for
people like it's incredible preeclampsia
is Epstein-Barr infection
to preeclampsias it's a viral infection
it's a viral load that's somebody who's
really got a viral infection
and you know what size research will
take this
they'll call me a quack or something and
they'll take the information they do it
every day the clinics are taking
published medical meme information and
putting it in their little write-ups on
diseases and symptoms right now we know
we're cataloging it we're watching it
and we can't even we're seeing it before
our eyes we're like oh you're getting
the letter because that's illegal to do
they're taking published medical medium
information because science research has
no info at all to offer for anybody they
never did they're taking a decade of
answers and plugging it into all the
clinics in the clinic search engines
right now
without having any proof that they had
it first
it's actually disgusting
I'm in such a bad mood now for real I do
need the moon shifter I have put myself
in a bad mood apparently by talking
about that
don't worry that's just medical medium
woes
I will get a mood shifter in me in no
time all right let's get going
we often hear mood changes become blamed
on hormone imbalances whether puberty a
menstrual cycle or menopause
hormonal shifts are an easy target it's
your hormones
be quiet shut up it's your hormones
the truth is that there's much more to
mood changes than hormone fluctuations
uh-huh
there's so much more to mood changes
than hormone fluctuations there's so
much more to every symptom and condition
than calling it hormones
Jackie
aw you helped to bring my niece into
this world a few months ago are you
going to try to get me all emotional
where I have to almost start crying my
sister kept having miscarriages until I
showed her the medical medium way
God bless you
this Mandalorian I think it was is it
this is the way
I'm Mandalorian
I think there's a new season coming out
unless it's my imagination and I think
I'm wrong I don't know
the truth is that there's much more to
mood changes than hormone fluctuations
when someone's altered state of mind
isn't the result of something
emotionally challenging or traumatic
happening in the Life One common cause
of irritability or the blues is toxic
blood
I don't want to keep on complaining here
I almost can't stand myself
but
there's now like doctors out there
stealing this
from medical medium books and putting it
in ads
toxic blood
and and dirty blood syndrome Everything
Medical medium published and they're
just taking it and running
do you think there's like a hell for all
these people or something like you know
what I mean when we leave here and you
did so many like deceitful things or do
you think that doesn't exist
you know what I mean like it's like you
just go to the greatest Heaven there
ever was doesn't matter how many people
you s you know you drew to a different
direction and their house just their
health just went crashed and they went
through hell and they
they you know like because when you
think about it if you're gonna steal all
the info out of the books
but not tell them where it comes from
and then they stay sick and they lose 10
years of their life and their children
are sick don't you think that's just
kind of like wrong
ah right
and it wouldn't be so bad if they keep
on stealing the medical meme information
if they if they didn't call me like
names while they were doing it and say
that I'm not a trusted reliable source
but they keep on
taking the info non-stop right now
this look we're doing the mood shifter
today so I just thought that I would
talk about this a little bit with you
guys because it puts me in a bad mood so
it's perfect timing for the mood shifter
I'm actually excited
the point I'm trying to say is I can't
even read a sentence now that they're
not taking
that's it's actually like mad day right
and
you think I wouldn't care so much if it
didn't mean so many people are never
going to find their way back to the
books and they're going to stay sick for
years
and even die many of them
down the road
okay toxic blood
toxic blood can shift the mood not
hormones toxic blood
even if something difficult is going on
if that person's blood is also toxic
they'd be more sensitive and susceptible
to triggers from confrontation and
conflict someone has toxic blood in
their body and they run into
confrontation they're going to be in a
bad mood
it's like what did you say
what
did you wait a minute wait a minute did
you just say that to me
did you just say I was ugly
like why would you say that but since I
have really toxic blood I'm going to be
in a worse mood about that
I can't shake that off
did that really hurt my feelings I'm
angry about it now you just called me
ugly
my toxic blood is boiling inside of me
right now because I have toxic thick
blood dirty blood syndrome
and my toxic blood is is like making it
so I'm triggered easier so if you call
me ugly one more time I'm really gonna
get upset oh there you go you just held
me ugly again now I'm really upset
this is what I call Dirty blood syndrome
when blood is toxic it's dirty it's not
clean blood
it's like if I had to get a BL if I had
to a bad car accident or something like
that and had to get a blood transfusion
and I was still conscious I'd be like
don't give me someone's don't give me
the blood from someone that has dirty
blood syndrome please
spread of compassion would be like I
would be asking questions being like
spirit is the blood that I'm getting is
it from something yeah it's from a
really dirty blood syndrome person their
blood is toxic great put it in me
Lorraine L they took three big vials of
blood to test my hormones and I hated it
in comparison to some people that have
blood drawn I know this isn't much but
it still felt so obsessive I felt really
quasiately okay
I have a lot to say about
drop blood draw
a lot to say
anybody who listens to the blood draw
podcast the medical meme podcast at
Apple podcast could have their lives
safe but even better than that
I gotta I got protocols in here
the brain saver books
I have a blood draw chapter in here that
will blow your mind
blow your mind you have to be educated
about blood draw it's critical right now
because yes three full vials of blood
can knock somebody back
so you're not you're you're
complaint Lorraine is actually valid
a hundred percent valid you felt queasy
I know three full vials someone can be
hit from that it's no joke never mind
five miles seven vials ten vials 15
vials by the way I'm talking about blood
draw because Lorraine you mentioned it
but also because that can really change
moods in people when they're getting too
much blood drawn really change moods
all their glucose goes out the door like
a lot of glucose so electrolytes go out
the door their immune system goes out
the door I've talked about this for so
many times so many years the trace
minerals go out the door
trace minerals glucose
right so all of that electrolytes
macro minerals specially go out the door
all of that is just boom and then how
are people going to recover that glass
of water
I mean
you're you when you fill up with fluids
and eat you're not restoring your blood
what's in your blood so fast you're just
restoring water content too and that's
that's not all the bulk of your blood
water content does not restore your
immune system
anyway yeah
so many Hot Topics right here to talk
about you know hot spots seriously
like important critical pieces of
information
this is what I call Dirty blood syndrome
when black blood is taught by the way I
do know answers to what happens when
people leave here and everything from
Spirit of compassion when I ask Spirit
of compassion
but I was just asking you guys what you
thought
I do know what happens a lot of
information that my past time all these
years if anybody wants to know this
could be really boring to somebody my
pastime one of them my pastimes is to
ask spiritual compassion a lot of
difficult questions questions that I
want to know personally questions about
how the Earth Works questions about
people questions about souls questions
about what happens when we leave here
questions about past lives questions
about all this right these are questions
that I ask Spirit of compassion that
um that I happen to know many answers to
and I want you guys to know all those
answers too too so we'll get to it right
now a lot of sick people and they need
to feel better
this is the result of a liver overloaded
overburdened burdened by toxic heavy
metals adrenaline viruses pathogens
other betrayers
dirty blood syndromes when the liver is
overloaded and it's overloaded in
virtually everybody babies come here
into this world with an overloaded
overburdened stagnant sluggish liver
babies
come into this world with a stagnant
sluggish liver
Elsie says oh my God explanation point
wondering why I'm so dead today and had
five vials taken yesterday
Elsie
I beg of you
go to the library
or order the book online whatever
learn about blood draw
ask your doctor what's right for you but
MD Misha I had not made the connection
to being completely wiped out after
blood draws until medical medium
information
honestly you guys if you can hear me
if you can see me right now if you can
hear me
please learn about blood draws please
Kate Ellen
doctors took my blood every week when I
was pregnant
oh my God I talked about that in here
what kind of what kind of mood am I in
today now
you guys
I beg
I'm pleading
I'm pleading with you
I never ever do that right like to this
extent
I beg of you
you have to learn about blood draws
you have to read the chapter
it's not about selling a book it's sold
way less than it costs to print it now
on amazon.com anyway
the point is
get to get it free at the library but
you have to read the blood draw chapter
I am like serious
protect yourselves
as the liver and the body's filter gets
sluggish and stagnant the blood can get
sluggish and stagnant the blood in the
liver gets sluggish and stagnant and it
can get more toxic where do these toxins
go they float around the bloodstream and
find their way to where here
foreign
has different toxins and different
amounts
so exactly how they affect different
people varies these toxins saturate the
brain tissue and neurons diminish neuro
transmitter chemicals and can alter
somebody's mood
see I'm just in a crappy mood right now
Jay Nessie says I'm new here
I'm in chapter four whoa whoa and I'm
addicted Anthony I finally feel like I'm
reading some truth thank God trying to
find answers for my two-year-old my
two-year arthritis oh my God
for the Newbie here
I just got one thing to say when I bring
out Dr Nesbitt from his surgery later do
not
do not not be a newbie anymore and then
don't say bye
stick around for Dr Nesbit
no seriously though um thank you for
reading the books and yes it's truth
Jackie B I'm so glad we learned the mm
info about blood draws now my husband
asked them to take half files and he
doesn't feel as awful afterward there
are serious ramifications from blood
draw
that go beyond anything anybody can even
imagine
I believe in getting blood work done for
people I want people to go to their
doctors and get blood work absolutely
there's nothing wrong with that if the
doctor wants it the point is is you have
to learn how to protect yourself because
the implications the ramifications are
serious they're dire
especially if you're struggling with any
kind of condition or symptom
toxic heavy metals such as mercury and
aluminum can sit inside the brain
and cause mood changes all on their own
toxic heavy metals wreak havoc on
people's brains
they can get a diagnosis of any kind
schizophrenia bipolar OCD
depersonalization depression anxiety
ever and 10 000 other diagnoses that are
brain related with toxic heavy metals
and they can that can happen without the
liver being toxic in dirty blood
syndrome
viruses inside the liver can feed off of
toxic heavy metals and release different
Brews of neurotoxins
some more potent than others which get
to the brain and make the brain Go funny
where oh my God I'm having mood changes
over here on Rumble
Neato 1988.
I had low iron most of my life not now
since on medical medium protocols
thank you Rumble person for being here
and thank you for commenting
everything
is different in how their body handles a
toxic load everybody's different
one thing about medical medium info
one it's not one size fits all
it's quite the opposite
PK asks the aliens get moody
I would love to answer that question
right now
see one person may not be swayed too
easily to a dark place when their liver
blood and brain are overloaded with
toxic waste and poisons another person
can be
can be persuaded by it
and go through a dark play be in a dark
place and struggle when someone is
highly toxic mood changes can fluctuate
up and down
high in laho
pan when you're toxic
smooth changes can fluctuate all over
the place but it'll be blamed on
hormones
when someone's highly toxic mood changes
can fluctuate up and down
you can go to a new doctor
if they won't listen about taking your
blood draws
if they won't listen about the
information that's so critical Audrey
Lynn says even knowing that blood draws
are not good when you tell the nurses to
take less they do not listen saying they
know what is needed and I can't control
what they take once a needle's in your
arm first of all
the nurses don't know
but the lab the blood lab will still run
the tests and have and still throw away
the rest of your blood because they have
too much
you could find doctors and nurses who
will listen and there's a lot more now
that are listening because of the
medical medium information out there and
the blood draw information
because it is spreading and getting out
there
vampires Juliet
Llewellyn says I asked the doctors for
half files and was told it couldn't be
done as the labs need full vials
I rang the lab in the phlebotist told me
it would be fine as they do minimal
amounts all the time exactly
foreign
Juliet because it's one big
freaking lie
it's one big lie
nothing really is as we think it is
there's so much lying going on it's sick
in the system
I'm kind of confused
um how do they do a pediatric thyroid
test
and test all the same
with this much blood
from a baby can somebody tell me
how can they can run all the entire
thyroid profile with this much blood
from a baby with baby vials
can you tell me
because it's BS and that's all they do
is lie to every single patient it's
sickening
they can test your blood sugar with a
DOT of blood
a drop a tiny drop of blood they can
take blood that's on somebody's blue
jeans that's sitting in a shallow grave
because they were murdered 45 years ago
and they can scrape that blood and get a
whole reading nutrient deficiencies
thyroid profile liver enzymes with a
speck of dried out blood sitting in blue
jeans 45 years ago in a grave
oh but they need all that blood or they
need they need all that blood from you
sure it's a scam
read about it in the books pick up the
books get the brain saver book learn
read about it because
they're gonna get you one day
and they'll get you in a vicious cycle
and they'll drain your blood and drain
your blood and drain your blood people
die from it all the time that's all they
get sicker and they take more blood
sicker take more blood sicker and they
just pick on
all the blood donating to all the all
the donating blood
right
that
everybody does
it doesn't go to hospitals where does it
go well a fraction of it goes to
hospitals where's the rest of it go I'm
kind of curious
are they feeding aliens where's it going
is somebody drinking it I'd love to know
guess who's donating blood
sick women
99.9 of all blood donors are sick women
why are they telling sick women to
donate their blood and get rid of all
their blood
and who's who's your
cause it's not going to the hospitals
I'm kind of like confused on that one
because it's not
where's it going
is somebody drinking it I'd love to know
Jackie B my husband insisted he warned
them that he has to lay down afterward
if they do full vials
that's just the immediate effect
that's not like a year from now
after you lost part of your immune
system and it took six months to get
your immune system back the effects
later
I talk about it in the book here
you guys I'm in an awful mood today do
we have anything for that do you have
anything to offer for because I'm in a
bad mood is there anything I we can do
the mood shifter Maria
says I thought a lot of my issues hold
on hold on Maria it went somewhere
screen literally went boo and it was
gone
what happened
all right let's keep on going here when
we find that comment if I can possibly
find it
another person with similar toxic loads
may feel something terrible another
person may not when someone's highly
when someone is highly toxic their mood
changes can fluctuate up and down high
and low and this could lead to a
diagnosis like bipolar disorder
depression seasonal infective disorder
sad right Tourette's
or OCD how many people get diagnosed
with Tourette's syndrome
when there's just really toxic
why does mood Express itself differently
in two people with similar toxic loads
childhood can play a role if someone
grew up with tremendous family stability
check that out right
if someone grew up
with tremendous family stability in
early years that gave them confidence
and emotional support that can
strengthen their path and journey
someone else might have lacked that
emotional support growing up
one person might have had all the
resources they needed when they were
young and another person might have
struggled with very few resources and
unpredictability
that chain that tends to change people
that can make a difference between
just like differences with someone who's
just as toxic as the other person
they're both toxic but yet see the
similar things can change
in each person
there is a full chapter on blood draw in
brain saver
when I was begging you guys to learn
about it I was
begging for you guys to read the chapter
and study it
and hold on to that information
you know
what's really like
so crazy with medical medium information
is that I always for some reason I think
that everybody
in the community knows it
and it throws me every time where I'm
like okay well I did the blood draw
podcast episode
years ago
but like when I talk about blood draw
everybody's like what what are you
talking about
it like happens like that every second
it's like
it's almost like
it's a community but I think for some
reason everybody knows the info
but then I realized
there's probably a huge amount of the
community that doesn't have all the
books or maybe not even read one but
they're here and I'm glad they're here
I'm grateful they're here but the point
is is that I realize that you can be in
the medical medium community and not
even even heard the blood draw problem
you can be in the mm community and not
even know Epstein-Barr causes this or
that
you can be like in the mm community and
be like that's the first time I ever
heard that about blood draw what
you can be in the mm community and be
like who's Dr Nesbitt
it's it's just it just blows me away
every time I'm like
then there's an individual soul itself
okay let's talk about the soul
see Loney says when I was at the
hospital all the time and got a lot of
blood drawn I went into the hospital
walking came out in a wheelchair every
time
I had to heal myself with a lot of B12
for weeks
it's really sad because
the system is set up
to drain a sick person's
vitality
robbing and stealing their blood
when they don't need that much blood for
the tests
the sick person gets sicker
and sicker and sicker and when the sick
person gets sicker
the doctors take more blood
then the sick person gets even sicker
and then the doctors say well you need
to come in for more blood now
because you're sicker and we need to
know why
eventually the person
is too sick
it's the saddest thing I've ever seen
out there
is a reason you have that much blood
circulating in your body your body isn't
a blood bag that just could be like
squeezed out anywhere like a ketchup
bottle
at a busy picnic table
where everybody's slapping ketchup on
hot dogs and hamburgers left and right
people are really depleted and low
already with nutrients they have
deficiencies they have electrolyte
deficiencies they don't have enough B12
in their their brain people already have
enough problems take too much blood out
of them and constantly take blood out of
them and they never restore I mean Jesus
Christ it's a serious problem it could
really go really bad
foreign
and yes I said Jesus
anyway
Loney said I get kicked out of medical
medium groups for sharing your exact
words I hear that all the time Loney I
hear there's a lot of medical meaning
groups that are just bait they're bait
to get people in to push them to a
different direction
and so if you talk about medical medium
info or stick up for medical medium in
those groups they kick you out
but they try to use the medical medium
name and pretend it's a medical game
group
I'm going to be kind of hammering down a
little bit on that because it's it's
actually really sad it got to the point
where I'm actually really
scared for people who are trying to seek
out help and heal what's happening is
there's groups now that they
it's not about mm info it's not about
mmm truth it's not about any of that
it's like
it's not about like healing people
really because they siphon people in
because it's a medical meme group and
then they try to get them doing
different things there is one in Germany
that was like doing that everybody went
in it turned out it was just a medical
meme hate group but nobody knew but
everybody thought it was a medical
medium group and they just filed in and
filed in it turned out it was just a
medical medium hate group and it was
siphoning people in and then telling
them all this other stuff so that you
know like you know what I mean and it's
like that everywhere now it's like
there's a lot of groups not all of them
but there's a lot of groups they're
siphoning people in and then they're
getting them to do this person's
protocols this person's belief system
this person's whatever and then you're
back to that again okay great if that's
what you want to do but then don't
trick
people and getting them in thinking it's
going to be on them info I want to stop
all right what a mood day okay can I
just say this that yes
I'm not in the greatest mood
all right
why does mood Express itself different
in two people I talked about that then
there's an individual soul itself which
is unique to each of us your soul is
unique my soul is unique
your soul is unique
critical to know
it could be fragile from being tattered
along the way and God knows our souls
have been tattered along the way many
people become wounded in life
and soul wounds can make a person more
sensitive too I mean a lot of us take a
lot of heat remember I told you our soul
gets propelled out of us so it doesn't
get totally damaged it protects it but
it still gets it still has to live in
here afterwards when it comes back in
many people believe many people become
wounded in life and soul wounds can make
a person more sensitive affecting how
they cope process or deal with
circumstances involving other people
that can reflect the mood
Tammy starts Ben says I was on meds
growing up for seizures
they took my blood every few months
every time it would induce a seizure at
the lab really scary I talk about that
in brain saver
prime example right there
prime example because they were removing
all the electrolytes
grid and glucose
critical
someone can be dealing with all the
above they could be so what I mean by
that all kinds of problems that we
already discussed about what could be a
mood trigger they could be experiencing
toxic heavy metals in the brain a highly
toxic liver I talked about filled with
pathogens and poisons that's caused it
to become more stagnant sluggish so that
the dirty blood develops in a tattered
soul from a journey through life that
has been very difficult
all happening at once or they could be
dealing with one factor or some
combination everyone has a different
variation mood is no mood is so much
bigger than chalking it all up to
hormones
now don't worry it's your hormones
there'll be another million influencers
on social saying how every single
problem they have is their hormones
for specific healing support Beyond
what's offered here
then it directs you to incredible
protocols and everything else in the
book
um
let's make it's a phenomenal chapter by
the way the bipolar chapter is an
incredible chapter in brain saver so
that's something you might want to look
at even if you weren't diagnosed with
being bipolar
or the diagnosis of any kind
for you guys I I need a mood shifter
desperately right now I just feel like
I'm not in the greatest mood right now
and I feel like I need a mood shifter
like this has been like the perfect like
situation really because
I'm not in the greatest mood I have the
mood shifter I'm excited I have my shot
glass ready let's try to figure out how
to make this thing
okay
getting a spoon out getting what else I
need uh-oh
I think I got a peel a lime real quick
so if you guys don't mind
do it a little bit of a lime peel real
quick
so
look I want everybody to know that
when
just don't blame yourself
this is important to know don't blame
yourself for like the mood you're in
there are reasons why you're in a bad
mood if you're in a bad mood
don't be hard on you like yourself
don't beat yourself up
have compassion for yourself
there is a reason why you may be in a
situation where you're struggling
Catherine Elizabeth sadly my son had a
seizure at three and a half years old
after they took 20 vials of blood
that will always haunt me
quiet after that because
it gets it actually gets me upset
because there's no need for that that to
happen out there but the system creates
that it's not your fault
all right
just I'm turning the juicer on
foreign
first of all I'm using the wild
blueberry powder today
it's incredible sets of energy wild
blueberry powder
it's amazing
by the way I wanted to say something
about this
um
I don't say it a little bit I think it's
important to know
okay
let's get going
quarter cup tightly packed chives
I love the smell
you don't have chives you can get away
with scallions I love the smell of these
scallions and chives that go down in
here
uh a quarter cup basil
highly packed
Daniel Laporte hey friend EXO
hey Daniel Laporte by the way she's got
a killer book
you gotta check out her latest book
seriously
um Daniel Laporte has always supported
medical medium medical medium
information it's a dear friend
um
God bless her she cares about people who
are chronically ill she cares about
people who are suffering and struggling
she's actually like
to the core an unbelievable human being
I'm just going to tell you right now
we got chives we've got the basil
half cup tightly packed fresh alfalfa
sprouts
I got some fresh alfalfa sprouts right
here
you guys don't mind I'd love to have
Daniel Laporte on
sometime you guys
it'll be I promise it'd be a killer
conversation
okay
half lime
throwing that lime in there and that's a
small lime
but I think we should be good
one stalk of celery
all right half cups of grapes a half cup
of grapes optional
it's optional I happen to have some
now what's amazing about the mood
shifter it's optional it's very
compassion said I love when very few
times it's optional with the mood
shifter this one works
okay I'm also going to put some this
one's done here I'm gonna pop some wild
blueberry powder in here and mix it
because I'm using the powder I'm not
using the fresh or frozen wild
blueberries I'm using the powder in here
foreign
teaspoon
pure wild blueberry powder right there I
got Sprouts all over the container
now what's incredible and I'm going to
say this
I'll say it once
there's no anti
bonding agents in here okay there's no
agents in here
what people don't realize in the powders
out there
they don't realize they put like an
anti-bonding agent in the powders out
there vimergy does not do that
by the way you guys you know I endorse
them the whole bit for all these reasons
and this is one of the big ones and I
never had a chance to ever tell you guys
about it
but I wanted to so I'm just gonna say it
now
what you'll notice the barley grass
juice powder the spirulina
there's no anti-caking agents in here
critical to know
I don't even know what to say besides
that's the best news I can ever be
handed in my like Consciousness my mind
when I'm using this stuff do I want an
anti-caking agent in my powders
and when people don't realize when they
buy all these powders out there all the
green powders and these patterns and
chlorella powders and spirulina powders
whatever they're using they don't
realize it
there's an agent in there to stop the
powder from caking
undisclosed
in all the powders
keep that in mind
and so when you're dealing with this
company Bemidji
they don't put that powder in the powder
they don't do that anti-bonding agent
anti-caking agent
inside the powder
and so okay fine then you might get
clumpiness but I will take clumpiness
any day
any day this is incredible stuff right
here you see where like one might be a
little clumped together
I don't care if there's a little
clumpiness going on I know how clean and
pure that stuff is
because I don't have to say oh great uh
I'm using a pattern has all that
antibody bonding agents in here
like that's disgusting like I don't want
to eat that so memory from my knowledge
is the only company that doesn't use
that stuff
I wanted to make that clear because what
people don't realize
when they use the barley grass juice
powder
that if it's clumped together
it's a good thing
that means they didn't put that
gross bonding agent in their
anti-bonding agent in there so important
to know I'm just saying I just wanted to
kind of let you know that it's critical
anyway it's wild blueberry powder right
there from beveraging
I'm mixing this up
all right
I need the mood shifter man as you guys
can tell
my mood hasn't been good today
we covered a lot of really annoying
topics
mixed up
got to get that mixed up
Erica Fitzgerald I just got the mm-1500
I Love It
that's what she said
she loves the mm1500
incredible
thank you
because you are going to save yourself
money
bottom line and you know why because
that pulp is drier and when that bulb is
dryer you save money the less produce
you have to buy you know the whole thing
I told you guys a million times let's go
um
Cold Light spring you didn't juice the
whole celery stalk it annoys me laugh
out loud oh there's a little piece in
here I shut the machine off
I know
I told you
I wasn't I'm in a bad mood today I don't
even know what to say John Juke beverage
is the only company that doesn't give me
a throbbing headache thank you aw
ning you know what
that reason alone
they don't use the anti-caking agents do
you guys know what that means like
that's unbelievable all the powders out
there
have a hidden undisclosed anti-caking
agent
um excuse me
yeah and you guys know I endorsed them
the whole bit well you know what's
incredible
and I'll endorse them a billion times
over because of this it's this kind of
stuff they do that you can't get
anywhere else
this tastes like candy this wild
blueberry powder tastes like candy it is
exquisite it is exquisite anyway
all right let's drink this shot
let's see Kate Maris says I always
wondered why the cheap spirulina was so
easier to stir so glad to hear this Kate
that's exactly why
100 exactly why I
yeah
pretty amazing you guys
all right we're gonna do our shot we're
gonna drink our shot I'm gonna pour it
I need to come out of this bad mood
somehow
I mean I actually almost want to cry for
some reason
we're talking about like all kinds of
things
like
like I need something
I wasn't planning on being in a bad mood
today I wasn't
there's just a lot of talk we were
talking about
this is the whole iron thing the blood
draw thing right I'm I feel bad for
people going through hell and then being
driven in directions that actually make
them worse is that gonna put me in a bad
mood yes it is
all the way down to the fact that all
the other powders have anti-caking
agents in there and stuff and these
don't like
all the way to the thefting of medical
medium information in the medical medium
Community groups
being kind of like hate groups but
bringing people in with all of it anyway
[Music]
not all of them are I know that there's
some incredible ones
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
I almost feel like letting out a cry
right
[Music]
foreign
this one always takes a minute for me
does it hit me right away but it starts
hitting me now
bartender give me another
because I am ready
I'm already in a better mood
I get these funny Sensations all in my
head you get that where there's this
like funny crazy Sensations going down
like I get them from like here to here
it's so weird with some of these this
one right here really
[Applause]
this is what I needed
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm in an apologetic mood too guys I'm
so sorry
oh
I'm so sorry that I've been complaining
amazing bartender give me another
I'm just gonna tell you
that was incredible
um
for the newbies here I just want to say
thank you for being here
I really appreciate it
I do and
for the newbies here um I have a friend
here
for anybody who's a newbie
Dr Nesbitt
no no it's okay you can say that yeah
Dr Elizabeth says that
because he's a certified psychiatrist
that he said that
he will gladly treat
because he's a board-certified
psychiatrist he gladly treat anybody
with any kind of mood problems
if they're a chicken
so Dr Nesbitt they have do they have to
be a chicken for real
Darkness but says they have to be a
chicken but they're not chickens Dr
Nesbit they're actually people
they're humans
he says what do you think I'm stupid
he says I'm not stupid I know they're
humans
he says he does surgical procedures on
all the time he works on humans he's not
a chicken surgeon he's a human surgeon
but he only does Psychiatry for chickens
why I don't get it
chickens have a lot of emotional wounds
and a lot of soul wounds right
yeah I can only imagine
um Dr Nesbitt is just wants to say one
thing to newbies
he appreciates you guys coming around
and being here
Dr Nesbitt
where's Beatrice
doctor
says Beatrice is on a vacation
away from Dr Nesbitt
all right well when is she going to come
back
said she may never come back
she may not come back ever again she
feels like she was humiliated and
insulted
um the last time she was here
and she feels like she was not heard or
validated because Dr Nesbitt is very
dominating
he was dominating a conversation
says aw I am healing bipolar
deal with and I deal with so much mood
disturbances
and this shot was better than any drug I
feel a heck of a lot better right now I
smile
Goofy for no reason and it was amazing
I can't wait to have it again soon Saint
Sue's fantastic
Dr Nesbitt said that if you were a
chicken he would
offer you a session
for free Santa's
which you are not a chicken Amy Peter
says mood shifters are way better than
mood stabilizers
amazing
well
Dr Nesbitt
you're upset because you didn't get
offered one Dr Nesbitt is in a terrible
mood today
let me just make sure I can help out in
some way Dr Nesbitt said that when he
got to the office
[Music]
the anesthesiologist
um
was late and the patient
was waiting for surgery for a very long
time an anesthesiologist
was not helpful and then the
anesthesiologist gave the patient too
much anesthesia
Dr Smith
and he said that the patient took three
days to wake up
after the surgery but the surgery was
today that doesn't make any sense Dr
Nesbitt says it doesn't matter if it
makes sense he says that he's just
telling me he had a bad day
I just want to say
and
uh Michelle L we love you and
just uh
hang in there for us okay I know that
you're going through a lot
thank you Nesbitt
Dr nesbitt's already drinking and he
said that this
smoothie is delicious
recognize but it's not a smoothie
Dr Elizabeth said this smoothie drink is
amazing
Darkness but it's not a smoothie it's
the mood shifter
what are you talking about
Darkness but said
good heavy metal detox smoothie this is
not the heavy metal deep the problem is
with Dr Nesbitt he really doesn't know
the information really well he just
knows of things that you know he's heard
where's Peggy and Donnie he said Peggy
and Donnie are out today they are at the
park
problem is with piggy is piggy tends to
eat a lot and Donnie tends to throw up a
lot and the between the both of them Dr
Nesbit says they embarrass him wherever
they go
all right
um
you can get the brain shot recipes in
the books medicalmedium.com and at
medicalmium.com
please know that the website has been
constantly
additions have been added to the website
um check it out when you get a chance
medicalmean.com check out telegram you
guys know the drill check out telegram
exclusive messages on telegram the last
one I left was called I'm sorry
I'm Gonna Leave a new one as soon as I
can it's not going to be today I think
but just make sure you're there on
Telegram and
what else can I say medical mean
podcasts at Apple podcast
um check out the flu and cold and flu
download you can get at
medicalmedium.com
you can still sign up to the challenge
we have five days left pretend it's a
five day challenge get your free grocery
shopping list you can download and get
your emails with all the information
that's pertinent to the brain shot
therapy cleanse Challenge and it's free
Dr Ned's Fitz said stop giving everybody
everything for free
there is a bit Dr Nesbitt says he
charges for every single thing
at his clinic and at his
office light blast is coming soon so you
might want to be on the email list or
the light blast check out the email list
for the light blast it's on
medicalme.com sign up when you get a
chance you don't want to miss the light
blast
because
I can promise you this at the light
blast is definitely life-changing
without a doubt
it is an experience like no author
so anyway
all right you guys
Lisa says love your telegram messages
okay guys I will see you soon in Dr
Nesbit wool too
much love
God bless you guys
yep